(Day 17)
I want to present our culture and tourist locations to people from other countries.
I think that students from other countries will also try and show off their own cultures as well.
If you need any help, just let me know and I'll gladly help you out.
It seems very fun.
Thank you so much.
I'm already disturbing you.
It's my project and yet I asked for your help today.
Last week we went with just the two of us.
We didn't need Uncle's help at all.
I don't get my mom at all.
"How can two kids go alone?"
"You must bring an adult with you."
I'm really not overthinking things.
Anyway...
Don't forget to observe Q for me.
Oh. So the reason why you were so adamant on me going with them is so I can observe your son?
Why, you don't trust them when they're alone together?
Well, aren't they worrisome? Think about it.
Normally, Q will work on something for just a short period of time.
This time, he tells me every reason he can think of.
Last week when he came home, he was smiling all the time!
Isn't that suspicious?
You're his mom, not the owner of his life!
No matter what happens, all you should be doing is either be happy or sad for him.
Why are you acting like his enemy?
But will he be okay with this kind of life?
Even your love life hasn't been working out at all.
What about yours? Aren't you currently a single mom?
What if other people find out and start to tease him?
What if they won't accept him for who he is? What will I do?
So what if other people won't accept him?
It's not his responsibility to make everyone on earth happy.
If someone doesn't like it, then it's their problem.
- But-
- Hey.
If your son is happy with his life, then you should be happy for him.
But if other people is happy while your son suffers...
Would you be happy about that?
Don't stress out too much.
We're here.
Uncle Man, why didn't you stop by the restroom for me?
Look at that child.
Let's grab our stuff and go wait for him in the garden.
Okay.
And I'll set your hair for you, I know how to do it.
Thank you so much.
Let's go.
Let's grab our stuff.
The bone on your shoulder.
Scapula.
Pelvis.
The bone connecting your spine to your legs.
What about... the cheekbones.
Zygomatic.
Cervical vertebrae.
The spine...
Behind your chest area.
Incorrect.
It's the neck area.
Here, come look at this.
It's just one question that I got wrong.
What does it say.
The neck area.
Memorize it.
- Okay.
- Good.
Next time, I'll schedule us for the afternoon.
I have to go pick up Mook since she has work to do today.
Okay.
I'm fine with whenever so pick what time works best for you.
I'm ready for your lessons every hour of the day.
Mhm, okay.
You're my number one student.
Oh, whose car is this.
Can you help me move it?
Pass me that, I'll go keep it in the car first. Can you try pushing it?
I don't know if it'll move.
Come on.
1, 2, 3!
What the hell, they blocked my car and still put the gear on Park.
I'm in a hurry here.
Calm down, I'll go tell the employee to issue an announcement to find the owner of this car.
Fine, I'll leave it to you then.
Okay.
Why won't she pick up?
(Someone parked in front of my car, I can't leave.
I won't make it in time, you should call a taxi.)
Wiman Saran Nawamin is a pavilion building with a spire hall in the middle of a pond by the Chao Phraya River.
The roof lowers the spire in the Mondop Shape.
Three-tiered decorations show the insignia of the grand building.
Wow, good job!
Thank you.
Where do we have to go next?
Oh, let's film some inserts and have some lunch first.
Okay.
Wait here, I'll get some water for you.
Okay, thank you so much.
Q!
Are you feeling tired? We can stop here for today.
We can film some time later.
If you're too tired, Uncle Man and I can manage the rest.
Oh. I'm not needed anymore am I?
You probably don't need my help anymore.
That's not what I mean. I just didn't-
Water's here!
- Here, have some.
- Okay.
Let me give you a massage.
Do you feel more relaxed?
Thank you.
Aren't you tired today?
The weather is so hot.
Oh, Q, what outfit should I-
Q!
Uncle Man, please hold on to this for me.
What's going on with them?
Maybe it's the heat.
Its been an hour since we made an announcement, not even one person showed up.
You can leave first.
I can wait with you.
I told you I'm available 24 hours a day.
Sorry. When I heard the announcement I was in the middle of lifting weights.
Wow!
If I had known that my car was obstructing such a pretty lady's car, I would've came running.
Since you're here, quickly move your damn car.
I've been waiting for a whole hour.
All of my schedules are fucked up now.
You should learn some manners next time.
Don't you know how to move your gear to Neutral?
Oh, a tomboy!
I already said sorry, what else do you want?
Fuck, and here I thought you were a woman. What a waste.
But that smart mouth of yours should be kissed by me once,
and I'm sure you can't get enough of it.
Asshole!
Stop harassing her!
Wait for me!
Q!
Q.
Why did you follow me? You don't want me here anyway.
Just go do whatever you want with whoever you want.
What's wrong with you? You were fine this morning.
Who told you that I didn't want you to come?
You're misunderstanding me. Tell me what's wrong, don't act like this.
This is how I am.
If you don't like it, then don't bother with me!
Fuck off!
Q, can you be more reasonable?
How about this.
If I did something to offend you, I'm sorry.
But you have to let me know what I did wrong.
That way, I won't repeat the same mistakes.
I just don't like it, okay?
I don't like it!
But...
I haven't done anything yet.
Shut up.
You like my uncle, don't you?
Why didn't you just come with him? Why'd you bring me too?
I like your uncle?
You're overthinking things.
Then what was that massage?
You liked it, didn't you?
Huh?
And what else? He fed you water.
Next, you'll be feeding each other food.
And eventually, you'll be feeding each other... something else!
Let go.
Stop it, Q!
You're seriously misunderstanding.
It's just a trifle matter.
Listen to me first.
No.
Why?
This whole thing...
is just a trifle matter to you, right?
Then what would it take for it to become an important matter?
Do you guys have to sleep together first?
Huh?
Let me tell you one thing.
If you want to become my aunt or uncle in law...
Then keep on dreaming!
Are you... possessive of your uncle?
Or are you possessive of me?
Watch what you're saying.
Me? Possessive of you?
Q, listen to me.
I don't have romantic feelings for your uncle.
Because the one that I like...
is...
Why should I believe you?
I don't care if no one believes me.
But the one person that I hope will believe me...
Is you.
Will you trust me?
See ya.
Bye!
It's already so late, Mind is still not here?
Why don't you call her first to ask?
Woah. She called me so many times.
She also left a message...
"There's a car parked in front of mine so I can't leave."
"I won't make it in time."
"Call a taxi and go there first."
Mind can't pick you up?
Yeah. I have to get going.
You bought your motorcycle right?
Can you take me to call a taxi?
I can just give you a ride.
You guys made up, right?
So what's up?
What's wrong with you today?
You've been throwing tantrums like a child.
What tantrums?
I'm still mad at you.
Let's finish filming first.
We need to have a talk tonight.
I'm the reason for your behavior?
Everything's resolved. Q...
understands now.
Now he's smiling.
Let me tell you one thing. I'm not into younger boys.
They like throwing tantrums and I'm too lazy to put up with that.
C'mon, get in the car so we can go to the next location.
Thank you.
I thought I wouldn't make it in time.
I haven't been on a motorcycle for a while, I enjoyed the ride.
Um... then... I'll wait for you here.
You can go upstairs and do your work.
I don't really have any work scheduled.
I'm just here for a casual meeting.
Bank, the director, wanted to meet me.
Maybe I'll get lucky and get casted in a drama.
You don't have to wait for me, I don't want to waste your time.
Mind will pick me up later.
Then I'll wait until Mind comes.
I'll wait with you in case she comes late, so you won't be lonely.
No need.
If you want to wait.
Just wait inside.
Come on.
Okay.
All done.
What were you thinking, charging in like that?
It's a good thing you weren't seriously injured.
If the guard didn't come in time, you'd end up in the temple.
Sorry.
My body moved on its own.
Anyways, thank you.
What you did was very brave.
Ever since I was young...
When I run into a problem, everyone thinks I can deal with it on my own.
No one has stepped in to help me before.
You're the first one.
I...
I know.
That guy deserved it.
But you have to be careful. He's a huge guy.
Thank god you didn't die from his kicks.
I didn't die from his kicks, but I might die by your hands.
Sorry.
I have to call Mook.
I don't think I can pick her up in time.
I'll be right back.
Why are you making that face? Did things not go smootly?
Who told you that? Everything went well.
Look, they even offered me a contract.
Huh? Then why...?
Mind called.
She said she ran into some problems.
So she can't pick me up anymore.
Oh...
What a bummer.
So... you got ditched by Mind...
But I'm still here! Do you need to go anywhere else? I can give you a ride.
Nope.
I'm sorry.
Because of this... you've been stuck with me the whole day.
It's nothing.
Next time, if Mind is not available, just call me!
I'm super fast and also drive safely!
You're talking as if you're trying to get a girl.
That was my stomache. I haven't eaten anything yet today.
Really?
I'm also hungry.
How about this.
You can choose whichever restaurant you want.
Since you've been here with me the whole day, I'll treat you to a meal.
Hm... are you sure?
You might go broke from treating me.
Wow.
I'm gonna go broke at this rate.
How will I have enough money to pay?
Don't look down on this place. The food here is amazing.
I've been eating here since I was just a kid.
Okay, I'll finish everything.
If Mind was here,
I wouldn't get to eat this.
How come?
When you're with a medical student...
"Wait, this has a very high percentage of fat!"
"Wait, this has very high cholesterol."
"This is even worse, so much sodium."
"You'll get bloated."
"This one will make you fat."
She'll be like that and it gives me a headache.
No wonder why.
I always see you dance.
It's because you don't want to get fat, right?
That's not it.
Those dance practices...
It's for the opening stage of the Awards Ceremony.
Actually...
the ceremony is in just a few days.
But...
I don't have a plus-one yet.
Then... do you...
Have anyone in mind yet?
I didn't really have anyone in mind.
But right now...
I think I do.
Actually...
I haven't even asked the person yet if they're free.
I'll give you a hint.
You know the person.
Not just casually,
But you know them very well.
I see.
X!
- Yes?
- Why don't you stay for dinner?
You can leave your outfit and props in the car.
I'll drive you back later.
Thank you so much.
Q!
Let's have a talk.
Then I'll wait for you guys inside.
Sure.
Uncle Man...
Did you know that your behavior today was very inappropriate?
How did you even come to that conclusion about X and I?
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I was frustrated either.
I understand. It's happened to me before.
When you like someone, you'll feel as if you own them.
You'll feel possessive.
You're scared someone else will take them away from you.
I just don't know whether I just don't like it when my friends become friendly with someone else...
Or I...
Do you feel this way with Toy and Frank as well?
Hm?
You already have your answer.
Just ask your heart.
But...
If mom finds out...
If my friends find out...
Isn't it just one of the many problems you have to face in life?
If you know what you have to face...
All you need to do is be prepared.
Love is always worth the risk.
But...
I'm just not sure.
Because when I'm with X...
I feel as if...
I know.
When love occurs...
it does not care about gender.
If it happens...
You just need to accept it.
Or... just let it go.
Then...
What do you think I should do?
That's up to you.
But don't let other people's feelings dictate your own.
Got it?
Don't worry.