Hey! Are you done yet?
Where do you keep the alcohol and cotton pads? I can't find them.
I told you to wash your face but you're washing your hair instead...
If it keeps getting wet, your wound will not heal.
I didn't think it would be hard to wash my hair with one arm.
Although it's not easy either.
Getting a head massage like this feels so nice.
If I ever have a partner...
and they do this for me...
I'd love them to death.
Shut up.
Come here, I'll wash the shampoo off.
Okay.
You're so...
Why am I doing this for you?
What are you smiling about?
Can you wash my face for me too?
You're so annoying!
Hey! It'll get in my eyes!
Don't you feel bad for me?
That's enough, can you give me some water?
Sure.
Here you go.
You're doing it like this?!
Is this enough yet?
Hey!
My arm hurts!
Why don't you go back home so you'll have people to help you out?
Why would you come here and sleep alone?
If my family knows what happened yesterday, I'll never hear the end of it.
Anyway, if you don't want me to sleep alone...
Why don't you come sleep with me?
No way.
Stay still, okay?
I'm asking you seriously...
Don't you have any close friends?
I always see you hanging out alone.
If it's in the past, I have a few.
But because my family had to move around often...
I don't have any close friends now.
But this time we're back here for good.
I'm thinking of finding someone I can befriend...
Someone around here...
Here.
It's done.
Your wound should dry up in around two days...
Then you won't have to cover it up anymore.
Thank you.
Anyways...
How's the bet going?
Don't forget the duration.
What should I make you do if you lose the bet?
Would you even be able to follow my request?
I'm sorry to say this but...
Someone like me...
Is not a loner like you.
Just wait and we'll see which of us will get to order the other person to do what they want.
Okay.
I can understand why you changed the tutoring location to a park.
But why do I have to jog?
You might not know this, but doing something other than just reading a textbook is good.
It will help your brain memorize things better.
It will link the things we remember and the things we do together.
Get it?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Even when the earth is constantly revolving around the sun, we still feel as if it's staying still.
What is this theory called?
The Relativity Theory.
Take that!
Wrong.
It's 'Special Relativity'.
The special theory of relativity.
The theory is about constant speed, not acceleration speed.
Go run a small lap while reciting the information.
Go.
Yes Ma'am.
Special Relativity.
The theory about constant speed, not acceleration speed.
Spacial Relativity.
Special Relativity.
I can't believe I have to take lessons and also help my friend.
Man, Q.
It's clearly your problem.
Yet I still have to be concerned about it.
(I hope you'll enjoy the egg tarts.)
(Thank you so much, Q.)
Special Relativity.
The theory about constant speed, not acceleration speed.
Okay, cut!
Camera 1 and 2, you can manage the insert.
Quickly!
You can go ahead and take a rest.
Okay, thank you.
Great job, Mook.
Your acting was very good.
Let me deal with the inserts first.
In the mean time, you can prepare for the next shot.
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
Oh, you're still here?
Yes, um, I bought this for you.
Wow, where did you get this from?
Oh, you even know my favourite flavour.
It's very refreshing.
You don't have to wash the dishes.
I can handle this by myself.
It's just a couple of dishes.
When my mom bakes...
Q had to wash a lot more than this.
I think it's nice when you do that.
Huh?
Just now, you used your name when referring to yourself.
I like it when you do that.
It's not like it's weird. My family talks like this all the time.
Well, we're done here for today.
I...
I'm going home.
And you...
You can call me X.
Come on.
Don't forget to rest a lot.
Rest? It's not even evening yet.
Up to you then. Do whatever you want.
And...
Where's my shirt?
I'm going now.
Just leave it here.
You can wear my shirt back.
This one's my favorite.
Then, if you're okay...
see you on monday?
I'm off.
Bye.
Q, can I come in?
Yes.
What are you up to?
Nothing. What's the matter?
Nothing!
It's just that since I've been busy, I haven't been able to talk to you a lot these days.
Oh.
Yeah.
Isn't this normal?
Or is something wrong with you?
Are you sick?
Um...
No, I'm fine.
But if you have something to tell me, you can go ahead.
I'm listening.
Oh... if it's about Rookie...
Then nothing's changed.
They confirmed with X.
Oh, okay.
And how is X? Is he okay now?
Do you have to visit him and treat his wounds again?
Hm?
No.
I have plans with Toy and Frank so the next time I see him should be on Monday.
Did you have any business with X?
No!
Um... I just wanted to tell you...
Before you decide on something, don't act too rashly.
Consider what you like or don't like. Think about it slowly.
You can always talk to me about anything.
I'm okay with everything that you like.
I'm fine with it.
What are you talking about?
I'm so confused.
Is there anything else?
I want to go take a shower.
Okay, I won't bother you anymore.
I'll get going.
You can always talk to me!
I know!
(Day 5)
Have some water.
Thank you.
Thanks, man.
By the way, don't you have tutoring lessons today?
This is the location for my tutoring session today.
Mook doesn't have anywhere to be later, so Mind will pick her up from here.
Actually I did have somewhere to be.
But they canceled the appointment, so I'm free now.
Mook!
I'm here to say thanks to someone who kept sending me things.
The snacks this morning was soooo yummy.
I really have to thank you, Q.
I finally get to meet you.
The egg tart and the snacks this morning...
And also the gifts on Saturday.
This morning?
Oh!
This morning, when you arrived just as the school gates opened.
Yes.
I'm happy as long as you liked it.
Oh right. Your family bakes pastries, right?
Next time, bring some for me to try.
I'll review it for you.
You will?
Wow. If my mom knows, she'd be very happy.
My mom and my uncle are both fans of you.
By the way, how did you know that my family bakes...?
Um... you're the one who told me.
When we were messaging the other day.
Me?
Yeah!
Ah, the chat messages through Instagram!
Oh, right! I'm quite forgetful.
Okay.
You guys have to go practice, right?
Then... I'll...
I'll cheer you on from over there.
Okay.
Hang in there, everyone!
Bye bye.
- Hey.
- How are you?
What did you guys talk about?
Well...
(Day 6)
Are you here to get something to eat from my house again?
Nah, I'm just here to send you off.
I'm worried you'll get into an accident again.
I'm sure you're planning to sleep at your condo anyway.
But if you're hungry, hurry up and follow me.
Mom won't say no to you.
Here.
I'll send you off here.
You should go inside.
Huh?
Won't you come in first?
You've already come this far.
No need to feel bad.
No thanks.
But don't worry.
I'll come by again for sure.
And also...
Also what?
Don't go all quiet on me. What is it?
You'll know when tomorrow comes.
See ya!
What is wrong with that guy?
(Day 9)
I want to eat noodles.
I can eat anything.
Nawa.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
What is it, Mr. Principal.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
I want you to film an introduction clip for Nawapol.
Since he got selected for the Ship for Southeast Asian and Japanese Youth Program in Japan.
Can you do it?
Me?
Why me?
I've noticed that you and Nawapol are quite close lately.
And didn't Nawapol helped you when you had that car accident?
Yes.
Just think of it as helping to promote our school and our country.
Even if you didn't get selected, you're still an important part of the process of helping our country become well known by the whole world.
You should be proud that-
Okay, I'll do it.
You don't have to say anymore.
I feel as if I'm about to go to the Olympics or something.
That's the spirit! Then, I'll leave it up to you.
Okay.
It's your plan, isn't it?
Make yourself available next week.
You could just ask me to help you directly.
No need to get the Principle involved.
(Day 10)
(Day 11)
When are you going to ask Mook to go to the Awards Ceremony?
(Day 13)
There are less than ten days left
That's right. I'm tired of messaging her for you.
I have lessons and tutoring classes.
You don't even seem to care about that bet with X.
You're even helping him film that video.
Yeah, what's up with you?
Honestly...
I'm not that serious about winning or losing the bet.
You guys can stop if you want.
What? No!
You can't just quit.
You asshole.
You scared me.
Why?
Even if we quit, I'm the one who loses the bet.
Not you.
Um...
Uh...
Well, right now everything is going according to plan, right?
She returns your messages nicely, right?
Right?
Right.
See?
If you were to give up now, it's like...
like... you're a loser!
And you'll come complain to us.
About how you never win in anything.
Right?
I've lost so often.
I don't care if I lose one more time.
But I think what Toy said also has a point.
Don't you want to get a taste of winning for once?
Even if you fall down ten times but manage to get up on the eleventh time, it'll still make you proud, wouldn't it?
Oh shit.
Look at how cool you've become.
Fine.
If you guys don't want to quit, I'll have to keep asking you guys to help me.
The Principle wants me to help X film his video.
I'll be busy all weekend.
I'm so sick of it.
Hm?
It's not like I want to go.
Really?
Q, did you know?
Lately, you've been spending even more time with X than with us.
But! It's okay.
You can leave Mook to me.
Up to you, then.
No worries, you can leave it up to me!