Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[growling]
[thumping]
[crashing]
[thunder crashing]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder continues]
[gasps]
[thunder rumbles]
[woman] I can't come over, Todd.
I'm babysitting.
Yeah, I finally got her to fall asleep.
Took forever, though.
I mean, I've never seen a kid
so scared of her own toys. [laughs]
[wind gusting]
[rumbling]
[creaking]
[gasps]
[thunder booms]
[whirring]
-[creaks]
-[gasps]
-[panting]
-[creaking]
[creaking continues]
[thunder rumbles]
-[roars]
-[gasps]
[creaking]
[squelching]
[buzzing and squeaking]
[male voice] Aah!
Kelly Ferguson.
-[gasps]
-[teacher] …formula--
[laughter]
[girl] It's not a nightmare, Monster Girl.
Just your life.
[laughter]
[teacher] Miss Ferguson,
I know you skipped a grade in math,
and we're all very impressed.
That doesn't mean
you can sleep through my class.
I'm okay. I'm good. Really.
Then calculate the volume
of that object using the proper formula.
♪ It can't get better than this ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no ♪
-♪ It can't get better than this… ♪
-Thanks.
-[clicking fingers]
-[teacher] Kelly?
-We're waiting.
-[record scratch]
Twenty-six pi squared.
-I didn't say to take a wild guess.
-That's not a wild guess.
That's the answer. 26 pi squared.
Actually, it's 25.97789,
but I decided to round up.
OMG, you are so smart…
-Said no one ever.
-[laughter]
-[school bell rings]
-♪ I had a dream ♪
♪ I got everything I wanted ♪
♪ Not what you think ♪
♪ And if I'm bein' honest ♪
♪ It might have been a nightmare ♪
♪ To anyone who might care ♪
♪ If they knew what they said ♪
♪ Would go straight to my head ♪
-♪ What would they say instead… ♪
-[echoing] Hey! Look who it is.
Monster Girl!
Raaaar!
[Kelly] Tell me the truth.
Am I always gonna be known
as the Monster Girl?
Well, I mean, you did tell people
that a monster attacked you. So…
Yeah, when I was five.
You ate crayons when we were kids.
No one calls you Crayola Mouth.
That's because crayons are delicious.
Let's face it, monsters aren't real.
Oh, my God.
Even my best friend thinks I'm crazy.
Yeah. You are crazy.
That's why you're my best friend.
-[crash]
-[boy] Hey! Give me my wig back!
You know the rules, Jesper.
-There's no costumes allowed.
-Hah! Yeah? It's Halloween!
This is unconstitutional.
-Give-- Everyone, listen up!
-[feedback squeals]
All right?
Big time Halloween party at mine tonight!
Costumes are not only allowed,
they're mandatory!
-[cheering]
-Okay?
We should totally go to that party.
I don't know. Jesper is a senior.
We're only freshmen.
Kelly, it's Halloween.
The one night we can be anything we want.
Anything in the world.
What do you wanna be?
♪ The future's so bright-ight and shiny ♪
♪ Lookin' up-up 'cause it's so blindin' ♪
♪ Flyin', flyin' high
They ain't gonna find me
♪ Now everybody's lookin'
Lookin', lookin' at me ♪
♪ Unbelievable, unbe-unbelievable ♪
Oh, we are so going to that party.
Yes… we… are.
[scoffs]
[man 1] Yeah, just set it up over here.
[man 2] Oh, we don't need a map.
Right… It should just…
-[crackles]
-Ow!
[woman] That's too high.
[crackling]
Hey, honey! What you doin'?
Oh, just… makin' a Halloween costume.
Oh! Uh… For what?
[sizzling]
Um…
Uh-- Halloween party at a friend's house.
And you were planning on going?
Uh, yeah, I am.
[gasps]
[sizzling]
Oh, I--
I may have suggested
that you would…
babysit for Ms. Zellman.
-Your boss?
-Mm-hm.
-The Ice Queen?
-Uh, yes, but don't-- don't call her that.
No, thanks.
Well, my company Halloween party
is tonight,
and I overheard Ms. Zellman complaining
that she couldn't find a sitter,
so I thought--
Well, I thought you could…
So, you threw
my name out there to babysit?
Yes.
-Mom!
-Well…
-Dad! Mom sold me out to her boss!
-[sighs]
-[Dad] Listen to your mother, Kelly.
-[Kelly scoffs]
-Thanks for havin' my back, Dad!
-[Dad] No problem, sweetie.
You know, I can barely
keep my phone charged,
let alone take care of some kid.
Okay. Kelly, please.
[sighs] Now, if I cancel on Ms. Zellman,
she'll be furious.
[whispers] This is the Ice Queen
we're talking about.
-But--
-Besides, it's only babysitting,
-and I think it will be…
-What--
-…really good for you. Plus…
-But--
…you'll make 15 dollars an hour.
You can totally do this, sweetie!
Hm?
Fine.
Thank you. Thank you!
You're gonna be great!
[sighs]
[buzzing]
[click]
[laughing] The Ice Queen?
[tinkling]
I-- I-- I mean,
your costume is-- it's literally--
Hi, Ms. Zellman.
Kelly. [sighs]
-This way.
-[jingling]
I printed up a list of no-no's.
Kelly!
[heels tapping]
"No ice cream, no gluten,
no caffeine, no dairy, no peanuts,
no more than 30 minutes of screen time"?
You have a stopwatch
on your cell phone, right?
-I… I--
-Because it's Halloween,
Jacob may have three pieces of candy.
-Oh! I've got some--
-No, no, no, no.
Raisins, dried apple chips,
or puffed rice cakes.
Also, no running, no shouting,
no discussing global tragedies
or current events.
-Got it.
-Emergency contact numbers.
Poison control, his doctor, his dentist.
And his sleep time checklist.
Learn it.
It takes three hours
just to put him to sleep?
If he goes to sleep at all.
[sighs]
Jacob?
Jacob…
this is your babysitter, Kelly.
[jingling]
Hi, Jacob.
Please don't go, Mommy.
-Halloween's scary.
-It'll be okay, honey. I promise.
Your muzzie-wuzzie loves you so much.
-This way, Kelly.
-[jingling]
[heels tapping]
Kelly!
[door closes]
I'll be home at midnight. Follow the list.
Lock the doors. And no trick-or-treaters.
None.
And keep Jacob safe.
Midnight. Sharp.
-[heels tapping quickly]
-Okay, bye.
-[clattering]
-[gasps]
[rattling]
[clattering continues]
[rustling]
[rustling continues]
Jacob?
What are you doing?
Hey! Spit that out!
[gasps]
Don't put me to bed! I can't go to sleep.
-Why not?
-I have bad nightmares.
Sometimes, at night,
that comes out of my fish tank.
It feels like it's coming to get me,
but Mom says it's just a nightmare.
I actually know a lot about nightmares.
-You do?
-Yeah.
And I get it.
Sometimes, they feel real.
Like, really real.
But it's just your mind
playing tricks on you.
They can't hurt you.
Mine can. I can make monsters.
There's no such thing as monsters.
But there is…
Quackers the Duck!
♪ Doo-doo-doo-doo, doo-doo
Doo-doo-doo-doo! Doo-doo-doo! ♪
And his main man, Tedster.
-♪ Doo-doo-doo-doo! ♪
-[cries]
Whoa!
-What happened to Tedster?
-I dreamt he was on fire.
And when I woke up, he was.
[Tedster, slowly] I want to hug you.
-I don't like his hugs.
-[sighs]
If it makes you feel any better,
when I was a little kid,
I thought my bad dreams
could come true too.
What did you do?
I grew up.
Now I'm just scared of real-life stuff,
like climate change,
and inequality, and talking to boys,
and, like, everything I read on Twitter.
It's really scary.
I'm not helping, am I?
[sighs] All right. Fine.
How about… I check under your bed?
[sighs]
[grunts]
-[screams]
-What is it?
Dirty socks!
[sighs]
Not cool.
Ah, classic.
Nothing in here either.
[creaking]
Okay, but don't turn off the lights!
I'm afraid of the dark.
You know what I do
when I get scared of the dark?
I make…
these.
These…
are my own personal night-lights.
This one's especially fun. Look.
[Jacob gasps]
Whoa.
[Kelly] You can have this one.
[Jacob] Thanks.
-[child 1] Thank you!
-[child 2] Come on!
-[laughter]
-[screeching sound effect]
[child 3] Trick or treat!
-Wait up!
-Thank you.
[screeching sound effect]
[man] Hey, everyone, slow down.
-[child] Trick or treat!
-[boy] Yeah, I know!
-[dance music playing]
-[Kelly] All right, engage my FOMO.
How's the party?
[boy] It's amazing!
Wait. What's your costume?
I am the crown jewel of nutritious snacks.
-I'm "Broccoli."
-[laughs]
Oh…
[lights buzzing]
[squelching]
[crunching]
[crackles]
-[loud pop music playing]
-[cheering]
Dude, dude!
Look who's here!
You gotta get over here, Kelly.
Deanna is about to walk that plank.
Are you broccoli?
Uh… Yeah, that-- that's me.
[laughs] I love broccoli.
-[laughs]
-[girl] Do you wanna dance?
-Go get 'em, Tommy.
-[Tommy] All right. I-- I'd love to.
[fire roars]
[fireworks exploding outside]
[lights buzzing]
[whirring]
[lights crackling]
-[bleeping]
-[robot] Enemy alert.
Enemy alert.
[whirring and crackling continue]
[male voice] ♪ Do as, mm-mmm… ♪
[creaking]
♪ Now give into the mm-mm-mmm… ♪
-[panting]
-[creaking]
[fireworks exploding]
[buzzing and creaking]
[squelching and cracking sounds]
What's up, Rhode Island?
-[fireworks banging]
-[crowd] Ooh!
[echoing explosion]
[whirring]
Look at what you've done here.
-Fabulous work.
-[robot bleeping]
Your Gift of Dreams
bringing nightmares to life.
Bravo, Jacob. Bravo.
Kell--
-"Kuh-kuh-kuh." Uh, no.
-[whimpers]
None of that.
[muffled groans] Mmm! Mmm!
-Come again?
-Mmm! Mmm!
Enunciate, darling. Try using your words.
[whimpers]
-I kid. I kid!
-Mmmph!
[continues whimpering]
Just a tentacle? Not attached to anything.
Now that's an outside the box nightmare,
even for me.
-[Jacob whimpering]
-Aah!
[thud]
You and I are about to unleash
your nightmares on the world.
[echoing crash]
[crashing stamping continues]
[rumbling]
[Kelly] Jacob?
-Mmm! Mmm!
-[rattling]
-[muffled screaming]
-[banging]
-[Jacob whimpering]
-[grunting]
[slurping]
[slurping continues]
Mm?
[choking sounds]
-Jacob?
-[slurping]
What are you doing?
-[roars]
-[gasps]
[growls]
[burbling]
[Jacob whimpering]
-[monster grunts]
-[Jacob squeals]
-Jacob! [screams]
-[monster laughs]
-[screeching]
-[Kelly gasps]
[chatters and shrieks]
[monsters babbling]
[shrieks]
[monster panting]
[Kelly] Get away from him!
[roars]
-[Kelly grunting]
-[monster growling]
-[shrieks]
-[grumbles]
[Jacob whimpering]
-Hey! Stop that!
-[growling]
[Jacob whimpering]
[squeals]
[babbles]
[female monster shrieking]
-No!
-[growling]
[monsters chuckling]
[squeals]
[grunts] No!
[rumbling]
[Kelly] Nine-one-one?
Hi. These-- these things just took
the kid I was babysitting.
I'm pretty sure they're monsters.
Yes, I am aware it's Halloween night,
but this… this is not a joke.
This is serious. These were proper
creatures of the night, they-- they--
Hello? Hello?
Who are you?
Liz Lerue. Babysitter.
We got a nightmare ping come from here.
-Who are you?
-I'm the babysitter.
I'll be the judge of that.
[sighs] Where's your charge?
-[baby coos]
-My…
The kid. Your child.
The human being you're
supposed to be responsible for?
-I don't know!
-[baby gurgles]
These things came out
from under the bed.
They took him.
Look, I tried calling the police,
but they thought it was a prank.
-Hey! You can't go in there!
-What'd these things look like?
Um, they were small and fat,
with crazy teeth and weird hair.
-How many?
-Um… three.
-[grunts] God!
-Height? Weight? Speech patterns?
What were they wearing?
Did they have eyes?
Um, they were two to three feet high.
Uh, claws.
They had weird mouths
and two eyes, lopsided.
This way!
They looked like this!
Toadies.
What's a "Toadie"?
Also, whose baby is that?
Is it yours? I'm not judging if it is.
This is Carmella.
-Carmella, say hi. Don't be shy.
-[gurgles]
I'm babysitting her because
that's what actual babysitters do.
We watch and protect our kids.
Now, stand over there
and play the quiet game.
[whirring]
[Kelly] Ow!
"The time of nightmares has begun"?
Which way'd they go?
[whirring]
Twelve degrees north-east.
[Liz] You're like a calculator.
What time are the parents home?
[Kelly] Midnight. His mom is very intense.
She would never be late.
[Liz] Okay. Stay here,
chew your hair, find out what you'd
look like with dog ears, I don't care.
But if the mom calls,
you act like everything's cool.
-Got it?
-[Carmella babbles]
Good.
[footsteps getting fainter]
[panting]
Excuse you! I'm coming with you.
No. You will just get in my way.
Or you'll get possessed,
hypnotized, cursed, boiled,
or turned into
a three-headed dog of darkness.
For real?
Wait, did you even see this?
-[whirring]
-[Kelly] These burn marks.
They come from out of Jacob's window,
run down here, and then they just vanish.
And those tracks.
They don't match the claws
that those trollies had--
[Liz] Toadies.
Toadies had.
And they have an entirely
different pattern and diameter,
which means
a completely different thing was here.
-[closes zip]
-[sighs]
Okay, CSI: Rhode Island.
-Your funeral.
-Ow.
-Jump on. The clock's ticking.
-[starts engine]
-[whimpers]
-[Liz] Hang on, Carmella.
♪ They strip away your senses ♪
♪ But intuition know-ows ♪
♪ That at night the senses ♪
-♪ Get ready for the show-ow… ♪
-We've got Toadies on our hands.
Bring me up on the tracker.
Are you talking to me?
Pull up a map of their main tunnels.
-"Tunnels"?
-Will you knock it off?
No! Not you, just some girl.
♪ It's goin' down, down, down… ♪
[Liz] Anything on the monster tracker?
GPR activity near Sharkie Park? Copy that.
♪ And it's gone runnin' ♪
♪ Trouble's comin' ♪
-[Kelly] GPR?
-[Liz] Ground-penetrating radar.
Toadies have a network
of tunnels under the city.
Sometimes our monster GPR
picks up their movements.
[chattering and squeaking]
-[Kelly] We're not going in the tunnels.
-[Liz] Nope.
-[clang]
-[Liz] We are fishing for Toadies.
[Kelly] Ball pits. So gross.
Like, gross to the third power.
[Liz] Math jokes, huh? Funny.
Anyway, look for a hidden tunnel.
Should be around here somewhere.
-[Kelly] How do you know all this stuff?
-[Liz] Check the bag.
[bleep]
"Babysitter's Guide to Monster Hunting"?
[Liz] It's a collection
of thousands of years' worth
of monster hunting wisdom
passed down through the ages.
Memorize the guide, stay alive.
So I'm not crazy.
[Liz] Found it.
-I mean, can you believe this?
-[babbling]
Uh, the Toadies dug their tunnel
right at the end of the slide,
so when a kid comes shooting down…
Whoosh! Right into their trap.
-[Carmella cooing]
-[Kelly] This is insane.
What should I do?
-Maybe take off her jacket?
-Okay.
-[clink]
-[whoosh]
-[snap]
-[click]
-[raspberry]
-[chuckles]
-[Kelly] Why do you need baby powder?
-[sighs]
-[Liz] Read the guide.
-[cooing]
[Liz] All right, come on.
"Beware.
Toadies love the smell of newborns.
They cannot resist a taste."
One of 'em pops out looking for a snack,
boom, got 'em.
You're using the baby as bait? No!
Listen, this is the only thing
that will get them up to the surface.
[grunting and growling]
[babbling]
[powering up]
-[Kelly] What's that?
-[rumbling]
-Those are sound vibrations.
-[Carmella cooing]
-[rumbling continues]
-[Carmella fussing]
[scrabbling]
[rumbling intensifies]
[burbling]
[growls]
-I can't do this!
-Kelly! No!
-[Toadie yells]
-[Carmella cooing]
[shrieks]
-[babbles]
-[Kelly yells]
[Liz] Oh, come on!
[screeches]
[Toadies chattering]
-[whimpers]
-[growls]
By the Order of the Babysitters,
I demand you return that child!
-[babbles]
-[blows raspberry]
-[Jacob crying]
-Come on!
Don't worry, Carmella.
I'm gonna keep you safe.
-[Kelly screams]
-[rumbling]
[hissing]
[whimpering]
-[growls]
-[Liz] Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Look what I've got.
If you give us the boy, you get sparkly.
-What do you say?
-[chatters]
[Liz] Come on,
don't play hardball with me.
-You guys love to trade.
-[Kelly muttering]
-[Liz] Jacob or sparkly?
-[Kelly] Okay. Hello. Hi.
Do we have a deal?
[scoffs]
-[growling]
-[grunts]
-[phone playing music]
-Okay. Damn.
Shut that off!
It's Jacob's mom!
Ms. Zellman?
Hi. How's the monster?
What?
Oh! You mean--
No. Yeah. Um-- Everything's fine.
Jacob and I are having so much fun.
-[Toadie gurgling]
-What's that noise?
Uh… It's… it's a movie.
That sounds like a scary movie.
Check the list, Kelly. No scary movies.
No, no, no, no, no!
It's-- it's a fun movie.
-It's about unicorns and rainbows and…
-[Toadie chattering and growling]
[running footsteps]
-[Liz yells]
-[roars]
What was that?
-[Kelly] Um…
-[chittering]
-A… unicorn fell off a… a rainbow.
-[Toadie squealing]
[Kelly] But it was saved by a cloud.
We're all good here.
Let me speak to Jacob. Now!
Um, no, he's sleeping.
You said you were watching a movie.
-[chittering]
-[Liz] Oh, no you're not! No!
No, he just--
he just fell asleep like that.
He did?
[laughs] Oh. That's a first.
Tonight is a night of firsts.
[woman] The tenth annual company
costume party is about to begin!
[partygoers cheering]
[Ms. Zellman]
I'm glad Jacob fell asleep early.
-[squealing]
-Yeah. Me too.
Remember. Midnight.
-Okay. Bye. Bye.
-Sharp.
-Bye, bye, bye.
-[Liz yells]
[Toadie groaning]
[Carmella chuckles]
[Kelly] I'm gonna be grounded
for all of eternity.
The Toadies left with Jacob.
So, how are we gonna get him back now?
That's why
this little creep's comin' with us.
-[Carmella coos]
-It's nine o'clock, Carmella.
-We'll get you home, sweetie.
-[cooing]
The Toadies always trade.
This is worse than I thought.
-[banging]
-[Toadie grumbling]
[squealing]
-[thumping]
-[groaning]
[wailing]
[groans]
[panting]
-[whimpers]
-[babbles]
-[Jacob yelling]
-[chattering]
[groans]
[crying]
Oh, hootie-hoo! Well, well, well.
The guest of honor has arrived, finally!
I trust your travels were smooth.
Mmm!
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
[clicks fingers]
-[gasps]
-[man sighs]
-[croaking]
-I wanna go home!
-You're not going anywhere.
Huh? Impressive, isn't it?
I suppose you want
to know how it all works.
[chuckles]
I've slowly, but surely,
accumulated 51 rare gases
and mixed them
with the perfect specificity.
Why, you ask?
To fill these beautiful tanks
with enough power
to manifest my army of nightmares
into actual life!
Aah! Terrors alive like never seen before.
-[wind whistling]
-Aah!
All I needed was just
one more little tiny ingredient,
a pathetic
yet highly imaginative little twerp,
personified in this case by… well…
you, get it?
[whimpers]
You, my dear boy,
will conjure an army
of infinite nightmares.
You and I are about to ruin the world.
Sleepy time.
♪ Kids, I come… ♪
[Kelly] Wow. We got the baby
back to her parents just in time.
I hope she wasn't too freaked out.
[Liz] Freaked out?
Carmella loves monster hunting.
♪ Kids, I come for you… ♪
How much did her parents pay
for you to look after Carmella?
Two hundo. Cash.
Is that the going rate these days
for using a baby as bait?
It was a good plan.
Ninety-nine percent of the time,
that should've worked.
And it's Halloween night.
What are you making?
Fifteen dollars an hour?
♪ Kids, I come for you ♪
[chuckles] Yes.
Welcome to my Nightmare Nursery.
Your new home.
I trust you're snug as a bug?
[whimpering]
Have you ever been hypnotized? It's grand.
[Jacob] Hm? No! No!
-[whimpering] No! Aah!
-Stop wriggling, you little worm.
My evil lullaby will put you
into a deep, dark sleep.
♪ Do as you're told ♪
-[choir joins in]
-♪What a gift, what a sight to behold ♪
♪ For the darkest of dreams ♪
♪ You'll surrender to sleep ♪
♪ Child, you'll do as you're told ♪
Why are you singing?
-How peculiar.
-What?
That usually works.
Aah! Your Gift of Dreams
is blocking my lullaby.
Bravo, Jacob. Bravo.
Alas, fear not.
I have a few tricks up my sleeve.
You will sleep, boy.
Okay, well…
when my mom wants me to go to sleep…
-Yes?
-She brings me a…
Hyper Cola Energy drink.
-Right.
-And chocolate-covered espresso beans.
Then I'm out like a light.
Do you think I was born yesterday?
I'm not stupid, boy.
♪ Bom, bom-bom
Bom-bom-bom-bom-bom-bom-bom… ♪
-[girl laughing]
-[boy] Yeah, I know.
[girl] Let me on your back!
♪ This is a private jam ♪
[laughter]
♪ I see you walking with a hippie dance ♪
[growling]
♪ Oh, your neon skirt dance… ♪
You work for Brown University?
-Something like that.
-What's in the bag?
-♪ Oh, no, no, no… ♪
-My professor.
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
-♪ You give me butterflies… ♪
-[bleep]
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
♪ You feel like paradise… ♪
-We're throwing the Toadie in the trash?
-[growling]
[Toadie screeches]
Yeah. That's exactly what we're doing.
♪ I want you to be mon amour ♪
-[door unlocks]
-[creaking]
Welcome to the Rhode Island chapter
of the Order of the Babysitters.
We're part of a super secret organization
with chapters all around the world.
The Greek goddess, Artemis,
Cleopatra, Merlin,
Rosa Parks, all babysitters.
[Kelly] Whoa.
Archimedes, Frida Kahlo,
Florence Nightingale,
Maria Tallchief, Noor Inayat Khan.
[Liz] Yeah. We've been around
for thousands of years.
Tell anyone about our location,
and I'll feed you
to our resident hobgoblin.
Listen up, SITs.
Our mission is Jacob Zellman.
Five years old,
possibly with the Gift of Dreams.
We have three hours and five minutes
until his mom gets back
and finds
her little bundle of joy missing.
[whirring]
Nothing new from the surveillance cameras.
Hey, Berna, will you start the laser scan?
-On it.
-[bleep]
[whirring]
[girl] All right. Let's take a look
in this Toadie's pouch.
What the heck? Is that half a duck?
[Kelly] It's a goose lamp.
-How big are their pouches?
-Who's the human?
This is Kelly.
[girl] And why exactly is she here?
She was with the kid when he got taken.
-We need to pick her brain.
-But--
Just search the thing for clues.
Rude. It's not a "thing."
It's a Monstria Chordata Amphibia
Carnivora of the Toadie subspecies.
-[sighs] Remove her.
-Cassie, this isn't your call.
You're just a Sitter in Training.
I mean, see this? And this?
And this?
Chapter Vice President. Okay?
It's gonna take me hours
to remove the items from its pouch.
Better get to it, then.
-I'm so sorry. So sorry.
-[Liz] Follow me.
Hey. So, this Jacob kid
really has the Gift of Dreams?
I--
I just told her what Jacob told me.
I don't even really know
what the Gift of Dreams is.
It's-- it's legendary.
A young kid who is supposed
to be able to bring dreams to life.
Or nightmares.
The Order was founded
to protect kids like that.
I could tell you a bit more
over a cup of coffee, maybe?
Pump the brakes, Casanova.
Can you make
one of your memory potions?
Uh… Yeah. I, uh…
I have a passion for potions.
-[Kelly] What is that?
-It's Minotaur Memory Dust.
Three parts beetle root,
one part gnome guano.
Yet, I have not tested this batch out yet,
so I hope I don't fry her brain.
Fry my brain…
Now, tell us every single detail
you remember when Jacob was taken.
♪ Do as, mm-mmm ♪
♪ Now give into the mm-mm-mmm ♪
Maybe I used too much beetle root?
No, I…
I heard that song
when I was a little girl…
[roaring]
[creaking]
[thunder rumbling]
[crunching]
[slithering]
[crackling]
[male voice] Ah, Kelly Ferguson.
I've been looking for a girl
who can make her dreams come to life,
and now here you are.
And you're all mine.
[man laughs]
-[babysitter yells]
-[crash]
[babysitter grunting]
[yells]
♪ Do as you're told ♪
♪ Now give into the darkness inside ♪
♪ Heavy eyelids sink deep ♪
-[Kelly sings along]
-♪ In the clutches of sleep ♪
♪ Mmm, listen ♪
[man and choir]
♪You'll do as you're told ♪
[choir] ♪ You'll do as you're told ♪
[Cassie] Why did it stop
on the Grand Guignol?
[boy] He's the Stealer of Dreams,
the Bringer of Nightmares.
Legend has it
he's collecting bad dreams from kids
to build a nightmare army.
That's him.
[Liz] What do you mean?
That's the monster who tried
to take me when I was a little girl!
No. No way.
Liz, those prints I found.
They were tail marks, just like this.
I think he's what took Jacob.
This can't be happening. Not again.
-A-Are you okay?
-Well, you see, her--
[Berna]
It's not our story to tell, Curtis.
"The Grand Guignol travels
in the Nightmare Realm.
The Boogeypeople are almost impossible
to locate when they are in there."
Boogeypeople?
Seven, actually.
They're like a monster mafia.
My whole life, my whole life
I was told this wasn't real.
That it didn't happen. But now…
-But now…
-This is why we don't let normies in here.
Each of us
has been through a monster attack.
This is from a Class Two Oozer.
[Curtis] Yeah, I've got one of those, too.
Fire-spitting Grunk.
-[Curtis] I was impaled by a Brush troll.
-[Berna] This is from a vampire rabbit.
-[Cassie] Krampus.
-[Berna] Thunderbird.
-[Curtis] Baba Yaga.
-[Cassie] Bunnicula. Paper cut.
-[Curtis] I got this from a Cloud Serpent.
-No one wants to see that, Curtis.
That's why we're here.
To make sure what happened to us
never happens to another kid.
-[straightens jacket]
-[sighs]
So how do we take down the Grand Guignol?
We don't.
Well, there is a way.
It's a combination between…
Angel Fire and Monster Punch.
Yet the ingredients are crazy combustible.
We're talking, uh, uh…
cobalt from Athena's tomb,
um… Chupacabra venom--
-None of which we have.
-Don't worry.
-I have my sources.
-[Kelly] And the Monster Punch?
That's the only way
to drive the Angel Fire
into the Boogeyman's heart.
It's crazy hard to execute,
even if you could get near him.
It's never been done.
There's a solution to every problem.
[Liz] All right.
Let's put that to the test.
Curtis, gather the essentials.
Yes! Time to geek out. Follow me!
Come on!
[bleeping]
[whirring]
-[Curtis] Check this out.
-[bell dings]
[Kelly] A jump rope?
[Curtis]
No, it's not actually a jump rope.
It's a net made
from powerful Stiltskin Thread.
Pull the handle and… pshoom! [chuckles]
[bell dings]
This is the Mist of Hypnos.
One spray can knock
a lesser monster out cold.
[Cassie] Stop trying to impress her.
I am not!
[bell dings]
And this…
is the Booyah Bear.
Yank the ear and throw. Go ahead.
Check it out.
[ticking]
-[ticking speeds up]
-It's-- it's not working.
-Throw it, Kelly!
-Okay!
Booyah!
[Curtis laughs]
Smoke diversion!
-[Liz] Don't waste the weapons, Curtis.
-[Curtis sighs]
Let's go.
-Back to work, SITs.
-Wait, Kelly.
One more thing.
The Cairo chapter found this
in a tomb in Egypt.
We haven't figured out all it can do,
but we know it can break any hex or spell.
Here, take it. It might come in handy.
-[Liz] Kelly?
-Thanks.
If you're insisting on coming,
you can feed the Toadie.
-Wait, wait, wait. I don't know how to--
-[Liz] Open it.
[snarling]
Hm. [belches loudly]
[chatters and growls]
[Kelly] It's getting away!
-No, it's not.
-[pulsing whir]
Did you put a tracker in the trash?
Sure did. And now he'll scramble
back to the Grand Guignol.
Finally, we can locate a Boogeyman.
You wanted it to jump out at me.
You knew it would escape?
We are trying to rescue Jacob, Kelly.
Let's get monster-hunting.
[scoffs]
[slurps]
[burps and sighs]
You've had your warm milk.
Twelve glasses of it.
Now go to sleep!
[scoffs]
Fine, one more.
-[telephone rings]
-[both chatter]
Oh! [sighs]
I said no loud noises!
-[telephone ringing]
-[babbles]
-[screeches]
-[grumbles]
What are you--
-[ringing]
-[spluttering]
-[babbles]
-[groaning]
-[thud]
-Yes.
Hello?
[babbles]
[Grand Guignol] Gnome Street?
What are you doing there?
[babbles]
What? Babysitters? Tracking you?
Ugh. I hate babysitters.
-[babbles]
-You're mumbling again.
No one enunciates these days.
[babbles]
No, don't bring them here,
you smell-feast.
[babbles]
I have a dear friend
right around the corner from you.
Lead them there and inform him…
ah, the babysitter buffet
is officially open.
-[gasps]
-[Toadie chuckling]
[bleeping]
The tracker says the Toadie's close by.
Take the right fork.
♪ Yeah, ooh, la, la ♪
♪ By the pool we're singing "Bailando"… ♪
[Kelly] It's the next driveway
on your right.
♪ Keepin' those blinds closed, yeah… ♪
-[cheering]
-♪ She said I wanna find somebody ♪
♪ By nightfall ♪
♪ Ooh, la, la, could it be you, baby?
I like you ♪
-♪ Oh, watchin' her move… ♪
-Come on, baby! Yes!
-Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-What?
-This is Jesper Huang's party.
-Bunch of sweaty teenagers?
Place must smell like
a smorgasbord to a monster.
Come on.
Toadie's in there somewhere. Let's go.
-Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
-What's wrong?
My crush is right there,
and I'm covered in dirt,
and smell like trash, and I wore
the exact same sweater to school today.
It's just a dude.
Victor Colleti is not "just a dude."
And Deanna's here. Great!
She looks amazing, of course.
[phone alert]
♪ Won't leave me lonely tonight… ♪
Great.
Liz, I can't go in there.
I'm having major anxiety.
What's wrong with you?
I mean, you're more scared of a mean girl
and some dude than a monster?
Fine. Yes, you're right.
Well, that girl you pointed to
looks far from amazing.
I mean, she's wearing a cat costume.
Since the dawn of time,
every basic girl
who has thought that she's hot
-has worn a cat costume.
-♪ I was lost in the rhythm… ♪
[sighs] And the guy, sure,
he's eye candy. I get it.
But that is not
what is important right now.
What we're doing is important.
You're obviously smart. Act like it.
Now move.
♪ Kiss me like your ex is in the room ♪
♪ Don't you be afraid of somethin' new ♪
♪ If you play it right
You can be that someone ♪
♪ Yeah, that someone
Who won't leave me lonely tonight… ♪
[bleep]
[Jesper] Oh, no way!
-Monster Girl's here!
-[girl] Hey!
[Jesper] Everyone, Monster Girl's here!
-[girl] Monster Girl!
-[Jesper] Now it's a Halloween party!
That's seriously your nickname?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. It's-- it's the worst.
I think it's pretty cool.
♪ Kiss me like your ex is in the room… ♪
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Oh! Oh, my!
-Sorry.
-Victor!
Is that your-- is that--
is that your costume?
Yeah, I-- I went as myself. Went meta.
Tried something different.
This way, Ferguson.
-[Kelly] I have to-- um…
-Now!
Thanks for the drink.
♪ Lost in the rhythm… ♪
[Kelly] That was him.
He talked to me!
Don't be that girl. Come on, focus.
Toadie's down here somewhere.
[squeaking]
-[clattering]
-[yelps]
-Be cool, Kelly.
-[whirring]
-I am cool.
-[whirring continues]
Super cool.
[light bulb pinging]
-[clattering]
-[deep groaning sound]
-Liz, I'm not cool.
-Just take the net. Sh!
Ready?
One, two--
-Are we going on three, or after three?
-Three!
[squeaks]
[hissing]
[growling]
-[roars]
-[Kelly yelps]
-What was that?
-[hissing]
-It's a trap. Shadow Monster.
-[banging]
It lives in the dark. We'll be fine
as long as the light stays on.
-[yells]
-[Kelly gasps]
-[burbling]
-[electricity crackling]
[chattering]
[squeals]
[all groan]
Don't worry, 'cause Jesper Huang…
-[dance music plays]
-…is always prepared!
-[cheering and whistling]
-[Jesper] Yeah!
[chittering]
I'll get the Toadie. You handle that.
What? Me?
Check the guide. Strengths, weaknesses,
how to defeat them, it's all in there.
Search "S" for Shadow Monster!
[hissing]
-[screeching]
-[Kelly screams]
Ah. Shadow Monster. Hates bright light.
[screeching]
[screeching and wailing]
Hey, is everything okay down here?
Oh, Victor.
Hi. Hey. Um…
-[screeches]
-Uh, yeah, everything's--
Everything's fine down here. Yeah.
-[Kelly] No, no, no!
-[hissing]
Don't come down here. Um, is there punch?
Let's get some punch. I'm thirsty.
-Are you thirsty?
-Am I?
-[Kelly] Come on. Let's go.
-[hissing]
[pop music playing]
You brought your homework to the party?
Catching up with, uh… with-- with bio.
You know, catching up, and extra credit.
Not that extra credit makes you a nerd--
Not that you're a nerd if you do extra--
My-- What?
[Victor] Uh… um…
Uh, yeah.
Found you!
Oh. You're here, too. How anti-fabulous.
-You know this is a costume party, right?
-She came as herself. Very meta.
[Deanna scoffs]
Riiiight.
Yourself.
Do you like dancing?
'Cause you're gonna love it
when you're dancing with me.
♪ Like I wrote a song-ong-ong ♪
Uh-oh.
-Kelly, where are you going?
-Finally. I thought she'd never leave.
[screeching]
[creaking]
[screams]
Victor. Oh, my gosh, you scared me.
[exhales]
-[chuckles] Sorry, I-- Sorry--
-Oh, I--
Sorry. Sorry. Um… Okay.
Um, I was gonna ask you,
when we were at the-- at the table…
-Yeah?
-[screeching]
-Why aren't you wearing your costume?
-Oh! Um…
-Oh…
-I, uh…
-What are you doing?
-Um, I'm sorry.
-Um, let me give you that.
-Um--
-Okay…
-And I will meet you in one second.
-One second. Please. Um…
-[screeching]
-Okay.
[Kelly] Stay back!
[Victor] Uh, okay.
Why? For how long?
-Oh, come on!
-[Victor] Hey, do you want me to come out?
[Kelly] Not yet! Not yet!
[screeching]
[bleeping and whirring]
Hey, everyone! Take a picture of this!
[all gasp]
Oh! Do not try that at home, kids.
[Deanna] That's entertainment.
Thanks for the freak show.
Hey, make fun of her one more time.
Go on. I dare you.
♪ Watch me go boom now ♪
♪ Watch me go boom ♪
[lullaby playing]
[toy rattling]
[Jacob] Hey! I'm still awake over here.
[sighs]
This is getting ridiculous.
I need something more powerful
to get this wretched boy to sleep.
-[gibbers]
-[Grand Guignol] What, what, what? No!
-And keep him alive, you imbecile.
-[babbles]
-[grumbles]
-[Grand Guignol sighs]
What are you looking at?
Wait. Hah! That's it.
Of course! What a brilliant idea.
You, watch the boy.
-[grunts]
-Hi. [chuckles nervously]
[grunts]
[Kelly] You almost caught the Toadie?
Little creep slobbered all over my hands.
-Eww. What is this?
-Don't know.
-[Kelly] Ugh.
-[Liz] Found it in his pouch.
[bleeping]
-[Kelly] I wonder where it's from.
-[fireworks exploding]
[phone vibrating]
It's my mom.
[vibrating continues]
Hi, Mom. Chh-- chhkk--
Sorry, you can't see me. I'm at-- Chh--
Camera's being all-- chh-- weird.
Where are you?
Chhh-- Uh, Ms. Zellman's.
Then why am I looking
at pictures of you
diving off a balcony on Instagram?
-She knows!
-You're at that party, aren't you?
Kelly Mary Anne Ferguson--
Kelly, please tell me
-that you didn't abandon--
-It's FaceTime.
Please tell me that you didn't abandon
Mrs. Zellman's child to go to a party!
-[Kelly] Of course I didn't!
-[gasps] Her voice went high.
She's lying! She-- Do Track My Kids.
Do-- do Track My Kids.
Berna, we're gonna need
some help around here.
On it. What's her mom's e-mail?
-[Liz] Need your mom's e-mail.
-alexaferguson39@gmail.com.
It's the green one. In the next page.
-Peter, it's the green one. Next page.
-Shh!
-[whispers] Mrs. Zellman will hear you.
-[laughs] Oh! Hi.
It's that one right there.
[bleeping]
-Do the app. Do the app.
-Okay.
-[chuckles]
-[bleep]
[chimes]
Oh, Um…
Well, you are at the Zellmans'.
Yeah, Mom. I-- Uh, yeah, I told you.
[Kelly] Okay. Gotta go. Bye!
[whirring]
[Liz] Ugh.
He took his tracker out?
That's it. Toadie's gone.
Game over. [sighs]
There has gotta be something
we're not thinking of.
Berna, any nightmare pings?
-Negative, Liz.
-[Kelly] Okay. That means…
That means Jacob's still awake,
which means…
the Grand Guignol can't get him to sleep.
So how does a Boogeyman
get a kid like Jacob to go to sleep?
-Curtis?
-Yeah, let me see what's local.
We have the Grit of the Sandman,
Somnolent Lotus Petal, or…
Oh! Uh, uh… Cat's Eye Amulet.
Cat's Eye Amulet?
-Uh--
-[Liz] Where can we find that?
Liz, you're not gonna like this.
It's at Peggy Drood's.
-The Cat Lady.
-[sighs]
-Rock and roll.
-♪ Like a boss… ♪
-Curtis, any luck with the Angel Fire?
-Getting the ingredients now, boss.
-♪ Like a boss… ♪
-[bleeping]
-♪ Like a boss… ♪
[in Spanish]
The petrified scales of a Kaluga Sturgeon?
Mm. That might be
a little hard this time of year.
[in Hindi] I might be able to find
some ground-up Mastodon tooth.
[in English] Possibly.
But I'm not doing the grinding.
[man on phone, in Spanish]
Chupacabra venom? In October?
You're crazy!
♪ In my lockdown ♪
♪ Next night, get the crown… ♪
[voices overlapping]
-[woman] Moshi moshi.
-Hey. Hi. Yes. Um…
I was really hoping
you had some Icarus Wing.
[in Japanese] An Icarus wing?
Are you serious?
[Curtis, in English]
Please tell me that you do.
[in Japanese] I'll see what I can do.
[Curtis, in English] Thank you.
♪ Like a boss… ♪
-Yes!
-♪ B-O-S-S, boss ♪
♪ B-O-S-S, boss ♪
♪ B-O-S-S, boss, B-O-S-S, boss ♪
Let's get to work.
[Kelly] So, what do I need
to know about this Cat Lady?
[Liz] She's an ex silent movie star
turned class five witch.
Last year, she and the Grand Guignol
teamed up
and almost destroyed
the whole babysitter chapter in Nepal.
And she once fed
an entire Girl Scout troop to her cats.
Here's the thing.
I… I'm kind of allergic to cats.
[Kelly] You're what?
[Liz] It's fine. It's the only way
we're gonna get back Kevin.
[Kelly] You mean Jacob. Who's Kevin?
-Never mind.
-Liz.
[cat yowls]
Tell me.
He's my brother.
The Grand Guignol took your brother?
I was six, Kevin was five.
It was midnight.
There was a scratch at the window.
I thought it was
a tree branch or the wind.
I jumped out of bed,
drew back the curtains…
and that's when I saw him.
He sang us a song,
and I fell under a spell.
When I came to, Kevin was gone.
I never saw my brother again.
I've been looking for him my whole life.
I mean, that's the reason
I became a babysitter.
Liz, I…
-I'm so sorry.
-Well, don't be.
-It-- it wasn't your fault.
-No one believes that.
Not even me.
-[cat yowls]
-[scoffs]
You have no idea what it's like.
To feel helpless? Out of control?
Like nobody believes you
but there's nothing you can do?
He came for me when I was a little kid,
and no one even listened.
But you know what changed things?
What?
Tonight.
You.
You did.
Okay.
Then let's do this.
We get in.
You distract Peggy.
I spray her. We grab the amulet. We split.
-Easy-peasy.
-[chuckles]
-[cat yowls]
-Let's just get this over with.
[cat wailing]
[Kelly] Wait.
[Kelly] So, how many cats does she have?
Oh…
Just a few.
Here and there.
-[laughs]
-[jazz music plays]
♪ Proceed with caution ♪
-♪ You kiss too nicely… ♪
-What can I do for you ladies?
-Looking for a room?
-♪ You might entice me… ♪
-[laughs]
-♪ Travel at your own risk… ♪
-[sneezes]
-[Peggy] Would you look at this?
Is that Liz Lerue?
[Liz] How do you know who I am?
Honey, please.
Monsters know Monster Hunters.
-Gotta know your enemies, right?
-[Liz coughing]
-[coughing]
-Liz. Liz, Liz!
-Are you okay?
-[Peggy] Ohh…
Not too great under pressure now,
are you, Liz?
-Where are the cats?
-I don't know.
-[Peggy] After all…
-Sit down.
…you couldn't save
your brother from the Boogeyman.
[coughs and gasps]
Poor little Kevin.
-[Kelly] You're gonna be okay.
-[Liz] Go spray her.
Try not to look at the amulet.
I'm glad you girls stopped by.
I love visitors.
Well, well, well. What do we have here?
[Peggy] Mercy me. The Grand Guignol.
What brings you to my neck of the woods?
[Grand Guignol] Your amulet.
You're a monster! [coughs]
And the sky is blue.
Tell me, do you have
any more brilliant observations,
-sister of the year?
-Where is he?
-Leave her alone!
-[Liz coughing]
Who do we have here?
[scoffs] Scared little Kelly Ferguson.
Long time no see.
I bet you didn't think you'd see me again.
♪ In the clutches of sleep ♪
♪ Listen, you'll do as you're told ♪
[Grand Guignol whispers] Now…
[thunder crashes]
[Grand Guignol] Come, child.
[high-pitched whir]
[groans]
[thunder rumbles]
[Grand Guignol]
Did you really think you'd killed me?
That takes Angel Fire to the heart,
and I don't suppose you brought any.
-Whatever is the matter?
-Cat's got her tongue.
[scoffs] Huh.
Huh.
-Now, Peggy, if you please--
-If I give you this…
[gasps]
…that makes up for Cat-mandu
and the cat-astrophe I caused there?
Absolutely, yes. And, as a bonus,
I'll let you keep… her.
Oh.
Very well.
This one, however, is mine.
-No!
-[crackles]
[grunts]
[laughs]
[Peggy] And now…
it's dinner time, my beauties.
[cats meowing]
Feast!
[cats yowling]
[gasping]
[yowling and hissing]
[loud yowling]
[meowing]
[purring]
[meowing continues]
Go! Go, go, go!
[meowing]
[water dripping]
[Kelly] Berna? Curtis? Cassie?
Kelly! You're alive?
The Grand Guignol, he… he took Liz.
I couldn't get her back.
I lost them. I--
-I lost.
-Listen, Kelly.
-Just head back to HQ. I've got a plan.
-But what if Ms. Zellman comes home early?
Don't worry. I already hacked into
Ms. Zellman's phone and I'm tracking her.
[sighs] Liz found this
on the Toadie at the party.
Check it out.
[phone chimes]
Toadies love sparkly things, right?
Well, maybe this piece of glass
came from wherever he has Jacob?
I'll run it through the database.
[bleeping]
[whirring]
I got a match on the glass.
It's from the Qeeqong lighthouse.
Yeah, but the Qeeqong Lighthouse
is condemned.
A perfect place for a Boogeyman to hide.
You're not going?
-Yeah.
-But, Kelly…
What is that thing?
This is the coup de grâce, my frenemy.
Tonight's been fun, but… nighty-night.
[whooshing]
No!
[Grand Guignol] Sleep tight.
Yes, yes!
Ah, yes!
-[whispering and growling]
-[whimpers]
-Yes.
-[Jacob whimpers]
[rustling and skittering]
Yes, my beauties.
[whooshing]
[crackling]
[motorcycle pulls up]
[rattling]
[creaking]
[wind whistling]
Berna, do you copy?
I'm here, Kelly.
I made it to the lighthouse.
In case I get lost,
my sweater's tied to the fence.
Kelly, you shouldn't be there.
-It's dangerous.
-I have to do something.
[creaking]
[wind gusting]
[echoing boy's voice] Liz!
-Hey, Liz!
-Kevin? Kevin?
Liz!
I miss you.
Kev! Where are you?
-Kev!
-Liz!
I'm right here.
Boo! [laughs]
Oh, you should see your face.
Aah!
-[sings with choir] ♪ Do as you're told ♪
-No. No.
♪ Darling girl, let the monster inside ♪
No, no, no, no.
-♪ Take control, it's so right ♪
-No. Stop. Stop.
♪ Everything will be fine ♪
♪ Long as you do as you're ♪
♪ Told ♪
-Aah.
-[clang]
Want to know a secret?
I sent your brother
to a dark, spidery place, far, far away.
[laughing]
Okay. Angel Fire. Let's cook!
Time for some dragon skins. Right.
And now, some kestrel eggs. Okay.
[wheezing]
I may need some paper towel.
[creaking]
[metal groaning]
[screams]
[yelling]
[low growling]
[yelps]
[whimpers]
[Jacob] Mommy!
And now, first place
for best costume goes to…
Jacob.
Ms. Zellman!
-[applause]
-[Ms. Zellman] Something's wrong. Jacob.
[bleeping]
Red alert, SITs.
Ms. Zellman's on the move!
[screams]
[gasps]
[Jacob] No. No!
[whimpers]
Jacob.
[snarling]
[Grand Guignol] Toadies, take care of her.
[Toadie chuckles]
[Berna] Kelly? Are you there?
Kelly?
I'm not getting anything.
We need to get
to the lighthouse right now.
But we don't have Angel Fire yet.
Or do we?
♪ Aaah ♪
Angel Fire! I hath made--
-Hey! Do not drop that!
-I'm here.
[alarm blares]
[crackling]
-What the--
-[system powers down]
I lost track of Ms. Zellman!
[Cassie] Why'd we lose power?
-[electricity crackling]
-[hissing]
That's why.
[snarling]
At least it's afraid of light.
[screeches]
But…
all the doors have electronic locks.
We're locked in?
-No, no, no, no, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
-[grumbling]
-Look what I've got.
-[chattering]
Look.
-Sparkly!
You love sparkly.
[chattering]
[scoffs]
[grumbles]
[laughs]
Aw, man.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I've got something even better.
[babbling]
[Kelly] And it's right…
-here!
-[screeches]
[yelling]
[growls]
[roaring]
Hm?
[yelps]
[gibbering]
-[clang]
-[grunting]
-[screams]
-[splash]
Booyah!
You guys stay here
and contain that monster.
-[hissing]
-I'll bring the Angel Fire to Kelly.
-No one's ever contained a Shadow Monster!
-If anyone can do it, it's you, Cass.
-That's your only way out.
-[Berna] I got this.
[Cassie] The light
from this glowfish will hold it back.
Just go!
[monster hissing]
Ah! Liz, you're alive!
-Jacob's this way. Come with me.
-Wait. I thought he was in there.
-This way, Kelly.
-Where are we going?
-Come on, Kelly.
[gasps]
Oh, no. He hypnotized you.
[both grunt]
I don't wanna hurt you.
But I will. [grunts]
[yelps] Ow, ow ow!
[Kelly] Please don't do this!
Remember your brother. Think about Kevin!
I know you miss him, okay? I know that.
But you're not alone.
You and I,
we can beat this together! Just--
[grunts]
Liz!
Liz! Liz!
-Liz!
-[snorts]
Are you okay?
What happened?
-How do I know it's really you?
-'Cause I'm gonna kick your butt
-if you don't help me up.
-Yeah, it's you.
Ow! Ow, ow.
[Toadie chattering]
-You tried to kill me, you know.
-Shhh!
We have to be quiet, or he'll hear us.
[Toadie yelling]
-[Curtis] We're gonna die.
-[Cassie] Not if I hot-wire the circuit.
-[Shadow Monster hissing]
-[Cassie] How much time do I have?
[whispers] I have no idea where he went.
[Cassie] Okay. Plan B.
Work with what you got.
I just need
to hook this up to these batteries--
-And then what? How do we catch a shadow?
-[hissing]
The Einstein Dimension Box!
-[gasps] That'll contain it.
-[Cassie] But how do we get it in there?
If we move together,
we can rope him into it!
-[whispers] Okay.
-Please get these lights working.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please…
-[laughs]
-Yes! You did it!
Okay. Be brave.
[hissing and screeching]
-[Cassie] It's coming straight for us.
-I'll go get the box.
-[Curtis] Okay. You need to come with me.
-Okay.
[snarling and screeching]
-[Cassie] Hurry up! Hurry up!
-[Curtis] I-- I'm going as fast as I can!
-[gasps]
-[Cassie] Here it comes! Get ready!
[roaring and growling]
[screeching]
[Curtis] Come on. We can do this.
[squealing and roaring]
You're gonna have to close the lid,
but whatever you do,
don't let him touch your hand.
Why? What happens
if he touches my hand, Cassie?
-What happens if he touches my hand?
-Just do it!
Yeah!
That is what happens when you break
into HQ and mess with my friends.
We caught it! No one's ever caught
a Shadow Monster before.
Yeah, we're legends!
[hissing]
-[rattling]
-Uh…
[hissing]
[purring]
It's actually kinda cute. Can we keep him?
[screeches]
I don't wanna keep him. I don't wanna…
[burbling]
♪ Dah! Dah! ♪
[humming happily]
[laughs]
[Grand Guignol] Oh, Liz!
Where are you, darling?
I need you
to deliver a message to my sister.
He still thinks you're under his spell.
[Grand Guignol] Have you met my sister,
Serena, The Spider Queen?
She thinks she's so cool and so evil,
just because
she's the Queen of the Boogeypeople
and I'm the baby brother. [scoffs]
Just a stupid little dreamer, am I, sis?
Just you wait.
Little brother will be in charge,
with my army of nightmares
waiting to rip humanity to shreds!
Hah!
How long have you been standing there?
Ah, whatever.
Did you lock your little friend up?
-Yes, Grand Guignol.
-[Grand Guignol] Marvelous.
We'll make
a fine monster-sitter out of you yet, Liz.
After tonight,
we'll be monstrously busy. Get it?
Grand Guignol,
there's a problem with the back tank.
If one of the Toadies has fallen in again,
I'm leaving them there. Come!
Aah! Yes, yes, yes!
[sighs] Good boy, Jacob. Good boy!
Now…
Aah!
What are you talking about?
It's working perfectly.
-My mistake, Grand Guignol.
-Yes, it was, you stupid child.
[sniffs]
[sighs]
Come down here, Kelly.
The stench of your fear gave you away.
Did you really think
you could sneak up on me?
Sneak up on the Boogeyman?
[chuckles] I invented the sneak.
By the Order of the Babysitters,
I demand you give us Jacob.
By the Order of the Boogeyman,
you're a blithering idiot.
You're no hero.
You're just a weak, small,
pathetic, insignificant little girl.
-[Liz] Give him back!
-[Kelly] No!
Oh! Nice try.
Berna, 70 degrees, 38 feet per second.
Just lob it!
Yeah. Nice arm, loser.
Who do you think you're dealing with?
I'm not the Tooth Fairy.
I'm the Grand Guignol.
Master of Menace, Sultan of Suffering,
King of the Monsters.
And you're babysitters.
I almost feel sorry for you.
-[monsters screeching]
-Toadies. Open the chambers.
Release our new friends upon the world!
Now!
Jimmy!
[groaning and gasping]
-[grunts]
-[Grand Guignol] Roscoe!
[yells]
-Toadies?
-[splash]
Oh, for-- [sighs]
We've rehearsed this for six months!
-[slurping]
-[Grand Guignol] Snaggle!
[panting]
[snuffling]
[Kelly] Try this.
-[grunting]
-[Grand Guignol] Come here.
[opera singer singing in German]
-[farting]
-[groans]
[Grand Guignol] No, not-- [groans]
-Please, not Snaggle.
-[dramatic aria continues]
[sings]
[gasps]
[wails]
[opera singer hits high note]
[groaning]
[Grand Guignol] Ugh! Never mind.
Bare your teeth, my beautiful nightmares.
Finally, our time has come.
Tonight is our night.
[monsters roaring]
Girls, what are you--
Ugh.
[thumping]
[whispering]
[thumping and growling]
[Grand Guignol] Playtime is over.
Babysitters.
[scoffs] You didn't really think you had
a chance to defeat me, did you?
Let's do this.
[yells]
It's the Monster Punch.
[coughing]
Is that the best you've got? [laughs]
Barely scratched me.
That's your weakness, isn't it?
Your sad, small, cruel,
insignificant little heart.
[Grand Guignol laughs] A heart?
[laughing]
[coughing and wheezing]
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
You're a loser, Kelly!
Call me Monster Girl.
[gasps]
Where-- where is he?
It's okay, Jacob.
He's gone. You're safe! Okay?
-No! No!
-Hey, what's wrong?
Wait. Why are the nightmares still here?
It's okay.
You don't need to be afraid anymore.
Hey, listen.
Tell 'em to take a hike, kid.
[whimpers]
[Jacob] I'm not scared of you.
-Now, go away.
-[growling]
You're stronger than they are.
You've got this.
-I said go away!
-[monsters cackling]
I'm not scared of you anymore.
[yells] Now, go away!
[lights clanking]
Can we go home now?
Your mom!
[Ms. Zellman] Kelly,
this is the sixth message I've left you.
Call me back right now!
[tires squeal]
♪ They'll bury my bones ♪
♪ You got me going on the brink ♪
It's okay, Kelly.
You don't have to check under the bed.
I think I'll have good dreams from now on.
I think you will too, bud.
[car approaching]
[brakes squeal]
-[car door opens and closes]
-Look…
you're not gonna tell your mom
what happened tonight, right?
That depends.
-[front door opens]
-Will you babysit me again?
[chuckles] Definitely.
[Ms. Zellman] Jacob! Jacob!
Are you okay? Where are you?
-Is everything okay? He--
-Shhh!
Oh!
He's okay, you see?
Oh, I-- [laughs]
I can't believe you got him
to fall asleep. You're a lifesaver.
Listen, if you're not busy
tomorrow night…
I'll be here.
Thank you.
♪ Whatchugot? ♪
-♪ Whatchugot?
-♪ Whatchugot? ♪
♪ Keep it goin' till I tell you to stop ♪
♪ Till I tell you to stop ♪
♪ I wanna love practitioner ♪
♪ A fun commissioner ♪
♪ I'm gonna finish it, let's have a ball ♪
♪ So whatchugot? ♪
-Hey…
-You're welcome.
I wasn't gonna say that, but…
Seeing as you displayed courage
and brains in the face of danger,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah…
I'm gonna talk to Mama Vee,
and I'm gonna tell her
you should at least
be allowed to apply to the Order.
-[gasps] For real?
-Don't get all excited.
You still have to pass Heck Week.
And you may have upset
the monster underworld tonight.
Serena the Spider Queen
is one of the Grand Guignol's sisters.
She's not gonna like this.
-What's a babysitter--
-In training.
…in training for?
And, Liz? We're gonna get Kevin back, too.
[Liz] Hey.
Better study up.
"Serena von Kessel,
AKA Serena Salazar, AKA the Spider Queen.
Half spider, half-human.
Likes blood of all kinds.
The younger the better."
[phone playing music]
♪ Face, face, hah, hah ♪
♪ You can tell my face, face ♪
♪ Ha-na, oh, na-na-na ♪
-♪ You can tell my face, face… ♪
-Oh, no.
♪ Hah, hah ♪
♪ Won't put you in my safe space ♪
♪ Ha-na, oh, na-na-na ♪
♪ You can tell my-- ♪
Hey, Kelly.
-Victor. Hi.
-Hey.
Uh, sorry I'm calling so late.
I was wondering if you wanted
to maybe go to the movies tomorrow night?
Aaah! [squeaks]
Okay. [inhales]
I'd like to, but…
I'm babysitting tomorrow night.
[chuckles] Okay. Let's, uh…
Let's talk at school on Monday.
-Bye.
-Later.
[sighs]
"The most beautiful
and charming of all seven Boogies.
Great fashion sense.
Her fangs eject
a deadly venom that can bewitch,
paralyze, or kill her prey,
depending on her mood.
Weaknesses.
Giant ego. Flattery. Jewelry.
-She's as fast as she is lethal."
-♪ I'm not the girl who cried wolf ♪
♪ I'm not the girl who cried wolf ♪
♪ Someday you'll notice ♪
♪ You're stuck where you are ♪
♪ Mmm, someday you'll look up ♪
♪ While I dance on the stars ♪
♪ I dream while you sleep in your bed
Counting sheep every night ♪
♪ You're treating me like I'm a liar
I'm losing my mind ♪
♪ I'm not the girl who cried ♪
♪ Aah, aah ♪
♪ Aah, aah-aah-aah-aah ♪
♪ Aah ♪
♪ I'm not the girl who cried wolf ♪
♪ Aah, I'm not the girl who cried wolf ♪
♪ Aah, aah ♪
-♪ Aah, aah ♪
-♪ I'm not the girl who cried wolf ♪
♪ Aah-aah-aah ♪
♪ Aah, aah ♪
♪ Aah, aah-aah-aah-aah ♪
♪ Tunin' out
And turning off the red light ♪
♪ I've given up already for tonight ♪
♪ So shut your eyes
And kiss me one last time ♪
♪ Let's say the goodbye
That I have in mind ♪
♪ Earnin' on my own, own, own ♪
♪ Like I wrote a song-ong-ong ♪
♪ Inside, I'm lost, anyway ♪
♪ Outside, I'm fine, honestly ♪
♪ Next time won't laugh, now I see ♪
♪ Just being me, yeah ♪
♪ Never felt so good to be alone ♪
♪ 'Cause crying in my skin
Is all I've known ♪
♪ Made myself so sick and tired ♪
♪ My hand inside the fire ♪
♪ Oh, I'm sorry, baby ♪
♪ I'm still feelin' strange, yeah ♪
♪ Earnin' on my own, own, own ♪
♪ Like I wrote a song-ong-ong ♪
♪ Inside, I'm lost, anyway ♪
♪ Own, own, own ♪
-♪ Inside, I'm lost, anyway
-♪ Earnin' on my ♪
-♪ Own, own, own
-♪ Outside, I'm fine, honestly ♪
-♪ Next time won't laugh, now I see
-♪ Like I wrote ♪
-♪ A song-ong-ong
-♪ Just being me, yeah ♪
-♪ Inside, I'm lost, anyway
-♪ Earnin' on my ♪
-♪ Own, own, own
-♪ Outside, I'm fine, honestly ♪
-♪ Next time won't laugh, now I see
-♪ Like I wrote ♪
-♪ A song-ong-ong
-♪ Just being me, yeah ♪
-♪ Inside, I'm lost, anyway
-♪ Earnin' on my ♪
-♪ Own, own, own
-♪ Outside, I'm fine, honestly ♪
-♪ Next time won't laugh, now I see
-♪ Like I wrote ♪
-♪ A song-ong-ong
-♪ Just being me, yeah ♪
♪ Do as you're told ♪
♪ What a gift, what a sight to behold ♪
♪ For the darkest of dreams ♪
♪ You'll surrender to sleep ♪
♪ Do as you're told ♪
♪ As the fire surrenders to cold ♪
♪ Heavy eyes sink deep ♪
♪ And surrender to me ♪
♪ Oh, yes, you'll do as you're told ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Do as you're told ♪
♪ Oh, my dear, let the monster inside ♪
♪ Take control, it's all right ♪
♪ Leave the whole world behind ♪
♪ Absence of light ♪
♪ Bringing all of your fears to life ♪
♪ You've got nowhere to hide ♪
♪ Oh, my dear, you'll be fine ♪
♪ Long as you do as you're told ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[choir singing]