'Why?'
'It wasn't over for me!'
'I waited for you
for seven years..'
'...and now it's too late.'
'I wrote you 365 letters.'
I wrote you
every single day for a year.
You..
...you wrote me?
Yes!
I wrote you every single day.
You..
It wasn't over for me.
It still isn't over.
Yes! Jon Ham, you
are so right!
It is the rain scene
from "The Notebook."
Aw, well, thank you.
I am a pretty good actress
but you all
are an excellent audience.
You guys are so sweet.
You're right, it would be
amazing to get to perform
in front of a bigger audience
but...I just don't think
that's in the cards for me yet,
boys and girls.
Stop it.
You're going to make me blush.
You know, it would be amazing
to be a real actress
like in Hollywood, but..
...I just gotta make it
there somehow.
♪ Been in a daydream
all my life ♪
♪ This place is like a cage ♪
♪ I'm feeling stuck
and don't know why ♪
♪ They tell me
where's your common sense? ♪
♪ Girl you got a big blue sky ♪
♪ And a picket fence ♪
♪ But I need something more ♪
♪ To step outside ♪
♪ A country home ♪
♪ To find my way ♪
♪ And now's the time ♪
♪ I know that
I have the courage ♪
♪ To spread my wings and fly ♪
♪ Somehow ♪
♪ Some way ♪
♪ I feel inside ♪
♪ My day is waiting for me ♪
♪ I'm gonna write my own story ♪
♪ My own story ♪
♪ One day they'll
shower me with praise ♪
♪ I'll have a real hard time ♪
♪ To keep the handsome
guys away ♪
♪ Followed by my adoring fans ♪
♪ I got the whole wide world
in the palm of my hands ♪
♪ And I'll be someone great ♪
♪ They'll know my name ♪
♪ And I'll have found
my purpose ♪
♪ Sometimes it seems ♪
♪ Against the odds ♪
♪ My dreams
are waiting for me ♪
♪ I'm gonna write my own story ♪
♪ My own story ♪♪
'Finley!'
Finley!
What is she doing?
She's pretending
to be a Disney princess.
- I mean, that is so sad.
- Yeah.
Oh, but I love
that one move with the arms.
I'm hungry!
Make me some food.
- Kale, you're in my shot.
- Whatever.
What did I tell you
about getting in my shot?
'Sorry.'
♪ You mad ♪
♪ You mad huh? ♪
♪ You mad you mad huh? ♪
Okay.
♪ Oh you mad? ♪
♪ Yeah you mad huh? ♪
Okay, it's ready.
Oh, my God!
♪ Don't try it ♪♪
- You just ruined my TikTok!
- Wow.
Oh, I...I'm so sorry, Saffron,
I didn't, I didn't know, I..
- It was really good.
- Oh, really good.
- Kale.
Here you go.
Oh.
What is this? Pork?
No, it's salmon.
Is there pork in it?
No. No, there's no
pork in salmon.
It's fish.
You-you said that
you wanted fish.
I-I said I wanted fish
fingers. Fish fingers.
These are not fish fingers.
Oh, my God, Kale!
Quit saying "Fish fingers."
Fish fingers.
Wait. What?
- What?
- No way!
I mean, there's no freaking..
What?
Oh, my God, stop. What?
- Guess what's coming to town?
- What?
- Guess who is coming to town?
- Who?
I'm gonna do it, I'm gonna do
it, I'm going to punch you
in the neck if you don't
spit it out, Saffron.
"The Hollywood film,
"Billy the Kid - The Musical"
has arrived in Dreary, Idaho."
That's where we live.
Okay.
"Cameras begin rolling tomorrow
as does a town-wide audition."
This is all about revenue.
Do you know how much money this
could bring in to this little--
Shut up, Kale!
Nobody cares about revenue.
You shut up, Saffron!
It's all about revenue.
Can you let her finish?
- Rude.
- Thank you, Finley.
You're welcome.
- Okay. Yeah, okay.
- Go on.
Blah, blah "Production value."
Okay, here, "The cast is led
by up-and-coming dreamy actor
Jackson Stone."
Jackson Stone.
"As you know,
Jackson was discovered
on a ranch in a town
not unlike Dreary."
Okay, like, they're talking
about farms. Nobody cares.
"The auditions will be held
at noon tomorrow at the Mill.
Come prepared
to sing, dance.."
Obviously and.. Wow!
- Mom..
- Oh!
- Saffron..
- I'm going to that audition.
- Oh, yes, you are.
- Oh, I am!
- I think I'm going to go, too.
- Oh, you're not an actor.
Well, that's fine.
Neither are you.
I'm obviously not going
to audition, Saffron.
I am gonna to be
Jackson Stone's manager.
You're not a manager.
Oh, really?
Then how would you explain
Wanda's Waffle and Sushi House
blowing it up on the 'Gram?
- That was all me.
- They have, like, 37 followers.
Oh, that's 35 more than you do.
Um..
Can I go, too?
Huh?
I want to audition.
Mom.
Oh, no. No.
You-you can't go
to the audition.
You have far too many things
to do here around the house.
Please, can't they
help out too? I..
Is it their fault
that your father
had to own a farm
with horses and pigs
that need to be milked--
No, no, mom, uh, pigs don't
need to be milked.
Okay, I will wake up
really early tomorrow
and I will do my chores and if
they are not finished in time
I won't go, I promise.
Fine...fine.
- Really?
- I'll leave you a list.
- Okay, thank you.
- Okay.
Oh, and you will also
need to take
that annoying little pig
to the butcher.
Mm-hmm, yes, pork chops.
Ba-boom! And see with that spin,
if we can get that spin..
With the, with the tassels
coming up, that's really nice.
'Hit me now. Hit me.'
'Yes! That's it!
That's it.'
'The studio is gonna love that.'
This is looking like money. This
is looking like money all day.
Mm!
Oh, Valerian! I...thought that
everyone was already asleep.
We were. What are
you doing in here?
I just, um..
You see, it's really
cold tonight
so I thought that maybe I could
sleep on the couch, you know
if that's okay.
No, Finley, that's not okay.
This isn't a flop house.
You have the largest
bedroom of us all.
It's not really a bedroom.
'Is that not enough for you?'
You have to kick us
out of our living room, too?
It's just...really
cold tonight, that's all.
Oh..
Well, take a blanket.
Surprise, surprise.
Guess who said no.
Here, it's for you tonight.
You've got to be cold, too.
I know.
I know you told me
she'd say no, I just..
...thought maybe..
Okay.
Man!
Okay..
Cold.
Goodnight, boys.
Goodnight, Jon Ham.
Goodnight, Dad.
Oh, God.
Tsk. Perfect.
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Take your hand now
keep up keep up ♪
What? Be nice!
♪ Take your hand now
keep up keep up ♪
♪ We gotta kick it with me ♪
♪ Take your hand now
keep up keep up ♪
♪ Gotta make some noise ♪
♪ Take your hand now
keep up keep up ♪
♪ We gotta kick it with me ♪♪
Well done.
Come here. Who was such a good
helper today?
You were!
'Finley!'
- Mom?
- Yeah?
Why are you all dressed up?
You're not auditioning.
Oh, well, I was thinking
I might, you know?
I mean, I was kind of
a big deal back in my day.
Your day was,
like, in the '60s
before they had cars
or iPhones.
I was the "It Girl" of 1987.
I was on the cover
of "Glamour Magazine."
No, you weren't.
Back cover.
- Nope.
- Fine.
I was in a print ad
in one of those big magazines.
Oh, the hemorrhoid cream ad?
You wish you had a
hemorrhoid cream ad, Saffron.
At least mom had a job,
unlike someone I know.
Who, you?
- 'Shut up, Saffron.'
- 'No, you shut up, Kale.'
Okay, breakfast is ready.
- Here.
- Oh, smells crispy.
And, um, I finished up
all of my chores
so, I'm going
to the audition.
- Mom?
- Yeah.
Um, you still need to take
that pig to the butcher.
Right, you know,
I don't really think
that we should put him down,
so why don't we just--
'Oh, you don't think so?'
You think we should just
keep hemorrhaging money
for your mangy
little animals, hmm?
- They are her only friends.
- It's tragic.
Like, who's she
talking to? The pig?
We're gonna sell this dump.
- Yes! Thank you!
- Oh, my God.
Yes! We are gonna sell this dump
and get the hell out of here.
- Yes!
- No, you're not.
- Hey, can we just--
- Oh, yes, I am. I am.
I could sell this house.
Kale, how much can I sell
this house for?
Well, obviously, I'd need
like a comparative
market analysis but probably--
You're not selling my house!
- Excuse me?
- Mom?
Look..
Guys, I was..
...I was born in this house.
Ew!
Okay, every good memory
that I have is in this house.
This is my home, so..
Oh, honey.
No, no, no, no, no.
It was your home
but when your father died,
it became my home.
My dad..
...built this home with his
own hands...board by board.
Yes, and when we sell it,
they will tear it apart..
...board by board.
Bored.
'I-I don't know.'
We don't know.
We don't do that.
No, no, no. That's..
Oh, are you and your boyfriend
going on a date?
I'm taking the pig to market.
- Oh, good.
- Yes.
And she'll cry "Wee, wee, wee"
all the way home.
That is so mean.
Thank you, Saffron.
- I think it's funny.
- Okay, bored with that.
- Back to me!
- Okay, show me again.
Oh, don't listen
to them, Jon Ham.
I would never let them
do anything to hurt you.
I'm just going to take you
to go see Jerry the Vet.
What?
No. He's not gonna give
you a shot, I promise.
He's just gonna watch you
for a couple of days
until Valerian
forgets about you
and then I can sneak you
back into the barn.
Okay?
- Oh, hi, Finley!
- Oh, hi, Louise!
- Hi, Jon Ham.
- Say hi.
Have you sold
any houses lately?
Not if I can help it.
I like this town
just the way it is.
Yeah. Us too.
- We'll catch you later.
- Okay, bye now.
Bye, Louise.
Come on.
Here we go!
Come on! It's like a playdate.
You like Jerry.
You do!
Oh!
Dang it, Jerry.
Yee-haw!
Yes! Perfect. Cut.
Thank you.
Okay, that's a cut.
Dancers, take ten.
'That was good, Peter.
Thank you.'
That one was better
than the last one.
Sophia, can we keep that last
leg they're moving like that?
That was awesome.
Thank you, Peter.
Okay..
Jon Ham, I need you
to pay attention.
I need you to be
a very good boy, okay?
'Like, a beat sooner
on that next one.'
- Can you do that?
- 'Well, thank you.'
This is my chance.
'Alright, guys, let's get it
cleared out over here.'
Okay, who's next?
Anyone wanna..
...audition today?
- I'll go.
- Great. Okay.
Hop on up on the stage.
Okay? Trevor!
'Trevor!'
'She's over in the trailer.
Do you need her?'
Okay, Trevor,
we are ready for you.
Oh, hey, oh, I gotta go.
Okay. Talk soon.
Buh-bye.
- Uh, fun.
- Mm-hmm.
'So, uh, who's next here?'
'Okay, first up.'
Uh, okay, sweetheart
'let's see what you got.'
- Sorry.
- 'That's alright.'
'Take your time.
Any time you're ready.'
- 'Quiet down.'
- 'Who's this? Okay, good.'
♪ Well I'm a walking menace ♪
♪ Got fire in my veins
and if you see me coming ♪
♪ Boy you best
step out my way ♪
♪ I'm a well known rambler ♪
♪ Yes I do as I please ♪
She's got a great voice.
Yeah. Not a very
sexy song, though.
♪ You will watch me soaring
with the wind behind my sails ♪
♪ I'm a force of nature ♪
♪ Look upon me and despair ♪
♪ Well there must be
somethin' in the water ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't be stopped ♪
♪ Better get up out of my way ♪
♪ No I can't be stopped ♪
♪ Go on get up
out of my way ♪♪
'Alright!'
She's good, like..
She's great!
She could play Wyatt.
Yeah. That's a
guy's role.
I need saloon girls, right?
What is, what's all that?
Well...why can't a girl
play the role?
'There were great female
gunslingers back in the day.'
Annie Oakley,
Calamity Jane, Mary Fields..
Yeah, I'm just not gonna do
that. I'm not gonna do that.
And I don't know who they are,
so I can't really reference it
but this is what I'm thinking.
I'm not using any of this,
but I love that you're trying.
No! Stay, Jon Ham.
Stay! Come on! Come on!
- No! Jon Ham!
- Whoa!
No!
- Hey! Hey!
- Hey!
Is that a pig?
Jon Ham!
Jon Ham! Jon Ham!
I'm so sorry.
Jon Ham! Right now!
Come here, right now!
Is that... Finley?
Oh, sorry! Excuse me.
Jon Ham! Jon Ham!
Ooh!
Oh!
This is so embarrassing
for her.
It's the best.
Jon Ham.
'Some pretty impressive
wrangling there.'
Yeah. Not too
bad yourself.
Jackson Stone?
Yeah.
Let's, uh, let's
get you out of this mud.
There you go.
Sorry.
Say..
Where'd you learn
to rope like that?
I...I'm usually better.
Somebody get
Jackson out of there, please.
Yeah.
- Jackson?
- Yeah?
- We gotta get you out.
- Excuse me.
- I'm so sorry.
- 'Two seconds.'
I didn't mean to.
- Yeah.
- Is that your pig?
- Yes. Yes, sir. He is.
- Okay, great.
Get off my set
and take your pig with you.
And I don't want to see
your face again, you understand?
- I understand. I'm--
- Okay, good. Get going.
Yeah! Go home, Pig Girl!
Get out of here, Pig Girl!
Yeah, get out, Pig Girl!
- What was that? That was good.
- I don't know what that was.
Hey, it's okay.
- That is so annoying.
- Come on.
She always ruins
everything for me.
We'd better get going,
move on to the next set-up.
I hear you, Derek, all good.
- Jackson!
- Kenny.
You okay? That was, I mean,
that was crazy, right?
You bet. Real wild.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
So, um, you, uh,
you wanna
do you wanna practice
some of the stunts?
I'll tell you what, Kenny,
uh, not right now.
I gotta get back,
alright?
Okay, cool, I just..
Say, you know who that
girl was back there?
I don't know, just some local.
Pork chop, pork loin,
spare ribs, bacon.
Is everybody happy?
Oh, don't take that tone
with me, little Pig Girl.
If you had just done
what I asked
you wouldn't have been
humiliated.
Yeah, now I have to prepare
all over again for my audition.
Did you get any ham?
- Great day.
- Good day.
Well, I mean, you were good.
We have to find
our legs on our end
but this is
how this stuff goes.
You know, it takes
the first week.
Jackson, hi. Wardrobe would like
you to try these on.
Uh, sure, but did they have
this color back then?
- I don't know.
- You don't like this?
- I don't think it plays.
- Yeah, I'm with you.
Thank you. Appreciate that.
Great work today.
- Sorry, man.
- Um..
Quickly, I can have him fired
if he's annoying you.
- No! No, no. I don't wanna--
- Are you sure?
- Excuse me, excuse me, Trevor.
- Yeah?
For the flashback, which one?
- Neither.
- Both.
- Um, so, tomorrow's a big day.
- Yeah.
And I'm thinking
for that scene, um--
Okay, hold on a second, Trevor.
I've got to ask you something.
- Alright.
- Tell me.
Talk to me. I'm here.
That girl today
from the audition.
- The wild, muddy mess.
- Pig Girl?
Don't...please don't
call her that.
No, no, no! I don't call her
that. That's what they call her.
They call her "Pig Girl."
I would never call her that.
Look, listen, um..
Do you think we can find
out who she is?
- You think we should sue her?
- No.
No, I, look, I-I-I just can't
get her out of my head.
Why? You spent, like,
20 seconds with her.
Okay, and it was the first
real 20 seconds I've had
since I started this business.
Aw, come on, man.
You little sucker, come on.
Okay, Trev, look, I-I-I don't
mean it like that. Alright?
What I mean i-is this..
...all of this nonsense
alright, it does,
it doesn't speak to me.
That beautiful girl back there
with the pig, she spoke to me.
Okay, Jackson.
Listen, you want to go frolic
in a pigsty..
...I want that for you.
I think it's important, okay?
But right now we gotta focus.
It's a lot of pressure.
This is a big movie
and we're going to do this
because we're a team, right?
We're going to finish
this movie
and then you and I are gonna
dive into my next movie.
And then, you are going to be
an A-list star
and you can pick
any chick you want.
- Mm.
- Right? You understand?
Tomorrow's a big day.
Let's get some rest.
Boom!
- You're the man.
- You got it, Trev.
'You are the man.'
'Today was
a really bad day, dad.'
They all called me "Pig Girl."
Yeah.
This was my only chance.
It's never
gonna happen, is it?
And you!
You owe me big-time, Jon Ham.
You do.
You're lucky they didn't
ban us from auditioning
after your little stunt. Ow!
You have any idea what a day
like that can cost production?
100k, easy.
Okay, well, they don't even
know that we're related, Kale.
Okay, let's keep it that way.
- Stop!
- Hold still.
If anyone finds out
you're Pig Girl
you'll ruin it for all of us.
Wow.
Is that what you're wearing?
I don't take fashion advice
from people who are
covered in pig poop.
- Burn.
- You like that?
Okay, don't wait up for us.
I'm sure we'll be invited
to the after-party.
Oh, there's no after-party.
There's always an after-party.
That's after you
finish the job.
- 'Then, there's a pre-party.'
- 'There-there's no party.'
I don't know what to say.
There's something about it
that I just--
- I'll be back.
- This is pretty cool.
No, maybe you're right,
maybe it's awful.
Yeah.
Great job, Terry and Tina.
Loved that. Oh, and loved those
little congas and the washboard.
We're gonna get
to you guys very soon, okay?
- I'm their manager.
- Oh, good to know.
Yay! Yay!
It is. I know, it is.
It is totally unfair.
It is the one thing
that I've ever wanted
in my entire life and it
is never going to happen.
How? How am I supposed to..
Exactly. Thank you, Jon Ham.
He gets it, you guys.
I mean, the director
literally said to me
that he never wants to see
my face again.
So..
I don't know what you guys
want me to do about that.
Well, giddyup.
Okay, next group, please.
You have the track? Okay!
Oh, it's, great,
okay, action.
- Who's this?
- The sisters?
- Sisters?
- Hello.
- 'Hello.'
- Hi.
'Hi, how are you?'
'Any-any time you're ready.'
Dolls, let's-let's
see-see what you got.
Hoo-wee!
It sure is a hot one today.
Hoo-wee! It sure is
a hot one today!
- That's what I just said.
- I know.
- But I can't remember my lines.
- Soffy..
'What do I say?
I forgot my lines.'
Uh, you know what,
ladies, just
you can just cut
right to the song.
- Okay!
- 'No pressure.'
Okay!
I can.. Okay.
We got this, yes.
Nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
♪ We're sisters
we're sisters ♪
♪ We're gorgeous ♪♪ And great kissers ♪
♪ So lucky to be sisters ♪
♪ With you ♪♪ With me? ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ We're sisters
we're sisters ♪
♪ We're kind and
never bitter ♪
♪ So lucky to be sisters ♪
♪ With you ♪♪ With me? ♪
♪ With you ♪♪
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Okay, and cut!
Thank you so much. Very good,
very good. Thank you.
Okay!
- Hire the girl.
- What?
But she can't sing
or dance or act.
No, she doesn't need to.
- Thanks!
- Uh, okay. Uh, anyone else?
'Uh, you, uh, you got
room for one more?'
Howdy, ladies.
Why don't you
hop up on stage
and-and show us
what you got, partner?
Yes, sir, yes, sir.
Excuse-excuse me, ladies.
Sorry about that.
He's cute, right?
Any time you're ready.
Clouds as mean
as you've ever seen.
Yeah.
Ain't a bird that
knows your tune.
Then there's a little
voice inside you
that keeps on saying..
"Kid..
don't sell your dreams so soon."
That's the theme song
from the Fuller House?
Sshhh! Shush!
'Everywhere you look..'
everywhere that you go..
there's a heart..
...there is a heart..
...a hand to hold onto.
'Everywhere you look..'
everywhere you go,
there is a face..
...of somebody who needs you.
Everywhere you look.
Yeah.
What? Sorry.
That, that's it. That, that's
all I got for the monologue.
- So..
- That's "Fuller House."
That was, ah, that was
surprisingly good.
Real nice work, man.
That was my favorite
show growing up.
What's your name, kid?
Huh. Fin...Fin..
Uh, last name, Finn.
First name, uh..
...Huckleberry?
Yeah.
You know, my-my parents were
real Mark Twain fans, you know?
So..
- Oh..
- Alright.
You know. Yeah, yeah.
But, um..
...you all can call me "Huck."
- Okay.
- Huck.
So, the following people
have been chosen
Caletta Rose..
Great. Great, great, great.
And, uh, Saffron Tremaine..
And Huck Finn.
Great.
Oops, sorry, folks.
Hold tight, just a second.
Yes?
What?
How?
- I can't wait..
- Ahh! A-ahem!
To work you.
You mean, work with me.
Whatever.
We lost the farm house.
What do you mean
we lost the farm house?
- Where did it go?
- It collapsed.
I just saw it yesterday, Bernie.
Well, it's gone today.
We shoot the farm house
in two days!
How are we going to
find another location?
We're going to
figure something out.
Ah-ah-ah!
If-if I may? Hi.
Um, just happened to overhear.
She's a patron of the arts.
Yes, yes and I want
to proposition you.
- She has a proposition for you.
- Yes.
I just happen to be the owner of
a historical country farm house.
True.
And we have a barn, and a
chicken coop, chickens, goats
filing cabinets,
hay, lots of hay..
Big property.
It's a big property.
The kind that you would need
for a production of this size.
Brass tacks, boys.
How much is it going
to cost me
to have you shoot
your movie at my place?
No, no, she's kidding,
she's kidding.
They pay us, not
the other way around.
Why don't we just say
that you give us, uh..
I don't know, 125 percent of
what you were going to pay
the house that you lost, throw
in some...catered lunches
hot, then you have
yourself a deal.
Sure.
Guys!
They're here.
Saffron?
Kale?
- Morning.
- Oh, have a seat, have a seat.
You know, I actually
saw your last movie.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Seen the PR.
That you're doing
for this one here.
It's my house, actually.
Oh. You got a real
nice piece of land.
- Say, how many horses do you..
- I don't know.
I figure I should
be managing you.
- How's that?
- Well, do you have a manager?
- I do not.
- You do now.
What type of managing
do you do?
Ever heard of Wanda's Waffle
and Sushi House?
I can't say I've
had the pleasure.
You will.
Listen, are you a meat guy?
You could be the face
of Jon Ham Bacon.
It's kind of a side
project I'm working on.
Look, I, um, I don't think
I really need a manager.
Not a meat guy?
Surprising.
Uh, how about tractors?
I'm working on a deal
with a local company here.
Uh, thank you, but no.
No. Okay moving on,
moving on.
I got you, though.
I got you with this one?
- Hmm?
- Money.
Everybody likes money, right?
I'm in with the banks.
"Need a loan,
call Jackson Stone."
This is all from my head, man.
I'm just winging it.
- I'm winging it, man.
- Wow.
- Apologies, apologies.
- Okay, yup.
You're a little all over
the place, ain't ya?
You need an animal like me
in your corner, Jackson.
Hmm.
Let's do this.
Wish me luck, Jon Ham.
Love you.
Okay, Jackson,
So, you just shot
all these guys.
Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow.
- And now you're out of ammo.
- Hmm.
Right? Okay.
And from behind you
comes this guy.
- Yeah. Hey, buddy.
- Kenny.
Okay. A one-on-one.
So, uh, Kenny?
You just, you just grab him.
Okay. How do you want me
to approach it?
I could do, like, a step over
toe-hold sleeper, or-or I could
do a figure-four arm lock.
Yeah, that-that's great.
You just go for him.
Just...just come for me, Kenny.
That's hot, that's hot,
that's hot, that's hot.
- No, uh, um..
- Hi!
I'm just not really
comfortable winging it.
Okay.
Fine.
Huck!
Huck, hey. Hello?
Oh. Ahem.
Yeah, uh, I'm so,
so sorry, folks.
Huck. Huck is here.
Yeah.
- Hi. Hi.
- Hi.
Uh, you ever do any stunts?
Oh, yeah.
Two, two years
of gymnastics, so.
That's, that's good.
Uh, go for him.
Uh, he's not,
he's not in the union...
No, that's fine.
Thanks, Kenny.
Just go.
Just go for him.
Uh-uh, okay.
- Yeah. Right now?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
- From back there.
Yeah.
- Ready?
- Yes, I am.
Ready.
- Yeah.
- That's perfect.
- That's great, that's great.
- Alright.
Oh, well, i-it's okay.
You see, I could do that!
I just thought you
wanted something..
- Mm-hmm.
- Good.
Actually, I'm thinking,
Kenny, maybe you, uh
might want to have
a break there.
- Cool. Cool, cool, cool, cool.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. It's probably tired from
all that work. Thanks, buddy.
Uh, thank you, you know,
for going easy on me.
Ah, well, you know,
I got little cousins
we used to play fight
all the time.
That's all this is,
you know?
- Yeah.
- Anyhow, you're a lightweight.
What do you weigh?
About 130-135?
123, thank..
Thank you very much.
- That was a joke.
- I gotcha.
You were so good.
'Let's shoot this.'
And remember, we're going
to do this in a one-er.
Which means we're going to shoot
the whole scene in one shot.
Okay? Everyone, remember here,
timing is everything.
So, if even one piece
of the puzzle is off
the whole thing falls apart.
So that's, so, what is
what is that?
Is that a phone?
- Bernie, Bernie, Bernie!
- Phones off! Please!
- Come on, guys.
- Sorry, guys. Sorry.
- That's alright. We get it.
- All good.
So, Jackson, I want you
to enter from over there, okay?
And, Huck, uh, you can
go around the corner
and wait for your cue, okay?
Now, listen, don't miss this.
If you miss it, you're going
to screw up the whole take
and then I'll have to beat
the crap out of you.
I'm joking, I'm joking.
But I will fire you.
So there's that,
you could get fired.
- That's not a joke.
- No, that one's not joking.
- Yes.
- Okay, good. Good luck.
See you on the other side.
Here we go.
Let's try one.
Okay, lock it up!
Roll sound!
Oh, my gosh.
- 'And action.'
- Hi. Okay.
I know I look
very, very strange.
I'm going to have to do
this real quick.
Good girl.
'Finley!'
What?
No, no, no, no, no. No.
Alright.
'Finley!'
Yes.
Where are you?
Where have you been?
You told me to milk the cow,
so I'm milking the cow.
Is that what you're doing?
- Yeah.
- That is disgusting.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know what? It only gets
really worse from here,
so you should probably
just go, like, right now.
Like, right now!
- You should go.
- Fine. I'm leaving.
There's got to be a better
way to get the milk out.
'Hi!'
- Hi.
- How's the filming going?
Filming's going well. We're
actually rolling right now.
Oh, rolling?
Okay, shh, she, shh.
- Rolling! Rolling.
- Yeah.
I owe you. Okay.
Jackson! Jackson.
Your cue, please.
Now, please.
Oh!
Seriously?
Alright. You wanna play.
Let's play.
Come on, come on.
Who's a good boy?
Are you a good boy?
Come on. Come on.
Let go. Let go!
Thank you.
Hope that was worth
getting shot for.
Cut! Yes!
- Huck?
- 'Yes!'
Come on up.
- Oh, boys.
- Thank you, Jackson.
You're a star, man.
You are a star.
- Thanks, Trev.
- Any time!
Huck, you nailed that.
You nailed that timing.
That's what I'm talking about.
- Really?
- That round-the-corner wave.
You didn't miss it.
You nailed it.
- Okay, let's move on.
- Okay.
- 'And we're moving on.'
- 'I'm thinking drone.'
Oh!
Jacket.
Ah! Inside out.
Oh.
Hey, if you need help with your
pants later, you let me know.
Oh, my god! What are you..
What is your..
You know, I really
appreciate that offer.
Good lookin'.
Any time.
- Yeah, you're good.
- Alright. Thank you.
Hey, uh, Huck.
Ahem. Jackson.
Really, uh, really nice
work today.
Man, you almost made me
bust up. I swear.
Well, I'm..
Thank you, you know, so much.
I.. I'm not gonna lie.
I'm sorta freaking out
that Trevor let me do
that scene with you.
Listen, listen. He let you
do it because you're good.
Alright, you're not afraid
to just go for it.
That takes balls.
Yeah, I-I got, I got those.
So, um...
what do you do
for fun around here?
Oh, ah..
There's a really nice lake,
actually. You can go fishing.
Hmm.
I-I'm sorry. You, um, you
probably meant for a night life.
Yeah, I'm looking for
a hot after-hours club.
Nah, I'm kidding!
Here, sit.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
That lake sounds real nice.
Man..
You must just wake up and pinch
yourself every single day.
Now how's that?
I-I mean, you-you get to travel
the world, you know, for free.
You live the dream
of every single actor.
You're playing all
these great parts
working with the
best directors.
- It's..
- Hmm.
Nah, look the truth is..
...I'd give all this up
to be back at my uncle's ranch.
You know, riding my horse
taking care of the land.
Yeah. That sounds real nice.
Hey, Jackson, I'm sorry,
I, I gotta ask, um..
How did you get here?
Ah, well, ah..
It was like in the movies.
A Hollywood producer
and his wife showed up
and discovered me.
Now I got two more movies
lined up after this one, and..
you know, all I want to do
is get back on the ranch, so..
But, what are you
gonna do, right?
What are you gonna do?
'Alright, we are back people.'
Well, looks like we're back.
Oh..
Hey, uh, hey, Huck?
Yeah?
I like talking with you.
Yeah, me-me too, Jackson.
- I'll see you out there.
- Alright.
♪ This was a dream
for all my life ♪
♪ I'm starting to believe
that it's finally my time ♪
♪ My heart is bursting
at the seams ♪
♪ Right here right now
is where I'm meant to be ♪
♪ And I've found
something more ♪
♪ And though I love
my country home ♪
♪ I feel alive
for the first time ♪
♪ I'm glad that I ♪
♪ Had the courage
to spread my wings and fly ♪
♪ Somehow some way ♪
♪ I know today's the day ♪
♪ That's been waiting for me ♪
♪ I feel the light
of the morning ♪
♪ And now ♪
♪ It seems ♪
♪ Against the odds my dreams ♪
♪ Were waiting for me ♪
♪ It's time
to write my own story ♪
♪ My own story ♪♪
'Okay, everybody, listen up!'
Day after tomorrow,
we shoot the big finale scene.
It is also
our last day of shoot.
So, we've got a huge day today.
'But you all have
a day off tomorrow.'
Yeah, I hear ya.
So, whaddya got goin'
for your day off?
Day off? I, um..
I haven't really had one
of those in a real long time.
Hmm. Nah, look, look, look
you gotta take advantage of 'em.
Alright? These long days on set
will catch up with you.
'Please do not play
with your prop guns.'
'Well, I'm going
to sleep in tomorrow'
and then I'm going
to check out this town.
I like it here.
'Let's do this!'
'Let's get this show
on the road!'
'Okay, full out
on this rehearsal here.'
'Nice, with the legs.'
Then we cut to Saffron.
She sexy-walks in.
We'll fix that later.
Then steady-cam onto the piano
pushing to the saloon girls.
Slide up the leg.
And now we're doing
a Busby Berkeley.
- Busby Berkeley.
- Bugsy..
B-Busby Berkeley.
Then the piano flies out..
Whoosh! Good!
Then we whip-pan
right to these guys.
Give me that wheel kick.
'Then we clap it. Laser focus.'
'Now here comes Kenny.'
'Saffron sees him.'
'She's going to do
some sexy-time with the hands.'
'This is weird.
Now they kiss. Ah!'
'Now Kenny's got the lasso
finale. Okay?' The lasso..'
'Kenny, you've got to have
that lasso spinning, Kenny.'
You gotta.. Oh, cut!
'That was close, though.'
Kenny, it-it was a mess, man.
No, no, no, no, no,
I got, I got it, I got it.
I just have to..
...make the knot tighter.
Uh, a-actually, all you gotta do
is loosen the hondu.
Okay, I think..
I think I know a little bit more
about stunt-roping
than this guy.
Right, Mr. Gymnastics?
Hey, Kenny.
Uh, Huck's right. You gotta..
You gotta loosen the hondu.
Okay. Huck, could.. Huck.
Could you come down here
and please
just do this for us, please?
Uh, yeah, sure.
I'm just..
Uh, I'm just going to take it
for a second.
Kenny?
Let go of the rope, Kenny.
Like, letting go.
And you're buh-bying.
'Thank you. Strong work, Kenny.'
If you could just step on back.
So, whaddya- whaddya want
from him?
Whaddya got?
Well, uh..
Ahem.
Usually, I like to start off
with a little bit
of a Texas Foot Stomp.
And then, uh,
when I'm done with that
I usually like to kick it off
with a little bit
of a Round The World.
'Oh, yeah. I love that, yeah.'
'Oh, yeah!'
And then I usually
like to finish things off
by going back
into The Wedding Ring.
He's like that girl
from the audition.
That girl wishes
she could do that.
Huck, buddy, that was insane.
Y-you keep surprising me.
I'm telling you.
You'd be surprised
how surprising I could be.
Kenny, you switch with Huck.
Uh, and, Huck, let's start
with the kiss.
What? What?
Okay, people, we're starting
with the kiss.
Yeah, big smooch. Let's do it.
Right, right. We're gonna..
Oh! Ahem! Hello.
Well, yeah. We're gonna..
What if, what if.. Hear me out.
What if we do the kiss, you know
after rehearsal, you know
once we're saving it, you know
for-for when the cameras
are-are rolling.
- You know?
- That's funny. Okay, let's go.
Anytime.
I just, I-I-I
I don't really know if..
He's probably
never kissed a girl before.
What? No!
No, Kenny.
I have kissed..
...tons of, of, of girls
ladies before.
Uh, like, so many.
So, so, so many. Uh..
...including my-my cousin..
Okay..
Look, look, um, I get it.
I get it, alright?
It's weird to just
jump in and kiss
a total stranger.
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
That's-that's-that's
exactly what I'm saying.
That-that is the only reason
that this is..
That this is
well, weird.
'Well-well, I'd say'
you just do a cheat kiss.
You don't even gotta touch.
A cheat kiss?
That-that's amazing.
Yeah, let's do,
let's do a cheat kiss.
That's a great idea. Cheat kiss.
That-that sounds like, uh..
we should do it.
- I mean, Trevor--
- No, no, no.
Guys, I can't have any of that
fake crap on my set.
I need authenticity.
I have to have the real deal.
And here I am. Kiss me, Huck.
And you can, like ,
really go for it.
Like, hey, totally go for it.
Right, right.
All the, all the things
you need to do.
- Yeah.
- I'm here for it.
Alright, yeah.
Well, I'm, uh..
Anytime.
I'm gonna go for it right now.
I'm gonna.. Kenny, your rope.
There you go, and..
Trevor, I'm just gonna
go over there and, you know
get myself loose
so I can give it.
I'm gonna give it to you,
so I'll be right..
Be right.. Oh my God!
What am I doing freaking out?
I can't do this. I just..
This is so..
You're fine, you're fine.
You're just gonna
go in there and you know..
Go in there and just gonna Huck
it out. Yeah, let's Huck it.
I'll be there
in two seconds, everybody.
Just give me,
give me one second.
Just go in there, you know,
and just..
Okay. Oh, my God!
Huck, just grab her
and kiss her.
Right.
Okay. Okay.
Anytime now.
Oh, God..
That was so..
I loved that.
Yeah, that was weirdly hot
yet not hot.
- So we're good?
- 'Yeah.'
Let's do one again
for the camera
so they can see it.
Yeah!
- One more time?
- Anytime.
She's here.
Come in!
Oh, hello.
So, this is the main house.
I know it very well.
I used to come here
all the time for coffee
and just to chat before..
...you moved in.
♪ Welcome to the show ♪
♪ One two three four ♪
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Well, howdy, folks.
Hey, Billy!
Now, sometimes,
when you're on the run
all you want is to slow it down.
A little R and R.
The only crime I see here
is no cutie around my arm.
So criminal!
Now, what's a guy got to do
for a little attention
around here, huh?
What, rob somebody?
- He's only kidding!
- Nah.
The only thing
I'm here to steal tonight
is your heart.
Ain't you just
the prettiest little thing?
♪ Jump on up my horse
little darling ♪
Well, giddyup!
We ain't got all day.
♪ Come take a ride with me ♪
Come on, girl, saddle up.
Come on!
♪ Jump on up my horse
little darling ♪
You know I can give you
everything.
♪ Come take a ride with me ♪
♪ Come take a ride with me ♪♪
Oh, oh! Oh!
- 'Cut! Cut it, cut it, cut it!'
- 'Cut! Cut!'
Hey, Jackson, Jackson!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- 'Are you sure?'
- 'Yeah, yeah.'
Here. You lost your hat.
'Let's go get First Aid.'
- There you go.
- Thank you.
I was so worried, I..
Uh..
Well, uh..
You good? Yeah, you're-you're
good, pal. Right?
Yeah, he's good, everybody.
He's, uh, he's real good, folks.
Just a big boy over here.
Let me check him.
Up, yeah. Yeah, ooh! Oh!
He's got it.
There we go. Yeah. Alright.
- Are you okay, buddy?
- 'We're just gonna..'
'You know, I'm thinking,
you know what?'
Uh, let's just,
let's just kinda regroup.
Let's take ten.
Let's take a break.
'No, no, no, I-I feel good.'
'I just wanna check him out'
'make sure
everything's alright.'
Alright, I'm just gonna go.
Excuse me.
My god, what was that?
"Jackson,
I was so worried about you."
No, you weren't worried.
You were..
No, no, no, no, no.
You are not selling my house!
We're not
much of a coffee family.
Valerian! You can't do this!
- Do what, Huck?
- Do, uh..
This, you know?
All-all of this.
I mean, this-this house
is amazing.
It amazes me that you have
decorated this all by yourself.
Aw, thank you, Huck.
I did dabble a little
in Interior Design.
Really, really, really nice.
Man, if this house,
you know, with all the..
Well, let's just say,
if I had this house
I would never sell it.
I would never,
ever, ever, ever sell it.
Have we met before, Huck?
Yeah. You look
familiar to me, too.
And where's that-that accent
of yours from?
Oh, uh..
You know, uh, I-I got
a real, real quick break
so I was just gonna
pop on in here
use the restroom,
if that's alright.
Uh, no. Ew.
Um, there's
portable toilets outside.
Alright. Yeah, yeah.
I'll go use those.
Got a real nice zing, though,
by the way
so it would have been..
Bye-bye.
Alright.
It's a lovely home, ain't it?
Oh, it sure is.
'So, as I was saying'
this property has been
in the Tremaine family
for over a century.
It's practically a landmark.
Oh, dump it.
The sooner the better.
'H-h-h-hold on, hold on.'
If we can get landmark status
would that add value
to the house?
Well, I don't know,
but it would guarantee
that the property
would be preserved.
Oh, pfft!
They can turn it into
a Chuck E Cheese for all I care.
'Yeah, she-she's right.'
Just get us some offers
as soon as possible, okay?
It breaks my heart to think
about selling this property.
'I always imagined'
that this house would stay
in the family forever
Finley having
little babies here.
The thought! Um..
The thought is so lovely.
But, you know,
teenagers these days
they just want to get out
and see the world.
'Ugh..'
Okay! New plan.
Change. Get back in there.
I'm just going to go..
I'm just going to change.
Okay.
Ahem. Hello, sir. How ya doin'?
Just dropping this bag off
to one of the ladies, you know.
Alright. Okay..
I'm so sorry!
So, so, so sorry, Miss!
My God! Okay..
Well, uh, I'm, uh,
let you two be.
I see
it's very occupied in there.
I can hold it.
God, that's disgusting. Oh.
'They cannot sell this house.'
Excuse me. Anybody in here?
No?
Oh, my God.
Sell the house!
They can't sell the house.
I mean, she's done
some crazy things before
but this is just..
- Okay..
- 'Huck?'
Are you kidding me?
'Huck?'
Huck?
I can tell you're in here.
Oh.
Excuse me, young man.
Now, unless you are here
for a fitting
and I don't believe
that you are
then I highly suggest
that you get on your way
before I have to call security
and have them escort you out.
Excuse me, have you seen
a man around here somewhere?
The only man that I see
is a disrespectful one
standing right in front of me.
'Does anyone have a 20 on Huck?'
That means now!
Young man, go. Shoo!
Get out of my trailer. Shoo!
It's my property.
This is my property!
- This is my property.
- Shoo!
'Where's Huck?
Does anyone have a 20 on Huck?'
'Please, people, help me here!'
'Really?'
Yee-haw!
How is my favorite client today?
- I'm not your client, Kale.
- No. Not yet.
But if you take a little lookie.
Right?
I mean, it-it-it is rough
but I think you'll see
where I'm going with it.
- I see something.
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
Okay, listen, um..
- Hey, Kale?
- Yeah, buddy?
Who is that girl over there?
'Oh, God, why?'
Well, I think that's the girl
from the audition, no?
Oh, yes. Yeah.
Yeah. That's Pig Girl.
Just a muddy little nobody.
Tragic, really.
Listen, I-I-I think
I hear them calling for me.
Alright? You hold onto this.
I-I love the idea.
Wonderful work.
I'll catch up with you later.
I was just hoping
maybe you'd take a look
at this contract that I drew up.
'Hey, hey, hey, hold on now.'
Hold on to this water
for me, too, bud.
Thanks. I'll be right with you.
Well, I'll hold that.
I'll be right here.
And she rides, too.
You want me? Come and get me.
- Hold on.
- 'Come on, boy.'
Let's go. Come on, boy.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on, let's go. Come on. Hey.
Come on. Hyah! Hyah!
Hyah! Come on.
Come on, boy.
Hey, hey, hold up!
It's okay, it's okay,
it's alright.
Who are you?
I think we might have
a little bit of a problem
with Jackson and Finley.
The only problem we have
is that you haven't managed
to sign him yet.
God, mom, that is so unfair.
He's impossible to get to.
He's either on set working
or hanging out with Huck.
I'm starting to honestly think
that those two might be..
...you know,
which would be very cute.
Um, that is totally ridiculous.
I happen to know
Huck is into girls
because when he kissed me,
it was so..
Right. There's also something
fishy going on
between Finley and Huck.
Okay.
Huck would never
be interested in Finley!
I didn't say
Huck was interested in Finley
I said Jackson was.
Oh! Oh..
I don't think we need to worry
about the Pig Girl.
Okay, listen, I can only hear
one conversation at a time.
Does anyone have eyes
on Jackson and Huck?
Alright.
There we go, there we go.
It's okay. Oh! Ow!
Come on. Come on. Attaboy.
Ah, she got away from us
this time.
That's alright.
We'll get her next time.
You're a good horse.
You're a good boy, alright?
You're alright. You just shied
away from that jump today.
It's okay.
'I can teach you.'
'You know, I had a gelding
just like you back home.'
How about a treat?
Let's get you a treat.
Yeah, these will do.
What do you say, hmm?
Yeah. There you go.
I can do almost everything,
but I can't control the weather
so just get me
a rain-cover set ASAP.
- Bernie!
- Oh!
Okay, I've got Huck.
I still need a 20 on Jackson.
Trevor's been looking for you.
Please don't wander off
like that again, okay?
Yeah, I won't.
I am so sorry about that. Sorry.
- Go talk to him.
- Oh, everything, though..
- Everything is great.
- Okay.
- Jackson.
- Hey, where ya been?
Where have you been?
I've just been
checking out the property.
Mm, yeah, it's a..
...real nice piece of land.
Beautiful, you could say, yeah.
Yeah, real beautiful.
I'd like to find me
a place like this some day.
That would be real nice,
real nice.
Jackson? Huck?
- Mm?
- Let's huddle up.
I heard "Huddle up."
That's me, right?
You guys need me for this one?
No, Kenny, we're fine.
- Yeah, let's go.
- Alright.
Alright.
Okay.
Ah-ah-ah!
The chemistry
between you two on camera..
...is-is-is magical.
It's weird.
So, I'm going to take
a chance on you, Huck.
I'm giving you the part
that I was going to give Kenny.
So..
...this is
for the big finale scene.
Take it.
Now, we have
a company day off tomorrow
so you go home, you work hard,
you memorize those lines
and don't be late again.
- No!
- Alright.
No, no, sir, I-I won't.
I promise.
This is everything to me.
Well, well, you can thank
your pal, Jackson, here
because it was his idea.
There it is. Good luck!
Bernie, shut it down.
- 'Okay, we are moving on.'
- See you, Trev.
Ahem.
- Jackson, uh..
- What's up?
Thank you.
I don't even know what to say.
No thanks needed.
Ah, look, I-I owe you.
Look, you saved me from having
to do the scene with Kenny.
Alright?
Uh, I-I really shouldn't
laugh at that
because I really feel bad
for the poor guy, you know?
Right.
Uh..
Huck, y-y-your..
your-your mustache
is a little askew.
Yeah.
Oh, um..
You know, Huck, I, uh
I figured as much.
You did?
Yeah.
You can't grow facial hair.
So what?
Yeah, yeah. Uh..
I-I can't grow facial hair. I..
Oh, it feels good to get that
off my chest, you know that?
- You got that.
- Alright.
It's 'cause I got such a,
such a babyface.
You know what I mean?
To get the part
I had to, had to look the part
but, you know, you got me.
Well, look, you're lucky.
I'll tell you what, I feel like
I'm shaving this every day
morning, noon and night,
you know what I'm saying?
- One day.
- Right, right.
Well, I'll tell you what, look
your secret's safe with me.
Okay?
Alright. That's good news,
yeah.
I'll catch you later.
- Thank you.
- See you, bud.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
The best part is that
even though
the lighting was really bad
the selfie was still really good
and I just felt like,
I don't know--
I, I am, I was gonna go
fishing tomorrow
since, you know,
it's my day off. Sorry.
You don't have a day off.
I meant your day off.
- Of filming, you know?
- Oh.
I'll make breakfast first.
- I want French Toast.
- Okay.
Fine, whatever.
Just stop talking.
Okay.
Saffron, if the director
pegged you as "Talent"
why hasn't he given you
a bigger part?
Mm!
You don't know anything, mom.
This is how
the film business works.
Oh, I know
how monkey business works.
What?
Boys like Jackson
are only after one thing.
That is not true!
What is not true?
How would youeven know?
Yes, Finley. How would you?
Because I, um..
I overheard
Jackson and Huck talking
when they were by the barn
and they said
the director thinks
Saffron is really talented
and he wants
to make her part bigger.
I knew it.
Yeah, I don't buy it.
I mean, no offense,
but we've all seen you act.
Don't be jelly.
Kale, she's right.
It's not about
how you play the game
it's about
whether or not you win.
Potato potato.
You do know
you have to say them differently
for that phrase to work, right?
Do you mind if I join you?
I'm so sorry!
I didn't know you were..
Um..
Do you know, the, uh,
the-the-the fish
they just they're-they're really
not biting over here at all.
I think if you, you know,
go up the lake a little bit
like way down,
it would be better.
Yeah, I think
I'll, uh, take my chances.
Great.
Um..
Okay, well, um..
have a, have a good day.
- You leaving already?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Is it something I said?
- No. No, no.
Uh, no, no you, uh, you are..
..fine. I, um..
Good luck, you know,
with, uh, everything.
Come on, now,
please don't go.
I-I have to.
You know, I forgot my bait.
You mean this bait?
Yup.
Yup, that, um..
That'll be the one.
If you could just, you know..
- Just right. Yeah.
- Thank you.
Now you're probably wishing
you had that horse
right about now, huh?
And you're probably
thinking to yourself
"Can I outrun him?"
I don't think so.
Look..
I know it's you.
- It isn't me.
- Yeah, it is.
- No, it isn't--
- Yes, it is.
- No, it isn't!
Fine.
Yes, it's me.
I'm so embarrassed right now.
Embarrassed?
For what?
Sorry, do you not remember me?
I'm the girl
that fell flat on her face
when she was trying
to wrangle her pig.
And I thought that was
some mighty fine pig wrangling.
Okay. I wasn't there
to wrangle a pig.
I was there to get
a part in your movie.
Well, look.
You're-you're going to get
another shot.
Yeah, a plain girl
from Dreary, Idaho
isn't getting another chance.
Man..
Look at me. Go on.
There is nothing plain
about you.
Now, will you come sit
and fish with me?
I was here first, so.
Yeah, keep staring at me,
I'll sell you both.
Finley!
Fin-ley! Anyone home?
No.
Sorry.
Oh!
Fantastic.
Disgusting. Absolutely dis..
You.
Shouldn't you be,
like, a sandwich
or something by now?
Let's get something straight,
Jon Ham, I don't like you
I don't like
your stupid little face..
Okay, calm down.
Bad pig. Bad pig! Bad pig!
Get away from me, Fatty!
Get away!
Hey, hey, hey, easy. Easy.
Oh!
What are you smiling about?
You just remind me of someone.
Mm. A girl back home?
No, no.
My friend, Huck, actually.
Oh!
Oh, that's, um
that's-that's weird.
Yeah, it's, uh..
You know, uh, I don't mean
that I think
you look like a boy.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I did not think
that you were saying that, no.
- You are a boy, right?
- I am.
- Yeah. I'm a girl!
- You're a girl!
Hold on, you've got
a piece of grass in your hair.
Oh, sorry. Got it?
Yeah.
That was, uh..
- That was, um..
- Weird.
That was weird.
But thanks.
Seriously?
Where would Finley keep..
Oh.
Stupid little trusting Pig Girl.
Oh, bee! Bee!
What is your problem?
So..
- My-my friend.
- Mm? Huck?
- Huck.
Yeah, no, he's, um..
- He's amazing.
- Oh.
Really? He's, like, a,
like a good guy?
Oh, yeah. No, he's a great guy.
I meant, he's..
...he's an amazing actor.
I'm-I'm sorry.
He's, like, an amazing actor?
Hmm.
You-you think that-that he's..
...that he's that amazing?
Like, he could, he could
go far or something
like in show business?
That, is, like..
That is like,
this sounds so cool.
Like, from you, especially..
- You know, from..
- Right, right.
That's really great for-for him,
you know?
Yeah, I'll, uh..
I'll let him know
how happy you are for him.
Yeah. Yeah, please do,
you know.
Oh, God! You devil pig!
Oh, God!
Oh, God..
Disgusting.
Oh, dear.
You know, this is
one of the best days
I've had in a long while.
Yeah.
Me too.
And, look,
I don't know about you
but, uh, I think
I need another shot
at that horse race.
Oh.
I just don't think
you could keep up.
You're funny..
...and you're kinda cute.
Stop.
You know..
...this business..
...it's just filled
with people pretending
to be somethin'
that they ain't.
But you..
...you're real.
Real.
Jackson..
I, um..
I have to tell you something.
Um..
I'm so sorry.
No worries.
Um..
Sorry. I'm..
Is everything okay?
I have to go.
- What is it?
- I am so sorry.
Wait!
I don't even know your name!
'Where have you been?'
Okay, um..
Look, I can, uh,
I can, I can explain.
Finley..
...are you and Huck, like..
What?
Saffron, no.
Finley..
...why don't you explain
to them?
Or should I say..
"...Huck"?
Why are we calling her "Huck"?
Did she change her name?
How am I related
to you people?
Okay, um..
Look, I, uh, I..
I messed up.
'Um, Valerian, I, um..'
I really wanted
to be in this movie, right and..
...the only way
that I could do that
was to, uh..
...disguise myself..
...as a boy.
Um, as-as Huck.
Wait!
Finley, you're Huck?
Ew!
Oh!
That's why Huck didn't
ask me out after our kiss.
- Saffron.
- 'Yeah?'
There is no Huck.
Yeah, I get that, Kale.
'Do you?'
Valerian, I'm..
I get it if you're mad.
I didn't--
Finley, give me your phone.
- What?
- Saffron, take Finley's phone.
Yeah, I..
I need that for..
Ew.
'I am not stupid.'
You have been laughing at me
all this time.
- No, no, no, no. Valerian, I--
- Look, shut up!
This is what's going to happen.
You are going to stay..
...in the barn tonight..
...and think about all the harm
you have done to this family.
And tomorrow, we'll tell Louise
to take
the first offer she gets.
We are finally getting out
of this hell hole.
- Valerian.
- No, quiet!
You have lost all rights
to have a say in this.
Stupid little Pig Girl.
'Wait, who's gonna
make me dinner?'
It's okay. Okay.
Dad.
Okay.
Okay..
You're kidding me.
Keys.
Has anyone seen Huck?
Okay, all departments
does anyone have a 20 on Huck?
'Negative at the camera trucks.'
Dammit!
Oh, where is he?
Hi!
Got it...got it.
'Anyone have eyes on Huck?'
Not in Wardrobe.
I think it needs to be tighter.
Hmm.
Okay, go to Circus
check inside his trailer.
- Who's over at Catering?
- 'Uh, Cam.'
Yeah. Both of you, just check.
You realize this is your job
to know where he is at all
times, right?
'Okay, Bernie.'
- Well?
- Nothing.
- Well, try his cell.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
Uh, Bernie! Bernie! Bernie!
I have an idea for you.
Uh, It's a good one.
Have you heard of Jon Ham..
Excuse me.
- What?
- Uh, hi. Jon Ham Bacon?
Well, we've been
thinking about expanding.
Jackson's onboard.
I'm his manager, by the way.
I'm his manager.
- Hi!
- Hello.
Snack.
Hello!
Anyone? Hello?
It doesn't do a bird's-eye,
the thing doesn't make sense
and that's what I'm saying..
Did you find him?
Went to voicemail.
- Go get Kenny.
- Yeah.
I need, uh..
I'm going to need
some sort of, um, sandwich.
I'm going to need a sandwich.
Agh!
You need me?
Yeah.
Yeah, I need you, Kenny.
Yes!
Oh..
You show up there.
You got some chocolate
on there.
Let's get rid of that.
Morning, y'all..
- Morning.
- What's going on?
Well, looks like
we get to do our scene
together after all, buddy.
And how's that?
Where's Huck?
He didn't show.
We can't reach him.
So, we're going to go
with Kenny.
Mm-hmm.
We gotta shoot.
I understand, Bernie.
Oh, this is your chance!
Really?
- Get over there.
- Really?
Don't blow it again.
You're very hard on her.
- Hi!
- Hi..
Howdy, howdy, howdy.
Oh. Ew.
Listen, now is really
not the time.
Oh, but, um..
...I heard that you wanted
to make my part bigger..
...and yes.
I'm sorry, what?
No, no, that's right,
that's right.
You mentioned that.
Uh, you guys discuss
that right now, alright?
I'm gonna go..
You're not. Don't do this to me.
Jackson.
What?
Are you..
What is that?
Again, I want to say
thank you to all of the locals
who showed up today,
ready to work
as Background Artists.
My mom would like
to discuss the game plan
for selling the property.
Things have changed, and..
Uh, shh! I-I can't hear
the nice lady.
We're just waiting
on one more cast member.
Hey, Huck?
Huck, where you at?
Jon Ham!
Yes! Good boy, Jon Ham!
Good boy! Good boy!
You got it, you got it!
Easy. Good boy, good boy,
come on!
Thank you!
Jon Ham..
...youare my hero.
It's showtime.
- I got Jackson!
- Okay, we got Jackson.
Okay, good. Let's do this, then.
Trevor, are we really
shooting this?
Yeah, I'm sorry, buddy.
We gotta.
- We gotta, we gotta.
- Okay.
'Actors to first position,
please.'
Yes!
And..
...action!
Everything you said was a lie.
It may've been a lie, Billy..
...but..
Uh, but, uh..
I am so sorry, I, I..
Can I get the line?
Can we go back?
I forgot, I forgot the line.
- Going again!
- 'Sorry.'
And..
...action!
Everything you said was a lie.
Oh..
It may have been a lie,
Billy. but..
Oh!
Aah!
I think that's broken.
- That was close.
- Ooh!
Don't touch him. He's fine.
Your, uh, your-your tooth.
Gone.
Is it noticeable?
- Let's go again.
- Go.. Uh..
- He's missing a tooth.
- I don't care.
We didn't establish teeth.
Get him up!
Okay, let me go again.
- Up you go.
- 'Up I go.'
Yup. Oh, Kenny's alright.
Coach, we're okay.
I-I got this.
I'll just go again.
'Okay.'
I'm going to make you proud!
'Okay. Ooh, I feel good.'
- Okay, we should go.
- Okay, let's go, then.
Here we go, and rolling.
Rolling!
Action.
Everything you said was a lie.
- We got this, we got this.
- This isn't going to work.
It's going to work.
Ugh..
No.
'Should we cut?'
No, we're not going to cut.
Give him the line again, please.
- Really?
- Yes. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Okay. Uh..
Everything you said was a lie.
'It may have been
a lie, Billy..'
It's all been a lie.
But I never meant to hurt you.
What's going on with his voice?
I should have told you
at the lake.
Lake? What lake? What lake?
Right, we shoulda..
We shoulda talked at the lake.
But I was too afraid to.
I was..
...too scared of..
...what might happen.
Is he taking off his clothes?
But I am sick
and tired..
...of being afraid.
You know our friend, Huck..
...he made me realize
that I could either
stay invisible..
...or I could be remarkable.
So, if coming clean..
...means losing everything..
...then it just wasn't
in the cards.
Who are you?
That's a good question.
Some people call me "Pig Girl."
My daddy, though, he called me
"Princess."
All I know is that
I have got one chance..
...and even if I end up
with mud on my face
I am going to take it.
Jackson..
I'm so sorry
that I didn't tell you sooner.
Um..
This is a lot to take in.
Yeah, I know.
Can you forgive me?
I don't know.
And cut!
Yes!
'Okay, I don't know
what that was.'
I don't know what that was,
but I'm loving that.
I am.. Oh!
You..
...are extraordinary.
I thought you were a.. Um..
- But you're a, you're a--
- 'Girl!'
- Yeah.
- A badass girl.
'I knew it!'
I knew there was something
weird about--
Shut up, Kenny.
I'm gonna put you
in my next movie.
The one starring Jackson.
You're not putting her anywhere.
You can't stop me from going,
Valerian.
Well, I guess if you want
to say goodbye..
...to your childhood home.
And the first thing to go..
...will be that little pig.
Straight to the slaughterhouse.
I don't really think
that you would do that.
Because I think
that there is a heart
in there somewhere, Valerian.
- For crying out loud. Louise?
- 'Yeah?'
Please.
- 'Louise?'
- Yes?
We'll take the first offer
you get.
Well, I'd have to get the
owner's approval to do that.
I just gave it to you.
'Oh, well, after our meeting..'
I did some digging
and it turns out
that Mr. Tremaine left
the property to his daughter.
He left it to me?
Not you.
His real daughter.
So, you'd have to ask her.
Is that true, Louise?
It is.
So, you're saying..
You've got squat.
Ahh..
I want this more than anything.
You guys have no idea
but I, I can't leave my farm
my animals, my home--
Hold on now.
I might be able to help you out
there.
- Hey, Trev?
- 'Yeah?'
Come here, bud.
What's up?
Look, I got...
I got good news
and I got bad news.
- Okay.
- Bad news is..
...you're gonna have to find a
new lead for your film.
Uh, excuse me?
The good news is...
Huck here is your star.
My name's Finley.
Now, that is a great name.
Think that really is.
Well, you know, it was written
for a male.
- It-it's an action film.
- Right.
But I'm thinking right now
that it would be so much better
with a female.
Finley.
Geez.
- I'm making calls.
- Okay.
And, Miss Finley
if it was okay by you..
Hm..
I could hang back
look after your farm.
Keep them horses in shape.
You know, since my step-family
won't be living here anymore..
I will need someone
to look after Jon Ham.
Right. Hey, Kale?
Yeah, buddy. Yeah.
Listen, I won't be needing
a manager anymore
but if you're interested
I will need someone to shovel
Jon Ham's poop.
I see.
Alrighty then.
- I'm not picking up poop.
- No..
- You're picking up poop.
- I'm not picking up pig poop.
'You're supposed to fix this,
Kale.'
You know, uh..
I could take off after you..
finish shooting
your movie.
Hmm.
Yeah..
...or not.
Or not.
There is somethin' about you.
♪ Now I know I know
I know yeah ♪
♪ Umm umm-umm ♪
♪ Once upon a time ♪
♪ It was never going right ♪
♪ But in the blink of an eye ♪
♪ It's then I got a sign ♪
♪ Everything fell right here
into places ♪
♪ And found its way to me ♪
♪ I guess it was supposed
to happen ♪
♪ Like it was meant to be ♪
♪ I got a feeling
that I'm gonna remember ♪
♪ This song forever and ever ♪
♪ There's nothing like a sweet
sweet sweet starlight ♪
♪ I'm feeling free free free ♪
♪ It's alright ♪
♪ Moving with the flow ♪
♪ Yeah this is my time ♪
♪ No matter where I go ♪
♪ It'll be alright ♪
♪ 'Cause the stars
will always align ♪
♪ Tell me who did ever know ♪
♪ That I may live here ♪
♪ I was feeling so alone ♪
♪ The future was unclear ♪
♪ Yeah I used to think ♪
♪ That my story was written
with an end ♪
♪ Now I know I have control ♪
♪ And I've got my pen in hand ♪
♪ I got a feeling
that I'm gonna remember ♪
♪ This song forever and ever ♪
♪ There's nothing like ♪
♪ A sweet sweet sweet
starlight ♪
♪ I'm feeling free free free ♪
♪ It's alright ♪
♪ Moving with the flow ♪
♪ Yeah this is my time ♪
♪ No matter where I go ♪
♪ It'll be alright ♪
♪ 'Cause the stars
will always align ♪
♪ Now I know I know I know ♪
♪ Ohhh ohh oh ho oh oh ♪
♪ There's nothing like ♪
♪ A sweet sweet sweet
starlight ♪
♪ I'm feeling free free free ♪
♪ It's alright ♪
♪ Moving with the flow ♪
♪ Yeah this is my time ♪
♪ No matter where I go ♪
♪ It'll be alright ♪
♪ 'Cause the stars
will always align ♪
♪ Ohhh ohh oh ho oh oh ♪
♪ Yeah I know I know ♪
♪ Ohhh ohh oh ohhh oh oh ♪
♪ The stars will always align ♪♪