Ai
I'm cold.
So let's find something to cure the cold?
FUCK
Well, you told me this month to be yourself.
How am I here?
Nhai
I want to make love
No, I don't want who are you.
spit out my friend.
My friend is not q pervert
ai
I said no.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you mad?
You're acting stupid.
Have you ever heard of the Gray Devil?
Daddy Teach you through a duck keychain, right?
I was taught through the tale of the gray devil.
there is that
everyone has a gray demon inside.
it is hidden in the human mind.
rely on anger
and people's frustration.
you will say
I'm the devil.
because I'm mad at you?
no
I'm just going to say
the more the devil eats them.
it grows bigger.
It will take hold of us.
if someone is swallowed by a gray demon
that person can't love anyone again.
I was once a gray monster.
what do you means..
You don't love anyone?
I have But not in the way I want
I love my family.
Love Grandpa
My Grand mother Ya Kaew
My father silpakorn
Jao Nan
but those love
it's not a knight.
have to endure it
over many years
then now
have you found a knight yet?
might be
knight in form of duck
My duck keychain?
may
Since I met Mr.ducky
the devil inside me
didn't dare to come out to rage again.
you might not be the devil in the first place.
I'm sleepy.
yeah
sleep
good night.
Knight
Nhai change your sleep position, I couldn't breathe.
yes
Hm.
What’re you doing?
Why?
Why look at your face like that?
Did you think that I tries to make love to you?
you are the one who tries to make love to me
Last night you hugged me and tried to kiss me
probably
I thought you are side pillow
Then here's the thing.
Or it must be Morning Kiss first.
hmm
Stop
Stop it
What time is it?
11 A.M.
go to take a shower.
Then I'll take you to eat.
then collect your things at your place
OK
What ?
sit properly
I don't want to say hi to your private part
go away
Why you are so violence
But i like it
you keep teasing me
Can you take me to Singh's bar? I left my motorcycle there
Singh..
Is he the person who was with you yesterday?
Who is he?
Singh is a brother next door
Known him since i was a child.
I has a little something to discuss.
And then, he's just playing.
you know, right?
That I am jealous.
none of my business
Go take a shower.
Shy?
Heh, hungry .
Why would you yell?
hungry I am so hungry
Don't you want me to take a shower with you
If you tease me one more time
I will break your model.
Please, Sir, Mr. Chen Nai.
why my heart beating so hard
Maybe it's because it's running. Yes, because it's definitely running..
Oh
no, it's not.
can't be tramble.
so you fell in love with my housewife mode?
Hey
why you got such a bad manner why don't you knock the door
What? That's it you are the one that doesn't close the door.
What, I think you're not careful.
Running to close the door, your towels might fall.
well I will not going give you what you want
damn damn damn!
Ai Where are you
can I use your lotion?
just choose and use any lotion that you want
oh
It's extraordinary.
I thought it is a lotion shop
I know now
Why he is so handsome.
Did he use lotion for shower instead of water
which one should I use
use the most right side
I used it frequently.
damn
I was shock. When did you come in?
In the way since you said I am handsome.
why are you here? Collect anything ?
I am here to wash clothes.
here it is
AW
You didn't wash it your self?
I see there's a washing machine.
depending on my mood.
If in a hurry,I will wash myself.
but your cloths and your pant
wash with my own hands.
Thank you very much.
Change from saying thank you
to accept my love instead
If you be my wife
i will say yes now.
No way
Why
You doesn't want to be with me.
my wife
What's wrong with you
Mia (wife*)
Mia	 Mia, Mia, Mia, Mia, Mia, Mia, Mia
is that it?
Ai
Aiyaret
I’m hungry
Can I eat it?
You’re so noisy
You can eat it
I bought for you
Microwave is here.
use the bowl
and make heat
It's cold
but still delicious.
Why
you never did?
Why don't you put it in a bowl, warm it up, sit down and eat?
Um..it's
I’m lazy clean the dishes
I’ll do it.
If my father see me do like this.
he will scold me
Actually.
My dad doesn't let me do it.
But here, Daddy is absent.
I did it.
Stubborn
Um you’re the first one.
That says I’m stubborn.
But my dad.
said I’m a good boy.
rarely to being naughty
-Because
-because you are too lazy to cry.
I am about to recall my childhood memories and ruined it
Tell me about your chidhood
but we have to keep walking and you can tell me about your childhood during the way
I will take the clolth and send it to the laundry.
OK
here's the thing
My family has 3 member
my dad
Me
my brother
My mom
passed away .
when I was 6-years-old.
My dad run a chicken rice restaurant.
it’s too good
So good
he get lots of profit and no time to take care of me.
My dad
so he left me with Shing's mother
the person who live next door
I said.
She treated me so well
Awwww
What's the drama then?
when I was a kid
I am so naughthy
I was crying
so loud
When P’sing heard it.
He did something with me.
put red lipstick on his lip
and threatened
if I don't stop crying.
he will kiss me.
Did you see that his face look like a gangster
It's haunted to me
I was very scared.
So I’m
still haunted me until today
I have an iron rule
if anyone is going to be Chen Nhai's lover.
no red lips.
I will never ever use red lipstick anyway
become my lover
I will make you comfortable
Yes
the kiss.
Can we kiss in the car?
there's a pourish spill all over your face
this restaurant?
I'm not hungry yet.
Is this restaurant?
what's the matter ?
Isn't it delicious?
I told you I want to have an easy meal just lunch box
why don't you let me
Why are you want the lunch box?
No nutrients.
Well, it's easy for me
put it in the microwave and you're done.
open mouth
Eat it so you can stop complaining.
Eat a lot so you can grow up quickly.
What?
full?
excuseme
can you pack for me
Okay, wait a minute.
Better to listen to music
Open now
yeah
That's my favourite song
I don't usually listen to it.
Oh
Aren't you listening?
This song is good
you know?
that secretly loving someone
How tortured it is.
it's good
Never mind
Ingfa, are you sure the Ai will come here?
I usually come here with Wine (person name)
But those 3 people are busy so it must be you and Bambi who have to help me.
Oh Jida, I'm more than sure
If they don't come, you can throw shit to Bambi's face.
Oh, why is it me, you must be hit.
Well, I want jida to throw at you. Why?
Sigh, I'm begging you.
Wow!
I miss this battle field.
Ai's gang is already here
Oh Bambi
can you blend with your friends in the group?
Sigh, you make me uncomfortable
Let's listen together. what did they say
Attack
It's not fun at all.
It's like I'm playing with only Nine
It's true what you said.
Oh, what about me?
I challenge you to play basketball with me
I give you 1 vs 4 players
they lost anyway.
Yeah, talk about Ai.
Recently, Ai and Nhai  go everywhere together
Did you notice?
Well, since Nhai  heart broken.
they stick together all the time
I wonder Ai might become Nhai lover
shit
What are you talking about?
what's wrong with you?
I guess.
It's not like that.
Nhai likes girls
As, probably
that's enough.
You can stop guessing.
if they really like each other.
I think it
normal
It's true what you said.
I said, Ai and Nhai
they are match
or are they already in relationship?
none sense
keep playing.
Hello
Here I come.
What are you doing?
Oh, Ton
hello
Nine and Intha coming too?
Hello
can you swears that you don't know
uh
Ai and Nhai didn't come?
Did you see them?
Oh, Nhai are so fierce.
Be kind to us.
we are here in peace
yeah
But where did Ai and Nhai go?
I don't know.
they are lovers
Where they are going
are no longer your concern
Well, Ton said at the beginning that they are not in relationship
oh
Are you here for sneaking us ?
no! we are not sneaking anything
even in this modern world
when you lie
Are they still using the highs pitch voice?
Don't you know?
that it's not smooth at all.
no! we are not sneaking anything
Oh, Enough is enough.
So jida and friends are you here for playing games?
Yes.
So that's fine.
The game we are playing need team member.
That's good.
And usually jida and her friends What game are you playing here?
or that
play these games that we are playing.
yeah
Let's go in first.
uh
Well, we'll go back.
Yeah, you're hungry right?
Well, yes.
So let's go.
bye bye
Why are you in such a hurry?
Let's play together again.
well
Jida and friend are being weird.
Why?
well it's normal
Let's play a game.
This tree is really naive.
Oh you
I just remembered that I was going to ask several times.
The day you brought me some porridge.
How do you know my room?
I keep tracking.
well asking from a friend?
yeah
Then that day I lost the way.
You come and pick me up again.
and then go to P' Sing's bar
how did you find me all the time?
ME
Ask from your friends.
But I didn't tell anyone where I was going.
Let's load the GPS together, shall we?
What is it?
Well, the map.
Well
Tell me
that you lost the way often
If there is an app
when you drive away
I can pick you up, right?
Good.
Take it, take it
Load it now
You really don't remember anything?
You only care what you are.
I guess.
You and I must be soulmates.
so I followed you right?
We are
true soulnates
don't be lunatic
I don't believe in soulmate.
oh yeah?
But Ton told me
that you are waiting for a clip of a gypsy card?
every week.
well
Just watching when I got nothing to do
Let's go
better go into the room.
I won't finish packing.
come
My sleeping nest
Shocked.
If you can't stand it
you can change your mind and we can go back to be friend
we are still on the point that can return
No
You wait and see.
I will make you
become a mature
aw
What is this?
You take a tissue.
Why are you stuffing them in your socks?
hey
nothing
do you always stay in your room?
I live here alone
It's a little cluttered.
It's normal.
I don't think so.
Well
You wait here.
I'll go get my clothes.
in a moment
i got a very good skill in packing thing
where do you go out for sleep?
Where?
well
It's depend
Ton's room
Intha's room
Sometimes I got bored.
I ride my motorcycle to other provinces.
and then find a hotel
Do you like hanging out alone?
nope
I don't have anyone to go with.
next time
you should ask me
well
Did you just mentioned we are sould mate
well you just
have to find me where i was your self
I'll go get my stuff.
Wait a minute.
Nhai
Come here.
Which one do you choose?
I'll do it.
It's okay.
I can do it myself.
Here we go.
Wait a minute.
you do this.
The clothes are completely wrinkled.
wrinkled clothes
it's chennhai style.
people already know my style.
I confess with honestly.
I'm very organized person.
when I saw you in your crumpled clothes.
I always want to take it off and iron it.
Actually
me
I can't iron my clothes.
then you should stop losing the way while riding
and instead paying your petrol
just hire someone to iron
oops
It's so hurts
It hurts to the point of my heart.
you are over acting
I like the way you keep organize , AI
because
it's something I don't have.
just now
You just told me
that you like me
I said I like the way you organize
that's it.
You said you liked me.
You quit bothering me.
otherwise i will
Nhai
you
Like me
release
Your eyes will tell.
that you like me
Like a friend?
not a lover
I think you
like me more than that.
you here
hey
What's wrong with you?
You want it too.
Are you mad at me?
Well
I don't know how to apologize
nope
I'm not mad.
or you
is
I didn't hate you just now.
I feel good too.
but all of sudden
I thought I was a man.
being together with a man
My body
Against myself.
It's okay.
I need some time.
If I like you more
or really love you
So there's no problem.
but
if we don't get along
I.don't want to continue the relationship until we can't look at each other
I can wait.
Ai
I'm
Sorry for kicking you.
Come here
I'll help you.
Hey
no
well
I meditated in a moment and it disappeared.
So you're going to let go of my mood like this?
So
turn around
you musterbrate your self I will as well
close your eyes
Well
Chen Nhai
I told you to close your eyes.
Stop thinking
Damn you
You are really spoiled.
Aw
Ai
Are you sucking my neck?
I'm not sure.
So you look.
hmm
seems to have bruise
Thank you.
It's okay.
I am sarcastic.
Oh
I thought you really thanked me.
Ton
What's the matter?
I've seen you go and eat for a long time.
Did you get dumped by a girl?
people like me.
got dumped
what's wrong with you then
isn't it?
I was just wondering
Does Nhai really like AI
Ton
Why are you stressed?
He's afraid of being left alone by this guy.
isn't it?
Hey Intha
Do you remember this?
The story that Nhai told you.
His first girlfriend.
back in high school.
yes
It's his first girlfriend.
as soon as he has a girlfriend
He left Ton alone
go for a movie date just only he and his girl friend
enough.
and you cry
that he refuses to go to the movies with you
at last
Nhai comes after you.
by going to see the same movie over and over again.
He was young back then.
now
I can watch alone.
Don't be fooled.
oh yes
and you?
stop teasing me
otherwise I will exposed your secret.
What are you talking about me?
oh
Inthra, the hot person
Always get mysterious gifts.
but I don't know who.
Why do you want to know?
you are too stupid
you never know.
Wow!
But it's true.
aww
Nine
I thought you are my team?
Have you heard?
No true friends
and permanent enemies
Hey, look at that.
Is there anything I can help?
people.
by the way
Is there anything I can help you with?
Oh no, nothing.
Oh
This isn't the opposite?
Well, Ingfah forgot something.
forgot something
Forgot what?
Forget anything around here.
We'll help you find it.
hmm
found it
Oh, this is an auspicious bracelet.
I've been looking for a long time here.
since I found it
Let's go back guys.
this time we will go back
actually go back.
seem like
We're going to meet them many times
Well, people look cool, right?
people will like it, it's not strange.
You go back to the table to eat snacks.
yes
Ai
wake up
I have to go get the motercycle at P' Sing's bar
Okay, okay.
Don't be lazy now.
You take a look at the love mark.
Is it gone yet?
How does the love mark dissapear in a few hours?
Damn you
What should we do?
Come help me figure it out.
Ai
wake up
You wake up early.
Ai
wake up
I woke up, okay, okay.
K?
hey
It's even more red, Ai
do you have a high collar shirt ?
shouldn't you wear high collar
Are you crazy?
wear like that, Singh knows that.
What do you know?
know you and I
Why?
Why me and you?
If it doesn't help you shut up.
You've been shy a lot lately.
not shy
about cruise
I'm sorry.
It's feel.
Yeah
That's it
stop doing that pervert face
You take off your shirt like this.
How can you not let me look?
I'm going to dress up in the weirdest outfit of my life.
until
You don't dare walk with me.
Let's do this
Go ahead.
No matter how weird you are.
I like you anyway.
and the more I like you
more and more every day too.
So
I haven't changed.
go like this.