[♪♪♪]
PROFESSOR:
Gloves, Kaminsky, gloves.
Lady's a study aid,
not Sharon Stone.
STUDENT:
Yeah, Kaminsky's instincts
are very basic. Ha, ha.
All right, pipe down.
That's enough for this group.
Ever seen a drowning victim?
Tomorrow's future faction day.
Uh, professor?
There seems to be some kind
of anomaly
in the pelvic region.
A penis, perchance?
[ALL LAUGH]
It's not an anomaly,
it's that, uh,
little boys
are created differently
than girls.
[THWACKS]
Slippery is what it is.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[KNOCKING]
PROFESSOR: Come in.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Paula Henning.
Seven hundred
and eighty-three points,
Robert Koch
competition, 99.
Second best score
in the country.
Nice going.
Oh.
So I guess that means I've been
accepted at Heidelberg then?
Yes. All that summer fun
to have to give up
to play with cadavers.
Now, the anatomy course
with Grombek is the best.
There's a lot to learn.
And it isn't easy.
So concentrate.
I was planning to go to Italy.
But then this is,
of course, a--
Great opportunity.
With your talent?
And you want to chase
Italian boys around?
The Italians, they can't keep
their hands off
of you.
Yeah.
[CHUCKLES]
Right you are.
Bye-bye.
Sorry.
Sure.
She's going
to make someone's day.
So?
WOMAN: Well?
[SINGSONG]
Heidelberg.
Yes!
[MAN VOCALIZING]
♪ The place in mind
Is always sweet ♪
♪ It's wonderful ♪
♪ And time to meet ♪
♪ It's a new thing ♪
Hello.
♪ Got to change up ♪
♪ Gotta let go of the past ♪
♪ For a new thing ♪
♪ For some new ground ♪
♪ Only change
will make it last... ♪
[CHUCKLES]
Hi, Grandpa.
Okay, listen for a minute. Your
liver functions are elevated,
your GFR is
less than 20 percent,
and I've just heard
Schutzenberger say they're
hooking you up
for hemofiltration.
Not only that, he's also
thinking of upping
the morphine
to five milligrams an hour.
Are you in a lot
of pain?
Oh, Paula. I've been dead since
Christmas, but no one notices.
They're just torturing me
with the machines
we put in when I was
running this place.
[COUGHING]
What about
your Robert Koch course?
Over 700.
Second best score
in all of Germany.
That's my girl!
And? Heidelberg?
I can't leave you alone
like this.
Ah, come off it.
My favorite granddaughter
is gonna make
her grandfather happy
and become an M.D.
Not some school nurse
or health insurance
bureaucrat.
Like hell.
A physician!
My successor.
You're my pride and joy.
I gotta go, Grandpa.
See ya.
Hey, do a good deed and yank
the plug on your way out.
[LAUGHS, COUGHS]
[SIGHS] Grandpa!
Heidelberg?
Don't worry, Connie. Those
red spots are only pubic lice.
You'll be fine.
Papa, this is a chance
of a lifetime.
Here, use this
when you get home.
You could try and be happy
for me for a change.
I had this idea
that you would join me here.
At least that's
what you said
or am I wrong?
It's that
research program
with Grombek I told you about.
If you make it there, you're
sure to be accepted at any
research institute--
Yes, or end up at the ritzy
clinic of your choice. Well,
making doctors rich and famous
is what human suffering
is all about. Isn't that right?
All I want is
to have the best
possible education--
My son, Kevin.
I told your wife
about his awful cough...
Connie, stay out of there!
Leave me alone!
Yes. Yes, yes, yes!
I want to make it big
even though you think
it's bullshit!
I don't want to end up
in some third-rate...
Go on.
Go ahead.
Finish it.
[SIGHS]
At least take
the blue one along.
You might want to go
out one night.
Mom, I'll be too busy
for that in Heidelberg.
There's nothing wrong
with dressing up.
Get pregnant,
ruin my career.
Thanks.
I'll remember that.
Mom...
Mom, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it that way.
Have you apologized
to your father?
Believe me, I tried,
but he's got this thing
about successful people
being crooks just because
he's never really--
By the way,
I know he can't
stand the guy,
but Papa needs
to visit Grandpa.
He's in pretty bad shape.
[♪♪♪]
Do you promise
to write me?
Oh, Mama, it's gonna be great!
Really great.
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
Where...?
Where am I?
Specimen's awake.
Anesthesia ?
Let's keep
the circulation going.
Two milligrams
of Promidal.
So have you
seen the list?
Mm-hm.
And?
Anybody
interesting on it?
Wh-what's happening?
Some guy from Berlin.
[♪♪♪]
[GASPING]
Oh, yeah, and a Henning.
Pick three.
Henning?
Mm-hm.
Which Henning?
Paula or Pauline.
Excellent grades.
[LABORED BREATHING]
That'll change.
A woman.
Try and sleep
with her
when she gets
to Heidelberg.
[GASPING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey! Don't I know you
from Munich?
Yeah, right.
You're in lab
with the professor.
You mean
the six-handed one? Oh, yeah.
Really. I always
get so damn embarrassed
when he starts to--
I let him have his fun.
I mean, what the hell?
Then you don't have to go
to any of his lousy lectures.
He'd never have the guts
to actually grab a boob.
So we're off
to Heidelberg.
Mm-hm. What, you too?
Hey, we can be roommates.
I bet you the place
is crawling with cute guys.
What am I saying?
Med students?
Well, you never know.
[CHUCKLES]
Excuse me.
MAN:
A doctor!
We need a doctor here!
WOMAN:
Isn't anyone
here a doctor?
Here, hold these.
He just passed out.
Must be the heat.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Easy does it.
Hello? Do you hear me?
Shit.
Hello?
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
Eight, nine, ten, eleven.
[COUGHING]
You okay?
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
Somebody clear
a compartment. Hurry!
We finally know
why we've been studying
all this crap.
David, when the heart
quits like that on you,
it's serious.
Cardiomyopathy
is what it is.
Severe heart failure.
The whole thing's sort of dumb.
Now and then I drop dead,
but otherwise no complaints.
I'm what you call
a textbook case.
If you're nice,
you can have my corpse.
First, we have to make sure
the rest of your equipment
is in good working order.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
This is the 435th specialist
or faith healer I've seen.
We're supposed to be getting
together tonight in some bar.
You can bet all they
get off on is that
it's such a rare disease.
I'm beyond help.
Don't say that.
Modern medicine can--
Here's my cell number.
We hang out
in bars, clubs and movies.
So if you need us...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Well, guys,
thanks a lot.
Goodbye, David.
Ciao.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
Poor David...
He's too young to be
experiencing heart failure.
♪ We've come a long
Long way together ♪
♪ Through the hard times
And the good ♪
♪ I have to celebrate you
Baby ♪
♪ I have to praise you
Like I should ♪
♪ I have to praise you ♪
♪ I have to praise you
Like I should ♪
♪ I have to praise you... ♪
[COUGHS]
Thanks.
So you're both
from Munich?
We'll let you two share
an apartment, okay?
No alcohol,
no dogs or cats,
male visitors
are permitted.
We make great pets,
you know?
[CHUCKLES]
I'm Phil,
by the way,
as in fill her up.
A comedian? Cute.
Come again?
Ah. Homey.
MAN [KNOCKING]:
Hello, anybody here?
All new students report
to the anatomy lab.
In the new wing.
On the double.
♪ I have to praise you ♪
Which way
to the anatomy lab?
Yeah, over there.
Excuse me.
Are you on your way
to the orientation
meeting?
We're going
to the anatomy lab.
Right.
That's it.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Oh, wow.
Spacey.
Maybe we're
too early.
Oh, I'm Paula.
Paula Henning.
Hello, I'm Gretchen.
Gabi.
I go to Tübingen.
Tübingen?
Hey, I used to date
this really cute guy
from there.
We both come
from Munich,
but we just met today.
Uh, I'm completely
nuts or...
I think I saw something,
uh, you know,
uh, move!
It, liked, moved!
That's not very likely.
[LAUGHS]
Of course not.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
So...
Do I know
your friend?
The one from Tübingen?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
Oh, God,
I don't like this.
[♪♪♪]
[SCOFFS]
Ha, ha, ha.
What are we,
scaring the babes?
Is this some Heidelberg
initiation rite?
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
[GABI FALLS]
It can't be.
No way.
It's impossible.
Impossible.
[FLICKERING]
Corpses don't move.
[CRACKING]
Okay.
You're real
and you're dead.
Why would a corpse move?
Muscles contract
when the nerves are stimulated.
And...
nerves react
to electrical impulses.
And impulses can be generated.
You send an electrical
impulse to a nerve fiber
and that makes
the muscle contract,
and you've
got movement.
Hm, got it.
There's always
a scientific explanation.
All you need is a power cable
and if you bundle it,
you can blow
every fuse on campus.
What the hell is this?!
[LAUGHTER]
A Frankenstein movie?
Some of us have ethics,
you stupid jerks.
[LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
One of these days,
I'm gonna get you.
Asshole.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
Excuse me.
They get to have Grombek
all year long
here in Heidelberg.
He can be
really tough on you.
He's a total sadist.
But he's brilliant in his field.
Who do you guys study under?
Well, I studied
under Botticelli in Berlin.
And now I'm doing
my internship
at the Sorbonne.
Huber in Munich.
Kledermann in Emden.
What? There isn't
a university in Emden.
But there's a butcher.
My uncle's a butcher.
He carves like a god.
[LAUGHTER]
You learn the difference
between tripe
and T-bone pretty quick.
You know how expensive
that is?
But, uh,
a doctor is something--
Meat's meat,
and it has its price.
Hearts cost more than livers,
breasts more than liposuction.
The only way to get rich,
and big bucks is what
we're here for, right guys?
[CASPAR LAUGHING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm your local
Heidelberger.
GRETCHEN:
Really?
What'd you do?
Major in steroids?
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, do me a favor
and let me know
next time
you take your clothes off.
[SIGHS]
You know,
I'm really pretty nice.
I know the names of lots
of flowers
and I love to hear
the birdies sing.
[LAUGHS]
But I happen to be
a med student.
Caspar.
Paula.
Henning.
Your grandfather
was dean here, right?
Fundamentals
of Neurological Anatomy.
Heidelberg '57.
That's a cute dimple
you got there.
[PIANO PLAYING]
[PATRONS SINGING ALONG
WITH PIANO]
Hey, looks like
you've been stood up.
I'll get you another one.
The restroom?
Come on.
I'll show you.
In there.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTS UNZIP, URINATING]
[MEN WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY
IN GERMAN]
MAN:
Okay. Go on.
[MEN WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY
IN GERMAN]
Hit her off.
[GASPING]
[♪♪♪]
[PATRONS SINGING ALONG
WITH PIANO]
Students all
drink too much.
Probably puked
all over the floor.
See you, boys!
Bye-bye!
This guy, Hein,
he's gorgeous.
Honest to God,
no matter where
you touch him,
solid muscle.
And he takes himself
so seriously.
It's so cute.
So, what happened?
Do you think
there's any hope for you
and your new boyfriend?
My boyfriend?
You know,
tall, dark
and weird: Caspar.
I mean, it was pretty
obvious that you two--
Oh, man, all you ever do
is talk about men!
It's like you're obsessed.
Jesus, I came here to work,
not sleep around.
What a pity!
[LAUGHTER]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ Na, na, na... ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na ♪
Finally,
it's getting late.
Is he still under?
Mm-hm.
♪ Na, na, na... ♪
Okay.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
We'll make the first
incision here.
Then, we'll work
with the arteries
and expose
the heart laterally.
That's good.
Very good.
[LABORED BREATHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES]
♪ Na, na, na... ♪
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
Help me!
Somebody help me!
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
Dead. What a pity.
We can't use him
anymore.
You hurt?
No, just scratched.
♪ Na, na, na... ♪
Now what do
we do with him?
Pity, our oh so modern
society prefers
to attribute everything
to emotional problems.
The surgeon who cuts out
whatever is sick
is no longer valued.
You see, people,
as I'd like to jest,
would rather die
in perfect health than be cured
by modern medicine.
[LAUGHTER]
Here in the new wing
of the department of anatomy,
you have access
to one of the most modern labs
in the world.
No pain has ever been
alleviated in this room.
No patient ever healed.
What we do here is
establish foundations.
Enhancing the ability
of physicians to save patients
or make their suffering easier
to endure--
The basics of modern medicine.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we consider you the best,
the elite, the future
of our profession.
When this course is over,
a third or even half of you
will no longer be with us
when diplomas are handed out.
Be grateful that we are
so uncompromising.
This strict selection
is the essence
of what we are here for,
and upholds the reputation
this school enjoys.
As you see,
Heidelberg is home
to one of the most
comprehensive collections
of anatomical specimens.
This facility
is for the exclusive use
of scientists and students,
and is invaluable for research
and instruction.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[♪♪♪]
My God.
Fantastic.
Wow.
Are these replicas?
No, no. Genuine human specimens,
plasticized.
All the water and fat
is sucked out of the tissue.
They'll keep forever.
You see that?
Right there.
I see what you mean.
Ewald Henning!
That's my grandpa.
GROMBEK:
Ms. Henning,
we are pleased that
your grandfather's so famous.
But I'm afraid
you'll have to get by
on your own merits.
[♪♪♪]
GROMBEK:
Following this lecture,
you will each be given
the research assignment
on which you must
turn in a paper
at the end of the course.
You will also be given
regular tests.
The first in three weeks.
After which,
the six weakest participants
will have to journey home.
The same holds true
for the second test.
Lectures are held daily
from 7:30 a.m.
until 12:00 noon.
The anatomy department,
lab and library are open
from 6:00 a.m.
to 10:00 p.m.
Your evenings and weekends
may be reserved
for independent study.
♪ New ground ♪
♪ Only change will make
It last... ♪
[GASPS]
PAULA:
David!
[EXHALES]
God, it's been, like,
10 years since
l smoked a cigarette.
In summer camp,
we used to sneak smokes
under the covers.
Camp.
Want to know what I did
there under the covers?
You've got
to be kidding.
But you know what?
It didn't taste any
better back then, either.
[♪♪♪]
Jesus, David's chest was
still covered with bruises
from when I gave him
the heart massage.
GROMBEK:
Magnificent!
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Picture perfect.
Couldn't we just plasticize
the heart and vasculature
and use them as displays?
No.
It's too late to preserve
the structure nicely.
Once decomposition
sets in...
This is highly interesting,
Ms. Henning.
Your acquaintance
is fascinating.
A miracle he survived
as long as he did.
And coupled with these
aneurysms, inoperable.
Perhaps you'd care
to remove his heart?
Unless you feel
it's too much
for a woman to stomach.
[SNICKERS]
You save
someone's life,
and before you know it,
he dies anyway.
We are doctors.
Look, he has cuts
and stabs on his abdomen.
Only medical instruments
are that sharp.
I presume that he was prepared
by a very clumsy deeder.
[SCALPEL CLANGS]
[INDISTINCT WHISPERING]
Asshole.
I refuse to believe
this condition
could've killed
David so quickly.
And his veins here--
Look at the jugular.
His blood
is like rubber.
He didn't have
a blood problem.
He had
a heart condition.
Bingo.
David was
terminal, Paula.
He was
a totally lost cause.
You're just feeling
could've saved him.
We came here to study
anatomy, didn't we?
[WHIRRING]
Want the skull open?
In a minute.
I've got to forget
I knew David
and examine him
like any other patient,
or I can give up
on medicine altogether.
[SIGHS]
I'm going
to check his blood.
[♪♪♪]
Professor Grombek?
Ms. Henning is here.
Thank you.
GROMBEK:
My dear colleague.
Please, come in.
My gosh, this is fantastic!
This one here's
from Central America.
Papilio demoleus.
Wonderful!
So light, so alive.
PAULA:
Um, about David.
I...just want to be sure
I had done all I could.
Well, your reaction was
calm, collected, scientific.
They called it "composure"
in my day.
Very impressive.
Don't you think it
was sort of odd that he--
Both of us realize
that your motives
are personal.
Emotion,
feminine intuition...
Any further involvement
would be...absurd.
But...
Would you like a cup of tea?
Or Mrs. Erhardt
can make us some coffee.
We have cookies
and crumb cake.
I advise you to forget
about your friend.
[SIGHS]
BERNIE:
That is totally not possible.
That's what I mean, Bernie.
I've never seen blood
with such a strange consistency.
Coagulation must've started
before death set in.
It's not just kind of gel-like?
No, it's more...
rubbery-like.
Was your friend,
uh, short, green and looks like
part of the Addams Family?
Addams Family?
Come on. Be serious.
Listen, I need you to run
a lab test on it,
so I'll send you a sample, okay?
Yeah, a tissue sample?
Uh...
Yeah, I'll see
if I can get you one.
Bernie needs fresh meat.
[BERNIE PANTS]
Liver, if possible. And
what's in it for me?
A kiss?
French kiss and a quick feel.
A kiss on the forehead.
Forget about the feel.
Ha, ha, ha.
So long, kiddo.
So long, big guy.
Your dad?
Uh, yeah, I...
You must have a very
close relationship.
No, that was a friend.
Not my boyfriend, but--
Oh, God...
Strictly professional.
Caspar, I happen to--
You must think
you're really hot stuff, huh?
I think you're
really hot stuff.
Come here a sec.
It won't bite.
It's that boy's blood.
Take a look.
Hm.
Never seen anything like it.
Cardiomyopathy--
Yeah, right.
[INSTRUMENTS CLATTERING]
Off to the anatomy lab.
At this hour?
I need a tissue sample.
If I wait 'til Monday,
it'll be too late.
Uh, what was it you wanted?
Oh, dinner and a movie.
Maybe dissect some bowels.
Something romantic.
Okay.
Give me an hour.
I'll meet you at the dorm.
[♪♪♪]
Stupid.
The dead don't look
any scarier at night
than they do in the daytime.
It's just a university building.
[SIGHS]
[HUMMING]
What the?
Huh!
[SIGHS]
What are you doing here?
I was just...
Student?
Uh-huh.
Your name is?
Paula.
Paula Henning.
I just wanted to...
Does the professor know?
Yes.
Yes, of course he does.
In fact he asked me to see
if David number seven...
I'm trying to find out
who had him transferred here
I need to speak
to his physician.
[♪♪♪]
Male. Age 22.
Cardiomyopathy.
Yes, who sent him here?
That's confidential.
Look, I really have to know
who had him transferred here.
[SIGHS]
LAB TECHNICIAN:
It's me.
Just had company.
Uh-huh.
I've got
the tissue samples.
There's something
really weird going on.
I've got to find the doctor
who had David transferred here.
The cadavers all come
from somewhere, don't they?
And the deeder has a little book
and if I could get...
You're a good kisser.
But your jacket smells
of formaldehyde.
Are you coming swimming
with us tomorrow?
[YAWNS]
Fucking corpses, I'm tired.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
PLAYER:
Hey, where you going?
Where the fuck
are they going?
Hey, Gabi, move!
[♪♪♪]
PAULA:
I took part in this competition
and I got...
the second highest score.
Nationwide.
So how'd you manage
to get accepted to Heidelberg?
GRETCHEN:
I got the highest score
nationwide.
You mean the Robert Koch
competition?
The one for seniors?
Hm-mm.
This is the third time
I placed first.
Do you think any
of those bozos
could still get it up
if they knew my IQ
was 50 points higher
than theirs?
PLAYER:
Cut it out!
Gretchen! What about...
Why Hein?
Every Supergirl needs a Superboy
and this one's super.
Hein!
Heiny!
HEIN: What?
Come here!
HEIN:
Now?
Come on,
get over here!
What?
Turn around.
Look at this latissimus?
Beautifully defined.
Erector spinae.
And here.
HEIN:
Come on, Gretchen.
Cut the crap.
Flex, please.
Gluteus maximus.
Sweet, huh?
Muah!
Thank you.
Nothing but shriveled up old
geeks in pathology.
Find one
that's too intelligent
and you could end up
falling in love.
Your friend Caspar's
got a nice bod too. Hmm?
Dig out something nice
in his pants?
Heh. What? He's not my...
Come on all they ever do
is sit around
and talk about
how big our boobs are.
[CHUCKLES]
It's kind of fun to sit around
and talk about dick sizes
in public.
Caspar!
We were just talking about you
and your little friend.
Friend? What do
you mean friend?
Carrot or banana?
[♪♪♪]
PAULA:
Have you ever heard
of a hospital in Heidelberg
with the initials AAA?
CASPAR:
With an exclamation mark?
Hm?
How'd you know?
It's a bunch
of doctors.
Anti-Hippocratic Society.
Where'd you see it?
On a cadaver.
It was branded on a cadaver.
It must have
been something else.
The Anti-Hippocratics
are a thing of the past.
They've been banned.
[CHUCKLES]
I, uh...
Don't you think this
getting a bit corny?
Huh?
You know what I mean!
The lake and stuff
and the sun setting
in Heidelberg.
The birds singing.
[SCOFFS]
What? You think kissing
is corny?
That's not what I said.
Well, maybe it's just
that dead guys
happen to turn you on
more than live ones do.
[SCOFFS]
Am I right?
Or am I right?
Forget it!
So? Is he right?
The nerve of that
son of a bitch.
I never want
to see him again.
Anyway.
AAA is the abbreviation
for
Age Actabile Antihippocrate.
Achieve the achievable?
I couldn't find any specifics.
Except that it's
a secret society.
Sort of a cross between
the Free Masons
and a college fraternity.
With these old rituals,
a lodge, the whole thing.
The point is
MDs always follow
the Hippocratic oath
and live by it.
You know, helping patients.
Healing them. Blah, blah, blah.
The Anti-Hippocratics
are totally into research. Here.
Experimental killing of the few
to ensure the survival
of the many.
Crazy, huh?
And here.
Founded in the 16th century,
it re-emerged
during the Third Reich.
Sporadic incidents
of anti-Hippocraticism
have witnessed in genetics,
artificial procreation,
pharmacology, etc.
One of the centers of
anti-Hippocratic movement
during the early 1900s
and the Nazi era was...
Heidelberg.
Hmm.
And David...
He's the ideal victim
for illegal experiments!
He's a young patient,
a rare disease
at an advanced stage.
His case was textbook!
STUDENT: Shh!
No, shit!
You mean that doctors--
Doctors here in Heidelberg
were conducting illegal
experiments.
I knew it!
I've been having the runs.
I mean a case
of diarrhea like that
has simply got to be
anti-Hippocratic.
Hey, Paula, seriously.
It really itches.
I think someone's branded me
on the ass.
[LAUGHS]
What? Promidal?
BERNIE [ON PHONE]: You got it.
Uh-huh.
Pro-mi-dal. Evil stuff.
Once upon a time
it was a favorite of...
taxidermists.
Plasma protein-based so it
extracts all the salt,
plasticizes the tissue
almost instantly.
The bloodstream would transport
a shot of the stuff directly
into every cell
of his body.
Let it harden and Rover
is set for display case.
Ew!
It was banned.
SPCA and all that crap.
The more you inject
into the subject's body,
the more the blood thickens.
And harder it is
for them to move.
And pretty soon,
statue time.
Paula?
You still there?
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Chemical structure
is totally simple.
An ordinary saline solution
could probably counter it.
Question is how did it get into
your friend's blood?
Yeah, I miss you too.
And your cute ass.
Come again?
What?
[LAUGHS]
That's nasty!
What's going on?
[GIGGLES]
Hm-mm.
Okay.
My father.
No smart ass
remarks this time?
[♪♪♪]
Gretchen, I found out...
Hey, Hein.
Hey, Phil.
[MOUTHING LAUGHS]
We were doing
our anatomy homework.
About David...
I got the histology report back.
Stuff's called Promidal.
GRETCHEN:
Paula's uncovering
a conspiracy.
It's cool.
It's all about doctors
who tattoo their initials
on their patients' asses.
Anti-Hippocratics.
I wish I knew what kind
of experiments
they were gonna do on David.
I need to go back
to the anatomy lab.
Um, sorry for interrupting.
No problem. Phil
couldn't get it up anyway.
[GROANS]
Phil!
It's hormones. Erectile tissue.
Come on, we're all doctors here.
God! Paula.
Hm?
We're gonna go eat
and have another go at it.
You wanna join us?
For dinner, I mean.
Thanks anyway.
And have fun.
I mean, good luck.
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
Uh, professor...
I need to ask you something
Um. Can you imagine why anybody
would want to inject Promidal
into a heart patient?
Promidal live.
Consider that highly unlikely.
I'm not a heart specialist,
but--
But that boy
with the cardiac condition
I took the liberty
of having his blood tested.
Didn't we decide
to forget about your friend?
Uh, what do you mean?
Are you forbidding me...
Don't you have a research
assignment you should
be attending to?
Have you begun to prepare
a histology report?
I thought I'd do it tomorrow
before the lecture.
Oh, by the way,
would you mind very much citing
the differences between
acute myelocytic leukemia
and acute lymphatic leukemia.
CASPAR:
Ow!
It seems you have
cut yourself by accident.
Well, these knives are sharp.
Grombek hates me.
I figured it out.
You're not even good.
You're stuck up
because you're so stupid.
Psh!
[GROMBEK LECTURING]
Cutting yourself like that.
Press down.
GROBEK:
This is where I...
You're good.
With this.
Hm-mm.
Women make great nurses.
[CASPAR MOANS]
I mean, you really know
how to touch a guy.
Hey!
You're so...
Hey, tell me just off the cuff,
is it corny here too?
GROBEK:
Miss Henning!
Are you still interested
in the Anti-Hippocratic Society?
I think I should come over
tonight and visit you.
About 10:30 or 11?
GROBEK:
Gotta break away
from each other.
[FAINT CLAPPING AND CHEERING]
Do you wanna try
some place else?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Yeah, yeah.
GRETCHEN:
So I keep on asking him,
Why the hell are you
cutting the eye out?
I mean the guy's lids
have already turned black
because the body had been
lying around for so long.
[GRETCHEN SLURPS]
And then he's like,
"No, no. This is easy."
Despite the fact that half
the guy's brain was splattered
all over the place from when
he dropped it earlier. Whatever.
[SIGHS]
[SQUISHING SOUND]
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
Ah!
[DRIPPING]
Hey, I know this!
Practice of the early
18th century
as a warning to traitors
who were going to be punished.
Three slits across
the offender's left cheek
with a scalpel.
Three cuts to the throat,
chest and abdomen.
[FOOTSTEPS]
MAN:
Hello.
Don't move!
I got a knife!
[SPEAKS MUFFLEDLY]
Jesus! What are you doing
in my room?
Is Gretchen here? I just wanted
to talk to her cause...
[HEIN SOBBING]
Man, just look at this mess!
Some kind of maniac is trying...
What's the matter, Hein?
Did I hurt you?
No, it's Gretchen.
I don't think
she loves me anymore.
Come on.
So you're having problems
with your relationship.
Gretchen feels really lousy too.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
WAITER: And don't come back!
We don't want your kind in here!
Then keep
your pants on, Grandpa!
Four Seasons.
They even offer to pay me cash.
To leave
the premises immediately.
Can you believe
we got a free meal?
My dessert?
Oh, lover.
You're turning
into a real savage.
But little Gretel only lets
really hard Hansels in.
Is there something
I'm missing here?
Anatomy test.
[LAUGHS]
[ANNA LOOS'
"MY TRUTH" PLAYING]
♪ You poke your nose
While I watch you ♪
♪ I wonder if you want me
To touch you ♪
♪ There's something behind
Your eyes ♪
♪ That makes you so televise ♪
♪ Sex machine is a real
Floor filler ♪
♪ TV screen
Is a serial killer ♪
♪ I've seen it all
But it's not real ♪
♪ It's not like the way
I feel ♪
♪ My feet moving
To your direction ♪
♪ Let me show you
My affection ♪
♪ What comes
After hard core? ♪
♪ What comes after hard core? ♪
[MOANS]
♪ Stop ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Keep quiet ♪
♪ Get down ♪
♪ Relax ♪
♪ Don't move ♪
♪ Just feel my truth ♪
And to think I had a ruptured
prostate on this very table
this morning.
Ugh.
Oh, baby.
Did I say something wrong?
♪ I didn't mean
To make you cry ♪
I'm sorry.
Game over?
♪ I'm sorry ♪
Darn.
♪ Let me sing you a lullaby ♪
Why those things always
so sensitive?
They look so uncomplicated
dissected.
Gretchen.
You know cause
most of the time
women don't even try
to understand men.
I mean, I'm not the world's
most outgoing person.
If you know what I mean.
Uh-huh.
But I--
I still have feelings.
And I'm sensitive.
I know you can't tell
from the way I look.
From being so strong
on the outside.
You're bored.
Should I...
No, no.
You know I really
care a lot about Gretchen.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Oh. Am I...?
Oh, no. Hein was just
getting ready to...
Hmph.
No, really I--
Right, Hein.
Weren't you just--
CASPAR:
I don't want to interrupt.
If you guys have something...
Hein, you can stay
if you want.
CASPAR:
Don't worry about it.
Some other time. See ya.
Is he...
Oh, no, no, no. I should...
Hey, wait a sec!
You were gonna tell me
something about the...
[SIGHS]
[HEIN CLEARS THROAT]
You'll be fine.
What's that?
I had a run in with a cadaver.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, really.
Give my love to Gretchen.
Uh-huh.
I wouldn't want
to make her suffer.
PHIL: Four?
GRETCHEN: Yeah, baby.
You're my fifth
failed attempt.
And to think sex
on the job
is the most normal thing
in the world.
You're an absolute nightmare
for any guy.
Hm.
Poor little Phil.
PHIL:
Ah!
[♪♪♪]
[MOANS]
They're a disgusting bunch
of low lives
and God sent me here
to punish you.
[LAUGHS]
What? Is it already over?
Aah!
HEIN:
Ah, Gretchen.
Such a lovely body.
Such an ugly
little whore at heart.
[HEAVY PANTING]
Ow!
Do you have any idea
how much you've hurt me?
How much I loved you?
Did you think I didn't
have any feelings?
What did you do?
That's it. No more sluts for me.
What did you inject me with?
Sorry, Gretchen.
It's all over between us.
And it's all your fault.
Just so you know,
I gave you 50 milligrams.
It's a pretty
heavy dose.
In fact,
it should kick in any second.
[PANTING]
[SNIFFLING]
How's your blood?
Is it getting rubbery?
Gotcha!
Oh, I get it.
You want out.
Here let me help you.
But I really don't think
you're gonna make it.
Wanna bet on it?
Hey!
If you make it to the threshold,
and I'll let you go. Deal?
Okay, on your mark, get set, go!
Gretchen, Gretchen, Gretchen.
Go! Go! Go!
Yes! Just a few more inches!
She just might make it.
But then...
Aw, too bad.
Wha-- What's happening to me?
[♪♪♪]
You beautiful,
beautiful being.
Don't be afraid.
You see from now on,
you'll be mine.
Muah.
[GASPS]
[LOCK CLICKS,
DOOR OPENS]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[MUTTERING]
[♪♪♪]
Everyday door is open.
Today I can't, closed.
[DOOR RATTLES]
Mr. Gunther?
Come on!
[CALLING INDISTINCTLY]
[CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[MUFFLED VOICES]
We'll see
about that.
What the fuck
is this?
Some kind of student prank.
You two can go now,
clean up later, okay?
We always
clean later.
GUNTHER:
Yesterday I found half
an intestine
under the fucking table.
What a fucking mess.
Fucking students.
Just pray you don't get one of
those fuckers operating
on you someday.
MAN:
Gunther, you think you can
manage just one second...
Have a little respect
for the dead.
GUNTHER:
Aw, fuck.
Okay, stiffs, who wants to get
carved up first?
Gunther, stop.
Number five.
GUNTHER:
Sixteen.
Three.
GUNTHER:
And six.
Hey, it won't open.
GUNTHER:
Have the fucking janitor
fix it later.
We'll take the one
next to it instead.
Hey, what the--
Jesus,
they cut off his head.
[♪♪♪]
[BELLS RINGING]
[BELLS RINGING LOUDLY]
If the Anti-Hippocratics
are trying to scare me off,
then it proves
I'm really on to something.
It's almost like real blood,
it'll never wash out of
the sheets that's for sure.
It's better
than brain matter.
I once ruined
this great cashmere--
Stop putting me on. I mean,
right here in Heidelberg,
there's this
criminal organization.
How does the threat go?
"The next blood
will be your own"?
The rituals and symbols are
ancient enough, David.
But the concept of illegal
and unethical medical research
is anything but antiquated.
Come on.
Planning a co-ed storm bed?
That's something
only Phil could think of.
Where is Phil,
by the way?
Anybody here seen Phil?
Not entirely.
GROMBEK:
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is what makes diverticulosis
such a classic disease
in the western world.
As you can see, radiological
diagnosis will very often result
in random findings at best.
DOCTOR:
Diverticulosis is usually
unassociated with any...
[DOCTOR SPEAKING IN BACKGROUND]
[♪♪♪]
Diverticulosis can also relate
to a form of appendicitis
common among elderly patients.
In some cases,
the physician can detect
a spastic colon
during examination.
It feels almost like a cylinder
in the left lower quadrant.
For now, I wish you all a very
pleasant weekend.
I needn't remind you
of our little test on Monday.
Look on the bright side,
those of you who pass
will have more room to work
and get to cut up
more cadavers.
[STUDENTS LAUGH]
[♪♪♪]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
Hey, Paula.
I want you to know
how much I appreciate
your help and all the time you
took for me yesterday.
You know, it does a lot of good
to know that...
that somebody
really cares about you.
By the way,
I settled things with Gretchen.
Yeah? You did? I thought
she went away for the weekend.
Look, I brought you a present.
PAULA: You didn't have to.
From Gretchen.
You know, Paula,
you should really drop
all this bullshit
about that loser David Rollof.
You're messing
with our research.
David's body was completely
worthless, it was dying.
It was terminal,
it's so obvious.
Paula, I really like you, but...
Mm?
Is this one
of your med-school pranks?
Hein! You crazy fucking psycho!
Quiet down.
We're not alone here.
MAN:
The cellular customer you have
called is unavailable,
or has traveled beyond
the cellular service area.
Please try again later.
The cellular customer you
have--
Mm-hm.
So there's not even a body?
There used to be, but--
And you don't know this
mysterious David's last name?
Or his address?
Or maybe zip code?
Oh, well.
At least we know
he had a brand on him.
It's the secret fraternity,
the "Antihippopota--"
"Anti-Hippocratics."
"Anticraptics."
You've got to understand it's--
What about Gretchen?
Margaret Mulman?
It's been days since--
Come on. So a co-ed didn't sleep
in her bed last night,
what's the big deal?
Hm?
Not exactly a news flash.
What? A severed finger?
[LAUGHS]
Remember last year?
When those med students,
those girls came in?
They reported a headless cadaver
twitching in the anatomy lab.
[ALL LAUGHING]
They used a high voltage wire--
Hey, Paula,
still chasing boogey men?
[♪♪♪]
Gretchen?
Caspar?
Oh, sorry. Is Caspar--
Have you seen Gretchen?
Um, yeah. Maybe she's, uh...
Hello, Paula.
"Dear Gretchen,
trying to reach you urgently."
Paula."
Come. Forget the others.
This is our project.
Okay. See ya.
Have you guys seen Gretchen?
I think I heard somebody
in the anatomy lab.
Gretchen?
Christ.
[♪♪♪]
Gretchen is on table three.
Or was it four?
I'm sick of your stupid jokes,
you psycho.
Where's Gretchen?
Look around. Come on,
you're the curious one.
Have you completely--?
Come you whore! Look for your
fucking whore girlfriend!
Afraid of the dead?
Three or four?
[WHISPERING]
Three, four.
Maybe she's
still alive.
[GASPS]
But then...maybe not.
Heh-heh. Jokes.
Jokes and gags.
Stupid college gags.
All dead.
Grungy, old,
rotting flesh.
Gags. Just joking, Paula.
Huh!
[HEIN LAUGHING]
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC
PLAYING OVER PA]
♪ Na, na, na na... ♪
Paula...
Paula.
Not afraid of me,
are you?
♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
Paula.
Paula!
♪ Na, na, na ♪
Paula...
Wait up.
Paula, wait up!
Don't be afraid.
I just want to talk.
Just talk.
Paula, there's nothing
to be afraid of!
Come on, I was just joking.
Come on Paula, wait!
Paula, I was kidding!
A little bit of joking.
Joking, I was joking!
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
HEIN:
Paula!
[LOUD BANGING]
[GRUNTING]
Hello?
Is anyone here?
[GLASS CHIMING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[♪♪♪]
Don't come any closer!
Sh. Relax,
you're safe here.
The lodge
is off-limits.
The lodge of the
Anti-Hippocratic Society.
You too?
Hmm. Yes,
of course.
The Anti-Hippocratics
are only interested
in the future
of medical science.
Most of us
are unspectacular.
We don't restrict ourselves
to narrow-minded traditions.
You've got psychopaths
with knives terrorizing people!
Loud-mouthed little boys
who like scaring little girls.
Do you really think we
would get any research done
if we paid attention
to ethical principles?
Heidelberg has
a reputation to maintain.
Do you know when we
last won the Nobel Prize?
This is about our leading role
in the medical field.
Funds for research,
commissions from the
pharmaceutical industry.
This is about financing
the education of the elite.
Your little
research assignments...
Where do you think
the tissue samples come from?
Well, I...
I was wondering
about that--
Why don't you ask yourself how
one of these so-called
ethics commissions would feel
about leukemia patients
being tested without their
knowing about it first?
I had no idea--
Of course not.
And who really cares?
And the terminal patient
barely notices.
They all want
to be healed,
but don't want to suffer
the consequences.
Yeah, but the
atrocities committed
by the
Anti-Hippocratic Society--
Oh, my God, Mengela!
So he went awry, like a few
other Nazi physicians.
Go ahead, condemn them.
But no one has ever recognized
the achievements of those men,
especially in
the field of anatomy...
at the time your grandfather
developed Promidal.
What?
Yes, he was grandmaster
of the lodge.
But I thought you knew.
He was here
until the end of the war.
But, my--
Yes, your grandfather.
They were only prisoners,
all critically ill,
all worthless lives.
But they were such
fantastic specimens,
dissected alive!
[♪♪♪]
Honey, you made it,
thank God.
Did someone call you?
Call me?
About your
grandfather.
What's going on?
But he needed to know...
how horrible he was.
Oh, Paula.
We can cut open a body
and examine it down
to the last little cell,
but we can't even come close
to the nature of the human soul.
You mean
it's true?
You love him,
and you hate him.
I've known that feeling
for the last 50 years or so.
[♪♪♪]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
The human specimens
we worked on were
all end-stage
articular mortis.
Two carinomas, one leukemia,
one cardiomyopathy,
all of them
terminal.
As for the other two
aforementioned cases,
I admit to being guilty
of bending lodge rules.
You leave the lodge
out of this.
We're looking at butchery,
the murder of fellow students!
You're a criminal, there isn't
any other word for it.
Yes, I violated the rules
of the Anti-Hippocratic Society
and accept the punishment
that awaits me.
Young man, our lodge
is a service.
It's dedicated
to the furthering and--
What? Dedicated
to occult mumbo-jumbo
to justify forbidden
drug testing?
Just so you can cash in
on the pharmaceutical industry?
The Anti-Hippocratic Society
has always placed itself
above the laws and prevailing
morality of their peers.
It's because of your petty greed
that our ideals are crumbling!
What's that?
You have the nerve--
I know the rules.
What we do
is real research.
Not your bullshit,
by-the-book medicine.
Who gives a damn about the aches
and pains of an old lady
who's gonna be six feet under
in a few months?
Just look at each and every
one of our specimens.
That's what science
is all about:
everlasting research
for mankind!
As his professor
and grandmaster,
I accept
full responsibility.
The jealousy killing has nothing
to do with the lodge.
I'm going to turn the case
over to the police,
despite the consequences...
even to me personally.
You can't--
You can't do that.
Do you hear me?
You can't do that!
You're making a big mistake.
DR. HENNING [ON VOICEMAIL]:
You've reached
the Henning family.
We're not in right now, but
leave a message after the tone,
and we'll get back to you
as soon as possible.
[BEEP]
My name is Grombek.
This is a message
for Ms. Paula Henning.
It's urgent you call me.
Heidelberg, 23-17-96.
Or come to my office
first thing in the morning.
We appear to have a much
bigger problem on our hands here
than we originally thought.
The police, uh--
I need, uh--
I need, uh, help.
Please.
[♪♪♪]
Unh!
[SOBBING]
Argh!
DR. HENNING:
I know I've never been
a very good doctor.
I haven't got your
talent for it.
But, you know,
I've made my peace with it.
But you've got
the talent, Paula.
You've got guts.
You can handle
things differently.
"Come to the specimen room
tonight at 8:00. Grombek."
Hm. Not 'til tonight?
Caspar's up
in our room studying.
Everyone is cramming
for the exam.
Have you seen
Gretchen anywhere?
Nope.
[SOBBING]
[♪♪♪]
Paula, what happened?
Hello.
Gretchen still hasn't shown up,
and my grandfather's--
Come on in.
Didn't Gretchen and Phil want
to go away for the weekend?
Yeah, but it's
just that--
[SOBBING]
Sh. Don't.
[SNIFFLES]
[♪♪♪]
♪ Your eyes ♪
♪ Of love ♪
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
By the way, I wanted
to tell you--
Oh!
[♪♪♪]
Professor?
Professor Grombek?
Hello?
[FOOTSTEPS]
[SCREAMS]
No, no!
You know,
I really loved her.
She's my greatest achievement.
[PAULA SOBBING]
Isn't the human body
fascinating?
Such a clever design...
incredibly intelligent system.
Yet, so breathtakingly
beautiful.
Isn't that why we
went into medicine?
See how brilliant
the colors are?
The flesh is fresh...
as if life were
frozen in time.
Promidal. It's not just used
to preserve rotting flesh.
Look, I was forced to cheat.
I had to use someone else's
carotid artery.
Funny, Gretchen's had this
stupid twist to it.
But here...
her heart.
Fantastic.
And her face...
was meant for me.
When I'm alone,
I can put it on--
[SCREAMS]
[SCALPEL CLATTERS]
Paula, you don't
get it.
Most people don't.
Gretchen will be
beautiful for me, forever.
And you will
be beautiful too.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
Caspar?
That wasn't nice.
I've been looking for you.
Because I wanted to explain...
and then that psycho showed up
and went at you
with a hypodermic.
What, he gave me a shot?
And what a shot.
Quick, Caspar...
Hypertonic saline solution,
10 percent sodium chloride.
Get me an IV.
This is lousy timing,
but I'm not a doctor.
What?
I'm a historian.
I'm doing my thesis
on the Anti-Hippocratic Society,
from its roots to 1945--
You've gotta mix it
up behind the door,
in the cabinet.
Hurry!
All I really wanted
was access to the library.
They don't like outsiders.
In the pack, the bottle
of sodium chloride.
What?
It says "NaCl" on it.
Here you go.
Yeah, I had to blow
my cover at the exam.
But I got all
the information I need.
Tell me, do you think that shot
had anything dangerous in it?
Caspar.
Oliver, actually.
Kaufmann.
Whatever.
Pull out
the plunger, hurry.
Yeah, yeah.
Mm-hm.
All right.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
No, other way around.
Like this? It reminds me
of the movies.
Oops!
And then get
the air out.
Yeah.
Ah, okay.
Show me
your behind--
No, an IV.
Intravenous, like junkies
in the movies.
No, I can't do this.
Caspar, give me the saline--
the saline solution,
or else I'll die.
Please, hurry.
Go into the vein
at a low angle.
Oh.
[♪♪♪]
Not bad
for a historian, Caspar.
Oliver.
Just in case, don't you think we
should call the hospital?
Tell me, what was that Promidal
doing in your medicine cabinet?
OLIVER:
Promi-what?
Promidal...
It's the stuff they've been
using to kill people.
Caspar?
It's...
our bathroom.
It's my deodorant too.
What the hell?
Hey, guys.
I'm not a med student.
I'm only interested in history.
Look at these.
They were all drawn
by Paula's grandfather.
A cross-section
of the sex act.
One could call this
the "eternal hard-on."
Or, to be precise,
half a hard-on.
[EASY-LISTENING MUSIC
PLAYING OVER PA]
I only injected three
units into you.
I'd say you've got
about four hours left,
provided you hold still
and don't move.
We even added pain-killer.
Wow, you being
a med student and all,
it must be pretty
interesting, huh?
Just think, you could watch
yourself being dis--
Heh-heh. Want
a hash cookie, huh?
Wow, if you catch
a buzz beforehand,
it could really
make your day, heh-heh!
So did you fuck her too?
Your little whore?
Who, Gretchen?
Hey, hey, enough
with the jokes.
Quit feeling me up.
You're hardly in a position
to be making dumb jokes, Caspar.
Ooh! Oh!
Oh, my God!
You impotent asshole!
Shut your mouth, or I'll slit
your vocal cords.
LUDWIG:
What are you doing?
HEIN:
I'm taking care of
this arrogant son of a bitch.
OLIVER:
Bunch of fucking maniacs!
I don't believe--
Shut the fuck up, asshole!
LUDWIG:
Will you shut the fuck up?
It won't do you any--
[♪♪♪]
OLIVER:
What the fuck?
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[GLASS BREAKS]
[SCREAMS]
OLIVER:
NaCl, you asshole!
N-A-C-L!
Would somebody please
sew me back up?
You're all fucking crazy!
[♪♪♪]
HEIN:
Cock-a-doodle-doo,
cock-a-doodle-doo...
She's got blood on her shoe.
[SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
[♪♪♪]
[PAULA SCREAMING]
[GROANING]
Paula?
Paula!
[♪♪♪]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING SOFTLY]
[PAULA GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
Just joking, asshole.
Hi.
Well?
What is it?
It's all still there,
don't be such a sissy, Caspar.
Who knows what kind
of permanent damage coulda--?
[♪♪♪]
Besides, my name
is Oliver.
Paula...
Don't be afraid.
I'll heal you.
I'm a doctor.
[GASPS]
You're not
even certified yet.
How corny.
[♪♪♪]
[MAN SINGING IN GERMAN]
GABI:
You know, it's enough
to make you sick.
STUDENT:
Ludwig was always
a little off-the-wall.
But Hein?
Well, uh, Hein was
actually, you know...
brilliant!
Uh, a genius.
Yeah, some genius.
Sure.
Did you see what
happened to her?
I mean, Gretchen...
She was plasticized.
I know.
Absolutely brilliant.
Apart from that, he was
a pretty nice guy...right?
Ha, ha. Especially
at the lodge meetings.
It's kinda sad
about the lodge.
I'm going to a big emergency
hospital in Berlin.
I hear the lodge is
pretty cool there.
They do anesthesia experiments
on patients, don't they?
Mm-hm.
What about you?
Oh, I'll be taking
over my father's practice.
Private practices aren't subject
to a whole lot of inspection,
so there's more room
to, uh, play around.
[BOTH LAUGH]
So has it been decided
who will be taking over
for poor old Grombek?
Maybe Stievers.
And? Is he also...?
Heh-heh. Tradition.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Morning.
GABI:
Good morning, deeder.
How are you today?
Same as
every day.
[SABRINA SELTUR'S
"ALLES" PLAYING]