Good evening.
What's your name?
I am Riri.
Sis, this is Asih.
Who is Asih?
I have to get home.
You call her "kuntilanak."
I know her as...
Asih.
37 YEARS BEFORE DANUR
Rain, rain, go away
It's raining in the village
And it's cloudy here
Who's the little girl in a veil?
Take a glance at her, and you will stumble
Oh, oh
Sweet girl
Bathing in the river
Her hair is all wet
If you don't pray or fast
You will be tortured in your grave
You've put together the crib.
There's still a month to go, right?
I know.
But Andi can't wait.
He said this might make the baby
come out earlier.
He's funny.
Ita!
Where did you get that?
It's from my colleague.
What do you think?
That thing looks older than me.
You're funny, Mom.
Let's use it for now.
-We can get a new one on my next payday.
-Okay.
Mom!
Please don't exert yourself.
Just ask me
and let me pump the water for you.
Okay?
There, it's full.
Come on.
Mom.
Don't you need a towel in the bathroom?
Thank you.
Ita.
Don't carry heavy things.
-Please ask me to carry them for you.
-Okay.
I forgot to bring them in.
-That's okay, Mom.
-Now, let's eat.
Tonight is my turn
to do the neighborhood watch.
I've passed two times already.
I should definitely do it tonight.
Take an umbrella.
Yeah, the weather is a bit strange today.
It's raining, but it's warm.
They call it the rain of the dead.
Mother, people die everyday.
And babies are born everyday, too.
Here.
Thank you.
THURSDAY, SEPTEMBER 4, 1980
SATURDAY, OCTOBER 4, 1980
THE BIRTH DAY OF AMELIA
Honey?
Mom?
Good.
One more time.
You're almost there.
Breathe.
Hold it. Take a deep breath.
Take a deep breath.
One more time.
The baby is almost here.
-You can do it.
-Push a little more.
A little bit more.
God, give her strength.
I can see the baby.
Keep pushing.
A little bit more!
Ita, I'm off to work now.
Bye, Amelia.
-Peace be upon you.
-And upon you, peace.
-Bye, Mother.
-Drive safely.
Let me take her out.
Morning sunlight is good for her.
-Here we go, baby.
-Thanks, Mom.
Don't keep her out in the sun
for too long, please.
My baby.
Mom?
The sun is already high.
We shouldn't keep Amelia in the sun.
It's too hot for her.
But I thought
I pushed her stroller up here.
You must've forgotten.
Ita?
Yes, Mom?
What is it, Mom?
I heard someone humming a song.
Was it you?
Have you taken your medicine?
-I'm not sure.
-You're not sure?
Let's check your schedule.
Thank you, but you shouldn't have.
Not at all.
My daughter is too old
to play with dolls, anyway.
Should I be concerned
that Amelia was born a month early?
Don't worry.
According to the Quran,
as long as your pregnancy
and breastfeeding period
totals to 30 months.
That means you must breastfeed your baby
for about two years.
By the way,
it's better not to put
your baby's crib near the window.
Why is that?
Spirits can peep from outside.
Until your baby is 40 days old,
you should always keep a close eye on her.
Don't take her outside for too long.
Especially at dusk.
When I was assisting a childbirth
in the neighboring village,
there was a rumor of a woman
committing suicide.
Creepy, right?
And what's worse,
they couldn't find her body.
They said before taking her own life,
she killed her own baby.
Please, I don't want to know the rest.
Please, never forget to put
a pair of scissors under your pillow.
So evil spirits won't come near.
Have you heard the knocking sounds
of the utility poles at night?
That means a wise man is walking by.
Nobody knows who he is, or how old he is.
Nobody knows where he comes from.
The people from the neighboring village
call him "Abah."
Abah?
They say he knows what happened
to the spirit of that woman.
If the number of knocks is greater
than the time of night,
then a spirit is present.
It makes my skin crawl.
Oh, oh.
My sweetie pie, how are you?
How is she today?
Thank goodness,
she's been very sweet all day.
What a good girl.
My sweet baby.
Rain, rain
Go away
It's raining in the village
And it's cloudy here
Who's the little girl in a veil?
Take a glance at her, and you will stumble
Oh, oh, sweet girl...
If you don't pray or fast
You will be tortured
In your grave
Mom, bring her in!
It's almost dark.
You have to bring Amelia inside.
I was just about to bring her inside.
A baby shouldn't be outside at dusk.
Ta...
please don't raise your voice
at my mother again.
I know, I'm sorry.
I was afraid
something might happen to Amelia.
I got you. My sweetie pie.
Ta.
Why did you put a pair of scissors
under the pillow?
Mrs. Sekar said
it will ward off evil spirits.
You're just being superstitious.
I'm not being superstitious.
I can feel something weird today.
Have you buried Amelia's placenta?
Not yet. I didn't have time this morning.
You shouldn't delay that kind of stuff.
You're putting her life in danger.
Do it tonight.
I think Amelia has a fever.
She's a bit warm.
A little bit of crushed shallots
on her forehead will do.
Bury the placenta now.
I don't want anything to happen to Amelia.
You haven't buried it?
All right, I'll do it.
What has her fever got to do
with burying the placenta?
Don't forget to say a prayer
when you bury it.
Yes, Mom.
You're still up?
I can't get enough breastmilk for her.
Did you eat the sweet leaves
I boiled for you yesterday?
Don't worry.
Mom...
I'm sorry for raising
my voice at you earlier.
I understand your concern.
Don't worry about me.
I'm going to wash myself before praying.
Ita?
Ita...
did you just come from the kitchen?
No. But I'm about to go to bed.
But I saw you passing the bathroom.
I thought you came from the kitchen.
No, Mom. I was here the whole time.
I'm going to bed now.
Don't forget to take your medicine.
I'm going to keep this doll in the closet.
She won't play with it, anyway.
She's too young for dolls.
Okay.
-Honey.
-Yes?
I think Mom's dementia is getting worse.
Well...
Just bear with her.
She is, after all, a grandmother, right?
There's nothing we can do.
Let's sleep.
I'm afraid that Mom...
Amen...
Amen!
Oh, my God.
Rain, rain, go away
It's raining in the village
And it's cloudy here
Who's the little girl in a veil?
Take a glance at her
And you will stumble
That's my baby!
I am dead serious.
I saw a woman last night.
Please ask the UstÄd to come.
Mom, you told me you thought
you saw me walking by you.
-When was that?
-You don't remember?
Ita, calm down.
You're just being paranoid.
I'm off to work.
Take care of your mom, Amelia.
Bye, Mom.
Ita!
Mom!
What happened, Ita?
RAIN, RAIN, GO AWAY
What is this, Mom?
Mom and I heard
a woman's voice singing that song.
Mom wrote it down in her schedule book.
So, you also feel there is
something wrong in this house?
You have to believe us.
What a slow night.
Just my luck.
I'll just be catching a cold tonight.
I'll definitely need someone
to scratch my back.
If it goes on like this,
I'll become as thin as a skeleton.
What's that sound?
That's odd.
That sounds like...
You startled me!
You look as white as a ghost.
Or did you just see one?
You see the goose bumps
on the back of my neck?
I'd rather not, thank you very much.
I heard noises before you came.
Odd noises.
Like a baby crying?
Mr. Andi's wife
just gave birth a few days ago.
No, not that. I heard chicks cheeping.
Chirp... chirp... chirp...
Mr. Andi must've buried
the baby's placenta in their yard.
Of course. It's our culture.
Where else?
In a volleyball court instead?
Are you mocking me?
They say if you hear chicks chirping
near where a baby's placenta is buried...
that means a female ghost is present!
Oh, my God!
-You startled me, Mom.
-What's wrong, Andi?
I saw the woman that Ita saw.
I believe you now, Mom.
Is that the same woman that you saw?
Oh, God.
Why is she haunting us, Mom?
I have no idea.
Please go to the mosque
and ask the ustad about it,
first thing in the morning.
Amelia? Amelia!
Amelia! Amel!
Amelia!
I've reported the kidnapping
to Mr. Sarwono.
And he said he'll report it to the police.
Our daughter was not kidnapped
by a living human!
What did the ustad say?
Mrs. Sekar said there's a man
who knows this stuff.
You have to go find him.
MIDWIFE
SEKAR NURMALA
Abah?
Her name is Kasih.
A name too beautiful
for the ghastly appearance that you saw.
No one knows exactly when...
her name became Asih.
Maybe...
when she left the village
to work as a babysitter in the city.
Only to return home with a baby,
born out of wedlock.
She was then disowned by her parents.
The villagers also cast her
out of their village.
That poor woman
took her own life
after she killed her baby.
Tonight...
marks the seventh day...
since she lost her baby.
But she had been in this house...
since the night you gave birth
to your baby.
Mom?
But can we still find my baby?
You!
You have something that belongs to her.
The comb.
Here.
Now I need some candles.
Please don't make any noise.
I need total silence to listen.
Actually...
you don't need to hold my hand.
Thank you.
Asih...
I've opened the door for you
to communicate with us.
I summon you.
Please come, Asih!
Stay here.
Please pray.
Silently.
Asih, stop playing around!
The father, come with me now!
Move!
Keep praying.
Start praying now.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
Your baby's cries.
She's behind the tree.
Thank God.
Mom, we found Amelia.
Where's Ita?
Ita?
Ita? We found Amelia.
Please take her to bed.
I'll walk Abah home.
Mom, let Ita and Amelia rest.
Rain, rain
Go away
It's raining in the village
And it's cloudy here
This is the smell of danur.
Asih!
Who's the little girl...
In a veil?
Take a glance at her...
And you will stumble
This is my baby!
No, Asih! Your baby is in heaven now.
Give me back my baby!
Your baby's not here, Asih.
Please, spare this woman.
She hasn't done anything to you.
Listen to me, Asih.
I want my baby!
Oh, my God!
-Oh, God!
-Oh, my God!
-Ita? Amelia!
-Oh, my God. Ita!
-Abah!
-Follow me!
My God, Ita!
Asih! Forgive those people.
Forgive your past.
I seek forgiveness from Allah, Ita.
Forgive yourself, Asih.
Go in peace. Leave!
You have to let go of the past.
Let your baby go.
Forgive yourself!
Forgive yourself. Go in peace.
Enough! Leave the woman alone!
-Leave her body! Leave her alone!
-You love Amelia.
-I seek forgiveness from Allah, Ita!
-Leave her body!
There's no God but Allah.
Allah the Almighty.
I seek forgiveness from Allah, Ita.
You love Amelia!
-Be strong, Ita.
-Leave her body!
-Oh, God.
-Oh, my God.
Thank you, Abah.
We are forever in your debt.
The most important thing is
you have to forgive Asih, all of you.
What about the comb?
Stick it in the ground
under the big tree over there.
I should go.
-Peace be upon you.
-And upon you, peace.
May you rest in peace.
37 YEARS LATER
Let's play under the tree.
What is that?
Stay here.