Lord Arai.
- Lord Arai.
Right this way.
You're early.
You're on time.
Very samurai of you.
Welcome to the House of Arai.
It's a pleasure to finally meet you.
I've never been in the presence
of a witch before.
I figured it was urgent,
since we are breaking
a 300-year-old protocol.
But I must say, I never expected
the House of Arai to be here,
so far from home.
Well, despite its appearances,
Budapest is the crossroads
of East and West.
Setting up here is--
Unnecessary?
Well, times have changed, Hirano.
We have both adapted to survive.
Sake?
Sake.
To trust.
So, what is this pressing matter?
Yurei is here,
and he intends to destroy all samurai.
But it can't be.
And I fear betrayal from one of our own.
We need your help, Hirano.
-With what?
-The Tengu Sword.
What?
The Tengu Sword was split,
so neither samurai nor witch
could abuse its power.
We have to unite them again.
And Yurei knows that
if we unite the sword,
it's the only thing that can stop him.
If that were true,
then he'll come after us.
And even more reason
we should never be in the same place.
Uniting the sword is not the answer.
If you can't protect your Warrior Blade,
then pass it on to another descendant.
What you suggested is no longer an option.
Yurei has killed all the others.
I am the last descendant of the 47 Ronin.
Suppose I believe you.
Are you saying
if I give you the Witch Blade,
you intend to fulfill the prophecy?
We can unite the blade,
and we can fulfill it.
Together.
Trust, Hirano.
The future of our two people
can begin in this room
if we work together.
How good is your magic?
How good is your sword?
Let's find out.
Yurei.
Sorry about your friend.
The last descendant.
It must be hard carrying all that weight.
Your whole life predetermined
just because of your blood.
Go fuck yourself.
I still feel it.
There's another.
-Ooh!
Sorry. Annoying tourist. Sorry.
Oh.
Of course his name is Richard.
Oh, look. It's the geishas.
Anyone need a coffee run?
Onami.
Oh, uh-- Lord Nikko.
Lord Okoro.
Lord Maeda.
Lord Shinshiro.
Lord Nikko.
As you all know,
the House of Arai has fallen.
Lord Arai was a brother to us all.
We must investigate what happened
and figure out our next moves.
What's there to investigate?
Arai is dead.
Yurei and Hirano are of the same blood.
Arai made a big mistake trusting a witch.
Unless Hirano was betrayed as well.
Why would Yurei kill one of his own?
Maybe Hirano refused to give up
the Witch Blade.
Whatever happened between Arai and Hirano,
we still have to contend with
the prophecy.
The Blade of the 47 Ronin,
fortified by magic and valor,
will be wielded by a true descendant
to defeat an evil borne from the past.
Arai was the last descendant.
He died, and the prophecy died with him.
The Record Keeper has seen another
who can fulfill it.
Lord Ikeda, are you still seeking counsel
from flimsy fortune tellers
and charlatans?
Come on.
Some of us respect our sacred traditions.
The Keeper had a vision
of another descendant.
A young American woman
here to collect her inheritance.
He saw the Warrior Blade in her hands.
You put your faith
in an outsider, Lord Shinshiro?
Oh, and a woman, no less.
Samurai blood is strong.
But sharing blood doesn't mean
she's bound to our cause.
We need to convince her
to honor Lord Arai's legacy.
"Honor."
I lost a good friend, Lord Shinshiro.
A brother, huh?
So you talk about honor. Uh-uh.
I am here to avenge him!
Avenge.
So, while you were busy, uh,
reading scrolls...
...my clan invested in modern weaponry, hmm?
We can protect ourselves
by finding and destroying the blade.
But we have sworn to protect it.
Keep your strays in line, Lord Shinshiro.
My apologies.
But if brute force were the solution,
we would not have devoted lifetimes
to the prophecy.
Guns do not defeat magic.
Let us take this evening
to think about it.
We can put it to a vote tomorrow.
Well, I hope you all will
come around by then.
Three, two, one, go!
-Whose face are you picturing?
-No one's.
Fucking Nikko
and his cock sucking bully.
Oh, so that's why you are so distracted.
I'm not distracted.
Look, here's a delicate situation.
Oh, a delicate situation?
Yeah, let's blow this shit up!
Onami, that's not the answer.
I'm just gonna find
the last descendant myself.
-Oh, no. She's plotting.
-She'd better not,
'cause Lord Nikko
wants her to stay out of it.
Yes, as geisha,
we give the men what they want.
We're onna-bugeisha.
Anything men can kill, we can kill better.
Stop provoking her,
or she'll end up like Reo.
Reo was protecting me. He was set up.
Maybe, but he's a Ronin now.
Oh, my gosh. Mai.
He can help me track down the descendant.
You think Reo would still help
even after being kicked out?
Yeah. Reo's a great tracker,
and he wants back in.
Oh, yeah. He would do anything for you.
I tagged our prophecy girl.
Tracking strangers seems highly illegal.
She didn't feel me tag her,
so it's not my problem.
Besides, we're in
the criminal crossroads of the world.
Budapest once had
a bad reputation for smuggling,
-but certain clans have histori--
-Spare me the history lesson.
God, you were never any fun.
You never listen.
-Know-it-all.
-Deviant.
-Teacher's pet.
-Flake.
Are you out past your curfew?
Come here.
Admit it. You missed me, didn't you?
Shut up.
Look at you, all grown up and shit.
-How'd you find her?
-Oh, straight to business then?
No "Hi, Reo. It's good to see you!
I missed you! I'm so glad you're alive"?
Geez.
These boring-ass samurai
have been clearly rubbing off on you.
You mock them,
and yet you secretly follow them
to their emergency summit?
Listen, I'm just looking out for you.
And the old man.
How is Shinshiro?
He misses you.
Yeah, right.
Luckily for you, I come bearing intel.
Hey, Rachel.
One Reo Special
and whatever she's having.
I'm not here to drink.
Make that two.
- Sure thing.
-So, listen,
me and the Record Keeper, we're like this.
Well, we've never really met in person,
but other than that, like this.
So I asked him about this prophecy girl.
Turns out she's got
quite the background check.
We should probably engage
before she gets thrown in jail.
Our prophecy rests in the hands
of a criminal?
Hey, now, let's give her a chance.
Former criminal.
Who's been trying to hock
some shady goods in a hurry.
She wants to sell
an ancient legacy for a quick buck?
Hey, student debt gives no fucks.
Why here?
Do you know how much
these people will pay for collectibles?
Look, the Record Keeper hacked
her emails and found a deal she made
for an online buyer
looking for an ancient samurai artifact.
As a matter of fact...
deal's going down right now.
Nero on Fire?
Is that shit stolen?
You don't even know me like that.
This is actually the one thing
I legally acquired.
I'll come back later.
Dude! What the fuck?
Oh, shit. She's on the move.
Let's cut her off.
Oh, fuck!
Stop running!
-You need to listen.
- Onami.
Uncle.
So oddly muscular.
Reo?
Lord Shinshiro.
Of all my apprentices, I chose only
the onna-bugeisha to join this trip.
To follow and observe this mission,
not recklessly lead your own.
But I found her--
the last descendant of the 47.
That was never your responsibility.
You should have come to me.
Or have I lost your trust?
I'm sorry.
Yo, does anyone wanna tell me
what the fuck is going on?
-Language.
-I tried to explain. You wouldn't listen.
Yeah, I typically don't stop and listen to
people chasing me with swords, asshole.
-Language!
-You're just mad I had you.
Keep telling yourself that,
knockoff Hermione Granger.
-We were trying to save your life.
-"We"?
Who the hell are these freaks anyway?
These freaks were sent to stop you
from fulfilling an ancient prophecy.
Look, I don't know what kind of con
you guys are running. Respect, but pass.
I am Lord Shinshiro.
May I ask your name?
Oh, uh--
Sorry that I didn't introduce myself,
Lord Shinshiro.
Um, I am Lord Go Fuck Yourself.
Her name's Luna.
Luna.
Did you collect your father's sword?
Why? What's it worth to you guys?
Your father was samurai.
One of the best.
A man with a great destiny.
Charming story about the guy
who knocked up my mom and ditched us.
Do you guys wanna bid
on the blade or what?
That blade is worth more
than money could buy.
Wow. Okay. Price just went up.
Luna, there is a lot about your family
that you need to know.
But not here.
We can talk at the safe house.
I'm definitely not following you
to a second location, dude.
Luna, you need protection.
You cannot be on your own.
Well, I've been on my own for years,
so I don't think I need the protection
of a John Wick fanboy.
-We should go.
-What the fuck?
Language.
You--
Just-- Just come with me.
We're just gonna leave
a beheaded dude on the ground?
I am sorry.
For what?
You had to do what you had to do.
Maybe I needed to learn the hard way
how to keep my temper in check.
Lord Nikko's pupil baited you,
and now he picks on Onami.
Small men pick on easy targets.
Small men pick on those
who do not yet know their own power.
They hope to snuff out your light
before it outshines them.
I will not let that same mistake
happen twice.
What the hell is this place?
It's a samurai safe house.
Each family has their own
underground network across the world.
Wow. Fancy.
Has this place got a bathroom,
or should I just go piss in a corner?
Follow me.
What are you, my PO?
Just tell me where it is.
What, you think ninja are gonna
ambush me in the bathroom?
Have you been ambushed
by a ninja in the bathroom?
Jesus!
-Ninja are patient, relentless.
In ancient times, they'd infiltrate
entire families for decades
just to strike when least expected.
Okay, well,
thank you for the history lesson.
I'm just making sure you stay alive
to fulfill the prophecy.
Oh, I haven't agreed to anything yet.
You know, your legacy is a privilege
some of us would Kill for,
and you're treating it like shit.
If you want this blade so bad,
just buy it from me.
Buy it? We need you to wield it.
First, we have to make it to the vote.
Hurry up. It'll be daybreak soon.
-You got something right there.
-Aw, thanks, princess.
Isn't that Lord Okoro?
It appears to be lockdown protocol.
Do you think they would attack
a hotel full of samurai?
Who's "they"?
-They probably discovered our location.
-Who the fuck is "they"?
-Ninja!
-Language!
You know what? Screw this.
You gotta be kidding me.
Thank you for meeting me early.
What's on your mind?
I'm concerned with your perspective
on the future of the samurai.
You asked to meet early to tell me that?
-I think we should--
-Ikeda.
However the vote goes, I trust it will be
for the greater good of all samurai.
You can't just go off on your own.
You said I'd be safer with your crew,
and clearly I'm not.
-Come with us.
-No. I'm out.
Getting a cab to the airport.
There's no place that's safe
while you have the blade.
-Are you always this dramatic?
-We're trying to save--
Holy shit.
We need to get you to safety.
Please, just listen to me.
Protect her at all costs.
Who are you?
-Luna! Let's go!
Think you broke it, dude.
Whoo!
Ikeda?
Keeper is here?
Are you sure?
No, I just love
creepy abandoned warehouses.
Relax. The clans rented this space
while they're in town.
What the fu-- frick is a Keeper?
The Record Keepers are an ancient group
of samurai prophets.
They preserve the records of history
and see glimpses of the future.
Oh, okay. But this one's home base
is just where high-school kids score weed.
We should head to a safe house.
We will, but we need some answers first.
Be aware.
-Remember?
-I remember her, yeah.
-Dude, uh, yeah. Crazy.
Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt
your energy drink commercial,
but we're looking for a guy named Dash.
-Whoa, Jesus!
-You must be the bodyguard.
We're looking for the Keeper.
My apologies, Lord Shinshiro.
Follow me.
♪ Swordplay ♪
♪ When we clash, let the hammer fly ♪
♪ Forty-seven warriors, a samurai ♪
♪ Dead before the sun
I look you in the eyes ♪
♪ At the hands of my katana
Meet your own demise ♪
♪ Know the fury ♪
♪ When sword upon sword
Decide the fate of the kingdom ♪
♪ Songs about a warrior
The villagers sing 'em ♪
♪ Challengers are fallin'
Just as fast as they bring 'em ♪
♪ A thousand throwing stars
Precision when a samurai sling 'em ♪
♪ Death dealers
Snatch your heart out your chest ♪
♪ Till everyone turns cold
Immortal breath stealers ♪
♪ Slicing through the enemy
Poison with no remedy ♪
♪ Till you reside in hell
Eternity with no amenities ♪
♪ The Ronin, everybody drop
Look how we zone in ♪
♪ Know what's going on when we get going ♪
♪ It's bloodshed
Leg, arm, arm, leg, head ♪
♪ Opposition fatal
They coughing up red ♪
So you're the one
who's been supplying us with information.
Yep. I'm Dash.
And this is my mobile record room.
Home to all your spy...
...hacking...
...researching needs.
-I'm Reo.
This place is sick.
Finally. Thank you.
Come, come, come, please!
♪ Tell 'em not to cry
Tell them haters give it up ♪
♪ 'Cause we moving too fast
Speed it up ♪
♪ Used to be broke
Now I'm in a Lambo truck, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ In my ride
Backing up... ♪
-Ooh.
You must be Prophecy Girl.
Yeah, yeah. I would love if--
if you could tell me what that means.
The Blade of the 47 Ronin,
fortified by magic and valor,
will be wielded by a true descendant
to defeat an evil borne from the past.
Am I supposed to know
what any of that means?
You see,
prophecies are kinda tricky to interpret.
For instance, the valor part.
The Tengu Sword is the Witch Blade
and the Warrior Blade fused together.
You have the Warrior Blade.
We're searching for the Witch Blade.
Okay.
And the--
The "evil borne from the past" part,
is that Onami?
That's Yurei.
He's the descendant of Mizuki.
She was the witch slain by Kai.
One of the original 47 Ronin.
And you, Luna,
are the last descendant of the 47
and the only one who can kill Yurei.
Okay, let's just pretend for a second
that I believe any of this.
How do you guys know
that you have the right person, right?
This sounds pretty important.
How do you know I am the last descendant?
Because I've seen it.
Uh--
Dude, are you okay? Are you--
On the next blood moon,
Yurei will unite the two blades,
which will unleash
the full power of his magic.
He won't stop until the bloodline
of the 47 Ronin is extinguished
and all samurai are destroyed.
-Here.
O-Okay, what-- what if we melt it down?
Right? Then nobody can get to it.
That is impossible.
Only magic can reshape it.
Which gives us two choices.
Either you fulfill the prophecy
and kill Yurei with the united blades or--
Or he kills me. Yeah.
And then nothing will stop him
from wiping out all samurai.
Okay.
So if I understand correctly,
we just have to find this Witch Blade,
unite it with the one I have,
and murder this Yurei guy
before the next blood moon.
-When is that?
-Five days.
From-- From now?
My flight leaves in two, so...
-Oh, I'm starving.
-Mmm.
I'm not able to get in touch
with any of the other lords.
All their trackers are offline.
Except for yours.
You put a tracker on me?
-Thought it'd be a good idea--
-You didn't ask!
Where is it? Take--
Maybe that's a good thing.
You did good, Reo.
Thank you.
Nikko's tracker went down at the hotel,
right as the attack went down.
Maybe he didn't make it out.
Do you think the ninja got them all?
Hopefully it's just that
their safe houses block my tracker.
We should stay here
and call for reinforcements.
We cannot leave
the prime houses unprotected.
What if that's what Yurei wants?
Lure us to our safe house,
so he can strike us all down like Arai?
I'll search for the lords myself.
Then they will help us
hunt for the Witch Blade.
We should stay together.
-Take the fight to Yurei.
-She's not ready for the fight yet.
Do you think she will learn
how to swing a sword in five days?
Yes.
She will learn
because she will have a great master.
You.
Me?
No way. I'm just an apprentice.
Not anymore.
You have been leading this mission
the whole time.
Now it is official.
And you will help train Luna as well.
So, you're leaving me in charge?
I'll be back as soon as I can.
-But it's too dangerous to go alone.
- I'll be fine.
I'll clear the safe houses.
You can use them, but don't stay too long.
Keep the Warrior Blade on the move.
So if you're putting me in charge,
then I say you take bodyguards.
One bodyguard.
Fine. Mai?
Let's do it.
Uncle!
Be careful.
You too.
If I do well in training,
do I have to dress like Onami?
Don't worry. You'll never do that well.
-What, you don't know the code?
-He must have changed it.
How the hell are we supposed to get in?
All right.
Looks like we go analog on this one.
-We are not breaking in.
-You got a better idea, Cho Chang?
We don't have time for this shit.
Just let her do her thing.
Fine.
Nice.
You're welcome.
Before you can strike,
you must be able to listen.
Ninja live in the darkness.
-They thrive in it.
They will strike from the shadows,
so you must learn to hear them coming.
By the time you see them,
it will already be too late.
All right. Your turn.
Just stick with the stabs.
Very simple, ladies.
First one to hand it to me wins.
Three, two, one, go.
Take a deep breath.
-What do you hear?
Dude, I hear five o'clock traffic.
-Are you listening?
-I am trying.
You must hear through the noise
and listen to what is really important.
-I just hear angry Hungarian people.
How are you the answer to our problems?
-Are you listening?
Dude, that blew out my eardrum.
My arms tensed, reared back and swung.
Plenty of warning
if you were truly listening.
Not bad.
Damn.
That samurai blood is no joke.
Pretty sure it's the New Yorker side.
-What the hell?
-Heard that one?
Yeah, I heard her sword
go straight for my trachea.
You heard the blade cut through the air.
But did you hear the scabbard shift?
The sword slide?
What's it like, anyway?
Being a real samurai?
-I'm actually a Ronin.
-What's that?
A master less samurai. It's what happens
when you break one rule too many.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh.
Guess we can't all be
prim and proper Japanese princesses, huh?
Onami's more like us than you think.
Shinshiro found her as a baby
and he raised her as if she was his own,
but nobody knows her ancestry,
so no matter how hard she tries,
the clans will never acknowledge her.
Three. Four.
Five.
Six.
Two.
Three.
Four.
So, when are you gonna show me that cool
spin kick you did at the cosplay party?
-You don't need to know that. Focus.
-Come on.
There are no points for fancy shit
in a real battle.
Oh. Okay, so you admit it.
You think it's fancy.
Man, being a samurai
is a lot of repetitive drills.
Actually, the term "samurai"
is used only for men.
We're onna-bugeisha.
What?
But you train like samurai,
and you live like samurai.
Tell me about it.
Hmm.
Thanks.
You have beautiful eyes.
Damn, dude. Can you be any louder?
I should actually be even louder.
Haven't you seen
that '80s ramen Western, Tampopo?
-No.
-What? It's a classic.
Slurping is a sign of respect,
and ramen is real-life art.
Mmm.
Smell the broth.
Notice that seaweed
just perfectly laying on top there?
Now, the chicken--
Before I eat it, I massage it,
I acknowledge it,
I thank it,
and I apologize to it.
-I'm sorry, chicken.
-That's why I'm a vegetarian, dude.
Aya says Dash has a lead
on the Witch Blade.
We should start heading back soon.
-You mean now?
-Yeah, now.
-But I just started.
-Oh, my gosh. Come on.
-Fine.
-Let's go. Nope. Let's go.
Oh, shit.
I gotta order a burger.
Are you fucking serious?
We don't have time.
- Luna.
-There's no line. I'll get it to go.
What is it?
I don't know. I think--
I think someone's following us.
Where? I don't see anybody.
He was just there.
Told you it was a bad idea to come here.
Will you quit being paranoid?
Nobody's following us.
We shouldn't have listened to you.
-We gotta get outta here. Now.
-Let's go.
Sorry.
I thought I was gonna have it that time.
Maybe I can't see the Witch Blade
because of its protective spell.
Mmm.
Good news is, if I can't find it,
Yurei probably can't either.
-I think we're being followed.
-We went to the food market.
How could you be so irresponsible?
You are supposed to be in charge.
-It was my idea. Blame me.
-Sorry, we don't have time for this.
Do you really think
our location is compromised?
We can't wait to find out.
Do you have a backup hideout?
House of Arai set up hideouts
all over the city.
Perfect. It's not like
they're using them anymore.
Too soon.
I see that now.
May they rest in peace.
Dash and Luna, hang back with me.
Clear!
Clear.
I'm trying to update Lord Shinshiro
on our movement,
but he isn't answering.
I'll check the tracker.
Hey, Luna, can I ask you a favor?
Sure.
While the action figures are busy, I...
could use your help.
I've uncovered some history
on the Witch Blade's protectors,
but nothing's triggering a vision
about where it could be hidden now.
Mmm.
Since your father was
the Warrior Blade's protector,
I thought maybe something in your family
history might jump out as a connection.
Dude, I don't know shit about my dad.
I could always just study
your Warrior Blade for a couple hours.
Uh...
Yeah, I-- I don't know.
Okay, never mind.
Um-- Do you mind?
It should cover your family tree.
Arrest records, news clippings,
birth certificate.
Let me know if something clicks for you.
Well, this is my mom.
She had a beautiful name.
Yeah.
Nita.
You know,
I used to have this photo of her.
But after she died, I kinda just...
left everything behind.
You can keep that tablet.
Are you sure? This is, like, 1200 bucks.
Thanks.
Okay, I'll let you borrow it
for a few hours.
It's the least I can do for $1,200.
I'm gonna need it back.
Okay.
Fuck! Nikko, Ikeda, Maeda, Okoro.
Now Lord Shinshiro?
How are they all still radio silent?
-Do you think Yurei--
-Shinshiro is fine.
They are on a search-and-rescue mission.
They are probably staying off the grid
on purpose.
It's not like him, and you know it.
Did you get a hold of Shinshiro?
His tracker's down.
-How long have you been trying him?
A few hours.
Hours? We need to find him.
I can check around the city tonight
if that helps.
-Hit up a few of my contacts.
-No. I'm gonna look for him now.
Okay.
Where are we going?
I'll-- I'll retrace his steps.
He was headed towards--
Someone was following you,
and you wanna go back out there?
-Shinshiro is missing.
-Your mission is to protect Luna.
Family comes first.
Don't worry.
Everything is--
Okay, Witch Blade, where are you?
You have the Warrior Blade.
I told you you are not samurai.
We're searching for the Witch Blade.
You're a witch, like me.
He saw me. He saw me.
Find out anything?
Warrior Blade. Witch Blade.
Luna.
I know you can hear me.
Come to me...
You've turned your back
on your real family.
Your entire lineage were witches.
Your mother and the one
she fell in love with, Hirano.
No, you're wrong.
I'm not.
You're not the descendant.
We are the same, Luna.
I--
This is one of the places
Shinshiro's tracker came
before going down.
That crest.
This is Lord Nikko's safe house.
How are we supposed to get in?
I mean, Dash is supposed to be tracking us
and doing his nerd thing,
but I don't know where he is.
Come on, Dash. Do your nerd thing.
Okay. That fucking hurt.
Now, where's the fucking blade?
Where's your fucking sleeves?
-Bingo. That should do it.
Ladies first.
Visitors?
Gag him.
I'm just saying,
nothing good ever comes
out of a hallway this narrow.
Do you think he's here?
I don't think anybody's here.
At least, I hope not.
Did you see anything?
- Shit! There's too many of them.
- What do we do?
Uncle.
Lord Shinshiro.
Yurei?
It appears you have someone
who belongs to me.
Her family needs her.
Luna is already with her family.
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
This is the Witch Blade.
See the engraving?
The witch depiction is closer
to the handle than the samurai one.
I just saw it in a vision.
But why would Arai have it?
Unless...
Arai wasn't her father.
Hirano was.
Meaning Luna isn't a descendant
of the 47 Ronin.
She's a witch.
Luna is not samurai blood.
She is mine.
You take one of mine, I take one of yours.
Go!
She has to be working with Yurei.
Maybe she doesn't know the truth.
Or we've all been risking our lives
for a pretender.
I gotta go eat.
Lord Nikko.
Get me my fucking sword.
-Are you okay?
-I have to talk with Onami.
Tell Onami what?
The ninja are already here.
No.
No!
-Uncle! I gotta get you out of here.
No.
Oh...
-Onami.
It's... okay.
Don't say that.
I need you.
And they...
need you.
You...
have always been...
a true samurai.
Lead...
them.
No!
-Ikeda.
-Get them to safety.
- Onami, let's go!
No! We can't!
-Now!
-We can't!
Shinshiro.
No. Let me go.
No.
Go! Go!
Let them go.
We need them to find the Warrior Blade.
Message sent.
The other lords' houses
are still offline.
Let's hope the ninja don't find them too.
I'm so sorry.
I should have listened to you.
I'll be in the car.
Whenever you're ready.
Did you know
this whole time?
I wasn't sure.
But you have to understand.
My mom, she was a healer.
She was nothing like Yurei.
Magic is magic.
-Just like a witch is a witch.
-Onami.
She doesn't fucking belong here!
Luna.
Hey!
I get it.
But anger's not gonna get you anywhere.
Trust me.
I thought all I ever wanted
was to be a samurai.
But I couldn't even protect my family.
Your clan, all the samurai,
they need you now more than ever.
It is your time to lead.
Shinshiro believed that.
I believe that.
Now, let's go prove him right.
Do you think there are others like Hana?
We can't trust anybody
but the people in front of us right now.
-What do we do now?
- The plan hasn't changed.
If Yurei reunites the Tengu Sword,
he'll become invincible.
So the only hope we have left
is finding the actual Warrior Blade
and keeping it from him
until after the next blood moon.
-That's tomorrow.
- Then we still have time.
Luna, I know you have some hard feelings,
but I wanted you to at least know
your family's story.
A man named Hirano
was actually your father,
the guardian of the Witch Blade,
a role inherited in his youth.
But protecting the sword proved
a dangerous task.
So he enlisted the help of witches
from around the world
specializing in protective magic.
He did not expect
to fall in love with a bruja.
Hirano didn't want his daughter
to inherit his duty,
So he sent Nita and his baby away.
He would spend the rest of his days alone,
traveling with the blade.
A moving target.
Hana betrayed us.
Warrior Blade at the Viragkert Cemetery.
Oldest Arai grave site.
Shit!
-Sorry. Excuse me. Shit. Sorry, sorry.
- Hey, watch it.
Fuck. My bad.
-Not mine.
-Not me.
Definitely not mine.
It's mine.
It's from Luna.
"Viragkert Cemetery."
Looks like she found the Warrior Blade.
Dash sent her a message before he died.
Luna's tablet seems to be moving
towards the cemetery.
She's going after it.
You guys go find Luna.
I'll gather my men and the weapons.
We'll meet later.
Shinshiro's safe house.
This looks pretty old.
God, I hope this is the right grave.
Join me, Luna.
I can help you become
what you were meant to be.
I've known a lot of men like you,
and I've survived just fine without them.
But with me, you'll have the power
to do more than just survive.
My magic makes yours stronger.
You can live a new life.
A fresh start, where you belong.
You know, if I was still in my teens,
my daddy issues would've
eaten that shit up.
-I'll take that, thank you very much.
We were too late.
-Don't tell me you failed.
-And your men?
They've been alerted. It takes time.
The blood moon is tomorrow,
and now we have to assume Yurei has
both halves of the sword and Luna.
So we're back to square one.
I think I might have a lead.
I'm still tracking Luna's tablet.
Think Yurei doesn't know, huh?
He'll be waiting for us,
and we're way outnumbered.
Like it or not,
we kill Yurei tonight, or we die tomorrow.
They're here.
Reo, Nikko,
take the fight to the next car.
Kill whatever makes it through us.
I don't take orders from you.
But it's not a bad plan.
Fuck this.
Whoo!
-Where the fuck are we?
We're getting off here.
You sure about this?
Not really.
But here goes nothing.
Soon, the sword's full power will be mine.
The samurai are on their way.
It is finally time to destroy them
and for the ninja to take
our long-overdue seat at the table.
And you, my ninja brother,
were the patient rot from within
that made this possible.
The samurai's arrogance will cost them.
We should split up.
It appears your friends have joined
the celebration.
Come on.
I came with you.
You said you wouldn't hurt them.
Another chance to prove your worth.
Wait. What does that mean? Stop!
You promised!
I hope you fight better than your sister.
Lord Nikko must be here somewhere.
Stay here.
Some of us respect our sacred traditions.
Guns do not defeat magic.
- Get them to safety.
-Go! Go!
I have to hand it to you, Ikeda.
Faking your own death.
You're one sneaky bastard.
I'm gonna cut that pompous tongue
from your mouth.
About time.
Thought you were gonna bitch out.
I'll let my sword do the talking.
Reo!
No!
-Where'd he go?
-I didn't see him!
-Where--
Cover us!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Shit.
Where the fuck is he?
Fuck yeah!
This is for my sister.
You can end this now, Luna.
But you're gonna have to make a decision.
Them...
or your family.
The sword! Keep it away from him.
Reo!
Luna, the sword.
On behalf of all samurai,
I send you to hell.
Reo!
They must be on the other side. Let's go.
Here's your fucking sword back!
I told you you're not the last descendant.
You're a witch, like me.
Onami!
Shinshiro found her as a baby
and he raised her as if she was his own.
Nobody knows her ancestry.
The Blade of the 47 Ronin
will be wielded by a true descendant.
You.
-You're the one.
-Holy fuck.
- Yeah.
Well done.
We should get going.
It's cool, man.
Don't mind if I do.
Thanks.
Wow. Ancient magical weapons
look good on you.
Thanks.
I guess vintage is becoming my thing now.
Hey, listen, I appreciate the invite,
but, um, are you sure
you want me in there with you?
Of course.
Then I'll follow wherever you lead.
Hey. You ready?
-Are you ready?
-Look, I'm wearing a suit.
Can't wait to bring a witch
to the samurai summit.
Okay, Prophecy Girl.
Mmm.
I'll see you guys in there.
Go get 'em, tiger.
Lord Okoro.
Lord Maeda.
The battle we fought
has claimed many invaluable lives.
But we found within our clan
the strength to fight back.
And that is why today we welcome
the onna-bugeisha into our samurai family.
Now I'd like to yield the floor
to Lord Onami.
Thank you, Lord Nikko.
First order of business: the Tengu Sword.
♪ Swordplay ♪
♪ When we clash, let the hammer fly ♪
♪ Forty-seven warriors, a samurai ♪
♪ Dead before the sun
I look you in the eyes ♪
♪ At the hands of my katana
Meet your own demise ♪
♪ Know the fury ♪
♪ When sword upon sword
Decide the fate of the kingdom ♪
♪ Songs about a warrior
The villagers sing 'em ♪
♪ Challengers are fallin'
Just as fast as they bring 'em ♪
♪ A thousand throwing stars
Precision when a samurai sling 'em ♪
♪ Death dealers
Snatch your heart out your chest ♪
♪ Till everyone turns cold
Immortal breath stealers ♪
♪ Slicing through the enemy
Poison with no remedy ♪
♪ Till you reside in hell
Eternity with no amenities ♪
♪ The Ronin, everybody drop
Look how we zone in ♪
♪ Know what's going on when we get going ♪
♪ It's bloodshed
Leg, arm, arm, leg, head ♪
♪ Opposition fatal
They coughing up red ♪
♪ When we clash let the hammer fly ♪
♪ Forty-seven warriors, a samurai ♪
♪ Dead before the sun
I look you in the eyes ♪
♪ At the hands of my katana
Meet your own demise ♪
♪ Know the fury
When we clash let the hammer fly ♪
♪ Forty-seven warriors, a samurai ♪
♪ Dead before the sun
I look you in the eyes ♪
♪ At the hands of my katana
Meet your own demise ♪
♪ Know the fury ♪