"We meet, come to know each other fall in love and part right after.
"This is how many sad stories evolve." Samuel Taylor Coleridge.
This is not a tragedy.
This is a story of love...
that we share, Noeru and me.
Did you draw them with pencil?
It's not about merit.
Did you draw a lot when you were a child?
I guess I did.
What is the magazine you said you are working for?
It's called "Splash".
Nowadays the illustrations of the famous are the latest rage.
My drawing are different from yours.
For me, the fun part is to work as a model.
I have to say...
yours are...
the best I've seen till now.
Tell me about this drawing The Boy and the Sea.
Do you think to write about it?
I don't like to explain my creations.
You are surely right.
But that's will not sell magazines.
Surely you are different.
As you will understand, that is not my problem.
OK. So will you satisfy my curiosity?
Your curiosity?
This painting is...
is the one I like most.
It reflects a part of my life.
I see.
This is the one I like best.
You are the first saying this.
All the others make stupid questions.
Like: "what is your favourite dish?" "what is your favourite colour?"
Your name was...?
I don't remember right now.
You have my business card.
Put Mr. Mamiya. How is your first name read?
Taishin.
Taishin Mamiya.
Welcome.
For two?
Can this be allowed?
Journalists don't gain so much.
This is my first important job.
Therefore it's different from the others.
I am more of an editor than a journalist.
Let me pay you dinner. Ask whatever you want.
You seem a business man.
Relax, it enters as expenses.
Ask what you want.
Really?
Waiter!
This, this and this. Without Green pepper.
Some of these.
And a bottle of...
- Dom Perignon, please. - Sure, sir.
No, the champagne was a joke, right?
- Waiter! - It's on me.
It's a present. Because I'm your first important job.
How much is a bottle?
I don't know. For sure it's expensive.
Give it to me. Thank you.
It's already open.
Now we have to drink it.
But it's on me.
Mr. Mamiya, You are one kind of a man.
I guess you are even more special.
You can not drink.
You are a minor.
Yes, right.
Kids should drink juice.
So, you'll have to drink it alone.
Of course.
It's too expensive to pour it away.
Cheers.
To what will we drink?
To your first big job.
Did you rent your studio?
My agency did.
I see.
Usually you sleep there?
Sometimes.
Often I stay in hotels...
or at friends.
I put up with anything.
You have a very liberal life.
Do you miss classes frequently?
What's that now?
Don't preach.
I don't preach!
But you are still a student.
At least finish the school.
By the way... about that drawing...
What drawing?
The one of the Boy and the Sea.
It's not for sale.
Don't get me wrong.
I was wondering if it was Cape Misaki.
I am from Misaki, therefore I ask.
Have you been there before?
It's not your business!
Don't ask about that drawing!
OK. I will avoid questions about your private life.
Are you seeing someone?
Well, no.
Why not?
You are quite attractive.
Why are you laughing?
This was the last I expected to hear.
Really.
You must have big success.
The truth is, I don't.
I am not like you...
I am not in fashion.
I am just an ordinary guy, you are a professional model.
I go to the rest-room.
Mr. Mamiya.
No, nothing.
What? You needed to go, too?
What's going on?
What's that?
Don't!
Stop!
Please...
Enough!
Don't be afraid.
Hey, Mamiya! Mamiya!
What about the interview?
What?
The article about Noeru Kisaragi.
I am ... working on it.
You are a fool, you know?
But you are still young.
In each interview you give a different image.
But your arrogance drives everybody mad.
It suits you.
But you seem to have no ambition.
You are kind of a rowdy.
Professor!
What?
Can I go to the sick-room?
Are you sick?
I don't feel well.
Of course. Go.
I knew you would be here.
You miss to many classes.
You won't make it for University.
You are skipping them, too.
There won't be a problem, I am smart.
Well, me too. You'll teach me.
Deal?
How about that interview about your work?
Was it OK?
Same as ususal.
You know how they are.
Where do you go?
I go for a piss.
"Without the slightest doubt there is love in this world.
What worries me is how to express it". Osamu Dazai.
MODEL AGENCY MACCHIATO DULCE
Hello? Is this you, Noeru?
What's up?
Do you remember this interview for "Splash"?
Sure! So? Some problem?
This journalist...
was very unpleasant.
He was dealing with me and my work with an arrogance...
That is not OK.
I will contact them right away.
You better will.
Just tell him to step by for an apology.
Concerning what?
I just want that he apologizes face to face.
Are you sure?
One moment, please.
Mr. Mamiya,
it's Mr. Ikari from Macchiato Dulce.
Really? For me?
Yes!
Hello? Mamiya speaking.
Yes, it's me.
Could you be more specific?
He really said that?
Right, sir. I am sorry.
I understand. Yes, tonight.
OK. Tonight. Yes.
Mamiya. What did they want?
Oh, it's nothing.
You are late.
Don't stay there. Come in.
You want a drink?
You shouldn't drink. You are a minor.
So, let it be.
No. Don't be mean, Noeru.
Now, out!
I didn't see you here before.
Get out I said.
Alright.
Call me whenever you want.
Can't be.
What's this about?
I think it's quite obvious.
I am not referring to that.
Why did you lie to make me come here?
Otherwise you wouldn't have come.
Ain't I right?
What is it that you want? Why from me?
I wanted to continue what we began.
Leave me alone!
In that case I'll leave!
Wait!
Are you sure?
Are you telling me that you can't finish it?
Yes, I am done for a 80%,
there are all the details.
I know it makes no sense.
But I can't finish it.
You are not serious.
You are risking your job.
I am a good writer, but this is too big for me.
Listen, please.
All the information is in there
it just needs the final touch.
Impossible!
We have no time. This article was yours!
I implore you!
Well, you must have good reasons
to be so persistant.
Listen, Irie!
Take care of Mamiya's article.
Impossible!
I am doing the VIP's gossip!
So leave that shit.
Thank you, sir!
What was going on with Noeru?
You are a fool, you know?
Are you seeing someone?
Look, don't do that!
Don't be afraid.
I wanted to continue what we began.
It's a present. Because I'm your first important job.
Cheers.
Are you sure?
How dare you!
You know,
you didn't write half of what I would have written.
What? Really?
Did you read it by chance?
Yes.
Come on...
First, it was not even my article.
You do your job, OK?
I am sorry.
You want me?
Who are you?
I... I just...
Noeru isn't here.
You came looking for sex, right?
No, I am writing for a magazine.
I came to talk to him.
Yeah, sure...
But you are just like all the others.
I am sorry,
right now, Noeru is having sex with somebody else.
I can imagine.
Are you his friend?
That's not your business.
Now I remember.
You were writing about his art.
Did you write this article that came out recently?
Yes, I contributed.
I read everything that is published about Noeru,
but this article was the worst.
Could you be more specific?
You have absolutely no clue what his art is about.
To what do you refer?
"What called my attention about the work of N. Kisaragi…
what his soft and exquisit mix of colours and lines.
His work reflects substancially
the love of his public.
His satisfaction and the feeling of being loved".
Isn't it correct?
You don't know nothing about Noeru. Nothing.
Well, that's what it seems.
Noeru's work does not reflect feelings.
He himself admits that.
This one is the only that shows his feelings.
It forms a part of his life.
Really?
Did he tell you that?
You seem a good guy.
But you have not even a clue.
You know why he is painting?
No.
For distraction.
It's like laying down with a different guy every night.
What do you mean?
He is not happy.
Especially when it comes to sex.
He is always so sad.
He just doesn't stop to draw these silly illustrations...
and lay down with men for distraction.
You like Noeru, right?
If I like him? No.
I love Noeru.
So why do you allow him to lay down with others?
Because I believe in him.
I believe that in the end he will choose me.
Is this you in this drawing?
Unfortunately, no.
This is Ken, his friend from childhood.
I know Noeru inside out.
He is more fragile and weak than anyone.
Therefore, don't be to hard on him.
"To love is to almost believe. Hugo".
Chidori has told me you were here.
I knew you would come.
After my three lengths you can make love to me.
I didn't come for that.
I came to talk to you.
I don't think I will become one of your conquests.
I will not come to see you ever again.
Neither will I work with you again.
Chidori told me about you.
He cares about you. Couldn't you quit to go with others?
You know you can't go on like that.
You know it, right?
For your own good, quit fucking around.
I am done. Will you help me out?
It's not about you,
I do it for Chidori.
You are the worst.
Don't get mad.
What's the point?
Alright, I will stop fooling around with others.
But only if you are able to catch me.
I am not a swimmer! Don't be absurd!
Let's go!
You want to fuck me, right?
You are crazy! You are so wrong!
Asshole!
You promised!
You had the face...! I thought you were dead!
This is how we grown-ups do it.
That way you tricked me.
Promise. You will quit laying down with whoever.
Now... We'll go for the second fase...
As long people have friends to share their sadness...
it becomes easier to bear". Shakespeare.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Suddenly you decided to attend class?
A lot of things happened.
What does that mean?
Come on, tell me.
Nothing.
Ah, before I forget...
Here you have an article I wrote for you.
Don't bother. I already delivered my own.
I'm sorry for overloading you.
I try hard to be a good student.
I am in a very boring meeting.
This is work! Cheer up!
I wish I could be as lazy as you.
To work, my friend!
"Wherever there is one of us the other is present". Hemingway.
"In love there is only one law: to make your love happy". Stendhal.
One, two, three. One, two, three. Horrible!
Listen!
Show me how it has to be! OK?
I can't do it like that!
Look: one -- two -- three. Can you see?
Now we do understand. There we go...
1, 2, 3 - 1, 2... Too fast!
I can't any more.
You need to practice.
I never learned to swim.
But you are in good shape. Do you practice any sports?
Earlier I was boxing.
Really? For how long?
Not much.
What does that mean?
You don't know?
No, should I?
Will you teach me boxing?
But at first chance I'll hit you low.
What was that good for?
This is a report about the most important hospitals of Tokio.
I choose the most apropriate and we'll cover it right away.
What is going on? Where are you going?
Listen, Chidori.
What is going on, Chidori? You changed a lot recently.
You are the one who changed.
And what is the problem?
Let it go!
What is going on, Chidori? This is not you.
Leave me alone.
"Jealousy is Amor's sister...
just like Lucifer is a brother of the Angels". Boufflers.
Chidori. What are you doing here at this time?
- He is here, right? - What?
He is in there, right?
What are you talking about?
Don't try to fool me.
Listen. I want to know what's going on.
Where did you hide him?
What do you mean?
It's all your fault.
What are you talking about?
About Noeru. Are you deaf?
What? What is with him?
How dare you! What's going on between you and Noeru?
You are his new flame, right?
You are very wrong.
Noeru and me, we are more like...
I know that you secretly went to bed with him.
Let's get one thing straight: it is not what you think.
So what kind of relationship is it?
- It's... - You fell for Noeru.
That is what's going on.
I will never allow that he'll be yours.
This is you!
For a moment I was worried.
I thought you were a ghost.
If you have something to say, say it.
We have a special relationship.
What do we have in special?
We are friends since we were little. You don't draw any more.
I was quite busy...
How? It's gone!
Where is it?
You know how important it is for me, right?!
He took it.
Where did you take it?
Let it go. You don't need it anymore.
Neither do you need me.
Don't be stupid!
Hit me. Come on, punch me.
It will make you feel better.
come on! What will you do now?
Tell me what you are thinking.
You want that little reporter, right?
What?
Be honest.
I want him.
And what about Ken?
Noeru, I love you.
I loved you since Ken.
You can't do anything without me.
We are made for each other.
You always come back to me.
I am the best you can have.
Together we can succeed everything!
You have only me! Wake up!
I am the one who wants you most...
in this world.
You have to believe me. It's the truth.
For me...
you are a friend.
It's good for you to draw.
You are talented.
Not more nor less.
"Sometimes it's better to be wrong about your motives than to listen to the truth". La Rochefoucauld.
Are you fine?
Are you hungry? Will you come to my place?
Don't try to resist!
Stop it now!
Please, no.
You are hurting me!
Don't you know who I am?
You are nothing. Who cares?
Stop it! Not in the face!
You know, I cancelled all your appointments.
What the hell were you thinking?!
You are already punished. Take care.
Taishin Mamiya.
Noeru Kisaragi.
Mamiya, is that article OK with you?
Yes, sir.
Career of Noeru Kisaragi stopped after brutal attack.
You chose a very bad moment. We were having a great time.
What do you have in your face?
Now I have a lot of free time.
You are hopeless,
you don't even know to keep a promise.
That's true.
You knew it right from the beginning, right?
What is it what you want?
Here you are useless. Get lost.
Why are you doing this?
Why didn't you keep our promise?
Our promise?
Promises are made to be broken.
No.
They are made to be kept.
All our relationship depends from this promise.
And now you spoiled it all.
You are stupid.
Only idiots believe in promises.
I decided to never believe...
in promises.
What are you refering to?
Ken didn't keep his promise.
He promised that...
he would be with me.
He didn't keep his word.
Ken?
You mean the guy from your drawing?
Who told you that?
Chidori.
When we met for the first time.
In school they bullied us, Chidori and me.
Ken was older, he defended us.
He was very tender.
Take.
Thanks.
You draw very well.
Ken was strong and tender. He was great.
I miss him.
He always praised my drawings.
I drew because I liked to make him smile.
Take, it's yours. That you get better soon.
You like wales, right?
You are good at drawing.
Did you ever see the ocean?
No, never. You?
No. When I'm grown up, we'll go togethr.
This is our promise.
Really? Is it a promise?
Yes, I promise.
Soon, one week later...
Ken died.
He did not keep his promise.
This was the first time that I realized what I wanted.
But...
when you love somebody...
is it so sad...
And if, to want somebody...
hurts me so much...
I don't want to...
feel love any more.
I won't believe in promises any more.
"When two people cry together for the first time
they understand how much they love each other". Emile Deschamps
Subtitles: translation from Spanish&corrections by Roman Felk
"The greatest joy Love can give you,
is to take your lover's hand for the first time". Stendhal
"Love is a sacred madness". Renaissance Proverb
- Good morning. - Good morning.
Mamiya, come with me.
What's up?
They've called from the Models' Agency to complain about you.
You do know, why, no? Don't oblige me to say it.
I believe in you.
If you deny it, I will defend you.
Tell me that it's not true.
I will support you.
I am sorry.
I shouldn't bother you any more.
This is my business.
Are you serious?
Yes.
"The moment one begins to love another, is when life really starts". Scuderi
It was you, right?
What does this mean, Noeru?
You told them everything.
Hello!?
I was informed that you lost your job.
Come on, the news already spread?
It was my fault.
Don't be silly. It wasn't your fault.
I decided to quit.
Don't lie!
It's true. Don't worry.
The decision was mine.
I guess you are at school, no?
What will you do now?
Life goes on. I will find a new job.
That's not what I mean...
I mean us.
It won't change anything.
That's what I needed to hear.
Were you concerned? How stupid.
Don't lose more time. Go back to your class.
Alright, I will.
I did it.
I have an exclusive about the actress that Arai is dating secretly.
What do you think?
Satoshi Arai? The famous?
I called him and he confirmed.
I think, he must be much in love.
With his own words.
- Are you sure? - Totally.
Ask for declarations from their agencies.
We won't accept a "no comment".
OK!
It's the big news of the week.
Awsome!
What do you think of this one?
Which?
This one.
"Employees needed by Macchiato Dulce".
That's your agency!
They would kill me.
Nothing like that. Send your curriculum.
Impossible. I never could be your agent.
You are a chicken.
You are losing your rhythm.
Shut up! I'll do it my way...
I need a sandsack that's human.
I got you!
I'll get you, asshole!
"Since she wanted me, I ask myself up to what point I became more respectable". Goethe
Coming!
Sorry for being late. It's because of the job interview.
Take!
You bought a cake? This is not like you.
It for celebrating.
What?
They gave me the job.
Really? Great!
I'll put some candles.
Don't even think about it. It's not your birthday.
Looks great!
Yummy!
Wait!
Come. Sit down!
For what?
Do as I say!
Today, in order to celebrate I will draw you.
I am far to shy to be a Model.
It's an honour, you should be happy.
How will I put myself?
Do you have a preferred pose?
Not really!
So do however you like.
I'm embarrassed.
How come? We do know already.
What do you want to say by that?
You have been with worse guys, no?
Let me see.
Over my dead body.
Come on, show me!
I am naked!
That's how you turn me on.
- Get it! - Great, isn't it?
Chidori.
Noeru!
Subtitles: translation from Spanish&corrections by Roman Felk
This way we don't regret nothing right, Noeru?
"If somebody asks why I loved the way I did
I'll answer that both of us were authentic.
That is my only answer". Montaigne