- Previously on "Chucky"...
[high-pitched]
I’m Chucky.
[normal] And I’m your friend
till the end.
You get that now, Jake.
We all have our secrets.
I’m gonna go kill your sister.
Wanna come?
[suspenseful music]
You snooze, you lose.
- Charles Lee Ray was
a serial killer
who died in the ’80s.
He transferred his soul
to a Good Guy doll.
- Chucky is alive.
- This is a problem
we can solve together.
- [grunting]
- You have no idea
how hard it’s been
getting one
of you little shits to play.
- Chucky, it worked.
- Jennifer Tilly!
- Hi!
[cheers and applause]
- Every Better Days Hospital
in the country
will receive a priceless gift
from her personal collection.
- Junior!
- [grunting]
[squishing]
- No!
- We did it.
- Drive!
[dramatic music]
- Are we there yet?
- When do we get
to start stabbin’ people?
- Wait, you got a knife?
- Yeah, I got a knife.
They passed ’em out
at orientation.
- What the fuck?
What?
- [chuckles] What?
I didn’t say anything.
[laughs]
- Don’t worry.
They say bald guys
are more virile.
They say chicks
just love bald guys.
[laughs]
- Yeah, well, they also say
it ain’t the size that counts.
So I wouldn’t worry about those
pathetic stick arms of yours.
- I don’t have stick arms.
- Hey, do I know you?
- Get back in your boxes,
all of you!
Don’t make me come back there!
- She is fuckin’ hot.
- Oh, forget it, Sticky.
Chicks like that need
someone more...
I don’t know...
virile?
- Does that guy look familiar?
- Yeah.
Come to think of it, he does.
- I can’t put my finger on it.
He’s just, like...
repulsive or something.
- He sure is.
- They don’t know me.
[tense music]
They don’t know you, either.
[both screaming]
- I’m done with you, Chucky,
and your tiny fuckin’ dick!
- [gasps]
- They weren’t there.
And they don’t know
what you did.
- You just keep your mouth
shut, buster, or I’ll--
[tires screeching]
[Tiffany gasps]
[gunshot]
[horns blaring]
♪ ♪
[all gasp]
- Andy.
Get him!
♪ ♪
- Shit.
- [cackles]
- [gasps]
- [cackling]
[grunting]
[engine revs]
[tires screeching]
♪ ♪
- This is for Kyle!
[all screaming]
[crashing]
[explosion booms]
[fire crackling]
[playful spooky music]
♪ ♪
[tender music]
[rings doorbell]
[door opens]
- Hey.
♪ ♪
- So, uh, I guess this is it.
- Well, only for now.
I mean,
I only live two hours away,
and I can see you
every weekend.
- Jake...
you know
that’s not gonna happen.
- [sighs] I know.
- It wouldn’t be enough,
anyway.
- I know.
You know, at this point,
I’ll take what we can get.
- ♪ This ain’t no lullaby ♪
[car horn honks]
- Let’s go, Batman!
To the Batcave!
- [chuckles]
On my way, Robin!
- You got a fellow foster
this time.
- Uh, yeah. He seems okay.
I wish I could say the same
about Pam and Larry.
♪ ♪
I wanna kiss you so bad
right now,
but they’re watching me.
- I get it.
♪ ♪
- I love you, Jake.
- I love you more, Devon.
- That’s not possible.
♪ ♪
- ♪ This ain’t no lullaby ♪
♪ But I can make it rhyme
for you, yeah ♪
♪ I can try, I can try ♪
- Jake!
- Wait, wait. Stop, stop, stop!
- ♪ This ain’t on symphony ♪
♪ But if you wanna sing
with me ♪
♪ Then I can try ♪
♪ I can try to lie ♪
♪ In the lullaby ♪
♪ ♪
- Holy secret identity.
- They’re watching.
- I don’t care.
♪ ♪
[laughs]
Um, all right.
Um, I--I’ll see you
this weekend, okay?
All right, cool.
[chuckles]
- ♪ Ooh,
why do you wanna lie? ♪
♪ Why do you wanna lie? ♪
♪ Another lullaby ♪
[dramatic sting]
[spooky music]
♪ ♪
- Trick or treat!
[man screaming]
[children laughing]
[spooky electronic music]
♪ ♪
[doorbell dings]
- Trick or treat!
- Shit!
[panting]
[doorbell dings]
- You scared me.
- It’s called coulrophobia,
the fear of clowns.
It’s caused
by childhood trauma.
- I’m not afraid
of clowns, all right?
I thought
you were somebody else.
But how old are you?
- Guess.
- What are you doing
out here all alone?
Like, where are your parents?
Your friends?
- They’re dead.
[chatter]
- Trick or treat!
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- Boo!
- Jesus.
- [giggles]
- ♪ Five little ghosts
went out one night ♪
[typing]
Shit.
- Holy Halloween costumes,
Batman.
I can’t believe you made these.
- Hey, never forget,
real superheroes can sew.
Is that a little loose?
- Yeah.
- Here, I got it.
The most important thing
in a utility belt
is a bobby pin.
- Good to know.
- Yeah.
All right.
Boy Wonder, the streets are
crawling with bad guys tonight.
It’s time to go fight
some crime.
- And the citizens of Gotham
will pay us in chocolate!
[phone ringing]
- Sorry, Give me a second.
Hello?
- Is Tamara home?
- Who?
- Tamara.
- Uh, think you have
the wrong number.
- Oh, I’m sorry.
- Uh, yeah, it happens.
No worries.
Hm.
[phone ringing]
- Where are you?
Wait, you’re still in Salem?
Jake, what the fuck?
- Holy profanity!
- Oh. Hey, Devon.
I’m here with Gary.
- Excuse my French, Gary.
- Jake’s taking me
trick-or-treating.
- I can see that.
Hey, can I talk to you
for a second?
- Yeah. Um, can you give me
a second, buddy?
- Jake, you know I love
how you look in tights,
but where the hell are you?
- I’m so sorry, Devon.
I’m not gonna be able
to make it.
- You’re telling me this now?
You’re supposed to be
on the bus.
Jake, I’m cooking
for you here, man!
- Pam and Larry
wouldn’t let me go.
They’re--they’re still
not cool with us.
- Screw ’em.
They’re not your real parents.
- Yeah, but they could be.
- Why would you even want them
if they won’t accept you?
- You know, not everyone
is just gonna
get it automatically.
I mean, you lucked out.
- Yeah, my foster mom’s
awesome.
She showed me off
to all of her rich friends,
and then she went to Paris
and I haven’t seen her since.
- You know, Gary’s a good kid.
He deserves a family, too.
He needs me.
- What about me, Jake?
It’s been, like, six months.
I miss you.
- I know.
I miss you too, babe,
but look, I know it sucks,
but let’s just focus
on Christmas break, all right?
- And what am I supposed
to do until then?
Jake, you’re the only one
I can talk to
about what really happened.
- I know. Me too.
- Hey, you heard from Lexy?
- Nope.
- Me neither. Something’s up.
[phone beeps]
- Let’s go, Batman!
- Yeah, um,
I’ll be right there.
Just a second.
- It’s been
125 seconds already.
[phone rings]
126, 127.
- Hello?
- Is Tamara home?
- Uh, still the wrong number.
- Is this 555-0131?
- Yeah, but there’s
no Tamara here.
- Weird.
- Hmm.
- Doing anything fun tonight?
- Uh, yeah, super fun.
I should probably
get back to it.
- How come you’re home
all alone
with your baby brother?
♪ ♪
- Who is this?
- Where’s your boyfriend
tonight, Jake?
- Screw you, Ellis.
Douchebag.
[phone rings]
Hey, you know what, Ellis?
You know, it’s bad enough
that you’re
a homophobic douchebag prick.
You know, the really sad thing
is, it’s totally unoriginal!
- This isn’t Ellis.
And I’m not homophobic.
I don’t discriminate based
on anyone’s sexual preference.
That’s not why I’m calling.
- Then why the hell
are you calling?
- To make sure you’re home.
Happy Halloween.
♪ ♪
[doorbell dings]
- I’ll get it!
- No, no, no! I’ll get it.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[phone rings]
Hey.
- Jake, I just got a weird call
from this douchebag.
- Wait, he called you too?
I think it’s Ellis, that
Neanderthal from my school.
But I don’t know, he--
didn’t he sound kinda...
familiar?
- [cackling]
Oh, Devon, you don’t think
it could be--
- Jake, I don’t think anything
could’ve survived that crash,
not even Andy.
- They never found his body.
- Even if he lives, how come
we haven’t heard from him?
[phone ringing]
- It’s him.
- Who? Andy?
- No, the douchebag.
♪ ♪
[doorbell dings]
What the hell?
- Trick or treat.
Smell my feet.
Give me something good to eat.
- Oh, no.
- That’s not very scary.
What are you supposed to be?
- The ghost of Halloween past.
Say hello to my friends.
- Oh, shit. No.
- Hi.
- Could I please use
your bathroom?
It’s an emergency.
[phone chimes]
- No! Caroline, no!
- Um--
- Look, she can’t hear us.
He muted us.
- Okay. It’s upstairs.
- Oh, wait.
Devon, wait.
Use your landline.
Call the police.
I’m gonna call Lexy.
- Jake, they’re not gonna
listen to me.
- Just don’t mention Chucky!
Just get someone over there!
- Okay.
[suspenseful music]
[line trilling]
- Shit, shit, shit.
- Yes, I’d like to report
a break-in at 3083 Fairburn.
Who cares how I know?
Just send someone now!
- Come on, Lexy, pick up!
- [laughs]
[phone buzzing]
♪ ♪
[line trilling]
- You gonna get that?
- Nope.
- No!
♪ ♪
- ♪ All I do is
tease my heart ♪
♪ ’Cause time after time
it yearns ♪
♪ But I’m dedicated, and in
the hustle and bustle ♪
- You sure about this?
- Absolutely.
- But your mother.
- She won’t be home for hours,
if at all.
- Your sister?
- Trust me,
I have her well-trained.
She’s not gonna bother us.
- ♪ I crawl back to you
in the deep ♪
♪ Wanna walk on water,
but I can’t find my feet ♪
♪ Yeah, so I crawl back
to you ♪
- Um--Lexy, you have
done this before, right?
- Have you?
- I think your first time
should be special.
- ♪ So I crawl back,
I crawl back to you ♪
- Okay, first,
I just need a bump.
- Me too.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [sniffs]
[coughs]
- Lexy, I really like you.
- Thanks.
- [sniffs]
♪ ♪
This just feels right,
doesn’t it?
- Please stop talking.
- No! No, don’t!
- Police!
- Jesus Christ!
- You kids okay?
- What the hell
are you doing here?
Did my mother send you?
- We got a report
of a break-in.
I’m gonna have a look around.
- Yeah.
- I should go.
- Sit down.
- Did the alarm go off?
- No. Someone called us.
Do you know a Devon Evans?
[dramatic music]
- Yeah, I do.
♪ ♪
[screams]
Help!
- Was there anyone else
in the house tonight?
- The ghost of Halloween past.
- Who?
- He asked to use the bathroom.
He said it was an emergency.
Then he said see ya later.
- Caroline, how tall
was this ghost?
- Well, he was about this tall.
- There’s nobody here.
No sign of forced entry,
either.
- Any dolls?
- What?
- Oh, no.
Lexy, I think it was--
- Officer, this is just
a misunderstanding.
My sister shouldn’t be inviting
strangers into the house,
no matter how bad
they have to pee!
Would you mind staying with us
until my mother gets home?
She’ll be pissed off
if you don’t.
- Sure.
- You can go.
- Thanks.
- He said he liked
to be hugged.
He said he was my friend
till the end.
At first,
he seemed really nice,
but he lied.
He had secrets.
Chucky always had secrets.
- Caroline, what were
Chucky’s secrets?
- He killed a lot of people...
- [screaming]
[crowd screaming]
- Including my daddy.
[people screaming]
- Caroline, you know
that it was Junior Wheeler
who did that.
- Your sister’s boyfriend.
Right, Lexy?
- No. Tell them, Lexy.
You saw him, too.
And now he’s back.
Chucky was the ghost
of Halloween past.
Tell them, Lexy.
It was Chucky.
- No.
No, Caroline, it was Junior.
Junior killed all those people.
Chucky is only a doll.
I mean, was.
- You understand that,
don’t you, Caroline?
- You can’t blame her
for having a hard time
accepting that her own sister
could invite a boy like that
into our lives.
- You never liked him,
not even before
he killed anyone.
- Exactly.
I’ve always been able
to read people,
and I could tell from day one
he was bad news.
- No.
He wasn’t always like that.
He was the sweetest boy
in the world.
- That boy
destroyed everything.
Your father,
very possibly my career,
if you haven’t seen
the latest polls,
and your sister’s childhood.
She can’t even sleep
without waking up
screaming every night
from the nightmares.
And she made me
get rid of all of her dolls.
- Yes, it’s called pediophobia.
That’s the clinical term
for fear of dolls.
- Sadly, it’s the least
of our problems.
- Actually, I think it might be
the ideal place to start.
- What do you mean?
- I’d like to try something,
if you’ll permit me.
- Um, okay.
- You know, I collect dolls,
recreationally.
Since I was Caroline’s age.
As a child, I had polio.
I was stuck in bed
for two years.
My babies were my only friends.
It really is
a fascinating hobby.
♪ ♪
This is Belle.
Wedding Belle, they called her.
She is incredibly rare,
a marketing concept
from the ’90s.
They made very few of these.
I use her sometimes
for therapeutic purposes.
Caroline, I think
Belle could help you.
Would you like to hold her?
- Go ahead, sweetheart.
You can do it.
- There. Oh.
[chuckles]
I think she likes you.
She needs someone
to take care of her.
Would you like
to take her home?
- Sure.
- She’ll be a good friend
to you.
- Oh, I’m so proud of you,
sweetheart.
So, so proud.
[sinister music]
[camera shutter clicks]
- Mrs. Cross,
thank you for inviting me
into your lovely home.
- Oh, thank you, James.
And please, call me Michelle.
- Michelle, do you miss living
in the mayor’s residence?
- Oh, you know,
that’s a beautiful house.
But my late husband used to say
we were really
just its caretakers
for a brief period of time,
a blip in Hackensack’s history.
- But after voters
overwhelmingly recalled you
from office
after the murders last year,
the single most violent era
in our city’s history,
you’re running
for a second term.
And I have to ask,
why do you deserve my vote now?
- As a survivor
of violence myself,
I think I occupy
a unique position of empathy
for everyone who lost somebody
in last year’s tragic events.
I know exactly
what they’re going through
because I’m going
through it, too.
The grief, the anger,
the guilt...
the survivor’s guilt.
But I promise
every citizen of Hackensack
that in my second term
as mayor,
I will show no mercy
to violent offenders.
One strike and you’re out.
[chuckles]
- I heard you had a break-in
here just last night.
What would you say to the perp?
- I’d just like to dare them
to try that again
while I’m home.
- And how about you, Lexy?
How are you holding up?
- Um, well, it’s been
a really tough year.
But I’m getting through it
with my family’s help.
- We’re getting
through it together.
Like all of us in Hackensack,
we’re strong.
Hackensack strong!
- Caroline, how about you?
- I’m fine.
- Hey, whatever happened
to Chucky?
[tense music]
- Um, excuse me?
- As I recall, she used
to drag that thing everywhere.
- Um, well, she has
a new doll now.
Her name is Belle.
- Caroline, does Belle
tell you to do things, too?
- What are you talking about?
- Well, at a press conference
last year, she said--
- Chucky told me to kill Mommy.
- Uh--
- Who is Chucky?
- Um, thank you so much.
- I’m sorry. Kids.
- Remember?
[tense music]
- Get out of my house.
- We have it on tape.
- Get out!
♪ ♪
- Dr. Mixter is full of shit.
- [sighs]
I knew it.
- Mom, too.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
You should be afraid, Caroline.
Dolls are horrifying.
Never trust any doll.
They’re all fucked up.
- You said the F-word.
- Yes. I know what I said.
That is how serious
this is, Caroline.
Now say it.
Dolls are fucked up.
- Dolls are fucked up.
- Never trust any doll.
- Okay, good.
And you can’t tell anyone,
or they’re gonna send you away,
okay?
- Okay.
- Cross your heart.
- Cross my heart.
- Okay, and...
♪ ♪
Keep this handy.
Sweet dreams.
♪ ♪
- Jake!
- Oh--
- You Ubered here
all the way from Salem?
I can’t just sneak off
in the middle of the night.
Neither can you. Do Pam and--
- We have to get Lexy, okay?
Have you seen this?
- Yeah, it looks familiar.
- If Chucky really was
at her house last night,
then why didn’t he kill her
when he had the chance?
- Maybe he’s just messing
with us.
Or maybe he’s trying
to get one of us to kill again.
- [exhales]
Let’s go.
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Uh, uh, baby,
you’re the devil I know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Better than the devil
I don’t ♪
♪ I don’t ♪
[knock at window]
♪ Maybe I could stop ♪
♪ But I won’t, I won’t ♪
♪ ’Cause, baby,
you’re the devil I know ♪
♪ I know, I know ♪
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Careful. Hey.
Shh, my mom’s downstairs.
- Sorry.
- It took you long enough.
- Yeah, it’s nice
to see you, too.
- Hey.
- This place isn’t bad.
I thought you said
it was a dump.
- Please.
I can’t even talk about it.
It’s like I’ve been demoted.
- I thought you quit.
- I’m sorry, Jake.
When did you stop medicating
your chronic anxiety?
- It’s not the same thing.
- It’s just a little weed.
What’s the big deal?
- Oh, no big deal,
if that’s all you’re doing.
Is it?
- Yes, that’s all I’m doing.
Jesus, I haven’t seen you
in six months.
You’re acting like
this is an intervention.
We have serious shit
to deal with.
Devon, what did you find out
about Caroline’s doll?
- Well, she looks a little
like the Bride of Chucky.
Remember that movie?
- Yeah, with Jennifer Tilly,
who we know really is
the Bride of Chucky,
Tiffany Valentine.
- Shit.
- Where’s that doll now?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[door creaks]
- Maybe it’s just
a coincidence.
- Did you test it?
- Yeah, I bashed the shit
out of it.
And it came from our therapist.
I mean, our family therapist
can’t be in league
with a supernaturally
possessed doll, right?
- Lexy?
- Shit, it’s my mom.
Um, get in the closet!
- What’s going on?
- I was just checking
on Caroline.
- Well, who were you
talking to?
- I was singing her a lullaby,
the way Dad used to.
- Oh.
Look at her. Aww.
I don’t think she’s slept
like that in months.
Maybe our luck
has finally turned around.
- Maybe.
- Okay.
We should leave her be.
Come on.
[door click shut]
♪ ♪
[door creaks]
[door shuts]
♪ ♪
[music intensifies]
- Caroline, what did
I tell you last night?
- Belle’s okay.
She’s not like Chucky.
She’s just a doll.
And I don’t want Mommy
to get mad anymore.
- Where is she?
- She left already.
She said you have
to walk me to school.
- Okay. I’ll be right back.
Here.
Look, guys, I’ve been thinking,
and maybe the other night
really just was a prank.
I mean, we were pretty famous
for a while after the murders,
and there are
some sick assholes out there
with way too much time
on their hands.
- Yeah, some sick asshole
who was able to get
all our numbers
and who also happens to be
just two feet tall.
- Short people can be assholes.
- I don’t know, maybe.
Yeah, are you okay?
- Yeah, I’m fine. Why?
- You just--you seem weird.
- You’re weird.
- Wait.
Wait, where are you going?
- To the bathroom.
Is that okay with you?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[doorbell dings]
[menacing music]
- Holy homemade bomb, Batgirl!
♪ ♪
- [laughs menacingly]
- I’m not Batgirl.
- Sorry, I mean Batwoman.
- My name is Caroline.
- You’re not playing it right.
- I’m still alive, aren’t I?
- Not for long.
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Sit down.
Amazing what you can do
with a little fertilizer
and some butane.
Kill anyone
within a 6-foot radius.
- Holy hostage situation,
Batman!
- Okay,
that’s already getting old.
- Gary, it’s gonna be okay.
- He’s gonna blow us all
to smithereens!
- No. No, no, Gary.
I won’t let that happen.
I promise.
This isn’t a game, okay?
How’d you get here?
- We Ubered.
I’ve been Ubering
all over Jersey today,
same as you, Jake.
Uber’s really made
being a killer doll
so much easier.
In the old days,
if I had to get somewhere,
I had to take a fuckin’ hostage
just to drive me.
Now, I can just arrange
to have myself picked up
and delivered anywhere.
It is so convenient.
- Just don’t do anything
stupid, Chucky.
- [laughs]
No, Jake.
Stupid would be you
and your idiot BFFs
falling right into my trap.
See, I needed the three of you
to get back together
so I could kill you
all at once.
But you never got
back together.
So much for BFFs.
I hang out
with my murder victims
more often than you assholes
see each other.
- We’ve been busy.
- Yeah?
Well, now, you’re all gonna
get busy dyin’,
just as soon
as Lexy gets down here.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Just let the kids go.
- Nah. The more, the merrier.
- Why are you doing this?
- There were 72 of me
on that truck.
I was gonna
take over the world,
and I would’ve gotten away
with it, too,
if it weren’t for you
meddling kids
and Andy
and that goddamn bitch
from hell, Tiffany.
I’m gonna kill
every last one of you.
- Wait, exactly how many
of you are left?
- Enough to make this
worth the sacrifice.
I die knowing
I took all of you with me.
You die knowing
I never really die.
[chuckles]
Just as soon
as Lexy gets down here.
- [sniffing]
♪ ♪
- What the fuck?
[ominous music]
- What about Andy?
- Andy is dead.
- And Kyle?
- They’re both dead.
- I don’t believe you.
- Well, you’ll see them
in hell.
Any minute now.
♪ ♪
- Is somebody here?
- God, I love my job.
- [gasps]
- [Taser crackles]
- Ahh!
- [Gary giggles]
[jaunty music]
♪ ♪
- [yells]
[bomb beeps]
[Gary screams]
[Chucky giggles]
- There’s no pain greater
than the permanent grief
that a parent suffers
after the loss of a child.
Think of the birthdays,
the ball games,
the graduations,
all the milestones that
should have been celebrated,
but now instead
will be a cause for mourning
year after year
by Gary’s parents.
- Foster parents.
- Excuse me?
- Pam and Larry
were his foster parents.
And they didn’t love him.
I did.
- Through your actions
and your negligence
and what you apparently thought
was just good, clean fun--
building a homemade bomb
around a child--
you and your friends
have denied Gary his life.
- If I may.
I think it is important
to point out
they’re children too.
- And they’ll be placed
in a facility
with other violent
juvenile offenders like them.
- I would like to suggest
an alternative.
I’ve done some work
with troubled youth
at the School of the Incarnate
Lord in Burlington,
along with the Archdiocese
of Camden.
They’ve had great success
with cases like this.
[ominous music]
These kids are responsible
for Gary’s death,
yet I’m sure we all agree
it was a tragic accident.
♪ ♪
They have been through
so much already
this past year.
I’d like to think
that they could learn
from their mistakes
and become good people
by thinking on their sins.
- It was a kamikaze mission.
He blew himself up.
He’s never done anything
like that before.
Which means that
more than one Chucky
made it out
of that truck crash alive.
- How many?
- Who knows?
But no matter what,
he’s gonna come for us again.
- Jesus.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, do you guys remember
Trevor Cain?
- Who’s Trevor Cain?
- He was a year ahead of us,
in fifth grade.
He made my life a living hell.
Taught me everything I know.
Trevor’s been here
for the past three years.
My mother sent him here.
- Maybe Chucky’ll take
care of him.
- That’s not funny.
Wait, guys, why does this place
look so familiar?
- This used to be
the Burlington Home
for Wayward Boys, remember?
Charles Lee Ray lived here
when he was our age.
[music intensifying]
♪ ♪
[bell tolling]
[screaming]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Good morning.
I’m Sister Ruth.
I’m a Handmaid of
the Immaculate Heart of Mary.
Welcome to Incarnate Lord.
Do you know why you’re here?
- Because God hates us?
- God doesn’t hate anyone.
He loves us even when
we’ve lost our way.
He wants you to seek
forgiveness
and to find your way
back to Him.
And if you’re not careful,
you might even have
a little fun along the way.
Follow me.
- He hates us so fucking much.
[jaunty music]
- ♪ Trust in the Lord
with all your heart ♪
♪ With all your heart,
please do ♪
♪ God loves you ♪
♪ Trust in the Lord
with all your heart ♪
♪ With all your heart,
please do ♪
[door slams]
♪ God loves you ♪
♪ And lean not upon
your own understanding ♪
♪ Fear the Lord
and love Him ♪
♪ That’s what
He’s commanding ♪
♪ Trust in the Lord
with all your heart ♪
♪ With all your heart,
please do ♪
♪ God loves you ♪
♪ Trust in the Lord
with all your heart ♪
♪ With all your heart,
please do ♪
♪ God loves you ♪
♪ And lean not upon
your own understanding ♪
♪ Fear the Lord
and love Him ♪
♪ That’s what
He’s commanding ♪
♪ Trust in the Lord
with all your heart ♪
♪ With all your heart,
please do ♪
♪ God loves you ♪
♪ ♪