- Previously, on "Chucky"...
- Sin is a choice.
- Hi, I’m Nadine.
- What the hell is all this shit?
- I steal things. - Everyone’s got their secrets.
- What’s your secret?
- I’m Father Bryce, headmaster at Incarnate Lord.
- They’ve had great success with cases like this.
They could learn from their mistakes.
- Leave the door open if your male friends are in your room.
- Don’t worry.
We’re all perfectly safe here when it comes
to Jake and Devon.
That’s Trevor. He’s evil.
- The Lord brought you here so I can finally
make things right with you.
- We received a new donation this morning.
- Boo! - [screams]
- Oh, my God. You made my day.
- [whimpering] - What do we do?
- Let’s just stand our ground. - Can’t let anyone else die.
- Now, where is the doll?
- I told you. I don’t know.
- What happened? Did you get him?
- It’s okay. She’s cool. She knows.
[both screaming]
[grunting]
- Why didn’t you kill him?
- Ever since he got here, Chucky’s been acting weird
and taking pictures all over the school.
He’s collecting information for someone.
- [muffled speech] - Who?
- That’s what we’re gonna find out.
- Where’s the doll, Jake?
- I have no idea.
- You have no idea?
Even though three days ago, you were locked in this office
alone with the doll,
during which time it went missing?
- Right.
- You know, it would be easy to punish you.
Have Trevor and the hall monitors
rip the place apart until they find it,
but I’m not gonna do that.
- You’re not? - No.
No, no, no, no, Jake.
This is a learning opportunity.
I want you to have the chance to do the right thing,
because I want you to know how it feels,
how free you are to confess your sins,
and pray for forgiveness.
Lunch is almost over.
I’m sure there’s some place you need to be.
- Thank you, Father.
You’ve given me a lot to think about.
- Jake...
I want you to choose the right path...
but I’m not gonna wait long.
- Okay.
[door shuts]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[door opens]
- What did Bryce say? - I don’t know.
A lot of patronizing bullshit.
Look, he wants the doll back, and he wants it fast.
- I don’t like to be without my dolls, either.
Their tiny features are very comforting.
- Okay, Lexy, did you find anything out yet?
- Just a bunch of weird selfies.
The angles are all wrong.
♪ ♪
And a name.
- What name?
- The Colonel.
That’s it.
Colonel Mustard? Colonel Sanders?
- We gotta get something out of him.
- What am I supposed to do?
He hasn’t talked in days.
♪ ♪
- Don’t you have his knife?
What are you doing here?
- Why are you taking pictures of us?
♪ ♪
- Ha.
- If you won’t talk, we’ll make you.
- Okay. Let’s do it.
- [grunts]
Ooh. Ooh, ooh, ooh.
[laughs]
- Sick fuck. He’s enjoying it.
- We can’t keep doing this.
Just to kill him before he kills us.
- Look, we need to know what he knows.
He’s our best bet at finding out
what we’re really up against.
Here. Let me try something.
- Okay.
- [grunts]
- Last chance.
How many of you are there?
- You know, if you’re gonna pull my hair,
at least tell me I’m pretty.
[laughs]
[playful spooky music]
♪ ♪
- For centuries, Western religious art
was focused on one idea,
directing our earthly human attention toward the spiritual.
So imagine how explosive something like this
must have been.
Here, Dali challenges us to imagine Christ
as we’ve never dared, from the perspective
of God himself.
Critics called this painting a stunt,
but perhaps Dali intended us to do the unthinkable,
really get inside God’s sorrow,
his pain, his loss.
[bell rings] We’ll pick up tomorrow.
Jake.
So what’d you think of that last one?
- Honestly, I’ve never seen anything like it.
- [chuckles] Wait till you see what I’ve got for you tomorrow.
How’s Devon?
I heard he was sick.
- Oh, oh, yeah.
It’s just a cold. I’m sure he’ll be okay.
- Of course.
But sometimes, when we’re overcome
with guilt or sadness,
we can make ourselves sick.
And if that’s ever the case, I’m always here to talk.
- To Devon.
- To anyone,
including you, Jake.
- You think I’m overcome with guilt?
- I think something’s eating away at you.
You wanna talk about what happened
to your foster brother?
- Um...
there’s more to it than what everyone thinks.
I don’t think I’m ever gonna be able to forgive myself.
- Jake, for what it’s worth,
in my experience,
sometimes in order to forgive ourselves,
first we have to forgive those who have sinned against us.
♪ ♪
- Uh--okay.
Yeah.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
- See you tomorrow.
♪ ♪
[eerie music]
- [sighs]
- Alexandra. Hi, there.
What’s that?
- Allergies.
I’m allergic to hay, pet dander, and nosy people.
- [chuckles] That’s funny.
You know what else is funny? - Rhetorical questions?
- Students can’t keep their own medicine.
It’s all locked up in the infirmary.
- Yeah. Hilarious.
See you later.
- Ativan? Clonazepam?
I saw your mom’s name on the bottle.
How is Mayor Cross by the way?
- I wouldn’t know. - Right.
Well, maybe I should call her former Mayor Cross
’cause she just lost the election.
- She lost? - Uh, yeah.
I was crushed when I heard the news, too.
You know, you should really be more careful around here.
This place is so strict when it comes to drugs.
If someone thought you were using,
well, you’d probably be stuck in here until you turn 18
just like me.
- Thanks for the warning.
- Have a blessed day.
♪ ♪
- [muffled straining]
[muffled pleas continue]
[muffled grunts]
Eech, ugh.
You didn’t have any clean socks?
- Don’t worry.
Won’t be a problem for you much longer.
- Ohh, I get it.
Big man gonna do
a wittle murder.
[laughs]
You don’t have what it takes.
Zero killer instinct.
And trust me, I should know.
- Shut up, Chucky. - No, really.
I’m like the MVP of serial murder.
- Shut up. - I’ve killed more people
than you have Insta followers.
- Shut the fuck up.
- [chomps]
[laughs]
You think you think you can fuck with me?
I killed your mother.
Hell, I even killed my own mother.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
[door opens] - Wait!
Devon, what are you doing?
- We need to talk.
♪ ♪
- Father O’Malley.
Hi.
- Oh, Lord, give me strength.
Hello, Nadine.
- I’m really glad you’re in here.
I kind of have a lot to talk to you about.
[sighs] Crazy week.
Wow.
You know that old saying when it rains, it pours?
Well, it’s funny, ’cause obviously sometimes
it just sprinkles a little, but--
- What is it you need, child?
- Oh, I need to confess.
- Oh, actually, Nadine,
the confessional’s closed for the day.
- It is? Oh, shoot.
Um, I kind of have a lot to go over with you.
Um, shouldn’t take more than 20, 30 minutes, tops.
Let’s say 45.
- Oh, I would love to help,
but I have to go elsewhere.
Right now.
- Oh, that’s no problem.
I’ll come back to tomorrow.
- Or maybe you could pray on it instead.
Yeah.
Have a good long pray on it, why don’t you?
- But Father, what about my sins?
I need to confess. I need to do penance.
What about my soul?
- See you tomorrow, Nadine.
♪ ♪
- We should kill him while we have the chance
before anyone else gets hurt.
He’s never gonna tell us anything.
- If we can’t figure out his plan, we’re sitting ducks.
- You can’t torture a sadist.
- No, all right? I’m not giving up.
- Look, it’s not in his DNA.
If he wanted to talk,
you’d have to completely reprogram him.
- Wait. Reprogram him--
Like brainwashing?
- [muffled] Hm? - Yeah, wait,
let’s try that. - I wasn’t being serious.
You can’t reprogram Chucky’s brain.
- Why not? I mean, it might work,
and I bet you know how to do it, too,
because you were super into that one podcast on MKUltra.
- Uh, no, I wasn’t.
- Okay, I’m gonna tell Lexy and Nadine.
We’re starting tonight.
[door opens]
♪ ♪
[thunder rumbles]
Man, it took you guys long enough.
- I brought everything I could find.
- I wanted to make sure Sister Ruth
didn’t catch us sneaking out.
She’s clenched tighter than-- - Okay.
Well, you’re here now.
- Oh.
Okay.
How was my day?
Easily my lifetime top five worst.
Trevor is a total psycho--
Never mind. - Okay.
So I know we’re here to plumb the depths
of the human psyche, but I just wanna say I’m really excited.
I’ve never been to a sleepover with boys before...
or girls.
- [sighs] This is crazy.
How do we even know if he can be broken?
- Look, if Chucky’s taught me anything,
it’s that anyone can be broken.
Let’s do it.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- All right.
Stage one, sensory overload.
[heavy metal music playing]
♪ ♪
[roaring]
- [choking]
Ahh!
- [laughs]
Pass the popcorn.
♪ ♪
[woman screaming]
- These drops will make him crazy.
- Hey, what’s that? What are you doing there?
No. No.
Not the drops!
♪ ♪
[whimpering]
- [man screaming]
[screaming]
- [whimpering]
♪ ♪
[thunder booms]
[speed metal song playing]
♪ ♪
[wet sloshing]
[zapping]
- [panting]
♪ ♪
[gurgling] [vomits]
Oh, God. No more.
- It’s working.
- Oh, it’s gross.
- They call this aversion.
The thought of violence is actually making him sick now.
- So he’s fixed?
- No, he’s ready for stage two.
Nadine, I think we could use your help here.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Aunt Maggie.
Chucky wants to watch the 9:00 news.
- Boop. - Not the unicorns!
No!
No, no, no, no.
[retches]
[cheerful music continues]
[birds chirping]
- ♪ The sun shining through my window ♪
♪ Hop out of bed and meet the day ♪
- [groans softly]
♪ ♪
[phone beeps]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Ah.
[whimpers softly]
Hey.
- Hey, hey, guys. Devon. [snaps]
[Chucky laughs] Guys, wake up. Come on.
Wake up.
Something’s happening. - Hey.
I like to be hugged.
Hi.
I’m Chucky.
Wanna play?
[eerie music]
- Hi. Who are you guys?
I’m Chucky.
- Yeah, we know.
Are you ready to answer our questions?
- Sure.
- Why did you break into the school?
- I don’t know.
- How many Chuckys are there, and what are you planning?
- I don’t know, and I don’t know.
- [sighs]
- Boy, I sure am sorry.
- We didn’t brainwash him. We brain bleached him.
- Well, maybe he needs more time.
I mean, it was a lot.
- Needs more time? Listen to yourself.
That’s Chucky, and he’s playing us.
This whole thing is just an act.
- [laughs] [all gasp]
♪ ♪
[humming]
- There. That’s better.
- Holy shit.
Who untied him?
- Oh, the ropes came loose during "My Little Pony,"
but I didn’t wanna bother anyone.
I’m hungry.
- Aww, it must be from all the vomiting.
- You guys aren’t actually buying this.
We’re talking about a knife-wielding,
murder-happy sociopath.
You know what? I’m done.
- Devon, wait. Come on.
Okay, well, um, I have to talk to him.
Can you watch Chucky for me?
- No. Sorry, I can’t.
I have to go do something.
- I can watch him.
I’m a really good babysitter.
- Oh, no, Nadine.
- No need to worry about me. I took four years of Krav Maga.
Plus I got this bitchin’ knife.
- Who are you?
- [chuckles] - [sighs]
- Um, we’ll be right back.
I’m gonna get Chucky something to eat.
[door shuts]
- [giggles]
- Devon, can you please just talk to me?
- There’s nothing to talk about.
The only safe Chucky is one that’s been killed,
cut into pieces, and burned.
Even that’s not a sure thing.
If you keep him around, someone’s gonna end up dead.
- What if we really changed him?
What if he could help us?
- What if he kills you, Jake?
What am I supposed to do then?
- Devon, look, I need this.
I need to try and do it a different way.
’Cause all I feel is guilt...
all the time,
and I don’t know how much more I can take.
If I really want to forgive myself,
I have to be able to forgive him first.
- [sighs]
This is a mistake.
I can’t lie to you.
I can’t tell you this is right.
- Just promise me...
for now that you won’t do anything to Chucky, okay?
- I promise.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
- [clears throat]
- [gasps]
Oh, Sister Ruth. Hi.
Um, do you know when the nurse will be back?
- I am the nurse.
- You?
Right, for sure.
- Don’t look so surprised, Ms. Cross.
I also teach auto.
- Okay.
I just have a headache.
Do you think I could bother you for an aspirin?
- I don’t see why not.
Nursing was a natural vocation for me.
♪ ♪
I have an excellent bedside manner.
- Alexandra. - Still Lexy.
- Just thinking about our talk from yesterday.
- Really? I’m doing my best to forget it.
- It’s just I’m so worried about you.
First I find out you have a drug problem,
and now you’re scoping out the infirmary.
- What do you want, Trevor?
- I just wanna help you.
I’ve learned so much in here thanks to you and your mom.
Learned that if you wanna survive in a place like this,
you have to put your faith in a higher power.
- Thanks, but no thanks.
Not really in the market for--
- I’m your higher power.
And if you don’t learn that quickly,
I’ll make this place a living hell for you, too.
- Listen...
I’m sorry for my part in sending you here.
I’ve been a bully, too.
I know what it feels like to go around
fucked up on anger and insecurity and fear
and then take it out on everyone else.
But I’m not like that anymore,
and you don’t have to be either.
- Now who’s preaching?
- Don’t do this.
- I own you now.
You think this place is bad?
You fuck up, and I’ll show you how much worse it can get.
[door opens]
- Go to class.
- No, Trevor, I don’t know where you can get condoms.
- Trevor Cain!
- Nice try,
but if it makes you feel any better,
my situation here couldn’t possibly get worse.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
-
I thought you were sick.
You shouldn’t be out of bed if that’s the case.
- Maybe it’s just something I ate.
The food here’s a little--
- Yeah, maybe.
- You’re right, though.
I should get back to bed.
- Or maybe the feeling isn’t biological.
Maybe it’s more philosophical.
- What? - Guilt.
It has a funny way of manifesting in us.
- Uh, I don’t think so.
- You sure about that?
Because sometimes the actions of others
weigh heavy on our souls.
Come with me to the chapel.
Mr. Evans, fix the tie and tuck in the shirt.
♪ ♪
- After my mom died,
my dad got me my cat, Mr. Pasta,
so I’d be less lonely.
I really miss him.
Only child here.
He really is like the brother I never had.
He’s really cuddly,
but he also likes his alone time.
And I respect that boundary.
- Wow.
Mr. Pasta sounds genuinely cool.
- So cool. [laughs] [door opens]
- Okay.
Here you go, buddy.
[light music]
♪ ♪
[bites, munching]
- OMG!
- Calm down, Nadine.
It’s Chucky, not One Direction.
- Mmm!
This is so crisp.
- Okay, that was kinda cute.
Hey, uh, where’s Devon?
- You don’t know?
[eerie music]
- Don’t look at me.
Last I saw him, you were following him out the door.
He never came back.
- Relax, Jake. I’m sure your boyfriend
will grace us with his presence soon.
- I gotta go to class soon.
Do you think you could just
watch Chucky again for me, please?
- I can’t. I also have class.
But I promise I can later.
- [munches, burps]
- Lexi?
- No. What?
- Come on, please. - No.
- So about later,
what’s the plan, here?
Father Bryce said that if we don’t have the doll
back on his desk by the end of the day,
then there’s going to be trouble.
I only say that ’cause I’m supposed to stop
getting in trouble. - Yeah, well,
Father Bryce can screw himself.
- Oh, my. [laughs]
This is fun. [bell rings]
- [sighs] Okay, please, Lexy.
Look, we’re in this together, aren’t we?
- Yes, okay, fine. Just go away.
- Thank you so much. You’re the best.
- Yeah. I’m aware. - [giggles]
- All right, I’ll see you in an hour.
- Hidey-ho.
[door shuts]
♪ ♪
- Devon?
Wait, what are you doing? - [sighs]
- Father Bryce sentenced me to hard labor
till Chucky’s returned.
- What? That’s bullshit.
- You’re telling me.
- Well, you’re gonna need a mani after this.
- Are you really that blind?
- What?
- You’re not the only one going through hell, Jake.
And every minute you keep Chucky around
is another minute we have to suffer.
- [sighs]
Look, I’m sorry.
I’m gonna fix this.
I promise.
All right?
- [humming]
Where do dolls come from?
- That’s a good question.
No idea where you keep coming from.
- What’s your favorite class?
- Napping. - How did you get your hair
so shiny? - Leave-in conditioner.
- Do you have a cat?
- Absolutely not.
- Do you have a boyfriend?
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- I did have a boyfriend.
Once.
- Was he nice? What was his name?
- Junior.
He was the sweetest.
- Junior. I like that name.
♪ Junior, Junior, Junior ♪
♪ Junior, Junior ♪
[tense music]
Where are you going?
♪ ♪
- [panting]
[door slams]
[divider slides open]
- What brings you to Him today, child?
- My roommate, her name’s Lexy.
- Nadine, please, stick to the process.
- Right. Sorry.
Bless me Father for I have sinned.
It’s been three days since my last confession.
Anyway, Lexy’s awesome,
but I think she’s addicted to drugs.
Actually, I know it.
My mom was an addict, and I recognize the signs,
and this time I won’t ignore them.
- Is that all?
- Lexy’s so cool.
Her hair is so shiny.
Have you seen it? It’s hard to miss.
Trevor is still the worst.
I know I’m not supposed to wish ill on people,
but I wouldn’t hate it if he [dialogue becomes distant]
had to sneeze every time he had cereal,
and Cheerios just flew out of his mouth.
- Are you putting God first, child?
Maybe if you focused on-- - Hold on.
I don’t wanna lose my train of thought.
- [sighs] - Oh!
And there’s this doll, Chucky.
He’s alive. I don’t know. - [sighs]
- How can a doll be alive?
The whole idea kinda violates everything
I believe in, right?
- Mm, yes. Right.
[suspenseful music]
- Maybe not actually.
I don’t know, if I believe in the Father and the Son
and the Holy Ghost, it’s not that crazy
to think that there are other spirits
just hanging out
in dolls, right?
♪ ♪
[rosary snaps]
Father O’Malley?
You okay?
- Yes, my child.
- Ah, well, I think that’s it.
For these and all my sins, I am sorry
and ask for God’s forgiveness.
- Okay. Sure. Why not?
- So what’s my penance?
- Ah, 400 Hail Marys.
- 400?
Seems harsh,
but you’re the expert on redemption.
- Yes. Yes, I am, my child.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[bell tolls] - Hail, Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women and blessed
is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death.
Hey, Sister.
[Ethel Cain’s "Family Tree"]
Hail, Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women and blessed
is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners--
- [breathing heavily]
- ♪ Let Christ forgive these bones ♪
♪ I’m hiding ♪
♪ ♪
♪ From no one successfully ♪
♪ Jesus can always reject his father ♪
♪ ♪
- Hail, Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women and blessed
is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners.
- ♪ And try to wash it off ♪
♪ Of his fingers ♪
♪ But he’ll never escape ♪
♪ What he’s made up of ♪
♪ ♪
- Shit. Shit!
- Hail, Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
♪ ♪
Blessed art thou among women...
- ♪ But he cannot escape his mother’s blood ♪
- And blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God, pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death.
- ♪ Wash it off of ♪
♪ His fingers, but he’ll never escape ♪
- Amen.
Lexy?
♪ ♪
Chucky?
[dramatic sting]
[bell tolling]
- Do you have a problem with my decision, Sister Catherine?
- I just think punishing an innocent kid
sends the wrong message.
- What message would you send?
That anything and everything is tolerated?
Did you know about Jake and Devon?
- What do you mean?
- You know exactly what I mean.
- Do I?
- Yes, you do. - You can’t do this to Devon.
- Jake, good to see you, too.
Students aren’t really allowed back here.
- Yeah, sure. - Ah, yes. Great job.
- Why don’t we go to my office?
We can talk about what’s bothering you there.
I have some scriptures that are highlighted.
- Don’t do that.
Devon has done nothing wrong.
He has nothing to do with this.
- Our sins often hurt the people around us
more than they hurt us.
Sister Catherine knows all about that.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Lexy?
Lexy?
Do you wanna talk
or not talk about it?
- [breathing heavily]
[sobs softly]
- Oh, no, Lexy.
- It’s not just this bad day.
It’s a lot of bad days,
and I’m doing my best
to keep it all together because that’s
what’s expected of me.
Cool, chill, funny,
exceptionally good looking,
well-dressed Lexy.
But inside...
inside I’m drowning.
Everything is up to here, and I’m doing my best
to stay afloat, but it’s impossible.
And I hate when Jake and Devon fight...
And I hate that my mom can’t just be normal,
and I hate Trevor and his dumbass face,
and, oh, I fucking hate that doll!
- I’m sorry about today.
I wish all days could be great.
It sucks that they can’t.
It’s not realistic.
And I know I can’t really fix anything.
That’s also not realistic...
but I can be your friend.
And good friends can make it through anything.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
- And now you’re stuck with me.
- Wanna get outta here?
I have a stash of Oreos in our room,
and no one can be sad while eating Oreos.
- Yeah.
Can we just hang here for a bit longer?
I don’t really wanna face the world yet.
♪ ♪
[eerie music]
[door opens]
- Oh, good job, Mr. Evans.
- Sure.
- You’re free to go.
I hope you learned a valuable lesson today.
- What do you mean?
- Jake returned the doll.
- He did? - Yeah, sure did.
- So the doll, it’s in your office, and he’s alone?
- Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Leave it alone, Mr. Evans.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[knocks]
- Lexy? Nadine?
Is anyone in there?
♪ ♪
See you forever, Alexandra.
[door opens]
- [laughs] - [chuckles]
[door slams]
[footsteps pounding]
- Gah!
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[coughs]
♪ ♪
No! No, no, no, no, no, no, please!
Please, please, please!
[whimpers]
- You see?
Oh, I never skip arm day.
[laughs]
[sickening thud]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- [panting]
Oh, my God.
- Oh, dear sweet God
mother of hail Mary Jesus.
Fuck!
- Ohh.
♪ ♪
- Where is Chucky? Did you give him to Bryce?
- No, no. I left him with Lexy.
- You took your eyes off a killer doll?
- I locked the door so he couldn’t get out.
Didn’t I?
Shit. I didn’t realize he’d be so wily.
What are the rules for brainwashed Chucky?
- There are no rules.
- I feel like this friend group
just needs to communicate better.
- Look, Bryce said Chucky was in his office.
He clearly walked out of our room,
killed Trevor, and went downstairs
to keep fucking with us.
- Why was Trevor in here?
- How do we know if this was Chucky, anyways?
- Who else would do this?
I would say Trevor, but you’re currently
standing in a puddle of him.
[knock at door down hallway] - Inspection!
♪ ♪
No running, ladies.
Inspection!
[knocking] - Oh, no.
Inspection.
- Oh, God.
First these uniforms. Now inspections?
- Come on. We’ve gotta hide him.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- Um, you’re not supposed to be here!
[music intensifies]
♪ ♪
- Okay.
[knock at door] - Inspection.
Headache?
- All better.
- Hm.
- Sister Ruth, you know the other day in health class
when we were talking about that one thing?
- Which day?
- Uh, it might have been last month, actually.
Uh, anyways, it really got me spiraling.
Do you think that flesh-eating diseases are a real threat?
I really like jumping in puddles,
but now all I can think about is
bacteria wanting to nibble me.
Sister Ruth, I really need to know.
And, oh, my gosh.
What about brain-eating amoebas?
- All good in here, girls
[door shuts] - [sighs]
- Wait, where are you going?
- Away from this.
- Devon, come on.
Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
♪ Unicorn ♪
♪ I’m the happiest, happiest ♪
♪ Happiest, I’m the happiest ♪
♪ Unicorn ♪
♪ I’m the happiest unicorn ♪
♪ I’m the happiest un-- ♪ [door opens]
Jake?
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[door slams]
- Oh, Jake’s on my list right, all right,
along with Devon and Lexy.
[laughs]
And, you know, I don’t usually eat cream puffs,
but today’s a cheat day.
[cracks knuckles]
[laughs]
♪ ♪
[eerie music]