[gunshot fires]
- I’ve spent some time with you,
I’ve spent some time with Chucky,
and I gotta say I like you better.
[screams]
- I thought you quit.
You seem weird.
- Holy homemade bomb, batgirl.
- Why are you doing this?
- There were 72 of me on that truck.
- This is for Kyle. [engine roars]
[crash]
- Exactly how many of you are left?
- Enough to make this worth the sacrifice.
[suspenseful music]
[screams]
- [giggles] - Gary!
- These kids are responsible for Gary’s death.
- [screams] - It was a tragic accident.
I’ve done some work with troubled youth
at the School of the Incarnate Lord.
- He blew himself up.
He’s never done anything like that before.
No matter what, he’s gonna come for us again.
- Guys, why does this place look so familiar?
- Charles Lee Ray lived here when he was our age.
- Welcome to Incarnate Lord.
Do you know why you’re here?
- ’Cause God hates us?
- He wants you to seek forgiveness
and to find your way back to him.
- [evil chuckling]
[ominous music]
[crow cawing]
♪ ♪
- [yawns] Mm.
[grunts, sighs]
[chilling music]
[whimpers]
♪ ♪
No.
No, no.
[whimpering]
[screams]
♪ ♪
[crows caw]
[elevator dings]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [humming]
Good morning, sweet face!
Rise and shine!
- What was that screaming?
- Oh, I’m sorry, Nica.
I didn’t mean to disturb you.
I was just--it was--
[grunting]
I--I had a bad dream.
- Well, that was probably your fucking conscience.
- Breakfast!
I don’t want to argue, Nica,
not when I’m so happy.
Are you happy?
Are you as happy as you make me?
- Take a wild guess.
- Uh-oh.
Somebody woke up on the wrong side of bed this morning.
[chuckles]
Come on now. What’s the matter?
- You chopped off my arms and legs, you lunatic.
- We’ve been through this before.
I cut off Chucky’s arms and legs,
so he can never come between us ever again.
- You kept me prisoner in this house for a year.
- We never have to leave here. Look around.
Everybody says Jennifer Tilly has impeccable taste.
- You’re not Jennifer Tilly.
- Another reason why you can never leave.
[giggles]
[plate clacks]
Now, if you’ll excuse me, Nica,
I need to speak with him.
[grunting]
[chilling music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[laughs]
Hiya, doll.
- Hello, Chucky.
What the fuck is this?
- [cackling]
[inhales sharply]
Oh, oh, I’m coming for you, Tiff.
You only think I’m stuck in that chair.
You’re gonna pay
for what you did to me, doll.
You and those kids,
you’re all dead.
♪ I’m gonna see you all rotting in the ground ♪
[laughs]
[cackles]
[playful spooky music]
♪ ♪
- "As Jesus came down from the mountain
"to meet with his disciples,
"a man beseeched him, ’Teacher..."
- ♪ The one with the power’s the one with the crown ♪
- "’By an unclean spirit.’"
- ♪ Ashes, ashes, it all burns down ♪
- "’And does of unspeakable things.’"
- ♪ Watch what you say and who you say it to ♪
- "’But I beg you, can you show my poor boy compassion?’"
- ♪ You never know who’s sneaking up on you ♪
- "’Is it possible still to redeem him?’
"Jesus replied, ’Oh, faithless generation,
"’how often must I tell you?
"’Anything is possible if you choose the Lord.’"
"Then, Jesus rebuked the unclean spirit.
"I command you, release this child.
Be gone, and never return!’"
"Then, Jesus took the boy by the hand, raised him up,
and he was saved."
This is the Gospel of the Lord.
all: Praise be to you, Lord Jesus Christ.
- So what does it mean?
- ♪ Turncoats and traitors ♪
- It’s a metaphor,
and I just--
I love metaphors.
Sin is a choice.
♪ ♪
- ♪ They sharpen their knives ♪
- It’s not complicated.
It’s primitive.
It’s that--it’s that devil on our shoulder
tempting us with sex, drugs, and whatever.
God is a choice too.
Confession is a choice.
And on God’s team, every confession
is a victory, because every confession
is someone who has made a choice
to take one step closer to God.
And God sure does love a winner.
[dramatic music]
- I despise sports metaphors.
- Peace be with you. all: And also with you.
- Let us offer each other the sign of peace.
- Peace be with you.
Hi, I’m Nadine.
- Hi.
- So what you in for?
- He who eats my flesh and drinks my blood abides in me,
and I in him.
[organ plays] [bell chimes]
♪ ♪
- Now what do we do? Do we go up?
- You Catholic?
- No, I don’t think so.
- Oh, then just hang here with me.
- You’re a heathen too?
- Oh no, I’m Catholic, but I sinned this morning.
I can’t take Communion again until I make my confession
to Father O’Malley.
- What did you do?
♪ ♪
- The body of Christ. - Amen.
There. That’s him.
That’s Trevor.
- That altar boy? - Trust me.
He’s evil,
and he’s brilliant.
He could teach Chucky a thing or two.
- The body of Christ.
The body of Christ.
- Phones.
♪ ♪
- Children.
Size four.
- Zero. - Not here, you’re not.
[eerie music]
- I have to wear this every day?
- [laughs] Welcome to my world.
And you’ll have to brush that hair
and take all the makeup off your face.
You look like Madonna,
and not the good one.
Ah.
Waist?
- 27.
- Young man, you’re underweight.
- Thank you.
- Good morning, Father. - Good morning.
- That was a wonderful homily.
- Thank you.
Hi.
I’m Father Bryce, headmaster at Incarnate Lord.
You must be Ms. Cross, Mr. Evans, and Mr. Wheeler.
Do you know why you’re here?
- Because God wants us to seek forgiveness
and to find our way back to him.
- Very good, Sister Elizabeth.
- Actually, I told them that.
I met with them when they arrived this morning.
- Oh Father, I started cataloguing everything
in the Christmas toy drive.
- I thought you were doing that.
- It’s still weeks away.
- Well, that’s wonderful, Sister Elizabeth.
No time like the present.
Sister Ruth, who don’t you go help Edward in the kitchen?
Sister Catherine and I will show
these kids to their rooms.
Follow me.
[soft dramatic music]
- By the way, Sister,
we received a new donation this morning
for your toy drive.
- Oh, how wonderful.
Who from? - Doesn’t say.
♪ ♪
- What?
- Don’t you see it?
Don’t you see him?
Our Lord’s image, plain as day,
right here in this doll’s face.
- Didn’t you see his image in a taco at lunch last week?
- That was different.
- Speaking of tacos,
hadn’t you be getting down to the kitchen?
- The girls’ dormitory is here on the second floor.
Boys are up on three.
Officially, you are not allowed to fraternize,
but I think I finally convinced Father Bryce
that simply isn’t realistic these days.
Just make sure you leave your door open if your male friends
are in your room.
- Don’t worry, we’re all perfectly safe here
when it comes to Jake and Devon.
- Oh.
- Hi, roomie.
That bed’s yours.
- I’d actually prefer the bed closer to the door.
You don’t mind, do you?
- I--I need to be close to the bathroom on account
of my bladder condition.
- Oh, don’t worry, she’s doing great.
She hasn’t wet the bed in weeks.
I’ll let you get settled in.
- Fellas, come on. [claps]
Let’s pick up the pace.
Boys are up here.
The girls are on two.
No fraternizing in the girls’ rooms.
No exceptions. - No problem.
- Young people today are bombarded
with empty messages of love.
- Hey, Devon, I think we should keep us
on the down low around here. - Fuck that.
- Look, Catholics aren’t exactly down with the gays.
- Avoid temptations of the opposite sex
until you’re mature enough to handle
the consequences, you know?
- Look, if we screw up, they’re gonna send us to juvie.
["Sugar & Spice" by Boyfriend & Pyra]
- ♪ Sticks and stones may break my bones, but ♪
- Gentlemen.
- [whispering] ♪ They won’t stop me ♪
♪ Sticks and stones may break my bones, but ♪
- You’re so pretty.
- Not for long.
- I’ve never been friends with someone so glam before.
- And now you never will be.
- Oh, please.
You don’t need all that makeup.
You’re just naturally glam.
- No.
I mean, we’re not going to be friends.
I don’t need any more friends.
They just move away,
get busy,
fall in love,
and they couldn’t possibly understand what
I’m going through, anyway.
Besides, I don’t plan on being here very long.
- No one ever does.
- How long have you been here?
- Since seventh grade.
My parents couldn’t control me.
- Really?
♪ ♪
Nadine, why are you here?
- Why are you here, Lexy?
I’ll tell you my secrets if you tell me yours.
- ♪ Break my bones, but they won’t stop me ♪
♪ Sticks and stones may break my bones ♪
- Trust me, you don’t want to know.
- ♪ Sugar and spice and everything nice ♪
♪ That’s what I like and what I’m made of ♪
♪ Nightmares and crimes and everything grime ♪
♪ ♪
- So we’re roommates.
- I’m sure you boys are anxious to get
on the straight and narrow,
get your lives back on track, back on the right track,
back on the fast track to God.
- I just love sports metaphors.
- Me too.
Get those clothes off and get dressed.
Class starts in ten minutes.
And gentlemen,
don’t be late.
[door shuts]
- [panting]
- Hey. It’s okay, Jake.
- [sobs]
It’s all my fault.
[crying] It’s all my fault.
- No, it’s not.
[indistinct chatter]
- Shit.
- You know Trevor?
- Knockoff Draco Malfoy?
Unfortunately.
[sighs] Okay.
I just need to come out swinging.
Show him who’s boss.
[door creaks]
[suspenseful music]
Hi. I’m Lexy.
I’m an old friend of Trevor’s.
Hey, did you know he was born with only one testicle?
- [stifles laughter] - [chuckles]
Or so he told me in fourth grade.
- And you promised you’d never tell.
- Oops.
- Look, Alexandra.
- Lexy.
I made your life a living hell back in the day,
and for that I’m truly sorry.
I hope you can forgive me.
For what it’s worth, I’m not the same person
as I was back then.
- So who are you?
- Someone who’s not ashamed of having only one testicle,
I guess.
- Banish anxiety from your heart
and cast off the troubles of your body.
- For youth and vigor are meaningless.
- Ecclesiastes 11:10.
- I can only imagine what you’ve gone through
this past year.
Everyone’s talking about it.
All those murders.
Dating a deranged killer
and that poor soul taken in your own home...
but I think the Lord brought you here
so I can finally make things right with you.
And I thank God for the opportunity.
It’d be a sin to waste it.
Peace be with you.
[eerie music]
- You can see how Hieronymus Bosch,
in his typical surrealist mode, depicts the seven deadly sins,
starting with wrath at bottom, and then moving clockwise,
we get envy,
greed,
gluttony,
sloth,
lust,
and finally, pride.
Can anyone tell me what the outer four
circles represent,
the so-called "last four things"?
Jake.
- They represent the four wages of sin:
death, judgement, heaven, and hell.
- That’s very good, Jake.
You’re familiar with the surrealists.
- A little.
I’m more familiar with the wages of sin.
- But why should we, as Catholics,
need to worry about this if we can just
go to confession and be forgiven?
- I’m gonna let you guys in on a little secret.
You know, despite what Father Bryce said in his homily
this morning, in my experience, sin isn’t really simple.
It’s actually super complicated.
Good people do bad things
for all kinds of screwed-up reasons.
It’s important for all of us to examine those reasons
and not treat confession like a hot shower.
Redemption can’t really happen
without a long, hard look in the mirror.
Any more questions?
- Are there any sins that are just...unforgivable?
- Well, I sure hope not,
because then I’m really in trouble.
[laughter]
Okay, page 43.
♪ ♪
- Hi. I’m Chucky.
Wanna play? - Not particularly.
♪ ♪
[footsteps]
- Boo! - [screaming]
- [chuckling] Oh, stop.
Really? Just looking at me
is scary enough to give you a heart attack?
- [out of breath] Oh, God.
- Oh, my God, thank you!
You made my day.
[laughing]
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
That’s vampires, right?
[snarling]
[tense choir music]
♪ ♪
Hi. I’m Chucky.
Wanna pray?
- [grunts]
- [cackling]
♪ ♪
[cackling]
[camera clicks]
[bell tolling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Shit.
- [gasps]
- Look at him. He’s taunting us.
- He isn’t doing anything.
- That’s what I mean. It’s diabolical.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[keys jangle]
- Could I have your attention, please?
Sister Elizabeth has been called home.
God rest her soul.
all: God rest her soul.
- Apparently, it was a heart attack.
Now, I know you’ll all keep her in your prayers,
but the best way to honor her is by honoring God.
So let’s get back to class, and let’s get busy.
Idle hands are the Devil’s playground.
I will be taking the sister’s classes
for the rest of the day, starting with study hall.
Thank you.
Okay.
- Okay. Children, to class.
- I can talk to you guys now.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- What do we do?
- We can’t tell anyone.
They’ll lock us in a mental hospital
and throw away the key.
- I say we make a run for it.
I mean, this isn’t a gulag.
There are no armed guards.
We’re not gonna get shot or anything.
Right?
- We have nowhere else to go.
So let’s just stand our ground,
give Chucky what’s coming to him.
- This is all my fault. If I never bought the fucker
at the yard sale in the first place,
none of this would have happened.
My dad, your dad, your mom,
Gary.
- Jake, stop blaming yourself, okay?
Chucky did it. He’s the asshole here.
- I can’t let anyone else die, especially you guys.
I have to get in there.
- You people lost?
- No, Father.
- Look, I know your history.
Dr. Mixter filled me in.
It’s just a doll.
I’ll see you three in study hall.
Now.
♪ ♪
- That guy reminds me of my dad.
- Yes. - Yes!
- No! - [laughs]
"If I get sole custody of the kids,
that’s another 10 grand in child support."
- You just won $11 million! - Hey!
- Hey! - Hey!
- I’m the victim here. - "I’m the victim here!
"You said it yourself.
Now, I’m gonna hit him where it hurts!"
[laughing]
"Hit him where it hurts."
- You do realize that that’s not you.
- Of course.
Jennifer Tilly did this role long before I took over.
- This is just sad.
- What?
- This--sitting here,
watching old Jennifer Tilly movies over and over.
When was the last time you booked a job?
- Nica, I told you,
we have everything we need right here in this house.
- Yeah, but at the rate you’re going,
you’re gonna lose this house.
I know you went through
all of Jennifer Tilly’s "Simpsons" money.
- [chuckles]
- How does someone go through $100 million?
- It’s not easy being me.
It’s not cheap being me either.
- Bullshit! Bullshit!
You know, when you first brought me here,
I thought-I thought I was gonna be
living with a real movie star. - Mm.
- Some glamorous and exciting.
Instead, I got this.
I got you-- a washed up imposter,
obsessed with her own fake past.
You need to get out of this house and get a job, Tiffany.
- [laughs] So you can escape?
Nice try, Nica.
- How the fuck am I gonna escape?
- Oh, that reminds me,
my darling Glen and Glenda are coming by this weekend
for their birthday celebration, so you know the drill.
It’s either the ball gag or the chloroform.
Your choice.
Oh shit, we’re all out of chloroform.
How did that happen?
[doorbell rings]
Oh my god. That’s not the gate.
It’s the front door.
- Help! Help me!
- Shh. - Help me!
- Shh. Shh. - Please help!
- Shh. Shh. You’re gonna ruin everything.
What is wrong with you? Shh.
- [cries]
- H--Hello?
- Oh, my God.
Ms. Tilly,
I am sorry to bother you, but I am a huge fan.
- H-how did you get past the gate?
- I climbed over the wall.
- Well, this is private property.
I’m calling the cops.
- Oh, Detective Sam Gavin.
- Oh.
- Beverly Hills Police, but I’m also a fan.
- Okay. Well, in that case,
Officer, maybe you would like to take a selfie with me?
- Detective, and, you know, I would love that.
But I’m actually here because of a missing person.
Ms. Tilly, have you ever heard--
- No.
- Ms. Tilly, have you ever heard--
- No. No. No. No.
- Ms. Tilly, have you ever heard of Nica Pierce?
- Oh!
Nica Pierce.
Yes, I believe I met her
when I visited that mental hospital back east.
You know, that’s one of the causes
I’m most passionate about--
women with mental health issues.
- Then you’re aware that-- - No.
- Well, shortly after your visit...
- Uh-huh. - She killed several people.
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
- And then she escaped.
- I can’t believe they’d be stupid enough
to let her escape.
Well--oh, you’re still here.
I mean--
- Yeah-- - Okay, bye.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Yes, Mr. Wheeler?
- Can I use the restroom?
- I don’t know, can you?
"May I go to the restroom, Father?"
- May I?
- You have exactly five minutes.
- Five minutes?
- Jake, you can’t just--
- You two can wait.
One pass, zero mischief.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- All right, you fucking asshole.
- Really, Mr. Wheeler?
[dramatic music]
Back in the old days,
we would have washed your mouth out with soap.
♪ ♪
We have different methods of teaching lessons now.
- You’ve suffered great pain in your young life,
but you’ve also caused great pain.
You know why? - I’m sure you’ll tell me.
- Because you’re lost
like every other kid that comes through my door,
but this place isn’t a prison, Jake.
Here, you don’t have to be an orphan anymore.
You can choose to be a son again,
of the Heavenly Father.
Lay down your burdens and let Him do the heavy lifting.
Just let go...
and let God.
All you gotta do is stop fighting.
- I’ll never stop fighting.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Your first Bible is something you’ll never forget.
I remember my father calling me into his study,
which usually meant I was in a world of trouble.
But on this day, he handed me the good book,
and he said, "Son, I want you to flip through these pages
"until you find a passage that speaks to you.
"And then, I want you to come back,
and I want you to read it to me."
I spent many nights with my father after that...
going through these sacred lessons.
Some of the best memories of my life.
This is yours now.
It’s time for you to find a passage that speaks to you.
[eerie music]
- Wait. Wait. What?
- I’ll check with you at the end of the period.
Maybe you could read me something.
- You can’t just leave me here.
- Do the work, Jake.
You won’t regret it.
♪ ♪
- Wait.
[panting]
♪ ♪
[footsteps]
- Thank you, Sister. - Father.
- Yes, Mr. Evans.
- I was just wondering where Jake is.
- Why is that?
- Well, he said I could look at his notes
from the sermon this morning.
- The homily.
- Right. Right. Homily.
- Well, that’s very charitable of him,
but you’re gonna have to wait.
- Where is he?
- He’s exactly where he should be.
And so are you.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
It’s just us now.
How many of you survived that crash?
♪ ♪
Oh, come on. This is stupid.
I know it’s you. Just talk to me.
All right. Have it your way.
♪ ♪
[camera clicks]
- Gotcha. [laughs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[laughs]
- Where’s the doll?
- I honestly have no idea.
- Did you even open it?
Open.
Turn to John 8:44.
Read it to me.
Loud and clear.
- [sighs]
"You are from your father, the Devil,
"and you choose to do your father’s desires.
"He was a murderer from the beginning
"and does not stand in the truth,
"because there is no truth in him.
"When he lies, he speaks according to his own nature,
for he is a liar, and the father of lies."
- I encourage you to choose the right father.
Now, where is the doll?
- I told you, I don’t know.
Can I go now?
- Thank God.
What happened?
- He got away.
- Shit!
- He took my picture. - What?
- He had this phone, and he took my picture
and he ran up the chimney.
Didn’t even try to hurt me or anything.
- Why would he do that? - No idea.
- Great.
Another killer doll with a shady plan.
’Cause that worked out so well the last time.
- Whatever he’s doing, we have to find him fast.
[eerie music]
[ominous music]
- There’s no lock?
- They only lock from the outside.
School policy.
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
- What the hell is all this shit?
- Look, I--
I steal things sometimes.
That’s why I’m here.
The really good stuff is under the bed.
- I mean, everyone’s got their secrets.
- What’s your secret?
- My mother is the antichrist.
- Moms are the worst.
- Here. Help me move this in front of the door.
- Why would we be moving the dresser in front of the door?
- Because I sleepwalk.
- Cool.
Hey, that’s your thing.
- My thing?
- Your secret.
- Yeah. Right.
Don’t tell anyone.
- Cross my heart.
♪ ♪
[camera clicks]
- [sniffs]
[coughs]
♪ ♪
[scraping]
- [screams] - [screams]
- [screams]
- Lexy!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What’s going on? - [gasping]
- Nadine. - Open this door.
- Now, I know this is intense, and you may be wondering
what’s going on--
- I know exactly what’s going on.
God’s punishing me for being a klepto,
but I found the doll in the stairwell.
He was a ginger just like me. - I know.
- And he was just so adorable
that I couldn’t help by myself and--
- You need to listen to me, okay?
Say nothing. - But--
- Nothing!
[people muttering]
- I want to know what’s going on right now.
- Of course. What would you like to know?
- Why were you screaming?
- Because I was scared. - Scared of what?
- What’s going on here? What’s happening?
- I was scared of...
♪ ♪
Bathroom.
- You were scared of the bathroom?
- No.
No.
I was scared of never seeing my old bathroom again.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Okay. - It was a great bathroom.
- You’re lucky to have a bathroom at all, young lady.
- Sister, please.
You’ll do well here,
and if you’re open to God’s teachings...
♪ ♪
- [panting]
- Where the hell could he be?
- I have no idea.
- [screams] - Jake!
[chilling music]
- [screams] [grunts]
[knife clatters]
[groans]
♪ ♪
[screams]
Oh.
Get off me, you brute!
Get off!
- What are you doing here?
- That’s for me to know and you to find out.
- Why’d you take Jake’s picture?
- Picture? What picture?
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
♪ ♪
- How many of you are left?
- Fuck you. I’m not telling you shit.
[spits]
[laughs]
- Hey!
I think I know what Chucky’s up to.
- Does he eat?
- I think so.
- Does he sleep?
- I have no idea.
- So, does he, like, go to the bathroom?
- God, I hope not.
There they are.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
What happened? Did you get him?
She knows. It’s okay, she’s cool.
So is he dead or what?
- We have something to show you.
Come on.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What the hell? Why didn’t you kill him?
- Think about it.
Ever since he got here, Chucky’s been acting weird.
- Mm-mm. - He took pictures of me.
He’s been taking pictures all over the school.
And every chance he got to kill one of us,
he ran away instead. Why?
- Because that’s not his job.
- Exactly. This Chucky isn’t an assassin.
He’s a scout. - Like a Boy Scout?
- Mm.
- No, like-- like a scout in war.
He’s collecting information for someone.
- [muffled speech]
- Who?
- That’s what we’re gonna find out.
- [muffled speech]
[tense music]
[oven door squeaks]
- Ahh.
- I love birthdays, don’t you?
[alarm beeps]
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh! That’s the gate!
[buzzer buzzes] [laughs]
They’re here! The twins are here!
[elevator dings]
- Tiffany, Tiffany, you don’t need to do this.
- It’s not that I don’t trust you,
but I still don’t know how that head got inside my bed.
- What? What are you talking about?
- I’m talking about Chucky. [laughs]
Maybe the two of you
are talking about me behind my back.
Maybe the two of you are plotting against me
deep inside that pretty little head of yours.
[laughs] Okay.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
[dramatic music]
[doorbell rings]
Coming!
I’m coming! I’m coming!
Hi. - Hi.
Remember me? Detective Sam Gavin?
I’m sorry to bother you again, Ms. Tilly,
but something’s just not adding up.
♪ ♪
- I think she’s starting to suspect something.
- If she finds out we’re working together,
it’s all over.
- Listen, asshole, the only reason
I even tolerate you being here is because I have to.
- After all we’ve been through? Come on, Nica.
Admit it. I’m growing on you.
- Like leprosy.
- You need me if we’re gonna get out of here.
- What I really need is I need to get you out of my head.
And I need to Tiffany to get what’s coming to her.
- You see, Nica? We do have something in common.
♪ ♪
- I think Nica Pierce is here.
- Oh!
You’re right, Officer, Nica Pierce is here,
but she’s innocent, I swear.
- That’s not for us to decide, Jennifer.
- Ms. Tilly. - Ms. Tilly.
- I guess deep down,
I always knew this day would come and--
- May I come in, Ms. Tilly?
- Be my guest.
- Thank you. - Mm-hmm.
[bird chirps]
[door slams]
[crow caws] [chuckles]
To tell the truth, I’m kind of relieved.
Officer Gavin, have you ever found yourself
in a position where you have to go against your own values
and everything you believe in as a human being
and a Christian to protect someone you love?
- Yeah, actually--
- Ha!
- [grunts, gasps]
- [laughs]
Not me.
Values are for losers.
[laughing]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[keypad beeps]
[call button buzzes]
Shit.
[The Slits’ "I Heard It Through the Grapevine"]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I bet, I bet, I bet ♪
♪ I bet you’re wondering how I knew ♪
♪ ’Bout your plans to make me blue ♪
♪ With some other guy you knew before ♪
♪ We’re two of a kind, you know I love you more ♪
♪ It took me by surprise I must say ♪
♪ When I found out yesterday ♪
- [panting]
- ♪ I heard it through the grapevine ♪
♪ Not much longer will you be mine ♪
- [timid chuckle]
[sighs]
Glen. Glenda.
It’s so nice to see your sweet faces.
♪ ♪
- ♪ I’m just about to lose my mind ♪
[playful spooky music]
♪ ♪