- Previously on "Chucky"...
- Last chance.
How many of you are there?
- My situation here
couldn’t possibly get worse.
- In order
to forgive ourselves,
first, we have to forgive those
who have sinned against us.
- If I really wanna
forgive myself,
I have to be able
to forgive him first.
- [vomits]
- We call this aversion.
The thought of violence is
actually making him sick now.
- Hi, I’m Chucky.
We didn’t brainwash him.
We brain bleached him.
- Don’t you see him?
Our Lord’s image plain
as day right here
in this doll’s face.
- I’m not going. I can’t.
Mom needs help.
We all do.
Just ask her,
"Who’s Tiffany Valentine?"
- No!
[sobbing]
- See you forever, Alexandra.
- How do we know
if this was Chucky anyways?
- Who else would do this?
I would say Trevor,
but you’re currently standing
in a puddle of him.
- [humming]
- I don’t usually
eat cream puffs.
But today is a cheat day.
[suspenseful music]
[cackling]
[ominous tone]
♪ ♪
Beautiful, aren’t they?
This one is for Lexy.
- [gasps]
- Just picture it jutting
out of her heart. [laughs]
If that little bitch
had a heart.
- Don’t you ever say her name.
Lexy’s my friend.
They’re all my friends.
- My God.
What the hell did those
monsters do to you, soldier?
- I knew it.
There’s another one.
- This one here is for Devon.
This jagged blade is gonna make
him scream like a little girl.
[laughs]
[pounding on door]
- [gasps]
- And these are for you
and your good buddy, Jake.
Friends till the fuckin’ end.
[laughs]
- [snarls]
♪ ♪
[screams]
- Ah!
- [grunts]
- Ha.
[intense music]
What the fuck, Chuck?
How did you get
to be such a wuss?
- I found something
better than killing.
[angelic choir singing]
- Don’t tell me.
You found it in there?
- [gasps]
- Chucky, open the door!
- [Chucky grunts]
- Chucky?
Chucky?
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- Ahh!
- [laughs]
[shimmering tone]
- Chucky!
Hey, you leave him alone.
- Face it.
You’re not good, Chucky.
- I am Good Chucky.
I am.
- Good Chucky.
- No.
You’re supposed
to be a killer, like me.
- [grunts]
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
- Jake.
There’s nothing you can do,
okay?
Just let them take
each other out.
- Ah! Ah! Ah!
- Look, I gotta help him.
- Ahh!
- Chucky?
Chucky, are you okay?
- [whimpering]
- You give us a bad name.
You’re weak, pathetic.
You’re nothing.
You’re the Chucky
no one will remember.
- Chucky, let me help you!
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Ah!
[gasps]
- I’m the Chucky
I choose to be,
asshole.
- [grumbles]
[both scream]
- [grunts]
[whimpering]
- Yah!
- Ohh, ahh--
[exhales weakly]
[intense organ music]
- [retches, vomits]
[humming]
[groans weakly]
How--how did I do, coach?
- You did great, Good Chucky.
- [sighs]
[playful spooky music]
♪ ♪
- Good Chucky, huh?
Look at what he did, Jake.
He’s a killing machine.
- Devon, he saved our lives.
He saved us from Chucky.
- He is Chucky.
- [sighs] I feel like
I don’t even know
how to talk to you anymore.
It’s like I don’t
even know you.
- What are you talking about?
- Jake, we’re supposed to
see each other every weekend.
And now, we’re
at the fucking Sistine Chapel,
as created by everyone’s
favorite homicidal maniac.
He killed Trevor.
How long before he kills
someone you love, again?
- It was that Chucky
who killed Trevor.
And that was a different Chucky
who killed Gary, not him.
- Gary’s never
coming back, Jake.
But you still have me.
And I’m not gonna let
Chucky take you, too.
There is no Good Chucky.
[tense music]
- Huh?
♪ ♪
That was awkward.
- Devon!
I find this act
of blasphemy deeply disturbing.
[knife clatters]
- [sighs] God damn it.
- [spraying]
- [breathing shakily]
- What are we gonna do, Lexy?
What are we gonna
do about [whispers] Trevor?
I mean, can we bury him?
No, we can’t bury him--
it.
Can we bury it/him?
- It’s just--it’s not fair.
- You don’t look so good.
I’m worried about you.
- You’re worried about me?
There’s a corpse in the closet
and a killer doll on the loose.
I’m worried about me.
Fuck, Nadine!
Don’t.
I’m going to the bathroom.
I need to be alone.
[door slams]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[door creaks open]
- [sobbing]
- If you don’t quit
while you’re ahead,
you’re going to die.
- I don’t know what you’re
talking about, Nadine.
- I do know something
about what
you’re going through, Lexy.
I’ve seen it close-up before.
Have you ever had a pet
that was your bestie?
I had five gerbils.
I got one each birthday,
and soon after,
I would get home from school,
and my mom would tell me
that they ran away.
And each one of those days,
I would feel like
my world was over.
I couldn’t figure it out.
Why would they leave me?
But the fifth gerbil, Houdini,
was there when I got back.
Fourth grade.
Mom had left the cage open,
and he was scurrying around
on the floor.
She was passed out,
and she wouldn’t
wake up that time.
I don’t think she ever wanted
me to have any of them at all.
But you know how moms are.
They do their best
to make you happy, right?
Can you open the door now?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- I’m sorry.
[sniffles]
I’m so sorry.
- It’s okay.
It’s gonna be okay.
- You know, doing the right
thing should be a crime.
♪ ♪
[grunts]
Oh, okay. Oh, okay.
You know what?
You trying to kill me?
- I’m not, but about that.
- Yeah, right.
Me and those two dorks have
taken down Chucky before,
and we’re gonna do it again.
You believe me, don’t you?
- Of course
I believe in you, Lexy.
Mr. Pasta would have a lot
to say about this whole mess.
- Yeah.
What would he say?
- Don’t be silly, Lexy.
Cats can’t talk.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[faint screaming]
[screaming]
- [gasps]
[light tense music]
♪ ♪
[evil laughter]
- I’m contesting custody.
- What?
- If I get sole custody
of the kids,
that’s another 10 grand
in child support payments.
- You just won $11 million.
- Hey, I’m the victim here.
You said it yourself.
Now I’m gonna hit him
where it hurts.
- Mom.
- What?
- We need to talk.
- Glen, there’s nothing to say.
Excuse me.
Can you move a little?
I’m trying to watch my show.
Glen, what are you doing?
- You don’t get
to play the victim here.
You murder people.
- Glen, it’s an addiction.
Have a little compassion.
I can’t help it.
I just like to murder people.
Is that so bad?
- I don’t even know
who you are anymore.
- And I don’t know
who the child
in front of me is, either.
The child I know would
never betray their mother.
- What did you expect me to do,
just act like you
keeping a prisoner
who you dismembered was normal?
[tense music]
Let’s just start with who
Nica is and what happened.
- If you must know,
Nica’s my girlfriend.
And sometimes your father.
- Stop lying to me!
- Don’t use that tone to me.
I may be a murderess,
but I’m still your mother.
- Okay, Mom,
who’s Tiffany Valentine?
- I’m not saying anything
until you tell me
where Glenda took Nica.
♪ ♪
No? No?
All of a sudden,
you have nothing to say.
All right, I’m out of here.
♪ ♪
Enjoy the show, sweet face.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Maybe it’s a miracle?
- [humming]
- Hey, you know,
you saved us back there.
I mean,
you’re basically my hero.
- Just doing my job.
[soft music]
- So what did it feel like
when you killed him?
- Like I finally
knew what I was for.
♪ ♪
- Um--
Here.
♪ ♪
There you go.
All better, Boy Wonder.
- Holy hematoma, Batman.
The Joker got me good.
- And the citizens of Gotham
will pay us in chocolate.
- [sighs]
- My sweet baby boy.
- Uh, what’s going on?
- Trevor’s gone.
- Wait.
What do you mean Trevor’s gone?
- As in not
in the place we left him.
- What happened to him?
- Good Chucky was saving us
from this other Chucky
that was stalking the halls.
- My sweet baby.
That mean, mean man isn’t ever
going to hurt you ever again.
- You guys seen Devon?
- No, but...
we don’t know how many
Chuckys are out there.
What if one found Devon?
- No, he’s fine.
He’s just being dramatic
and punishing me.
- I know you guys are going
through a rough patch,
but you love each other.
Will you please
stop fighting that?
We’ve got actual things
to fight against.
- Yeah.
Who would take
Trevor’s body, though?
- An ally?
- Or an enemy?
♪ ♪
- I’ve tried so hard, Devon,
with you and your friends.
I’ve given you the benefit
of the doubt time and again.
But, clearly, your particular
brand of wickedness
is going to need a firmer hand
to be corrected.
- You’re absolutely right,
Father.
How could I
possibly convince a believer
of supernatural evil?
It must just be a series
of violent, elaborate pranks
pulled off
by some traumatized teenagers.
- Open Leviticus,
and read it.
[eerie choir music]
♪ ♪
- Father Bryce,
I have asked you repeatedly
not to interrupt me when I’m
in session with the students.
My time here is precious.
- This couldn’t wait.
- Sin never waits.
Does it, Father?
- Sin never waits, does it?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Who should we blame for this?
Please, tell me.
Sister Catherine?
No smart tongue today?
How convenient.
Dr. Mixter, what about you?
Weren’t you the one
that recommended
these violent kids be admitted
here in the first place?
And where have you been
during their reign of terror
throughout these hallways,
this sick abandon
of everything holy,
what God is trying
to tell them,
what I, Dr. Mixter,
am trying to help them see?
♪ ♪
Do you not take
any responsibility?
♪ ♪
- Father--
- As always, I have stepped in
and done what
you are too weak to do.
That’s why Devon
is currently reading the Bible
in the chapel by himself.
And that’s where
he will remain until--
- Father Bryce,
is that really necessary?
Maybe these kids need
someone to talk to.
I mean, are you punishing him
for blasphemy
or for creative prowess?
- Why not both?
- Because curiosity
isn’t a sin.
Challenging the institutions
that guide us
should be encouraged,
not rejected.
- Sister Catherine,
not everything is a challenge.
Dr. Mixter,
please help me out here.
- Actually,
I do agree with Father Bryce.
This is a display of violence
and casual pageantry,
and it crosses the line.
- Spare me.
If you’re feeling a lack
of control of the student body,
maybe it’s because
you’re lacking it, Father.
Devon is a traumatized kid.
- This isn’t trauma.
This is evil.
- Evil.
- Sister Ruth, please.
- I did not become
a Sister to validate
or answer to your fits
of self-righteousness.
This is not an inquisition.
- That’s exactly what it is,
an inquisition by me.
- Those medieval relics
look good in this office.
Maybe next time, we can burn a
kid at the stake. Hm.
[tense tone]
♪ ♪
- Devon has--
Devon has exhausted his options
here in Incarnate Lord.
Maybe they can straighten
him out in a youth facility.
- I disagree with you.
I think I can still help him.
- I hope you’re right.
Sister Ruth,
get rid of that abomination.
- Yes, Father.
♪ ♪
- Not here, Sister Ruth.
- Yes, Father.
- Get it out of my sight.
♪ ♪
[driving rock music]
- This is bullshit.
♪ ♪
- So, Meg,
did you enjoy the party?
- It was--
it was certainly dramatic.
- Thank you.
- I hope Glenda
comes back soon.
Don’t you, Glen?
- Yes.
Where did that
sibling get off to?
It’s so seldom
we see the two of you apart.
You know, once I caught
them trying to board a plane
to England, alone.
They are such a bonded pair.
They certainly
can be a handful. [laughs]
- So could we
when we were younger.
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah.
- You remember
that time in high school
when we snuck out to meet
with the Dean brothers?
- Yes, yes.
- What were their names?
- I don’t--
[stammering]
- Chandler and Ram?
- What? Ra--
[laughs]
It was so long ago.
It was almost like
we were different people.
I wanna be Jennifer Tilly.
I wanna be a star.
[chanting]
And switch and switch,
switch, switch, switch.
So how long
are you planning to stay?
- As long as it takes.
- Oh, oh, dear.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, okay. Hm--
[stammers]
If you’ll excuse me
for a minute, I just--
I’ll get--I’ll be right back.
And--ooh.
Uh-uh.
Nosy, nosy, nosy.
[giggles]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[humming]
More bills.
Do you have a check for me?
♪ ♪
Hm, isn’t that precious?
Nice try, Jennifer.
Now you’re just going
to have to write it again.
- But I’m starving.
You promised me chocolate.
- Chocolate?
Oh, I love that portrait of me.
I look so beautiful.
- That’s me!
I look beautiful.
- Anyhow, there’s something
even more important
that I need from you.
- Tiffany, what more
could I possibly give you?
For years, I’ve made you
money playing online poker
and voicing Bonnie
on "Family Guy."
I pay the bills and answer
all my own fan mail.
And for what?
Just a little bit of chocolate.
That’s all I ask.
- Shut up with the exposition,
Jennifer.
I need answers about you.
Why, you ask?
- Actually, I didn’t.
- I’m about to embark
on my greatest
acting challenge yet.
I need to convince
your sister, Meg,
that I’m you, Jennifer Tilly.
- [gasps] Meg is here?
- Now, tell me
about those Dean brothers.
♪ ♪
[soft music]
- What’s going on?
- Trevor’s missing.
- What?
- Either he crossed over into
Narnia or someone took him.
Fingers crossed for Narnia,
but I’m pretty sure
that’s not a real place.
- He wasn’t in the closet
when we came back
from the bathroom.
- Wait,
maybe someone was cleaning up
for the other Chucky,
like the bad one?
- Well,
the Good Chucky was texting
somebody named the Colonel.
Maybe they’re the ones
that took Trevor.
We should look
through this again,
see if we missed anything.
- I sure hope you find Trevor.
♪ ♪
I just feel so bad.
Who would do
something like that?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Devon.
- You,
you would do
something like that.
You killed my mom.
You killed her dad.
- What?
- You’re basically responsible
for killing
Jake’s whole family.
But for some reason,
he doesn’t seem
to care about any of that.
- Because that wasn’t
his fault.
That was a different Chucky.
He’s not like that anymore.
♪ ♪
- I--I--
I have to go.
- Chucky, wait, you can’t--
♪ ♪
[somber music]
- Did I really do those things?
- Oh, no,
that was a different you.
- Like that other me,
the big guy.
- Yeah, exactly.
There’s a lot of you.
But, you know,
you’re all different.
- Where did we come from?
- Well, it all started
with this guy named Charles.
He actually lived here
a long time ago,
when he was a kid.
And, well, when he grew up,
he split his soul
into all of you.
And that’s why you’re alive.
- Was he a good person?
- [sighs]
- If I came from someone bad,
that means that I’m bad too.
That means I could hurt you.
- No, no.
- I shouldn’t be around anyone!
- No, I--I want you here.
- Why?
- Because you’re good.
Look, I know you’re good.
- But what if there’s
still evil inside me, too?
- Wait, you know what?
Look, I have an idea.
But we’re gonna need some help.
- [sighs]
- So you and Jake?
- Yeah, yeah.
Not great.
- Understatement
of the century.
- I mean, do you get
this whole Good Chucky thing?
’Cause I don’t.
- Every time I look at him,
I see Junior’s face.
- I just feel like he doesn’t
hear me sometimes, you know?
Or he won’t.
- Chucky fucks everything up.
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
- I mean, yeah,
but even when we thought
Chucky was dead, Jake--
I mean, none of us ever
saw each other, ever.
Maybe Chucky’s
not the only problem.
- I mean, I wanted to talk
to you guys every single day.
Everything just felt so hard.
♪ ♪
- I just don’t want Jake
to get himself killed, or us.
He’s lost touch with reality.
- So what do you
wanna do about it?
[phone buzzing]
It’s like looking
through my mom’s Instagram.
- Wait, wait, go back.
What’s that?
Is that a doll’s foot?
Go to the next one.
There, an arm.
- What the hell?
- I think they’re bread crumbs.
- What?
- You know,
like "Hansel and Gretel,"
like he’s leaving
a trail for himself
to find his way back home.
We have to get out there.
Maybe this trail will lead
to more dolls or this Colonel.
If they don’t see us coming,
maybe we can take ’em out
for good.
- Should we tell Jake?
- So what do we do now?
- So then, the priest
usually says something like,
"What do you ask
of God’s church for Chucky?"
- I ask for a clean slate.
- Cool.
You could’ve also
just said baptism.
- Oh.
- Oh, right.
Godparents,
they’re usually part of this.
You know, like,
the people who are, like,
going to guide the baby--
the Chucky during its life.
- You.
You could be my godfather,
Jake.
- [chuckles]
Oh, yeah, sure.
Wow.
Do you wanna be the godmother?
- I would love to.
both: Aww.
Okay.
Then there’s some questions.
Do you renounce Satan,
and his works,
and all his service,
and all his pride?
- Yes, yeah.
- Okay,
that’s a yes for me, too.
Do you unite yourself
unto Christ?
You know,
let’s just skip the rest.
You get the gist.
Okay, now it’s time
to pour the water.
- Okay.
Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, buddy.
I’m just gonna--
Just put you right there.
There we go.
All right.
I baptize you
in the name of the Father...
[choir music]
♪ ♪
The Son...
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
And the Holy Spirit.
♪ ♪
- Amen.
- Okay, well, that’s it.
You’re clean now.
No more evil.
- Wow!
What a feeling!
And it was so easy.
Thank you.
♪ Thank you, Jake,
thank you, Jake ♪
♪ Thank, thank,
♪ Thank you, Jake,
thank you, Jake ♪
♪ Thank you, thank you, Jake ♪
♪ ♪
- Come on.
We’re on our own now.
♪ ♪
[bell tolling]
[rustling]
[clattering]
- What in the name of heaven?
[intense music]
[shrieks]
♪ ♪
- I am risen!
[chuckles]
- You are risen indeed, Lord.
- And it didn’t even
take me three days.
[laughs]
- I knew it.
I knew it was you.
♪ ♪
How can I serve thee, Lord?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Ta-da ♪
- Oh, a new outfit.
- Yes, in this house,
we dress for dinner.
[laughs]
I’m sorry to keep you waiting.
Meg.
Meggy, Meggy, Meggy, come here.
Sit here.
You know, when you were talking
about the Dean brothers
earlier,
it really brought back
some memories.
- Oh, such as?
- Yes, like,
remember when they wanted
to raise money
for the orphanage
that they grew up in?
So they got
the whole band back together.
And then the cops
were after them
for their unpaid
parking tickets.
But they still managed to play
the Palace Hotel ballroom.
And then
they got thrown in jail,
but they still managed
to save the orphanage.
- Jennifer?
- Yes?
- That is the plot of
"The Blues Brothers."
♪ ♪
- Shut up.
It is not.
- Yes, it is.
- No, it’s not.
- That bitch!
- Excuse me?
- I have to go.
- Jennifer?
Jennifer?
Jen?
Yeah, I don’t--
♪ ♪
- You tricked me,
you little troll.
- [chuckles]
I don’t know what
you’re talking about.
- You’re a disgusting little
smarty pants, aren’t you?
I am going to make you sorry
you ever were born.
I am going to make
your life so miserable.
You are going to be the most
unhappy dolly in the world.
- Mom?
- You--
♪ ♪
- What the fuck?
- It’s not what it looks like.
- Jennifer--
- Oh, Meg, it’s me, Jennifer.
In here.
I’m in here.
Meg, it’s me.
- It’s not what
what looks like?
What is going on here?
- Please, please, help me.
I’m trapped.
- Jennifer?
Jennifer. Jen--
- Ah--
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. How?
- Meg, look out!
- [screaming]
- Ah!
[dramatic music]
[screaming]
- No!
- [screams]
- No! No!
[both screaming]
♪ ♪
- Ohh!
[sobbing]
I’m sorry.
- Meg.
- I’m sorry.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, I’m sorry,
- Tiffany, what have you done?
She was my sister.
- I’m sorry, I’m sorry.
- Who are you?
[dark music]
- My name is Tiffany Valentine,
and I’m your goddamn mother.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- There.
[sighs]
Couldn’t he have just
dropped a pin or something?
- Hey, we’re getting closer.
Okay?
Let’s keep going.
- Ugh.
- You fucking monster!
- I know how this
all must sound.
Take your time, sweet face.
- I’ll kill you.
I’ll fucking kill you.
- Mommy’s here.
- You fucking maniac!
You bitch!
I really hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
- If you’ll excuse me
for just one minute?
I am trying to have
an important conversation
with my child.
If you don’t shut up, I will
lock you down here to starve.
Do you understand me?
No more chocolate!
- [gasps]
Ah!
Now shut the fuck up.
[chuckles]
Sorry. Sorry about that.
- You lied to us
our whole lives.
- Well, yes.
But it’s complicated.
I never meant
to hurt you and Glenda.
I just--I wanted
to give you everything.
Tiffany--
Tiffany Valentine is a loser,
but Jennifer Tilly
is a beautiful,
beautiful movie star.
I wanted you to be proud of me.
But...
I--I see now
that it was a mistake.
I was never good
at being Jennifer Tilly.
And I wasn’t that good
of a mom, either.
- Mm.
- I’m sorry.
I was trying to be somebody
that I wasn’t.
And I did the same thing
to you kids, also.
♪ ♪
- What do you mean?
- I have one last
birthday present for you.
[playful dark music]
♪ ♪
That belongs to you.
[opens box]
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
It’s me.
What about Glenda?
- It’s for them, too.
- I need to show this to them.
- Let’s go get them.
- Ah--
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[tires screech]
- Look.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
What the fuck happened here?
- Every dead Chucky’s
a win, right?
♪ ♪
[faint groaning]
- Someone’s inside.
[groaning continues]
Holy shit.
- What the fuck is this?
- Jesus.
Holy shit.
Andy.
- Oh, my God.
He’s alive.
[muffled screaming]
- Charlie?
- Dr. Mixter?
- That’s Colonel to you.
♪ ♪
- [pained grunting]