Happy New Year!
I'm Ryo Saeba, or City Hunter,
a private detective.
I like to work alone and stop crime.
I have a sidekick named Makimura.
But he's not as dashing
and as good a fighter as me.
He's not as good-looking and short.
Do you think it's right?
But we're close friends.
We've been through thick and thin.
We are invincible!
But he slipped up on one occasion
when he was alone.
Makimura!
Makimura, are you okay?
Do you think you'll be okay
after being shot 20 times?
Makimura, nothing will happen to you.
Ryo Saeba, I'll leave first.
Promise me you'll take care
of my sister, Kaori.
Okay, I swear I'll take care of her
till someone takes care of me.
One more thing. Keep your hands off her.
Okay, I swear I won't go after her.
All right. Now, I can rest in peace.
Makimura!
Since then, Kaori became my only family.
What I didn't realize was that
little girls grow up very quickly.
Faster than you can ever imagine.
Don't you agree?
Why did I ever promise Makimura
I won't go after her?
Makimura, I know I made a promise.
Can I change my mind now?
No!
Since then, Kaori has become my assistant.
I never knew what she felt about me.
Until one day...
Damn Ryo Saeba, sleeping again!
Hey, Ryo Saeba.
Hey, wake up.
Hey, get up. Stop sleeping.
It's time. Wake up!
Hey.
Ryo Saeba, you're with us all the time.
Won't Kaori be jealous?
What? Kaori?
She's like a sister to me.
She's at home cleaning the toilet.
What? Cleaning the toilet?
Ryo Saeba, she's like a cute puppy dog.
Her? She's big and fat.
She plods along like an elephant.
She eats seven meals a day.
She likes going out and fooling around.
She's fine with any guys.
Whenever you ask her something,
she just sticks out her tongue,
holds up her hands,
and sways her hips from side to side.
I want to give her away.
But there are no takers.
Damn you, Ryo Saeba!
That feels good!
Hey!
Wake up!
Stop sleeping! Hey!
He's Ryo Saeba. I'm his assistant, Kaori.
We're here to see Mr. Imamura.
Hey, wake up, Ryo!
You're at the client's office!
Hey, wake up!
What kind of perfume
and foundation do you use?
What skin care products do you use?
What do you do?
-I'm a secretary.
-I see.
What's your name?
I became a midget!
Hey, what are you thinking?
None of your business!
Mr. Ryo Saeba, I'm Koji Imamura,
head of Imamura Publishing.
She's my only daughter, Shizuko.
Her mother died when she was young.
So, she's very rebellious.
Last year, I met a lady.
Our relationship developed fast and
intend to get married this year.
But Shizuko objected and left home.
After many inquiries, I've discovered
she went to Hong Kong alone.
So you want me to find her for you?
Yes, but not by force.
Don't worry.
He won't be violent to the ladies.
Great! Any news of Shizuko?
I have to talk to you.
-Talk!
-I prepared a birthday present for you.
What? A skateboard gang?
Where? Victoria Park?
Ocean Park?
Do you like cruises?
Yes, I do.
-Let's take a cruise on a luxury liner.
-What? I see.
You just have a way
of getting information.
What did you say?
-Would you like to go on a cruise?
-I see.
Idiot! Don't you know how to drive?
Kaori, get off now and go over
to Victoria Park at once.
See if Shizuko is there. Go.
I'll check Ocean Park.
We'll talk later.
Damn you, Ryo Saeba!
Run me down!
Come on!
What's the big deal of having a car?
Come on, run me down!
Next time, I'll smash it with a hammer!
Shizuko, are you Japanese?
Do I sound Japanese?
How about going to a disco tonight?
Not having enough fun now? Let's go then.
Hey!
Sorry!
Hey, you're Shizuko Imamura?
This is too easy.
Who are you?
I'm Ryo Saeba.
Your dad hired me to bring you home.
Hey, don't run!
-What's the matter?
-He tried to molest me! Stop him!
What?
Hey, why did you bully my girlfriend?
You bad guy! You beat me!
After him!
Don't go!
Damn! He got away!
Sorry!
Shopping for something, Miss?
Can you help me, Mister?
Me?
Yes, you.
Sure!
What?
Kaori, where are you? I'm starving.
I haven't eaten all day.
Where did you go?
"Ryo Saeba's birthday..."
RYO SAEBA'S BIRTHDAY
My birthday?
How miserable.
There's nothing to eat on my birthday.
Half a cracker?
Kaori, where are you?
Happy birthday!
I'll be damned...
So many ladies remember my birthday.
Surprise!
Do I know you?
You think about it.
Forget it. Let's not think about it.
I'm starving. Let's have some cake.
-We'll feed you after we tie you up.
-Yes.
Sure, let's do it.
I'm starving.
Are you short-sighted? Over here.
No, but you are! We have never met.
Why are you celebrating my birthday?
You've arrested our men.
-We're making you pay!
-Right!
-Hit him!
-No!
Don't go!
After him!
-Listen to me!
-I don't want!
No!
You have nowhere to go. Stop running!
Hit him! Over there!
Grab him.
Freeze!
Put down your weapons!
Happy birthday...
Kaori.
What are they doing here?
They're trying to kill me.
But you're holding a gun.
What game are you playing?
-Ryo!
-What?
Who's she? She's so ugly!
She's my...
Damn you, Ryo Saeba!
I hate you!
I'm going on a cruise with my cousin!
Kaori.
Jeez.
It's all your fault, you bitches!
Don't use your gun if you're man enough!
Fine!
Let me show you my skills.
Don't come any closer!
You should've dumped that asshole
Ryo Saeba a long time ago, Kaori.
He's got such a big nose and tiny eyes.
He's just a muscle man.
What's so good about him?
-You dropped your pants.
-What?
Who the hell are you?
An apology is not enough!
You'll never know what I'm saying.
You foreigners are disgusting.
You queers!
I hope you all get AIDS.
How can you say that?
Didn't your father teach you any manners?
You dropped your pants again.
Kaori!
Wait for me!
Wait up!
Of course!
Hey!
Where have you been?
Why do you walk so slow?
It's time, let's go!
That's so humiliating!
You know him?
Ryo Saeba. He's a private eye.
He's Ryo Saeba?
He's a real pain.
Kaori!
Welcome.
Sir, please show us your invitation card.
Have a gum.
Sir, I need to see your invitation card.
-The card, right?
-Yes.
You have a great sense of humor!
Hey, hold on.
MAHJONG CLUB
Mahjong club membership card?
I'll find a way to get in there.
-Please. You may board the ship.
-Thank you.
All guests, please take note.
Fuji Maru is about to sail.
I'm starving!
I got on the ship so easily.
Let's get something to eat.
Be extra careful when working on deck.
Where's the restaurant?
It's...
-I know.
-You...
Grab him, but don't alert
the other passengers.
Have a drink, sir.
Come on, sir, have a drink.
Thank you!
What are you doing?
-I didn't see anything.
-You looked up her skirt!
Hey, don't step on the bread!
Hey!
You stepped on my bread!
Why did you do that? Give it back to me.
Over there. Get him!
Catch!
DANGEROUS, KEEP AWAY
-Did you see him?
-No!
No?
Where did he go?
Look around!
There's a ship in front!
Sound the foghorn.
Yes, sir.
Please.
What a beautiful room!
-Put the luggage away.
-Okay.
Hold me.
You fell again?
I lost my balance again.
That's because you carry too much weight.
This is the Fuji Maru liner.
They say that all the passengers
onboard are filthy rich.
Do you think I'll find
a rich and handsome boyfriend?
Don't forget your mission.
My job is to act as your cover.
Do I get a reward if you crack the case?
Of course. If the tip is correct,
the terrorists are planning
a robbery on the ship.
Why don't they cancel the cruise?
Because we have no proof.
Even my superior wouldn't commit himself.
I have to come onboard and investigate it.
Are you armed?
I brought a few things.
You almost kicked me.
You're very late.
We got stuck in traffic.
This is a nice room.
Let's enjoy ourselves here.
You shouldn't be late.
We can't afford to slip up.
Take it easy. Relax.
Let's enjoy our time for now.
Until midnight.
Come on.
You won't get to know any rich men
with the way you're eating.
I can't help myself.
Are they all chewing gum,
or have I gone deaf?
Saeko, look, it's that fool
from this morning.
There's always trouble
wherever Ryo Saeba goes.
-Hi.
-Hey!
Don't get bitchy.
I want to.
He's so horny. Aren't you scared?
All men are like that.
He'll go for any woman.
Who's better than me?
-He's poor.
-What?
What a waste of time!
Hamburger.
Don't go, hamburger.
-You like them?
-Very much!
Just wait, they'll be ours tonight.
-You go that way, I'll go this way.
-Follow me.
Sorry!
Hurry!
Here we come!
Wait!
Kaori, we'll get married
when we reach Japan,
have a few kids,
and say goodbye to Ryo Saeba for good.
He'll come looking for me.
Not when we're at sea.
Unless he can fly.
Kaori!
Protect me!
No problem!
What are you doing?
Why are you here? Why don't you go
with your six girlfriends?
I can't hear you.
Get lost! Leave us alone!
I've turned deaf, Kaori.
You always turn a deaf ear on me.
I'll come back on three conditions.
One, never meet another woman.
Two, never date another woman.
Three, never look at another woman.
Damn! I'm deaf!
I really can't hear you.
Forget it!
What?
If my cousin weren't here,
I would use my Lethal Dragon Claw
to kill you!
What?
Let's go!
It's your lucky day!
-Let me tell you a secret.
-What is it?
The doctor says I have hemorrhoids.
-Really? Why are you swimming, then?
-Don't tell anyone.
I can hear everything!
Mine's eight.
Banker has nine. Banker wins.
Good!
I lost with an eight, that's outrageous!
I told you the banker would win.
You wouldn't listen to me.
I'm betting on the banker!
-Welcome!
-Why do we need two rooms?
This is a romantic cruise.
Don't you think a great love story
will take place here?
Tonight, why don't I...
Fine! You can sleep in my room tonight.
All right.
But, I'll go and sleep in your room.
I've been badly bruised.
But, I'll get rid of it.
Hey!
Rocky, don't ever feel
ashamed or inferior.
You must have no shame,
set aside your pride
until you win her heart.
You will surely succeed!
She'll belong to me!
That's lecherous enough!
Let's go and have a few games.
Don't forget we're on a mission.
Jeez, we might pick up some clues
at the gambling table.
Hey.
That man is good-looking.
He must be rich.
Stop dreaming. That's Gundam.
He's the gambling king of Asia.
He'll take your money
as well as break your heart.
Wherever he goes, trouble follows.
Seven.
Mine's seven.
Four.
Eight, I've won again.
You always get either an eight or a nine.
You must be cheating!
Come on, take your losses like a man.
-Search him!
-Yes, sir!
Sorry, sir.
Don't make trouble here, sir.
I was only defending myself.
Here, take this tip.
Get rid of this for me.
Cash me out, please!
-Please continue!
-It's all right.
Thanks!
Your ace of hearts.
Keep it as a souvenir.
Hey, let me have him
if you don't want him. What a waste!
He has good taste.
Okay, Let's synchronize our watches.
It's exactly 23:31 p.m. now.
Another 29 minutes till midnight.
Vincent, you and Team A
move in four minutes.
Yes, Boss.
Mike, you and Team B
start in nine minutes.
Sure!
Kim and I will be in the casino
enjoying the view.
Relax!
We'll succeed for sure.
You heard the boss.
Don't cause any trouble!
Okay, I have here a list of 30 names.
They're all millionaires.
We take over the ship
and take them hostage.
What about the others?
The sharks should be hungry by now.
Throw them into the ocean.
Go to the next room and take a look.
Yes, Boss.
Let's go!
Who is it?
Room service, miss.
Hold on!
Come in!
What's the matter? Can I help you, miss?
Something happened.
I need to see the captain. Where is he?
Relax! He's resting now.
Tell me what the matter is.
No, it's very serious.
Sorry, captain's orders. I can't help you.
A group of terrorists is planning
to take the passengers hostage.
Where did you hear this?
I overheard them.
They're planning to hijack the ship.
I'll take you to the Captain. Follow me.
Careful.
I'll starve to death
if I still don't get something to eat.
A rat!
I can have a snack after all!
Where's the captain?
He's in the nightclub.
Why did you bring me here?
You said there are terrorists.
Yes!
I'm one of them.
You...
We're taking over the ship
and ship the rich men to Thailand.
You scum!
Sorry, little lady!
Sorry!
Ryo Saeba, what are you doing here?
I came to see you.
Here, hold this for me.
That was my snack!
Don't move!
If anyone moves, he gets it.
Shizuko, go now!
Got it.
-Shoot!
-Don't!
No bullets? What a pain.
Attention, Squad 3,
kill the couple in white.
Wait for me!
Search around!
Over here!
Hey.
Move and I'll shoot.
You...
-Are you all right, Shizuko?
-I'm fine.
How handsome!
I meant him.
He's not bad.
He's a good fighter. He's not even afraid
of that tall, black guy.
I can handle two or three
at a time in real life.
Get up and attract their attention.
What? I don't understand.
You're the bait.
No way!
You've wasted all the bullets, stupid!
Don't worry, I still have my fists.
Two or three is nothing for you, right?
Grab them!
Let's go!
Shit! What now?
That's your line.
What now?
Don't worry, I'll take care of them.
Are you all right?
Not a scratch!
That hurts.
Come on, go ahead and kill me.
Your shoes are so large!
Don't come near!
Put me down!
Ryo Saeba!
Help me! Ryo Saeba!
I dare you to put her down!
Don't come near.
You're incredible!
Ryo Saeba!
How many terrorists are there?
I don't know.
-How many guns?
-I don't know.
Find a place to hide.
Where's safe?
Your room.
I just came from there.
They won't look for you there.
Thanks, Brother Siu Lung.
Don't mention it!
Don't move!
Don't move. Hands on your heads!
We're taking over the ship.
In your dreams!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Captain Williams will now
uncork the champagne
to wish everyone a pleasant voyage.
Please welcome him!
How great would it be
if Ryo Saeba was here?
What's so great about that?
How's my bow tie?
Fine.
-There really are terrorists!
-Don't be afraid.
Why did you drop the gun?
We meet again, gorgeous!
You finished one off?
-What are you doing?
-Looking for something to eat.
Tobacco? Damn!
That's hazardous to your health.
Hey, do you have anything to eat?
Want some gum?
That will do, too.
What's that?
A microcomputer.
It contains the identities
of every criminal.
Just scan their prints
and it will call up their rap sheets.
Understand? Bend over.
We'll scan your butt
and find out who those men are.
Ryo Saeba, also known as City Hunter.
A private detective.
Distinguishing features are
handsome, a womanizer,
a good fighter, honest, intelligent,
reliable, and nice to his parents.
It was you!
Just kidding!
They stayed next door.
Their prints will surely be there.
John Chan, international terrorist,
wanted by 17 countries,
ex-member of at least
two terrorist groups...
See? Let's see who else is there.
How do you do, Mr. Chan?
Time to go!
Allow me to introduce myself.
You may call me MacDonald.
I only want money.
Please don't do anything stupid.
If you cooperate, we won't kill you.
Otherwise, you'll be executed.
Here.
I have a list of names.
I will read them off one by one.
When you hear your name, come forward.
I'll shoot and kill anyone
who doesn't comply.
Okay, I'll start now.
Mr. Robinson.
-That's me!
-Don't go.
-I'll be dead if I don't.
Wait here.
Give it to me.
-What?
-Hey!
-He is hitting us!
-Play the game, not us.
What are you doing here?
Playing Street Fighter.
There are terrorists on the ship.
Do you know that?
You're terrifying enough!
They're holding hostages, understand?
What a bummer!
What's the best way to the casino?
Take the elevator.
Jeez.
I mean secretly.
Just don't tell anyone.
Never mind! Call the police!
Don't go running around!
Understand?
Now what?
Let's go and cool down.
Cool down?
Let's play a little game.
I want you all to empty your pockets.
Give us your cash and jewelry.
Give them to the men in red.
Hurry.
Hurry up!
After that, form a line.
Since you like to gamble,
I'll be the banker
and let's see who the winner is.
Good. Excellent.
Ryo Saeba is on the boat and on the loose.
Go get him! I want him alive!
Yes, sir.
Let's send a distress call!
Look what this is!
That's amazing!
The newly-invented transmitter.
Watch this, pal.
This is a transmitter?
I got this from
the Shopping Channel for 500.
Really?
What's that? Don't you know?
-You pressed one, two, three, four.
-Yes!
-What is that?
-It's a cipher.
What does it mean? Look up!
-There's a word. Let's read it.
-All right.
Stay in line!
You're the first. Please sit down.
You like baccarat?
Sure!
Good! Let's begin.
Mine's seven.
Good, seven.
Mine's nine.
Six.
I've got six too.
-It's a tie.
-Sorry, the banker has the advantage.
Next!
I won't bet. I'll die if I lose!
Be a gentleman. Take her to your room.
Get up!
No!
-Wait!
-What is it?
I wanted to ask you
if you would like some of this tonic...
Let me play first. Trust me.
Seven.
Let's play another round.
-Over there!
-Okay.
Incredible! 12 wins in a row.
Mr. MacDonald, do you want to know
where Ryo Saeba is?
You know where Ryo Saeba is?
Of course!
Tell me and I'll spare you.
I don't know.
Go over there and distract him.
You...
Hey, that has nothing to do with me.
Ryo, what about me?
Stay there and don't leave.
Okay.
Ryo Saeba!
You're a good fighter.
The blonde guy took Kaori. Go rescue her.
-There's still one up there.
-I'll go after him.
What's your hurry?
Let's get the mood right first.
You're great! I really like you.
So you enjoy a little rough stuff?
It's my turn!
Okay, go ahead. Not there, here.
Fantastic.
It's my turn again!
-Feeling good?
-I'm feeling so good.
Here I come.
Kaori!
-Why are you here?
-To save you.
I don't need your help.
We're having a good time here.
Who is he?
I'm Ryo Saeba.
Ryo Saeba?
I heard you can fight, City Hunter.
He's pretty good, too.
Hit him now!
You laid a finger on my girl?
He said I'm his girl?
Ryo Saeba, what did you say just now?
What?
Say that again.
Damn!
Not that!
You're right, I can fight!
Don't move!
Freeze!
I'm not moving.
Give me a gun!
-Don't give it to him.
-What?
Fight me if you can.
-Get her!
-Yes, sir.
Hello, nice to meet you, Mr. Ryo Saeba.
Damn!
Drop your gun and let's fight,
Colonel MacDonald.
You know me?
Colonel MacDonald of the US Commandos.
You're nothing but a bandit.
Yes, you're right.
And now, I'm sentencing you to death.
I want to appeal.
Appeal denied. You're to be executed
before sunrise tomorrow.
No!
Where's Ryo Saeba?
That's none of your business.
Stop bickering. Didn't he go to save you?
Maybe he's been captured.
It's up to us now.
We've got to save Ryo Saeba.
-How do we fight? With our fingers?
-I have guns in my room.
He nearly killed Ryo Saeba
and me just now.
We're not armed. We need to ambush him.
I'll distract him.
Good idea!
Let me try.
Help her!
No problem!
I'm here to surrender. Don't kill me.
Do whatever you wish.
I like strong men.
Hello, I'm very busy. Talk to you later.
You!
I surrender. I like strong men, too.
You'll keep me company tonight.
No way!
You smash the door down.
Kaori and I will rush in.
Will it hurt?
Not really. Go on.
Charge!
Duck!
Don't move!
Hit him!
Let me.
Dragon Claw!
That's really cruel.
Change into something comfortable
and regroup.
Sure.
All right!
The men's room is that way.
Right!
Choose your weapon.
Here. You take this.
I don't know how to use it.
I want this one.
It's too heavy.
Move aside!
Good!
What are you doing in your pajamas?
You said to get
into something comfortable.
We'll split up
to save the hostages and Ryo Saeba.
I'll rescue Ryo Saeba.
Let's go get the hostages.
Okay.
We'll go and get Ryo.
Mr. Ryo Saeba, this is your last time
seeing the sun.
Everyone gets a last wish.
Say it.
Can I have wonton noodles? I'm starving.
He's insane.
He wants wonton noodles before he dies?
Sorry! No.
Damn Caucasian, you even said no to that.
All right. Prepare for execution.
Wait!
What are you doing here?
Nice to see you, princess.
Please let him go.
You only want money.
My father owns Imamura Publishing.
I can ask him for lots of money.
Do you think I'll believe you?
You can call my dad's office.
The number is 0252429.
Remember the number
and call to check it out.
Does he mean that much to you?
He's the best man that
I've ever met in my life.
We'll inform your father in Japan
about the news of this man's death.
You scumbag!
Freeze!
Drop your weapons!
Let's go.
I'm losing my balance again!
-Get them!
-Yes, sir!
-Catch!
-My hands are tied.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Give me the gun!
Take it.
Take it!
Shoot him!
I'm not that heavy, right?
You're crushing me!
Duck!
Give me the gun!
Hide up there!
What?
Come on!
-How?
-Follow me!
Get up!
How silly. I forgot to untie the rope.
Gosh.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
-What the hell?
-Let's go!
Thunder Strikers?
AIR POLICE
You go this way! You go that way!
The rest of you follow me!
Anyone here?
I told them not to go running around.
Did you apply makeup?
Untie me!
Behind you.
Untie me, quickly!
Tatsumaki Senpuukyaku!
Round 1, fight!
Dosu koi!
Yoga Fire!
Tiger!
Hadouken!
Sonic Boom!
-Hadouken!
-Sonic Boom!
Who's next?
Spinning Bird Kick!
Shouryuuken!
Yatta!
Hadouken!
-Tatsumaki Senpuukyaku!
-Spinning Bird Kick!
Yatta!
Let's see what you can do
if I unplug this.
Yes!
It hurts!
Are you all right?
What happened?
I don't know.
I know, he's dead.
He's still alive!
Good if he dies.
Go to the upper deck.
The Thunder Strikers are here.
Let's go over there.
-Wait!
-What?
-Where's Kaori?
-She's gone to the casino.
I'm going to the casino.
-Walk over there.
-What happened?
Hurry!
Hey, they're over there. Hurry!
Careful! Split up!
Get in!
I'll take my chances.
Damn!
Gundam!
Gundam.
-How are you?
-I'm fine!
Thanks to your ace of hearts!
The Thunder Strikers are here.
Get to the upper deck with the hostages.
What about you?
I'm helping Ryo and Kaori in the casino.
You all right?
I'm fine.
But next time, let's go on a date.
Be careful!
All right!
Kaori!
Ryo!
What?
Watch out!
You're out of bullets again?
Don't worry!
Ryo, behind us!
Aren't we a team?
Ryo!
I've been waiting for you.
Don't move!
Why are you holding her?
She's my weapon!
I bet she's your girlfriend.
MacDonald, the Thunder Strikers are here.
You can't get away.
I can still get away if you're my hostage.
Let's make a deal.
If you get them to let me go,
I'll let her go.
Don't let him get away!
He badly injured my cousin.
Where?
I'm dying already.
You're pathetic.
Behind you!
Thanks!
I'm screwed again.
Goodbye, Ryo Saeba!
You're finished!
Don't kill me!
I have seven children to look after.
Please don't kill me.
You asshole, 100 years in jail
is too kind for you.
How about 200 years?
Look at you! Hold your ears!
I will.
Repeat ten times that
you'll never do this again.
I dare not do it anymore.
Can I go now?
In your dreams!
Ryo Saeba, catch!
I shouldn't have done that.
Catch!
Over there!
Up. Down.
Up. Left.
Right. Left.
-Together.
-Whatever.
You can't hit me!
Dodge!
Come on!
-Bastard!
-You still can't get me!
Well?
Come on!
Goodbye, Ryo Saeba!
Ryo Saeba!
Are you all right, Saeko?
No, just a flesh wound.
I'll carry you, all right?
All right.
-Ryo Saeba!
-Yes?
Kaori.
-Are you all right?
-It hurts!
Where?
Everywhere!
Let me carry you.
Better?
Good, all safe and sound.
No, what about Shizuko?
Damn! I forgot!
Hey, take care of Saeko for me.
Ryo Saeba, you're pissing me off!
Shizuko!
Ryo Saeba!
Shizuko, please don't run away again.
I won't. I won't run away ever again.
I'll do anything you say.
-Really?
-Yes!
Give me some wonton noodles.
I'm so hungry!
Ryo Saeba, are you all right?
I'm most grateful to you, Mr. Ryu Saeba.
It's my pleasure.
Please, sit.
Mr. Saeba.
I would like a word with you in private.
I'll wait outside.
Me, too.
I'll see you out!
Hold my calls.
Shizuko has changed
since she came back from Hong Kong.
It's all because of you.
You flatter me!
I hope you'll marry her.
You're the only one she'll listen to.
She's my only child.
My darling baby.
The love of my life.
When I retire,
my son-in-law shall inherit everything.
Shizuko is a pretty girl.
I believe you wouldn't reject it.
Why?
I'm too lazy.
Besides, I can't be tied down.
I'll never get married.
Your friend has just left in a hurry.
Let her be.
Thank you, Mr. Imamura.
Pay my fee or I'll charge you interest!
Where did she go?
-She went that way.
-This way?
-What's your name, miss?
-Choi.
Choi.
Kaori, where are you going?
This is for you.
Don't be like that. Kaori, listen.
I'm not listening.
You're going to be his son-in-law and
you expect me to tag along as your maid?
You know I hate sashimi.
I only like congee and fried dough.
Don't get mad! This is for you.
Ryo Saeba!
Ryo Saeba.
Saeko.
Do you have time?
Yes.
Want to go with me to Disneyland?
Sure!
What a nice flower!
-It's for you.
-Thanks!
Ryo Saeba!
Incredible!
I'm dreaming again! Please don't wake me!
Take turns!