(theme music)
(squelching)
(breathing shakily)
(gasps)
-(birds chirping) -(sighs)
(crow cawing)
The crow came back again.
(screeching)
Stop it!
Ah!
(gasps)
(thuds)
BOY: Are you okay?
(groans)
(grunts)
(bones cracking)
(moans)
(grunting)
(panting)
(shaky voice) Monster...
(breathing shakily)
Monster.
He's a monster.
Mo... monster.
I'm not!
(sobs)
(exhales deeply)
(foreboding music)
(breathing shakily)
(statics)
(indistinct chatter)
(breathes deeply)
Damn it.
JIYOUNG: Feels great to be out of there.
I was so annoyed earlier. It wasn't obvious, was it?
(laughs)
(indistinct chatter)
-(startled gasp) -Ah.
Oh, my God, what was that? That was so creepy. Did you see his eye?
(murmurs)
JIYOUNG: Let's go.
-Excuse me. -So creepy.
Oh, he's coming, he's coming, he's coming.
Uh, excuse me, just a moment.
I would like to ask you something.
What?
Um, you were in this area with a man before, right?
Oh, it doesn't have anything to do with you.
-Uh, we're kind of busy. -Seriously, what the hell?
Oh, I mean, I'm not a weird person...
(paper rustles)
OH JINSEOP
(indistinct chatter)
-Enjoy. -Thank you.
CUSTOMER: More side dishes please!
(indistinct chatter)
(suspenseful music)
So what happened?
Oh, we got picked on by a pervert.
So the man with an eye patch came after you specifically, Sunhee?
Well, I don't know, it was really annoying.
Huh?
What are the odds of seeing Jinseop at a place like this?
Yeah, right. He always eats alone. I wonder why he's eating here...
JIYOUNG: Maybe he wants to hang out with people like us sometimes.
Um, can we sit with you?
(chuckles slightly)
Sure, why not?
MYUNGHOON: Thank you.
(ringtone playing) ♪ ...low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
(grunting)
(groans)
(breathes heavily)
(breathing shakily)
(whimpering)
SPICY BEEF SOUP, OX-KNEE SOUP
(breathing heavily)
Wow, this song's getting popular lately. It's because of Z.
(ringtone playing) ♪ ...colorful junks... ♪
SEONHUI: Oh, right, Jinseop,
you were looking for a jingle for the Nister commercial, right?
(tongue clicks)
Yeah.
That song you just heard,
there's a rumor that Z will be covering it.
What do you think?
Yeah, I'll look into it.
(panting)
PUNGJO SUNDAE
Why the hell are there so many of these shops?
(groans)
(grunts)
(inaudible chatter)
NAM SAN HOUSE ORIGINAL SUNDAE SOUP
(panting)
So many side dishes.
MYUNGHOON: Jinseop, what do you think of Sunhee?
Sunhee seems to have feelings for you.
(both laugh)
JINSEOP: What are you trying to say?
Well, you see, I'm interested in Sunhee and I'd like to try asking her out.
I wanted to know if that's okay with you.
It's okay.
What?
Really?
Good luck, I'm heading out.
Uh, you haven't finished eating...
NAMSAN HOUSE, ORIGINAL SUNDAE SOUP
-(grunts) -I'm sorry.
(both laugh)
Where's Jinseop?
Ah, he said he was leaving first.
Huh?
But why...
(gasps) The eye-patch man.
He followed us in here, what do we do?
Oh, no...
(Jiyoung gasps)
(gasps)
-DONGSOO: Excuse me, can I... -Who the hell are you?
(customers gasp)
(grunts)
No, I'm just... I'm looking for someone.
I'm sorry, but who exactly are you looking for?
Wasn't there another person sitting here?
There's no one, you bastard, why are you asking about that?
Perhaps your boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
(grunts)
You-you better get lost before I call the cops.
OFFICIAL_Z: GREAT SONG. COULD I CONTACT YOU THROUGH DM?
LONELY GUITAR MAN: I'M SORRY. I DON'T USE DM FOR PERSONAL REASONS.
THIS SONG IS AVAILABLE FOR ANYONE TO USE, SO FEEL FREE TO USE IT HOWEVER YOU WANT.
Z.
He may think that you didn't comment this yourself.
Then I'll just hurry and record it.
Once they listen to the complete version,
everyone would think that it's my song and that I wrote it myself.
What if you run into problems after recording?
He said it's not copyrighted. Others might claim it first.
You're right, there's someone who already arranged and posted it.
Huh?
(water trickling)
DONGSOO: I don't see it.
Why do I see it then not see it randomly?
(keyboard clanking)
(mouse scrolling)
(clicks tongue)
(sighs lightly)
Looks like there's not much progress in the investigation.
(static)
Then first, I'll check the horoscope for your date of birth.
(keyboard clacking)
Tell me your birthday.
Well...
It's not the horoscope I want. I came to ask a question.
Please go ahead.
Um, what do all of those mean?
They are symbols of the planets in the solar system.
Ah...
Then what about this?
That is Pluto.
Pluto...
Then could Pluto, November 29th, and December 12th,
be linked in any way based on astrology?
(keyboard clanking)
Both dates are days when Pluto and Venus make a conjunction.
Conjunction?
YOUNGRAN: Okay, this is Pluto and this is Venus.
Can you see that both planets' symbols are inside the same boundary?
Multiple planets gathered to form angles
within the same boundary are called "conjunction."
What's all this?
Each star symbolizes different meanings.
If Venus is a symbol of beauty and art,
then Pluto symbolizes destruction and regeneration.
The King of the Underworld, sometimes called the Grim Reaper.
In other words, it could be a cycle of death and art.
Then when would that conjunction take place again?
It's not a common occurrence.
(keyboard clanking)
YOUNGRAN: December 20th, and then...
December 25th.
On Christmas too?
YOUNGRAN: When the orb hits zero, December 12th and December 25th
are placed at the center of conjunction,
and the cycle goes into retrograde.
When the conjunction begins again,
it ends on January 6th.
(pencil rasping)
(doorbell dings)
(rasping continues)
(doorbell ding continues)
How did you know where I live?
I know everything about you, Jinseop.
What do you know about me?
Could you try to get to know me first?
If you just tell me to go away...
JINSEOP: Come in, for now.
(door lock beeps)
It looks cleaner than a model house.
Do you want to get yourself clean too?
You said you wanted to show me everything.
(pensive music)
RELIABLE POLICE, SAFE COUNTRY NAMBU POLICE STATION
-(siren blares) -DETECTIVE CHOI: Oh, Youngran, what's up?
What?
And then?
Yeah.
You want me to come over there?
Ah, you'll come over?
How long will it take?
Oh. It was the symbol for Pluto.
That's right, symbol for Pluto.
YOUNGRAN: Actually, the meaning behind constellations or stars
are interpreted differently depending on the country.
In a Christian viewpoint, Venus is interpreted as Lúcĭfer.
-Known as Lucifer. -What?
The devil?
(breathes heavily)
YOUNGRAN: That's right, the devil.
Also called the fallen angel.
(grunting)
(moans)
DETECTIVE CHOI: The devil. Fallen angel.
Okay, fine, but how did that young man
find out about the date of the murder
and its connection to astrology?
This... This Pluto symbol, it's classified.
Classified?
Yeah.
(inhales sharply)
I did tell him about the calculation
for the dates of conjunction occurrence.
What does he look like? His characteristics?
-Firstly... -Yeah.
-He's good-looking. -Hey, Gye Youngran, damn it...
-Okay, okay. -(tongue clicks)
Eye patch.
Eye patch?
He had an eye patch on his right eye.
-Hey, give me that thing, hurry up. -Yes, sir.
Come on.
(clears throat)
Mm, handsome.
Hey, come on!
It's him, this man.
Hey, put this guy on the suspects list,
and, uh, check all CCTV footage
within two kilometer radius, and trace his movements.
Yes, sir.
(clears throat)
Is that guy really the culprit?
Not yet. Well, I don't know yet.
Hey, thanks for your help.
Treat me to a meal.
(chuckles) Okay, got it.
(chuckles)
-Let's go eat. -Yeah.
SUNHEE: How can it be so perfectly organized...
(scoffs)
(light music)
(foreboding music)
Found him!
Here, the eye patch, the eye patch.
(beeping)
What? This is that psychopath?
(indistinct radio chatter)
Play it again.
(keyboard clanking)
(door creaks)
(breathes deeply)
(gulping)
(exhales deeply)
MAN: Oh, oh, oh, hey, hey, hey, where are you going?
Come here, huh? Come here!
Hey you little runt, come here. Oh, my goodness.
Huh? Oh my, hey, where are you going?
Hey, Pipi, what are you barking at? What is it, huh? What's wrong?
(dog barking)
(train engine rumbles)
(foreboding music)
FOURTH CORPSE ART FOUND
IN HANYUL PARK AT 7:40 A.M. TODAY
FOURTH
FOURTH CORPSE ART FOUND ON DECEMBER 25TH…
(indistinct chatter)
(siren wailing in distance)
(Detective Choi sighs)
(ominous music)
-(indistinct chatter) -(cameras clicking)
DETECTIVE CHOI: It's really in that order of dates?
Then the next would be January 6th, and there's only about ten days left.
Come on, do you believe that? Damn it.
We'll catch him somehow before it happens.
(sighs)
(snickers)
(crowd clamoring)
-EUNPYO: Out of the way! -DETECTIVE PARK: What is it?
(woman screaming)
-Oh, hey, that, that, that bastard. -Get that bastard first!
Hey.
(elevator door closes)
(paper rustles)
Sunhee, is something wrong?
Where is Jinseop?
I don't think he's come in yet.
Shouldn't he be in soon?
(whispers) I was hoping you could help me.
What can I help you with?
(inhales deeply)
(suspenseful music)
Go this way.
(Dongsoo panting)
Come here, come here, you bastard.
(groans)
(panting)
-Ah, damn it. -THUG: Hey!
-(moans) -(grunts)
-This bastard. -(grunting)
Come here, you bastard!
(groans)
-(Dongsoo groans) -(thug grunts)
(panting)
Hey, what are you doing?
(screams)
(Dongsoo screams)
(groans)
(grunts)
(blood trickling)
(groans)
(soft chuckle)
Ew, this is gross.
Hey, hurry up and put this back on yourself.
(breathing heavily)
Why... why are you doing this to me?
That's none of your business.
(groans)
(grunts)
(laughs)
That's amazing, Connect.
Co... connect?
(snickers)
What do you want to do?
If you want to keep this a secret, you'd better kill him now.
Ki... kill him?
(Eunpyo grunts)
(Eunpyo exhales deeply)
The cops will be here soon.
-(electricity crackles) -(grunts)
If you want to kill him, you must hurry.
(breathing shakily)
DETECTIVE PARK: Stop right there, you son of a bitch!
(both grunt)
-(groans) -Ugh...
Hey, who were you chasing, huh?
(pants)
I was just jogging, what are you talking about?
Ugh...
(panting)
(both pant)
You, you weren't with them?
(Irang panting)
I figured they would lead me to you, so I followed them.
(panting)
He called me Connect. Was that what you wanted to check?
At least, I don't think of you as some bundle of money.
Bundle of money?
What do you know about Connect?
(breathes deeply)
It's kind of a long story...
Do you have a phone?
What are you... Give it back, now.
I'm making it too easy. No fun.
(cell phone vibrates)
I'm Choi Irang. Save my number.
If you don't call, I will. What's your name?
You don't need to know.
I think you should hide out here for a bit longer.
If you want to stay here, then you can do that.
(sighs)
Hi, I want to talk to you alone.
(beeps)
-It will be quick. -(elevator dings)
(elevator door opens)
I saw something at your place when I came over.
The sketch book.
Ah...
There were things like corpse art drawings.
Surprisingly well-drawn...
Aren't those drawings popular online for being artistic?
I was just copying them.
Then what about the drawing of this morning's murder?
SUNHEE: Where'd you find that?
It seemed like you drew it before the murder even happened.
I also saw the drawing on the last page.
What are all those?
You saw them all?
(chuckles)
(cell phone rings)
MAN: Man, where did everyone go?
Ah, I'll try calling Sunhee.
Well, Jinseop, I'm just…
I don't really know what's going on,
but Sunhee asked me to…
No, Myunghoon.
This man, this guy is...
He... he's a murderer.
(ominous music)
(Sunhee screams)
(groans)
What do you think you're doing?
(grunts)
(groans)
(scoffs)
(grunting)
(ringtone playing) ♪ High-hanging metal ♪
-♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪ -(grunts)
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
-♪ The sound of the city ♪ -(grunts)
♪ Colorful junks ♪
♪ Hugging them ♪
♪ And putting them together ♪
(gasping)
(grunts)
♪ Though it's quiet ♪
♪ Feels like being thrown out of the city ♪
DONGSOO: Who is this bastard...
fighting right now?
♪ ...and you'll hear ♪
♪ My sound in the city ♪
♪ A similar sound ♪
♪ It's sad… ♪
Crazy bastard, this crazy bastard.
What's wrong with him?
♪ Thrown out of the city… ♪
(gasps)
(both groan)
No.
(inaudible chatter)
(gasps)
(glass shatters)
(thuds)
(crowd screaming)
♪ It's sad ♪
-♪ Though it's quiet… ♪ -(groans)
(stammering) Spare me.
It's my first time I'm seeing your eyes so full of life.
They're pretty.
(whimpers)
♪ Born like that… ♪
I'll do anything.
I'll do anything for you, Jinseop, so please...
Thank you. If that's so, then...
♪ With the similar sound… ♪
No. No, stop it!
-(screams) -♪ Find the brother ♪
♪ With the similar sound… ♪
Then, can I ask you for a favor?
Anything.
I can do anything, I'll be better.
Let's keep that mouth shut.
(Sunhee yelps)
(bones crack)
(breathing shakily)
(sobbing)
(static)
Damn it...
-(breathing shakily) -(crowd screaming in distance)
♪ High-hanging metal ♪
-♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪ -(groaning)
BUSINESS HQ 3 JIYOUNG
(breathing heavily)
It is because of this song?
That crazy bastard.
(breathes heavily)
What in the world just happened?
(closing theme music)