(theme music)
DETECTIVE PARK: What's your name?
Your name. Kid, are you deaf?
Ha Dongsoo.
(surgeon chuckles)
Oh?
Oh, what's up?
Did something happen?
(body thuds)
(groaning)
JINSEOP: How about we have a nice chat.
I got a lot of questions about this eye.
(panting)
Hey. Scream and I'll slit your throat.
(groans)
Go ahead, you can talk.
Please don't kill me.
Just let me live.
I'll tell you everything.
Only if you talk.
My eye.
Let's start with how you got it.
SURGEON: I... I don't know.
I just did the surgery.
I don't know anything.
That's not what I wanted to hear.
(whimpering)
(clattering in distance)
(approaching footsteps)
(foreboding music)
(clicks tongue)
This damn geezer…
Hey, gramps!
(glass shattering)
DETECTIVE PARK: Why did you break into M&amp;T Planning?
What were you doing running from the crime scene?
Did those thugs have anything to do with it?
Come on!
Not gonna talk, are you?
DETECTIVE PARK: Fine. See for yourself.
Explain this photo.
(Detective Park clears throat)
What are you, a hyena?
People are dying left and right,
and it's strange that you keep showing up.
(clears throat)
Hey.
(whispering) You went to see the astrologer, right?
Astra.
God, can you believe this guy?
(sighs)
How'd you know that what you talked about with the astrologer
at Astra had anything to do with the corpse art?
DETECTIVE PARK: All right, this bastard did it.
(chair clatters)
Hey.
Say it, you scumbag. We know you killed them.
Say it, damn it. You killed them! Right? Say it.
(panting)
DONGSOO: I knew 'cause of...
(panting continues)
'Cause of a vision.
A vision?
No, I mean...
(breathes shakily)
Th... the vision...
It was kind of like seeing double, maybe?
(sighs)
If you're gonna keep this up, there's nothing we can do.
You want psychiatric evaluation, don't you?
(both grunting)
DETECTIVE PARK: Let's do a quick test.
How many am I holding?
No, I don't always have them.
(Dongsoo groans)
(shaky breathing)
Sometimes, uh, how do I...
So, I get this insane pain out of nowhere,
that's when the vision starts.
-Why, you piece of… -Sungjun.
(breathes deeply)
(sighs deeply)
You know, it's unusual.
Yes, it really is an unusual case.
So…
we have to throw common sense out the window
and deal with this.
All right.
(exhales deeply)
Sit down.
You can put your eye patch on if you want.
You know,
I don't think you're lying.
And it seems like I'll have to take your story about the visions
as it is to get you talking, right?
Hmm?
So I just gotta ask...
Out of all the visions, which one concerns you the most right now?
(breathes heavily)
The one about the murder that's about to happen.
Murder?
Three little girls, elementary school age.
-DETECTIVE CHOI: Little girls? -(Dongsoo breathes shakily)
DONGSOO: I saw the drawing, the design.
It was a new drawing... Different from the past four corpse arts.
What about the symbol for Pluto. How'd you know about that?
DONGSOO: It was drawn there too, in the corner of the design.
Right, then...
Here. This is the victim's body.
It was carved on the corpse art.
Really?
(sighs)
DETECTIVE CHOI: Just so we're clear,
I don't think you did it.
I just wanna protect you as a witness.
(inhales deeply) So tell me.
Hm. Why?
How...
do you get those visions?
(gulps)
(breathes deeply)
Those thugs…
(gulps)
I...
You wanna go somewhere else?
(surgeon groans)
SURGEON: I'm telling you! I don't know anything.
What's that? What're you gonna do with it? What're you gonna do to me?
(whimpers)
Just... just what, just what are you gonna do?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
Ah!
(croaking)
(breathes deeply)
Oh, oh, okay, okay just, please just stop.
I'll tell you everything, please stop.
Tell me what?
Whatever, whatever it is you want, all of it.
(groans)
And what do you think that is?
(grunts) Please, please stop.
(sobs)
(groans)
(yelps)
(surgeon groaning)
You even got someone to stalk me after the surgery, didn't you?
(breathes deeply)
At first I thought, maybe it was for customer follow-up.
But it was for the eye, wasn't it? What is this eye?
It... It could be a Connect.
A Connect?
It's been over two months
since you came to us, right?
(grunting)
(breathes heavily)
Help me.
(groans)
Whoa, how'd you find this place? What happened to you?
(grunts)
You look like you work at an office.
I heard this place doesn't ask a lot of questions.
Think you can patch me up?
(scoffs)
Who knows what'll happen if I put my hands on you.
Go some place else.
JINSEOP: I'll pay.
A lot.
Huh?
(chuckles)
Well, what does a doctor care about his patient's job?
Go lie down on that bed.
Don't bother trying anything dumb…
while I'm out.
My cancer's all over my body.
(chuckles)
Looks like you've done your research.
(both laugh)
DETECTIVE CHOI: How do you like this place?
It's a nice place to talk.
This is the rooftop.
Don't do anything stupid.
(chain clanking)
(foreboding music)
(Dongsoo groans)
(cracks)
(pants)
(grunts)
(panting)
SURGEON: Typically after getting the eye and the internal organs,
the rest are just thrown out.
That day, I was working like any other day,
but he ran away.
Ran away? Did the anesthesia not work?
Well, I opened his chest,
but he ran.
Like the cuts just healed in the blink of an eye?
(tense music)
So you know.
DONGSOO: Why my body is like this…
how it became like this, I couldn't tell you if you asked.
I just don't know how it happened.
(scoffs)
I did not expect that.
They call this type of body...
They call it a Connect. I just learned about it.
So basically, a body called a Connect rolled in,
and you decided to test an eye transplant...
(foreboding music)
...on me.
Around the year 2000,
Jeongdo Pharmaceuticals made this groundbreaking discovery
in biotechnology at their research facility.
They called it "Connect",
and people said…
it was a revolutionary invention in bio-transplanting.
Some even said it could have something to do with immortality.
So that means I have a body part that's immortal, right?
We share the vision.
Whatever he sees,
I see.
That's good news, right? To someone with late-stage cancer.
Please,
you said you wouldn't kill me.
(sobs)
(grunts)
(groans)
(laughs)
That was everything.
Now what about you, detective? What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna expose me?
It's the only way we can convince people. The only way.
And I have to do it 'cause I'm a detective.
'Cause I have to protect victims and catch criminals.
(scoffs)
What, so what I did doesn't matter…
'cause I'm a monster?
Yeah, how'd the background check go?
DETECTIVE PARK (on cell phone): Long story short, it's...
Wait, just a second.
Go ahead.
Everything that Ha Dongsoo told us about his identity is fake.
His fingerprints aren't even registered.
And, well, that makes it legally impossible to say he even exists.
Completely unidentified.
You heard it yourself.
Detective Park, look into those organ hunters a little more.
DETECTIVE PARK (on cell phone): Already on it. Oh Jinseop, too.
Did you lie to me?
(sighs)
Your part's done. We don't need...
(shouts) Detective!
I'm the only one who knows the faces of the kids he's gonna kill.
-So please just let me go. -No.
We need to stop him.
We're gonna catch him. So let it go.
(foreboding music)
DETECTIVE CHOI: What are you doing?
Hey, stop it.
(groans)
I said, stop it.
(breathing heavily)
(clatters)
(Dongsoo breathes shakily)
This world's never been kind to me.
I shouldn't have trusted a detective.
Don’t move.
Stop right there.
-I said, stop! -(gunshot)
Get down. Get down.
Stop!
(gasping)
Argh... (gasping)
(foreboding music)
(groaning)
(gasping)
Damn it!
(groaning)
(panting)
(Dongsoo groans)
OFFICER: Excuse me.
Excuse me. Are you all right?
-(moans) -(officer groans)
Hey, go, go, go, hurry!
Move!
(yells)
OFFICER: What is it?
Hey, Jinsoo!
Hey, what happened up there at the rooftop?
(both pant)
AUTOMATED VOICE: The number you have dialed is unattended.
(line ringing)
ORGAN TRAFFICKING GANG LEADERS: MINSOOK: BOSS 1
MR. KIM: BOSS 2 EUNPYO: HEAD HENCHMAN
ORGAN TRAFFICKING GANG HENCHMEN: BIGMAN, GANGMAN A
WOOJIN: TAIL HIGHER-UP?
POWER BEHIND JEONGDO PHARMACEUTICALS
START OF THE INCIDENT
99% CONNECT = DONGSOO
The person you have called is not available. Please leave a…
Damn it, why isn't he picking up?
-(clatters) -(sucks teeth)
(exhales deeply)
Did he... get caught?
(foreboding music)
(sighs)
Whoever it was, bring him to me now,
if you don't wanna end up there yourselves.
I said go find them!
(indistinct shouting)
(sighs) Ah...
(sighs)
(cell phone ringing)
Yeah.
This is Woojin, sir.
MR. KIM (on cell phone): I'm busy, make it quick.
Oh Jinseop hasn't been home since yesterday.
Man, people just love going missing here. These idiots just keep disappearing.
(clicks tongue)
(sighs) So, what do I do? Should I break in?
Grab anything that can be a lead.
Yes, sir.
(grunts)
(sighs)
(spits)
AUTOMATED VOICE: The number you have dialed is unattended.
Leave a message...
(foreboding music)
(wrapper rustles)
(panting)
(ominous music)
An aspiring novelist wire-tapping and tailing people.
Damn, you do all kinds of things.
You interested in that eye that went to Oh Jinseop?
You don't gotta talk.
-You'll spill eventually. -(moans)
(sighs)
Did you guys even know
who Oh Jinseop was before the transplant?
(laughs)
We don't care about that. We just need the money.
(Woojin grunts)
(breathes nervously)
(siren blaring)
DONGSOO: I'm gonna set all the elementary schools
in the city on fire.
You know I'm serious.
Any kid walking the streets...
is gonna die.
(siren blaring continues)
Yeah.
DETECTIVE PARK (on cell phone): 119 just reported
a possible terrorist attack and sent us a call recording.
Oh, yeah?
And the voice is Ha Dongsoo's.
Then send a shut-down notice to all the elementary schools in the city.
Say there's a terrorist on the loose.
Heard he'll bomb an elementary school, something like that.
I'll report to the higher-ups, be quick. Okay.
REPORTER: Breaking news.
Early this morning, a threatening call was made announcing
a bombing of all the elementary schools in Seohan City.
An elementary school in the city actually suffered an explosion
-around the time of the threat. -Interesting move, Guitar Man.
And firefighters were dispatched and put out the fire in an hour.
Fortunately, there were no casualties.
(sighing)
(light music)
OFFICIAL_Z: DID YOU LISTEN TO THE SONG?
I'M CURIOUS TO KNOW WHAT THE ORIGINAL ARTIST THINKS
OF COURSE I LISTENED TO IT. YOU'RE THE BEST MUSICIAN.
LONELY GUITAR MAN: OF COURSE I LISTENED TO IT.
YOU'RE THE BEST MUSICIAN.
OFFICIAL_Z: WHEW… I WAS WORRIED…
GLAD TO KNOW YOU LIKED IT.
DONGSOO: Man…
OFFICIAL_Z: YOUR SONG IS REALLY GREAT. EVEN BETTER THAN MY ARRANGEMENT
SO DON'T GIVE UP… REACH ME IF YOU WANT TO MEET
IT'D BE EVEN BETTER IF WE COULD PLAY TOGETHER.
(exhales deeply)
(groans)
(groaning continues)
NEW TEXT MESSAGE: CAN YOU SEE THIS?
IF YOU CAN, CALL ME
(groans)
(cell phone vibrates)
(chuckles)
Who are you?
JINSEOP (on cell phone): Hiding the caller ID, that's a surprise.
That's not even your phone.
JINSEOP: You seem smart.
What do I call you? Guitar Man?
-JINSEOP: Pyromaniac? -Shut your trap, you lunatic.
(laughs)
You're a real hothead. You were like that at the office building.
You think the world revolves around you?
Not after this.
(chuckles)
It's too late, you know.
What do you mean?
JINSEOP: I mean it's already gone on to the next phase.
Don’t you think it's fate?
That one of your eyes ended up with me.
Tell me, what's the next phase?
That's for you to find out.
I want you to know everything about me, okay?
Let's talk again, Connect buddy.
Oh!
Man, it's a dog turd.
Damn it.
MALE PASSERBY: Just my luck.
(ominous music)
DONGSOO: Why didn't you answer my call?
I'm sorry, I was dealing with something.
You were right.
They know I'm a Connect.
It might get dangerous for you too.
Right now, your place is the least safe for you.
SCREENING SCHEDULE: AUDITION
DONGSOO: Wow, this place was a movie theater?
IRANG: Are you gonna run away again?
If you're scared of getting caught, you better stay here.
I'll go get your eye back.
DONGSOO: How?
However I can.
What do you know?
What do you think I don't know?
What it's like living as a Connect?
I don't think we're that different.
What?
Try stabbing me.
Are you insane?
You'll know once you stab me.
And if you get hurt?
Are you gonna take responsibility?
(gasps)
(soft trilling)
You're the same as me?
Yeah.
Did you lie?
About being saved by a Connect?
Half of it was true,
the part about getting hit by the dump truck,
and surviving thanks to a Connect body.
I was gonna tell you after you got your eye back.
(sighs)
You don't need a band-aid.
IRANG: I wished I did.
This is something weak kids,
normal kids put on.
This was proof that I was one.
So I started putting it on, but one day
it kind of became a talisman.
When I have this on,
they wouldn't find out I'm a Connect.
But...
You're right.
I don't need it anymore.
(band-aid rustles)
I'm happy.
Mm?
That there's someone just like me...
I'm really glad that it's you,
Choi Irang.
You don't have to suffer alone now.
Neither do you.
Give me that.
Gimme your hand.
(light music)
(upbeat music)
(suspenseful music)
(Z inhales deeply) Let's go.
(car alarm beeps)
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
(both laugh)
(murmurs)
Huh, oh.
(gasps)
(groans)
This is what happens when you steal someone else's song.
(rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
(suspenseful music continues)
(groans)
(grunting)
What, what's wrong?
(ominous music)
DONGSOO: He didn't give up.
(panting)
(foreboding music)
(Z grunting)
♪ A similar sound ♪
(breathes heavily)
(gasps)
(closing theme music)