(theme music)
(foreboding music)
(singing) ♪ High-hanging metal ♪
♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city ♪
DONGSOO (singing): ♪ Colorful junks ♪
♪ Hugging them ♪
♪ And putting them together ♪
♪ This is my sound ♪
♪ It's sad ♪
♪ Though it's quiet ♪
♪ Feels like being ♪
♪ Thrown out of the city ♪
♪ Was I ♪
♪ Born like that? ♪
(exhales slowly)
Pretty eyes.
Sorry?
Do you have good vision?
(in a scared voice) What?
I mean...
-you have nice eyes. -(breathing shakily)
-(Eunpyo grunts) -(Dongsoo light groan)
(strained groan)
Pretty eyes.
(grunts)
(grunting)
Sweet dreams.
(faint breathing)
A LEAF DROPS IN THE YARD SAD BUGS UNDER THE FLOORBOARD
I CANNOT STOP YOU FROM LEAVING BUT TO WHERE ARE YOU GOING
A SHARD OF HEART STOPS LIVING LONELY DREAM, ON A NIGHT WITH
BRIGHT MOON
WHEN SPRINGTIME LEAVES NAMPO FULL OF GREEN DO NOT FORGET YOUR PROMISE
(faint breathing)
(clanking)
(clanks)
(squelching)
(surgeon grunts)
(grunting continues)
(tires screech)
(crackles)
(light buzzing)
(exhales deeply)
(plastic rustles)
(foreboding music)
(gasps)
(grunting)
(breathes rapidly)
(surgeon grunting)
(grunts)
(panting)
Connect?
DOES ANYONE KNOW
AN URBAN LEGEND CALLED CONNECT?
ANYONE?
I'VE HEARD OF IT.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING UP STORIES
FOR MY WEB NOVEL.
IF YOU HAVE INFO PLEASE SHARE IT. COME ON.
(birds chirping)
(yawns)
(indistinct in distance)
(birds chirping)
(foreboding music)
(camera shutter clicks)
(blood plopping)
(foreboding music continues)
It's a person...
(breathes deeply)
-POLICE 1: Look away. -POLICE 2: Move, move.
-(indistinct chatter) -POLICE 3: Pull it out, come on!
POLICE 4: Hey, hey, pull it out!
DETECTIVE CHOI: Yeah, at ease.
POLICE 1: Please move back. Move back, please.
POLICE 2: You can't walk around. Oh, please get out of there.
POLICE 1: Excuse me, over there!
DETECTIVE CHOI: How on earth did they do this?
(grunts)
POLICE 5: Wait!
Oh, you cannot take pictures.
Whoa, no, no, no. You can't take photos here.
No, stop, stop, stop. Hey, push them all back.
-(indistinct chatter) -POLICE 6: Move back, move back!
Please move back.
I said do not take pictures!
POLICE 6: Do not take pictures, do not take pictures!
Move back!
CORONER (on speaker): Please look at this.
This looks like...
It looks like it was carved a few hours after death.
DETECTIVE PARK: What's that? Hold on. Is this letter P from the alphabet?
DETECTIVE YEOM: The bottom looks like an L.
DETECTIVE CHOI: Is it a signature?
You know, like when an artist finishes a painting
and puts their signature in the corner.
Ha. You mean, like marking his own signature?
Perverted bastard kills a person and then...
imitates an artist.
(siren blaring in distance)
(guitar strums)
(guitar strumming continues)
DONGSOO: Who might be getting transported this time?
(guitar strums)
(pained groan)
(strenuous breathing)
(electricity crackles)
(crackling continues)
(grunts)
(groans)
(statics)
READ MORE ABOUT TODAY'S ASTROLOGY AND UPCOMING ASPECTS BY THE HOUR.
DONGSOO: Zodiac signs?
(breathing heavily)
(grunting)
DONGSOO: What are they looking for?
(breathing heavily)
Where is this?
Eye drops? (breathing heavily)
(breathing heavily)
It's gone.
(Jinseop blows)
DONGSOO: What is all this?
(gulps)
(breathing shakily)
Could it be...
(surgeon grunts)
(pants)
(sneers)
What are you looking at?
Huh?
(foreboding music)
(trembling)
What... what the...
-(cell phone ringing) -(gasps)
Ugh. That startled me, damn it.
(cell phone ringing continues)
Yeah, what? Yeah, I'm doing it right now.
Cornea and liver?
Oh, you don't need those?
Oh, come on...
What's with this sudden bullshit?
Huh?
Yeah, okay, got it.
Just don't forget the money you promised me.
(chuckles)
Yeah, yeah.
(slurps)
(exhales deeply)
Yeah.
All right, bye.
(sighs)
(clatters)
(gasps)
(grunting)
(panting)
(breathes shakily)
(grunts)
(groaning)
(breathing heavily)
(surgeon grunts)
Hey, is anyone out there? Get in here, quick!
(grunts)
SURGEON (shouting): Hurry!
(clatters)
(breathes shakily)
DONGSOO: That night, when both my eyes were pulled out...
Was it transplanted to someone else?
(pants)
Is that why... I can see what that person is seeing?
(breathing shakily)
(sighs)
I should have taken both eyes back then.
(breathes deeply)
(breathing shakily)
(sighs deeply)
(grunts)
(Dongsoo groans)
(fireworks whistle)
(fireworks crackle)
SEOHAN CITY, A LARGE CROWD GATHER AT "SAMJI PORT FIREWORKS FESTIVAL"
(sighs)
(chuckles)
Goddamn it. Fuck. This is the worst.
(sighs)
DETECTIVE PARK: First victim, Kim Hyemi.
FIRST VICTIM: KIM HYEMI VICTIM 1 KIM HYEMI
SECOND VICTIM: PARK YONGSEOK VICTIM 2 PARK YONGSEOK
Second victim, Park Yongseok.
DETECTIVE CHOI: There's nothing that connects the two cases.
Neither case looks like it was caused by grudge.
Man, we were just digging up info on Kim Hyemi for nothing.
VICTIM KIM HYEMI AGE: 22 / OCCUPATION: COLLEGE STUDENT
I mean, if young women were the only targets,
we could approach it as a typical crazy sex offender case.
(inhales deeply)
But they killed the victim with so much care and effort
and decorated the victim like an artwork.
This sick psycho...
Even the crowd thought it was an art display.
They embalmed the body, angled it perfectly...
(inhales deeply)
...and even used resin to coat the body.
(scoffs)
(inhales sharply)
They made a tear in the flesh and deliberately let the blood drip?
Could this be intentional or a mistake?
Did they want to show off?
(sighs)
Ah, if only Detective Choi could sniff out some kind of lead,
that would be great.
You haven't had nosebleed yet, right?
Nosebleed? What is that?
Huh? Nosebleed is nosebleed. This guy is curious about so many things.
Let me show you. (clears throat) Here.
When he comes across a lead that makes him think "this is it,"
his nose bleeds.
(all giggle)
-Why is that? -DETECTIVE CHOI: Hey, come on.
Well, it's not like you can hide it.
Oh, his grandmother is a big-time shaman.
Many of his relatives are too. It runs in the family, right?
Is it fun? Making your supervisor look weird?
Go ask forensics for the resin component analysis
then find out the purchase route and seller.
-DETECTIVE 1: Yes, sir. -DETECTIVE 2: Yes, sir.
DETECTIVE 3: Yes.
JUNK SHOP
(grunts)
(crackles)
He should have already been back by now but I still haven't heard from him.
What could he be doing out there? (sighs)
He could have waited a few days for the car repair.
Oh, my. But he just couldn't wait and went out with his handcart.
I'll go find him.
(clatters in distance)
(dog barking in distance)
STUDENT 1: Go ahead and say something, damn it.
MAN: I was out of strength and I lost grip. I made a mistake, okay?
(student scoffs)
I'm sorry, okay? I am sorry.
I mean, you just hit a person, so you have to apologize. That's a given.
-STUDENT 2: Huh? -MAN: Yeah.
If you're broke, can you kill someone and then just say "I'm sorry"?
-STUDENT 2: Damn it. -MAN: Come on, please, ah...
"Sorry" doesn't cut it!
I'm begging you like this, please.
Now, what is this? I don't need this.
(laughing) STUDENTS: Whoa.
STUDENT 2: I mean he's not even listening to me.
What are you all doing right now?
Sir.
Hey, what are you doing here? Go back.
No, how could I? What do you think you're doing right now?
-Damn it, let's go. Quickly. -(grunting)
Huh? Wait, where do you think you're going?
I'm talking to the man who just hit me and tried to run away.
Hey, do you want to die?
Hey, look how scared this guy looks. Man, you're scared as heck, aren't you?
(all laugh)
-Hurry up and go. -I'll call the police.
That little...
(student 2 groans)
(Dongsoo grunts)
-STUDENT 2: Come out, come out. -STUDENT 1: Out, out, out, out.
STUDENT 3: Knuckle ball kick!
Get off me, you son of a bitch.
-STUDENT 2: You little... -(Dongsoo groans)
(Dongsoo grunts)
(indistinct chatter)
(groans)
(student 1 breathes deeply)
(Dongsoo pants)
-STUDENT 3: Oh, oh. -STUDENT 1: Where are you going?
(students snicker)
(student 1 scoffs) You ready to get stabbed?
(students laugh)
(breathing shakily)
STUDENT 3: He's trembling. See that? Do you see that? Huh?
(student 2 murmuring)
This bastard!
(student grunt)
You crazy bastard, why didn't you move? Damn it.
(students moan)
STUDENT 3: Hey...
(groans)
Let's just stop here, okay?
(student 2 grunts)
Hey, this bastard. A monster...
GIRL 1: Monster.
BOY: Monster.
GIRL: Mo... Monster.
STUDENT 3: He's a monster!
(students grunt)
I'm not!
(breathing shakily)
(moans)
(groans)
(grunts)
(pants)
(moans)
(breathing heavily)
(pants)
STUDENT 3: Hurry up, damn it.
STUDENT 2: Hey, hey, hey, hey, let's just call the cops, come on.
Oh, stop it. That old man went to call the police.
Oh, let's just fucking go, okay?
Hey, did you see that bastard was missing an eye? So gross.
-Oh, the eye. -Oh, man.
Hey, stop!
(both groan)
What was it that you saw?
KARAOKE
MR. KIM: So he sure hasn't left this town, huh?
Keep looking. Finding that bastard is most important.
ALL: Yes, sir.
MINSOOK: Why are you all just standing around?
MINSOOK (on radio): You heard him. Go look for him.
Man, what a halfwit.
What are you doing, losing a game?
(deeply exhales)
If the old quack is right, this is going to be a huge jackpot.
Right?
(deeply exhales)
A body that does not die
would be a living bundle of money.
Exactly, right? And that old quack had to lose him. So annoying.
(clicks tongue)
MR. KIM (on radio): What was it called, "Connect"?
Wow.
So, something like that actually exists?
Bingo.
(light music)
MAN (singing): ♪ High-hanging metal ♪
♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city, oh, oh ♪
♪ Colorful junks ♪
♪ Hugging them ♪
♪ And putting them together ♪
♪ This is my sound, oh ♪
DONGSOO: That song earlier, was it your original?
Oh, no. The song is from the internet.
But singing with this melody sounds a lot better.
The sound quality of the original is kind of bad, and the singing is also...
(clicks tongue)
Ah, is it?
YOUTUBE
DONGSOO (singing): ♪ High-hanging metal, low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
Is it not that good?
♪ The sound of the city ♪
(smacks lips)
♪ Colorful junks... ♪
(sighs)
(pen rasping)
(pained moan)
(grunts)
(grunting continues)
DONGSOO (singing): ♪ High-hanging metal, low-hanging leaf ♪
(pained moan)
♪ When they bump ♪
-(groans) -♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city ♪
(grunting)
♪ Colorful junk... ♪
(exhales deeply)
(panting)
It... It's gone.
(breathing heavily)
What on earth is this?
(breathing heavily continues)
Monster.
BOY: He's a monster.
(Young Dongsoo groans)
(gasps)
(moans)
(moaning continues)
Mo... monster.
(shatters)
(breathing heavily)
I have to get it back.
(breathes shakily)
KARAOKE
(foreboding music)
(sighs)
Bastard's got guts.
He came back here again?
(laughs) That bastard.
-(pants) -THUG: Catch him!
We'll make sure to catch you this time!
How dare you show your fucking face here?
(indistinct shouting)
(pants)
(ominous music)
(horn honking)
(ominous music continues)
(Dongsoo panting continues)
Oh, please. Oh, damn it.
(both breathing heavily)
DONGSOO: You sons of bitches!
(shouting)
(all grunt)
(Dongsoo groans)
(panting)
(all grunting)
(rattles)
(Dongsoo grunts)
(moans)
(Dongsoo breathes heavily)
RAILROAD CROSSING TRAIN PASSING THROUGH
(train horn honks)
(panting)
IRANG: You're going to get caught.
(breathing heavily)
Who are you?
-(breathes deeply) -(indistinct shouting in distance)
(hurried breathing)
That's a dead end. Go that way.
-(thugs' indistinct shouting) -(Dongsoo breathing heavily)
Hurry!
Go!
SALES, RENTAL CONSTRUCTION, LOAN CONSULTING 798-70
-(thug indistinct shouting) -Damn it.
(panting)
(whimpering) Damn it. It's a dead end.
(breathing shakily)
(breathing heavily)
Ah, damn it.
Did you do this on purpose? Are you one of them?
Sorry, I had to see this for myself.
What, what is it? What, what are you doing?
(pained moans)
(groans)
(pained moan)
(breathing shakily)
(thugs' indistinct shouting)
(hurried breathing)
(light moan)
(thuds)
(alarm blaring)
Welcome.
(thugs indistinct shouting)
(tires screech)
(light clicks)
I COMPLETELY AGREE WITH PLATO'S WORDS THAT THERE IS NO CORRECT ANSWER
TO THE BEAUTY OF WOMEN. BEAUTIFUL FIGURE...
DRAWING A PRETTY LINE THROUGH, SO THAT I CAN PLANT FLOWERS ONTO THE BODY
THAT CAN BRING OUT THE SUPREME NOBILITY OF BEAUTY.
BLOOD IS THE SOURCE OF ALL LIFE.
LIKE WATER, BLOOD IS SELF-EVIDENT AND CLEAR.
WHAT CAN I TRY? FEELING OF FALLING?
DO I SHARE THE SAME DNA AS HIM? AM I A PART OF HIM?
IT'S UGLY...
IT'S SLANTED AND DISTORTED.
NOT DISTURBED, SO THAT THE PAIN WILL REACH THE BONES.
BLOOD VESSEL, TENDON, ACHILLES TENDON.
(foreboding music)
SHOUT OUT THE BEAT IN THE DARK A CHANGE FOR ME
Z@OFFICIAL_Z FOLLOW
JOINED SEPTEMBER 2010 FOLLOWING 21 / FOLLOWER 197,895
29TH MONDAY
CLICK TO UN-MUTE
PRACTICE PIECE 03
DONGSOO (singing): ♪ High-hanging metal ♪
♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city ♪
(crowd indistinct chatter)
-WOMAN 1: Look at that, it's crazy. -MAN: What a lunatic.
WOMAN 2: What are the police doing, not catching this guy?
(crowd indistinct chatter continues)
POLICE: You cannot take pictures. No pictures.
DETECTIVE CHOI: Ugh, damn it.
(foreboding music)
How was your trip?
I haven't heard from you at all during your vacation.
I didn't want to rope you into the pain of having to come up with ideas.
Not because you were trying to keep a distance?
(humming)
(groans)
Jinseop.
(grunting)
(groaning)
Jinseop, are you okay? Did something get in your eye?
No.
(groaning)
DONGSOO: Who is this woman?
Where is this?
(breathing heavily)
What was that song?
Huh?
The song you were humming just now.
Oh, uh, that song was recommended by one of my favorite singers.
Oh...
I've heard it somewhere.
I definitely, definitely recognize this place.
(breathing heavily)
DONGSOO: W... when I would go around collecting things...
DETECTIVE YEOM: Detective Choi.
Huh?
Could you take a look at this?
(sighs)
What is it?
There are people who are following that lunatic.
What?
Mm, American.
It's German.
Oh, German. What's it say?
The translation says,
"The perpetrator of this murder is the worst criminal,
but their artistic sense does draw out my admiration."
(scoffs)
This is French.
Tell us what it says, boy, the damn translation.
"I wish the case would be resolved as soon as possible,
but it scares me how part of me is looking forward to the next piece."
I'M SCARED THAT HE'S A MURDERER, BUT I ACKNOWLEDGE HIS ART. TALENT IS BORN!
Vietnamese.
This is Mongolian.
(inhales deeply)
(sighs) Oh boy, they are all turning crazy.
(pained moan)
(breathing heavily)
(trembling voice) Ah, again.
(foreboding music)
DONGSOO: What is this?
(breathing shakily)
This is...
I SHALL PROVE IT. THE NEUROTICISM WHICH FREUD SPOKE OF,
THAT HAS CONFLICTS WITH EGO, ONCE GAVE ME TEDIOUS,
TEETH-RATTLING FEAR, BUT IN FACT...
(breathing shakily)
CORPSE ART
SEARCH CORPSE ART
(startled breathing)
The person who took my eye...
(stammering) ...was a murderer?
(breathing shakily)
(indistinct chatter)
It's here, it's here!
Find out everything about this guy.
Okay, so this guy is a strong suspect.
(breathes deeply) See?
Really?
(sighs lightly)
-Come on, you bastard. -(pained moan)
DONGSOO: He is here.
(foreboding music)
OCTOBER 14TH - FATHER JANUARY 21ST - 23RD
FEBRUARY 5TH - MOTHER SEPTEMBER 28TH - 30TH
DONGSOO: Give me back my eye, you murderer.
(closing theme music)