(theme music)
DOLCHI
Yeah, did you find her?
MAN (on cell phone): Yes.
(suspenseful music)
MR. KIM: Stay close to her and learn everything you can.
Where they're based,
if they live as a group or mooch off of someone,
how many there are.
(grunts)
(groans)
BOSS 2
Ugh, so annoying...
I heard you found her.
Separated from the eyeball and currently alone.
She hasn't left Seohan City yet.
Ugh, they were right under our noses
and we let them go like idiots, oh, man...
We'll keep this between us...
I won't report to the higher-ups.
Oh, of course, we worked so hard for that information.
Yeah, with the eye patch, it's gotta be Ha Dongsoo.
That little…
(sighs)
I mean, he could jump from the rooftop, this is nothing for him! Damn it.
(scoffs)
He's certainly different.
Right?
(Detective Choi inhales deeply)
Why did Oh Jinseop pretend to be Ha Dongsoo?
Sir?
To pin the murder charge on him?
Or is it something else?
You mean, this... this... this is O... Oh Jinseop?
I know how this ends.
Go arrest Oh Jinseop, right now.
(Gideun snores)
Wake up! Gideun!
(groans)
(snarls lightly)
-Pack your things, too. -(Gideun grunts)
Starting tomorrow,
we'll have a better place to eat and sleep in than this hole.
(growls lightly)
From now on, we'll crush anyone...
who tries to take advantage of our power.
(Gideun growls)
(growls)
(foreboding music)
(scoffs) What are you looking at?
JINSEOP: You see what beauty could come from using the human body as a medium?
You should recognize that surgeon from before.
Organ trafficking gang...
(breathes shakily)
Where is Z?
What would you do if you knew? Would you help him?
Stop getting innocent people involved.
We're polar opposites.
I wanted to ascend into a plane of eternal beauty
despite being born into a life of insignificance.
You were born outside a world that doesn't want you,
but you still so desperately wanted to become a part of it.
I create art,
and you sing,
and the two of us met through eye transplant.
Doesn't this conjunction of fate feel beautiful?
Oh, wait, maybe for you it's repulsive?
Isn't it obvious?
JINSEOP: Well, be that as it may.
In the eyes of the world, you and I are both treated like monsters.
(breathes deeply)
(tongue clicks)
The same but complete opposites.
That relationship itself creates newness.
Whether that is beauty or something more fundamental.
Light and shadow, negative and positive, man and woman.
If things far apart can be linked
as one...
How about it? Would you like to live with me as one?
What?
We become one, by attaching my head to your body.
You sick bastard.
Where's Z?
(breathes shakily)
DONGSOO: I... I came as promised,
bring me Z.
You leave me no choice. I must start the experiment.
Experiment?
(whimpers)
(breathes heavily)
Mr. Z, I'm sorry,
because of me you're... (sighs deeply)
(Dongsoo sniffles)
Who...
Oh, I am, uh...
I'm Guitar Man.
Lonely Guitar Man.
DONGSOO: Shut up.
(laughs)
Guitar Man?
Oh, I'm really sorry,
you were kidnapped to lure me here.
What do you mean?
So…
How do I start?
(breathes shakily)
That bastard is the corpse art killer.
The corpse art murder case?
Yes. I've been keeping track of his crimes so far, and, uh...
A detective?
Oh, no, I, I'm actually not...
Oh, Guitar Man.
Yes. Uh, you covered my song.
It was an honor, really, and, uh...
You seriously suck at explaining.
(breathing shakily)
Wh... what are you doing?
(groaning)
(Dongsoo groans)
(sucks teeth)
This is it, right here. The reason Guitar Man is lonely.
(soft grunt)
You're probably thinking, "What in the world is this?" Yes?
(panting) Oh, no.
Don't do it, stop!
(groans)
You damn psychopath!
-(sobs) -(laughs)
It wouldn't connect back, normally.
See? That's to be expected.
But his finger...
(Z gasping)
(breathes shakily)
Interesting, isn't it?
But this is not the purpose of this experiment.
The important part is just about to begin.
Take a good look at what happens to your finger.
(breathes heavily)
(Dongsoo grunting)
(gasping)
How did something like this come into this world?
(Dongsoo breathes heavily) How should I know?
JINSEOP: Don't you dare call him a monster.
All of this is a miracle.
That life was created in this universe, that a Connect has finally appeared,
and that I've met him.
(breathing heavily)
You don't need Z anymore. Right?
I'm here now.
That is true.
Spare Z's life, please.
Okay, I'll let him go.
If you accept my proposal to become one with me.
"Become one"?
N... no, that's not it, you m... misunderstand.
What this bastard means is that he'd cut my head off
and switch bodies, or something like that...
Doesn't that sound weirder? Think about it.
(breathes heavily)
You're really the corpse art murderer...
(panting)
If Guitar Man doesn't accept my proposal,
then I'll be putting you up somewhere as my next piece.
(breathing shakily)
You crazy bastard.
(clanking)
(laughs)
MINSOOK: Wow, what a cool Santa Claus we got here.
Who's there?
Who is it?
(knocks on door)
Oh, look who's here.
Our missing wallet turned itself back in, then?
I got tired of running around. And I brought a friend, too.
(Gideun growling)
What is that?
A monster?
(Gideun snarling)
(gasps)
You shouldn't say something like that all of a sudden.
IRANG: It's taboo.
Say it again.
What?
Monster?
(snarling)
(roars)
(grunts)
(Eunpyo exclaims)
(growls)
(all grunting)
(pants)
(grunts)
(roars)
(groans)
(grunts)
(gasps)
(growls)
(snarls)
(grunting)
(groans)
(shouts)
(growls)
Yeah, okay, yeah, hang on, sir, remember how we couldn't recover
some photos in that digital camera found at the irrigation channel?
-Yeah. -They were all completely recovered.
(sniffles)
Send them right now.
Aw, Sungjun, ah...
Oh, oh, damn, wait a second.
-Man, you make my life so difficult. -Are you all right? Wait...
(exhales)
We can find the GPS data for this photo here, too, right?
Of course.
DETECTIVE CHOI: Let's go over here, right now.
Yes, sir. Yeah, right, Detective Choi and I are heading down
to that building in photo number 28 now.
So you inform the superiors
and bring every SWAT team member available.
(whimpers)
(Dongsoo shouting) Let Z go right now!
(breathing heavily)
By saying that, do you mean to accept my proposal?
(breathing shakily)
(groans)
(breathes heavily)
(Dongsoo gasping)
Oh...
(breathes shakily)
Mr. Z.
Can you hear me?
Mr. Z...
Sorry.
(breathes shakily)
You were uncovering...
(gasps softly)
...that damned murder case,
and I got in the way, didn't I?
(breathes shakily)
(stutters) No.
It's all my fault,
I dragged you into this.
(breathes heavily)
Feels like I got in the way...
(coughs)
(breathes shakily)
Sorry...
I couldn't be...
of any help....
(Dongsoo gasps)
(gasps)
DONGSOO: Mr. Z.
Mr. Z.
(scoffs)
Oh, Mr. Z!
(sobbing)
Y... your arrangement for that song...
was truly the best.
I... I really wanted to say th...
thank you, I'm sorry.
(breathing shakily)
(chain rattling)
(grunts)
(inhales sharply)
(shouting)
(pants)
(groans)
(grunts)
(breathes heavily)
He got out of his binding?
(scoffs) That never gets old.
(grunting)
(panting)
(Gideun growls)
Tired from all that fighting, aren't you?
(rumbles)
Take a break.
(faint thud)
(ominous music)
(grunts) Ah, please, please, oh, come on.
(grunts)
(exhales sharply)
-IRANG: Dongsoo? -(gasps)
Irang?
Irang! (gasps)
(grunts)
(yelps)
Who are you?
(grunting)
A Connect...
JINSEOP: There's a woman, too?
(breathes shakily)
What's happening?
You burnt an awful lot of cash.
I did think the corpse art was uncanny all the way around,
but you really put your whole back into it behind the scenes, huh?
Can your bodies' abilities be passed down to the next generation?
That's what I wanted to know. But you're curious too?
I wonder what a rich murderer is into.
You want to take Dongsoo's body and make a baby with me?
Or would you like to take my body and make a baby with Dongsoo?
Surprise, surprise. Maybe you're into the latter, huh?
And which do you prefer? Either way, we will bear a Connect's offspring.
Personally, I want nothing more than for you to die here right now.
Hm, that will go according to fate. And your name is?
Irang!
Hey! He was talking to me!
(grunting)
(both grunt)
(groans)
(grunting)
(scoffs) Ha, you bastard...
(yelps)
(groaning)
(grunts)
(breathes heavily)
Ah...
(sighs)
(exhales deeply)
(whispers) Sir, looks like we could enter
through up there.
-Go that way. -Yes, sir.
(pants)
I... Irang, what happened to you? Are you okay?
You're one to talk.
Where is he?
Someone's here, but I don't know who.
He went that way.
You go finish him.
I'll leave how it ends up to you.
What do you mean?
Fate or chance, it doesn't end here.
The future must be changed.
(Gideun growls)
-(roars) -(gunshot)
(panting)
(grunts)
(gun clanks)
(gags)
What the... This one's a Connect too?
(grunts)
(breathes heavily)
(soft growling)
We'll have to get rid of you. You know too much.
DETECTIVE CHOI: I remember you.
From the security camera at Oh Jinseop's building.
So you're a Connect, too?
There you go again with that nonsense.
It would have been better for you to play the fool.
Is Oh Jinseop here?
And Ha Dongsoo too?
What difference would it make if you know? You're going to die here and now anyway.
(chuckles softly)
Even if I die, I want to uncover the truth...
That's what detectives do.
Oh, how noble of you.
And how unfortunate.
If you didn't know anything, I would have helped you with the investigation.
We will survive, whatever it takes.
(Gideun growls)
Killing a few detectives to reach that end?
That's nothing.
(low growl)
(scoffs)
(inhales deeply)
I thought I'd seen my fair share of bad things in life,
but I guess I have a long ways to go until I've seen it all.
I can't imagine what tough lives you and Ha Dongsoo must have had.
(mellow music)
JINSEOP: How much are you able to recover from?
(rattles)
For example...
What would happen if I shot you in the head?
(laughs)
Would that stop your body from moving temporarily?
If that works, the next time you open your eyes,
your body will have been swallowed...
by late-stage cancer.
(coughs)
What have you been trying to do all this time
with that immortal body of yours?
Don't tell me some pathetic dream to live
a normal life was all it was.
DONGSOO: I'm not like you.
If I could, I'd live an ordinary life.
I will never give my body over to you.
♪ High-hanging metal ♪
♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city... ♪
DONGSOO: You don't get to sing the song I created.
♪ Colorful junk ♪
♪ Hugging them ♪
♪ And putting them together ♪
♪ It's sad ♪
♪ Though it's quiet ♪
♪ Feels like being ♪
♪ Thrown out of the city ♪
♪ Was I ♪
♪ Born like that? ♪
(scoffs)
(spits)
(mutters)
(gags)
(retches)
(grunts)
(groans)
(breathes heavily)
(screams)
(grunts)
You bastard, how many people have you killed?
(gags)
(breathing heavily)
(gasps)
(panting)
(groaning)
(Jinseop groans in pain)
(gasping)
Give me back my eyeball.
(screams)
(groaning)
(groans)
(grunting)
(groaning)
(breathes heavily)
(grunting)
I'll give you a taste of your own medicine.
(breathes heavily)
Stop it!
(pants)
Don't. I am begging you to stop.
(breathes heavily)
(breathes deeply)
No matter how despicable and horrid
this murderer is, if you kill him,
I have no choice but to prosecute you,
because you will also be a murderer yourself.
(mutters)
This lowlife...
took precious lives.
(Dongsoo breathes shakily)
Is that right?
Yes, well, it's over.
Leave this all to me, and you'd better get out of here.
You've got someone waiting for you.
Irang.
Pretty soon SWAT guys will barge in here.
They won't bat an eye at your story.
(sighs)
(foreboding music)
(gunfiring in distance)
Dongsoo, we have to go. They're coming.
They?
(creaking)
Hurry!
(foreboding music)
(growls)
(foreboding music intensifies)
(closing theme music)