(theme music)
DONGSOO (ringtone playing): ♪ When they bump... ♪
BUSINESS HQ 3 JIYOUNG
It is because of this song?
(breathes deeply)
That crazy bastard.
(angry breathing)
What in the world just happened?
WOMAN: I think it was someone from M&amp;T.
MAN: I thought it was someone from the production team.
(indistinct chatter)
21 MARKETING COMPANY JY COMPANY OFFICE 20 M&amp;T PLANNING CEO OFFICE
(indistinct chatter in distance)
-(woman whimpering) -No way, did someone really fall? Huh?
Was it a man or a woman?
(shaky voice) It...it was Myeonghun, it was Myeonghun. Myeonghun...
-Myeo... Myeonghun? -(rough breathing)
Pick up...
(hurried breathing)
MANAGER: Jiyoung!
(ominous music)
(hurried breathing)
(whimpering) Sunhee, Sunhee!
-(siren blaring in distance) -(gasps)
(screaming)
(Dongsoo panting)
(panting continues)
(foreboding music)
-(indistinct chatter) -(gasps)
(panting)
(breathing roughly) This bastard...
(door clatters)
(breathes deeply)
You're done, you psycho.
(rough breathing)
What's your problem? Are you crazy?
You... I saw e... everything, you bastard.
(shaky voice) What you have done.
(breathes rapidly)
Where is the coat?
What?
Where is that coat? You bastard.
(breathing shakily)
-(clatters) -What's your problem?
I don't have a coat, okay?
(breathes deeply)
Damn it.
(door slams open)
(door slams close)
(breathes heavily)
(breathing shakily)
I know you're in here, you murderer.
Open the door, you bastard. (breathes heavily)
Corpse art. Bastard.
(pants)
Ugh, shit, you bastard. Murderer!
(groans)
(breathing heavily)
Hey, you crazy bastard!
-SECURITY: Excuse me, sir. -Yes, sir. Here, here, here.
Oh, it's not me. Damn it, it's not me! Let go, let go!
Come on, sir, let go of me!
-Stay still! -Stay still.
-DONGSOO: Sir! -(security 1 grunts)
Trespassing and assault weren't enough, you pervert?
Oh, boy.
Damn it, that's not it. Let go of me. Just let go, come on!
-SECURITY 1: What do you mean "let go"? -SECURITY 2: Please stay still, okay?
(grunts, exhales deeply)
(angry breathing)
(groans)
DONGSOO: Come out!
Come out, you son of a bitch! It was this asshole here!
(groans)
-Sir, please! -SECURITY 2: Relax or you'll get hurt.
-(indistinct chatter) -Move aside, please.
You're making a mistake.
If you got something to say,
you can talk about it at the police station.
Let me just see his face, his face. I just need to see his face!
SECURITY 2: Whose face are you trying to see?
That murderer... Sir, please, it wasn't me. It really wasn't me.
-What wouldn't it be you? -Go tell the police.
AUTOMATED VOICE (on speakers): The door is closing.
(Dongsoo breathing shakily)
JIYOUNG: Eye patch...
(rough breathing)
It was you, wasn't it?
What...
(angry breathing)
(shaky voice) No, it wasn't me. It wasn't me.
You're the man who's been following Sunhee!
-That's you! -Whoa, what are you doing?
Oh, come on.
-(gasps) -(breathing shakily)
What is this?
Damn it.
(employee gasp)
-EMPLOYEE 1: Look, he's got no eye. -EMPLOYEE 2: His eye, it's...
Why doesn't he have that eye?
There's another dead person?
Yes. I found her on the rooftop. I already called the police.
(sobbing)
It's not me, it's not me. He's over there in the stall. Fuck!
He's got my eye, that, that bastard!
Cut the crap.
Hey, you son of a bitch! Wherever you are, I'll find you and come after you!
(grunting)
(strained moan)
JINSEOP: Corpse art.
So, he knows about me? But he doesn't know my face.
How is that possible?
What's wrong? What happened?
It seems like Myeonghun fell down.
What?
Myeonghun?
Ugh, it's so gross, damn it.
(sighs)
1 WELCOME
It was you?
Well, he's been hanging around the building lately.
I did think it was odd.
Can we please go peacefully?
-(electricity crackles) -(security staff groans)
(groans)
(rough breathing)
(security 1 grunts)
(electricity crackles)
(breathes deeply)
Glad to see me again, right?
(scoffs)
(soft chuckles)
DETECTIVE PARK: They say the eye patch man
has been roaming around the company these past few days.
There were company employees
who testified that he's been stalking the deceased Lee Sunhee.
DETECTIVE CHOI: Why was he following Lee Sunhee around?
(Detective Park inhales sharply)
DETECTIVE PARK: But if the eye patch man
killed Hwang Myeonghun and Lee Sunhee,
then the timeline doesn't make sense if you take a look at this.
Because the eye patch man entered this building
after Hwang Myeonghun fell from the rooftop and died.
What about that woman who helped him?
-Please show us the entrance gate footage. -Yes, sir.
DETECTIVE PARK: Apparently, she entered a few minutes
-after the eye patch man entered. -Ah...
DETECTIVE PARK: This woman took the employee badge
from the bathroom outside the gate over there.
DONGSOO: Wherever you are, I'll find you and come after you!
(sighs)
But how?
(sighs deeply)
(ominous music)
The transplant?
(sighs) This does not make sense.
And yet it does.
(chuckles slightly)
-Excuse me. -JINSEOP: Yes.
-Are you Team Leader Oh Jinseop? -Yes.
Uh...
(sighs)
Do you have time to answer a few questions?
Yes.
Okay.
(grunts lightly)
DETECTIVE CHOI: By any chance, do you recognize this man?
Yes.
He made that much ruckus,
so it'd be weird if I didn't recognize him.
Ah...
Ah, I see. All right.
Well, while we're on the topic...
while he was causing that ruckus, where were you watching from?
The hallway.
What was he shouting while causing the ruckus?
He said thief, or something like that, I think.
Thief?
Did he shout "something" thief?
I'm not sure about the details...
I heard he said something like "eyeball thief."
What's the point of this?
Why would you ask when you already know?
Oh...
For now,
I do not know.
(ominous music)
I remember Sunhee telling Jiyoung that a man missing an eyeball
and wearing an eye patch was following her around.
If it's about that, you should ask her...
Ah, I just did check with her.
Ah, Mr. Oh, were you wearing a coat when you came to work this morning?
A coat?
Uh, I heard the eye patch man was looking for someone's coat.
-Could we take a look at your coat? -(sighs)
Uh, wait a minute.
What are you doing right now? Huh?
You should be catching the culprit,
but instead, you're asking silly questions to an innocent person!
You think you can do whatever you want just because you're cops?
-How could you say something like that? -I mean...
It's okay, Jiyoung.
The detectives should keep all possibilities
open in their investigation until they reach the conclusion.
I totally understand this little bit of disrespect.
Thank you for your understanding.
But, what I want to ask is...
Yes, what is it?
What is that tissue for?
Is it to lessen the anxiety on the subject you're interrogating?
Ah, this... this, ah, yes.
(chuckles awkwardly) I, uh, had a bit of nosebleed earlier.
Is it still bleeding?
(lightly chuckles)
(clears throat)
(ominous music)
Thanks.
(sniffles)
(slurps)
Now, tell me.
Who... Who are you?
I'm a novelist.
To be?
(lightly chuckles)
Well, even if I do become one, it might be over with just one novel.
I just wanted to write about Connect.
Why?
I received help from a Connect when I was young.
There was a kid who helped me
when I was about to get hit by a dump truck.
The kid got hit by the truck instead of me.
And that kid was a Connect.
(sniffles)
Was it a friend?
No, I had never seen the kid before.
The kid was crushed under the truck, and it was brutal.
The truck driver was scared to death and didn't know what to do,
and then ran away.
But surprisingly,
the body of that kid,
was restored in the blink of an eye.
Just like you.
And then the kid just disappeared.
I didn't have time to say thanks, and no one believed me.
So, the incident wasn't reported at all, as if it never happened.
But I remember.
I remember that kid who cared to save me that day.
And then one day, I heard an urban legend about a body that does not die.
That's when I started digging.
What about you? Do you know who's after you?
Aren't they organ traffickers?
IRANG: That's right, but it looks like there's a higher organization
that actually does the organ trafficking,
and the ones after you are organ hunters, who specialize in capturing people.
So you were caught by them and you ran away from them?
(clatters)
DONGSOO: Yeah.
DOES ANYONE KNOW
AN URBAN LEGEND CALLED CONNECT?
ANYONE?
So, I left a reply comment there, and I was able to meet them.
This is what I wrote back then.
And then we agreed to exchange information,
but we had different motives so we just sounded each other out.
IRANG: But obviously, no real information came of it.
I was able to find various information,
through the tapping device I planted there.
Tapping device?
From you, a novelist?
Well, it is illegal, but...
they are criminals anyway.
Thanks to that, I learned about you.
(sighs deeply)
(inhaling) So...
What is this Connect?
(exhales deeply)
It's not a simple cut-and-dried story.
Based on the information I collected,
they're connected with Jeongdo Pharmaceuticals.
Jeongdo Pharmaceuticals? You mean...
Right, the number one corporation in our country.
What is that?
If you're concerned, do you want to investigate it together?
(sighing)
I am concerned, but stopping the murders is more important right now.
Murder?
When I was abducted,
I lost an eye. And that eye was transplanted to a man...
(sighs)
(sighs deeply)
That bastard has it.
My eye...
(laughs)
(inhales deeply)
Sorry.
But how do you know?
That his eye is yours?
(sighs lightly)
Because I had visions.
DETECTIVE CHOI: He's an unbelievable narcissist.
Oh Jinseop?
Yeah.
We were the ones attacking him,
yet he bared his teeth at the one who's trying to help him.
Huh?
When?
He seemed more annoyed with the woman
who defended him than us who were interrogating him.
He is triggered by completely different things
compared to ordinary people.
(ominous music)
IRANG: I've never heard of anything like that.
An ability to have vision even after having the eye transplanted to someone...
(sighs)
Well, it's up to you to believe it or not.
What else happens?
You know, thoughts being shared...
Well, it's not really something like that...
(Dongsoo sighs)
Ah...
(breathing shakily)
(light music)
Looks better than the eye patch.
(breathing shakily)
Everyone is looking for a man with an eye patch.
Keep that on whenever you go outside.
(clatters)
Would you like it in a bag?
-Ah... -Yes.
WANTED FLYER OF MURDER SUSPECT
I, uh, I'll just take it.
I rang up for the bag too...
Oh, please take this.
(breathing shakily)
Man, this is driving me crazy.
(groans)
What's wrong?
(panting)
We're... connected.
(groans)
DONGSOO (singing): ♪ High-hanging metal ♪
♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪
Just as I thought, it's because of this song...
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
This voice...
(grunts)
DONGSOO (singing): ♪ The sound of the city ♪
Is it possible that it was...
♪ Colorful junks ♪
...this guitar man?
(ominous music)
Ah, wait.
(panting)
He's listening to my song. I think my eye is responding to my song.
What do you mean?
(groans)
Are you saying that your vision is linked when he listens to your song?
(pants)
Ah...
The pain is gone.
(chuckles)
(breathing heavily)
It's gone.
(breathes deeply)
IRANG: Do you think he found out? That you've been watching?
DONGSOO: I don't know yet.
If he finds out,
he will come kill you.
Can he really kill me?
He could kill you through social media if he reveals your face
and your bodily secrets with a video on the internet.
(sighs)
Keep a low profile for a while, and let me do the probing.
Okay?
(Dongsoo grunts)
(clatters)
MAN: Oh my...
My goodness, what little savings I have
is all about to go into my wife's hospital bill.
This life of mine, seriously.
It's like living in hell.
There is nothing good. Oh, goodness.
MAN (on radio): Next up, we'll play a new release by Z.
It's a cover of another artist's song.
Original song and lyrics by Lonely Guitar Man.
Rearranged by Z.
Z (singing over radio): ♪ High-hanging metal ♪
♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city ♪
♪ Colorful junks ♪
♪ Hugging them ♪
♪ And putting them together ♪
♪ That is my sound ♪
♪ I feel a little sad ♪
♪ Feels like I'm thrown out of the city ♪
♪ Is that how I was born? ♪
Dongsoo.
Isn't this the tune you've always been humming?
(song continues)
Maybe there are good things in this hellish world sometimes.
Z (singing over radio): ♪ That is my sound... ♪
Is that so?
I guess so.
Wow, but it really sounds different when played by a professional musician.
Z (singing over radio): ♪ If you listen in closely to the city ♪
♪ My sound is in it ♪
♪ That is my sound ♪
♪ When it becomes quiet
I feel a little sad ♪
♪ Feels like I'm thrown out of the city ♪
♪ Is that how I was born... ♪
Z: The thing is, we don't know anything about his identity either.
There's the royalty issue about lyrics
and the music so we really tried to look for him, but we couldn't find him.
I heard the copyright fee is going straight to donation. That is my sound.
Oh, that's a shame. I thought it would be a perfect fit for our advertisement.
(exhales deeply)
A big corporation is amazed by a nameless amateur.
That's unbelievable, right?
I think that's why I'm so drawn to him, an artist who's not swayed by money.
I mean, it even makes me feel happy.
(exhales deeply)
(foreboding music)
DETECTIVE PARK: So...
Why are you after the eye patch man?
I said I was just jogging.
For diet.
Enough of that bullshit.
What, someone like you who looks they loan out small amounts
and take huge interests?
(smirks)
Huh? Huh?
(grunts)
DETECTIVE CHOI (on speaker): You're still doing this?
Let him go.
DETECTIVE PARK: Detective.
DETECTIVE CHOI: Let him go.
THUG: Can I go?
(Detective Park grunts)
(sighs)
DETECTIVE PARK: Go.
Go. And don't come back.
Get out!
DETECTIVE CHOI: Let's do this the easy way.
First, keep that eye patch man on a tight leash.
It's me, Woojin, sir.
MINSOOK (on tape): Why is it so difficult to get a hold of you?
You know how important that money is to us, right?
How about the guy with the transplanted eye, huh? Woojin?
"Woojin"?
(chuckles)
WOOJIN (on mobile phone): Yes, he's doing the regular 9 to 5
like a common office worker.
Yeah, okay, keep your eyes wide open and watch carefully, okay?
Damn it, he was about to die any moment anyway,
so why did we transplant the eye to him, huh?
MINSOOK (on tapping device): Right?
It's an eye that can be sold for a high price,
so we should take it before he's cremated, right?
-He's dying? -MINSOOK: My pretties, where... huh?
What?
The... the baby is gone.
Both of them?
No, no, Sodom is here, but Gomorrah is missing.
Where did it go?
MR. KIM: Aw, come on...
MINSOOK: What are you doing? Find it!
Ah...
MINSOOK (mumbling): Damn it, where is it?
Huh?
MINSOOK (on tapping device): It's a tapping device.
MR. KIM (on tapping device): Who the fuck dared to...
Come on. (clicks tongue)
It's her, that novelist bitch.
She said she didn't have enough battery on her laptop and came over here.
May I plug in to charge here?
So she wasn't looking for source material to write a novel? That was a lie, too?
We should beat that bitch up first, right?
(exhales deeply)
Maybe she knows more about Connect than we do?
FUN, EXCITING, LOSE WEIGHT DAILY LIFE PERSONAL DEFENSE
VIRTUAL TARGET PRACTICE PICKLEBALL, SPORT FOCUSED EXERCISE
(ominous music)
One, two, three, four.
This is where the culprit lives?
(Jinseop coughs)
(breathing heavily)
(groans)
(breathing deeply)
(foreboding music)
(groans)
(breathing heavily)
(panting)
(ominous music)
WILL DO. I WILL TURN THEM
INTO MINE. CLOSE YOUR EYES AND IMAGINE.
FALLEN ANGEL.
SEE ME.
AND SAY THAT I'M BEAUTIFUL.
WHY WAS I BORN INTO THIS WORLD? WHAT WAS I MEANT TO DO IN THIS WORLD?
HUBRIS, REASON ENOUGH TO BE ABANDONED.
(groans)
DONGSOO: He's sick with an illness?
Yeah, that's what they said.
That it wouldn't be surprising if he died any moment.
Then could that...
have a connection with the murders?
(inhales sharply) I heard your song.
It was nice.
Ah... (sniffs)
Oh, not the original, but Z's arranged version.
I guessed so, too.
(laughs) Just kidding.
(laughs, sniffles)
-What's wrong? -(groaning)
-You don't have to be so dramatic. -(groaning)
I said I was kidding.
(groaning)
I can see myself. (pants)
What?
Me? What? Why?
(foreboding music)
THIS TIME I WILL COME FIND YOU.
YOU CAN LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
DONGSOO (in shaky voice): That bastard...
That bastard is toying with me. That son of a bitch.
(foreboding music continues)
(Dongsoo grunts)
DONGSOO: He's even announcing the next murder.
(breathing shakily)
He knows you're connected.
(panting)
DONGSOO (ringtone playing): ♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city ♪
(cell phone vibrates)
Yeah.
Shut up, and don't do anything until I get there.
(sighs)
Jogging, my ass.
MONITORED BY SECURITY CAMERA
POLICE (on radio): There were too many...
-(indistinct chatter) -(lightly clears throat)
SINGER: Hey, it's been a while.
Hey.
Did you hear Z's cover? It was awesome.
Come here real quick. I was just about to play. Have a listen.
Ah, I'm actually in the middle of...
Come on, have a listen.
(guitar strums)
♪ High-hanging metal ♪
♪ Low-hanging leaf ♪
♪ When they bump ♪
♪ And rub against each other ♪
♪ The sound of the city ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, oh, whoa ♪
♪ Colorful junks ♪
♪ Hugging them and putting them together ♪
-♪ That is my sound ♪ -(groans)
(breathing heavily)
♪ Oh, oh, when it becomes quiet ♪
(breathes heavily)
(gasps)
(foreboding music)
(ominous music)
(tires screech)
Whoa, whoa.
Damn it.
(groans)
POLICE
DONGSOO: Let go, let go! Hey!
Ugh!
Hey!
(panting)
DONGSOO: Ugh, damn it...
(breathes heavily)
Let's go somewhere quiet.
(grunts)
(soft laughs)
Huh?
Oh, what's up?
Did something happen?
(groaning)
-Let's have a talk, shall we? -(surgeon groans)
I have a lot of questions about this eye.
STATEMENT RECORDING ROOM
(door closes)
(ominous music)
(closing theme music)