[chorus vocalizing]
♪ Andalasia ♪
♪ That happily-ever-after place ♪
♪ Always remember Andalasia ♪
♪ And a smile will always be
Upon your face ♪
[speaking French] Bonjour.
[Pip] Once upon a time
in a magical kingdom called Andalasia,
a baby was found in the forest.
With no mother or father to speak of,
the baby was raised by the animals,
who loved her as one of their own.
-[babbles]
-[Pip] And her name was Giselle.
Giselle grew into a beautiful young lady…
with a loving heart and a secret desire.
♪ I've been dreaming of
A true love's kiss ♪
♪ And a prince
I'm hoping comes with this ♪
Until one day, she won the love
of Andalasia's bravest prince!
But then, Giselle was pushed
through a portal by an Evil Queen
and landed in a strange
and extremely confusing kingdom called…
[chipmunk 1] ♪ New York City
New York City ♪
[clamoring]
[chipmunk 2] There she met Robert,
who was a lawyer with dreamy eyes
and a daughter named Morgan,
who saw magic everywhere she went.
So Giselle and Robert fell in love.
And they lived…
♪ Ever, ever after ♪
-Dad. Dad!
-[young chipmunks giggling]
-[both] Come on! Read it again, Dad.
-[chipmunk 1] Get over here!
What if I told you that "ever after"
wasn't the end of their story?
-[grunts]
-Oh!
We've heard this story a million times.
That's how it always ends.
Uh, uh, uh.
You only heard part of the story.
See, it turns out, New York wasn't
Giselle's happily-ever-after after all.
-Huh?
-What? Huh?
Well, I'm not too proud
of my part in this one,
but if you two will get into bed,
I'll read it to ya.
[both giggle]
This story begins
where the old one left off:
in the kingdom of New York
after "happily ever after."
After? But there is no after,
Yeah. You just get married
then nothing ever happens to you again.
Oh, not in this world.
Over there,
things would never stop happening.
For Giselle, a few years went by.
Morgan sprouted up, and eventually,
Robert and Giselle had a baby.
A beautiful girl named Sofia.
And for one moment,
Giselle truly had it all.
And that's when things began to change.
First, with all the baby stuff,
their castle in the sky shrunk two sizes.
Then, life got so busy,
it felt like a sleeping curse
fell over them every single night.
But the hardest part of all was Morgan.
She became what that world calls
a "teenager."
And it felt to Giselle
that she had set out to a faraway place
where she could never go.
With so much change,
Giselle started feeling
that life in the kingdom of New York
wasn't such a fairy tale after all.
And that's when she saw… a sign.
And, suddenly, she realized
their happily-ever-after
might be somewhere else.
So, Giselle and Robert began their quest
for a new happily-ever-after.
All right. Next stop: "Monroeville."
Where the hell's Monroeville?
-[shouts, grunts]
-[bird's wings flapping]
I don't know.
It's got to be better than here.
[Giselle] I know that change can be scary,
but it can also be exciting.
Think of all of the wonderful new people
you're going to meet
who will love you just as much as I do.
And remember,
whenever you need a friend, what do we do?
[vocalizes]
[vocalizing]
[birds coo]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[clears throat]
-Morgan, can you try and help out here?
-[typing]
I am helping. I'm literally telling
the entire Internet about my kidnapping.
Everyone agrees it's a tragedy.
You know, a lot of people move
to the suburbs from the city,
and they're wildly happy.
Yeah, well, I was wildly happy here.
Can you back me up on this, Sofia?
[babbles]
You are no help.
So, who's excited for our new adventure?
-Very excited.
-[gasps]
-Oh, that's… sarcasm.
-Sarcasm, yeah.
But, Morgan, I promise,
Monroeville is the perfect place.
Perfect for you, maybe.
Not so much for me.
-Morgan--
-Ah, ah, ah. No speeches.
If we're gonna do this, let's just go.
Teenagers are like this. She'll be fine.
I hope so. [sighs]
We really did have magic memories here,
didn't we?
We did. And we'll have more.
Trust me, if I learned anything
from meeting a princess on a billboard,
it's that sometimes
you just have to take a leap.
Hmm.
[chuckles] Let's start our new life.
[Pip] And so they packed up and moved…
♪ To a place where there ain't nothin'
To perturb ya ♪
♪ Or disturb ya ♪
♪ A new and magic kingdom ♪
♪ Called suburbia ♪
[Giselle] Isn't it wonderful?
[both] It's the closest thing to Andalasia
I've ever seen.
-[Giselle chuckles]
-[Morgan] Our house is like a castle.
I'll have my own room.
You've told me a million times.
[giggles]
-Hey, look.
-[bell tolls]
[Morgan] Mm-hmm.
[Giselle] Well, you never know, Morgan.
Maybe Monroeville will give you
a little magic like I had growing up.
Hmm.
[Robert] Here it is.
[Giselle] Oh, good. The walls are back up.
[Morgan] The walls were down?
-[contractors chattering]
-[hammering]
-Oh.
-Oh, boy.
Wow. Interesting castle.
We're running a little behind schedule,
so you just have to have vision.
[gardener] A new baby in town.
-[gasps] We would've brought gifts.
-Oh.
We're great with naps,
if you ever need help.
Oh, my. Thank you.
-I might take you up on that.
-Mmm.
-Oh, should we go check out our new home?
-Yeah.
It's all part of the adventure.
Bye. [laughs]
-[drill whirring]
-[hammering]
[contractors chattering]
-That goes in the living room. Thanks.
-[Morgan groans]
Yeah, that's not an adventure.
That's a landfill.
-A land filled with adventure.
-[groans]
Here, let me take my little princess
and show you the rest of the house.
-[fussing]
-Yes. It's okay. Off we go.
I am going to go see if one of those
movers will move me back to New York.
I know it's hard to start over
someplace new.
I did it once.
Not really on purpose,
but I found that you just have to
look at things the right way.
Oh, no.
Here, I'll show you.
Please, we really don't need to…
-♪ Here we are ♪
-…sing.
♪ A family starting over ♪
♪ Where life will be nicer and newer now ♪
-Oh.
-[contractor] Whoa! Watch yourself!
[chuckles]
♪ 'Neath the sparkling sun
In a fresh, clean sky ♪
♪ Our dreams will come true
Even truer now ♪
[gasps, chuckles]
♪ In a yard
That's full of four-leaf clover ♪
♪ We'll bloom
Where we've been transplanted ♪
♪ And life will be brimming
With even more ♪
♪ Joy in store
Than before ♪
♪ And even more enchanted ♪
Sorry.
♪ We're so blessed
To have our little castle ♪
♪ We'll sing
As we gaily unpack our trunks ♪
♪ We'll be best of friends ♪
♪ With the local deer, the fluffy raccoons
And the cuddly skunks ♪
-[both] Oh.
-[chitters]
Oh, my.
♪ Far away from all the noise and hassle ♪
♪ Our wishes will all be granted ♪
♪ And even the nastiest birds will tweet
Extra sweet ♪
♪ I repeat ♪
♪ We've left behind those city lights ♪
♪ For riding bikes and flying kites ♪
♪ Now we will be ♪
♪ Suburbanites ♪
♪ And even more ♪
♪ Enchanted ♪
-[sander whirs]
-[construction worker] I'm all right!
[whirring continues]
I think.
-[Giselle] Okay, keep them closed.
-[Robert] Don't open your eyes.
-Don't open your eyes.
-Keep your eyes closed.
Feels so scary right now.
Yep. They are closed.
Don't be scared.
Here you go. Right here. Ready?
-[gasps]
-[Morgan] Okay.
-Okay.
-Open them.
-Oh, wow.
-Mmm.
[Morgan] This is… wow.
Wow.
[Giselle] I know I got carried away,
and you can change anything.
I just wanted you to have a real room
when you got here.
[Robert] Yeah. She made them promise
that it would be done.
It's beautiful, Mom.
Really?
[chuckles]
Oh, pretty soon,
this whole place will feel like home.
You'll see. You'll see.
-[Robert] Uh, yeah.
-[Morgan] Yeah.
[chuckles]
-Good job, honey. Good job. Good job.
-Mmm.
[all gasp]
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-[Giselle gasps]
-Oh, my--
-Shut it off! [groans]
-That's my stuff! Oh, help!
-[Robert] Smother the flame!
-What--
-[Robert] Grab a blanket!
-[Morgan] Put it out.
-[Robert] Careful!
-Oh!
-[Morgan] I can't--
-[Robert coughs, sighs]
-Those were all of my clothes!
[neighbor 1] Hello, hello!
Do we know somebody?
No. But we can. [chuckles]
[neighbor 1] What are you? Color-blind?
That's not green. That's aqua.
-What are they? Fish?
-[neighbor 2 clears throat]
-[gasps] Oh.
-[neighbor 3] Oh.
Hope you don't mind. Door was open.
-Giselle and Robert, right? And Morgan.
-Oh. Yeah.
-Oh, and little Sofia.
-[murmuring]
-Why, yes. How did you know?
-Hi.
Malvina Monroe.
-[gasps] Oh.
-I would've sold you this house,
but I deal in slightly more
upscale homes, so…
Mm-hmm.
-Rosaleen and Ruby!
-[Ruby] Oh! [chuckles]
[Robert] Oh, they smell so good.
-Oh. [chuckles]
-[Robert chuckles] Oh! Wow.
-Giselle.
-It's really something.
She made it all herself.
Even the baskets. [chuckles]
-[Robert] Really?
-[gasps]
I weave.
Well, that's very nice of you.
And a little weird.
Morgan,
why don't we take these into the kitchen?
-[grunts] Thank you.
-[Giselle] Thank you.
-Nice to meet you.
-We'll just get right--
Bye now.
I have one that age too.
-So pouty.
-Oh. [chuckles]
But he's still the apple of my eye.
-Of everyone's eye.
-[chuckles]
More like the apple
of everybody's whole face. [chuckles]
Oh-- [laughs]
Now, if you all need anything,
I'm your gal, all right?
-Oh. Mm-hmm.
-I know this town better than anyone else.
So modest. She made this town what it is.
Oh, yeah. She's like a queen around here.
[chuckles]
Oh. Well, then I'm doubly honored.
I think that every town
should have a queen, so…
Yeah.
[Robert] Good night.
[sighs] Well, that wasn't exactly
the first day we'd hoped for, but…
[Sofia babbles]
Maybe we should've waited another month.
No, we pushed it three times.
Don't worry. We'll settle in.
-Listen to that.
-[crickets chirping]
-[Giselle gasps]
-That is so much better than 5th Avenue.
Mmm, no, that's just weirdly louder.
Those crickets composed that song
just for us to say,
-"Hello."
-[Robert chuckles]
As a thank-you,
we should build 'em a resort.
-I don't think they have one of those.
-[laughs]
Can we just talk about the fact that
we moved out here to get more space,
and now we're just
sleeping in the same room?
-I know.
-Morgan, we talked about this.
It's just until the smoke
clears your room.
[clears throat] Yeah.
-[Robert grunts, chuckles]
-[Giselle sighs]
♪ Here we are
A family starting over ♪
[Morgan] Mom.
Okay.
-[alarm beeping]
-[bell tolls in distance]
[Sofia crying]
[Giselle] Hmm?
-[Robert groaning]
-[Giselle yawning]
[tolling continues]
Why is your alarm going off?
It's still yesterday outside.
[groans] I'm a commuter now.
Oh, where's the fire?
[crying]
Oh, it's okay, baby.
It's okay, sweetheart.
-[birds chirping]
-[crying continues]
[gasps] Fire!
Oh.
Oh, no! Oh--
Oh, yes. It is a lovely morning, isn't it?
-Um… Oh!
-[Robert] Ow! We gotta move these boxes.
I'm so late.
I can't figure out this commuting thing.
Coffee, thank you so much.
I'm gonna get some cream for that.
-Oh, my God. What is that smell?
-[Giselle] Oh!
-Good morning. I made you some, um…
-[Robert grumbling]
-…toast.
-Toast?
Yeah.
Well, it's a miracle.
One of my shirts survived.
[both exclaim]
-Oh! I am so sorry! Are you okay?
-[Giselle] Oh, no!
-[Robert] Oh, my goodness!
-Oh, my God! The--
-I'm fine.
-Did you get burnt?
No, but this is my only outfit!
-[Robert] So sorry.
-[rumbling]
[Giselle]
Oh, the king and queen of Andalasia?
Nancy! Edward! What are you doing here?
Oh, well, we had to build a portal
to your new home.
-[Nancy] A girl!
-Hi.
-[Nancy] Oh, hi!
-Hey.
Hey, wow. Ah?
-♪ Robert! ♪
-[Robert chuckles]
-[Edward laughs]
-[grunts, chuckles]
Congratulations on the increasing size
of your progeny.
-Ah.
-Thank you. Thank you.
Uh… [stammers] …your dwelling.
Uh, are you poor now?
-Edward!
-No, we're not poor.
Oh, it's what they call a fixer-upper.
-Yeah, it's-- We're--
-Ah, I see, a fixer-upper!
Yes. Once your peasants have dug out
the moat and added a turret,
and a balcony from which you can sing,
bathed in the light of a forgiving moon…
-I see it now.
-[gasps]
-Okay. And on that note, I'm off.
-[Edward chuckles]
-Oh, no.
-Bye.
-Well, let me show you the house.
-Okay.
Robert! [chuckles]
Uh, it appears
you've forgotten your sword.
Oh, no. I don't have a sword.
Oh, I just assumed that,
now that you are a country squire,
-you'd have more need of a sword.
-No, still a lawyer.
Ah, tragic.
How desperate you must be
to truly do something.
-I do a lot.
-Yes, of course.
A brave front is required
to face a life as barren as this.
Perhaps this will help.
[Robert grunts]
-It's yours.
-Oh, no!
[laughs] No, I couldn't.
Oh, no! You must.
Robert, this sword and I have slayed
many a beast.
And seen magnificent adventures,
testing both body and spirit!
May it do the same for you.
Thank you.
[exhales]
I wish you well.
Hmm?
[drill whirs]
Ah! Thank you, peasant.
[Edward] Hmm.
We missed her birthday last month.
But we just had to make sure
that the goddaughter
of the king and queen of Andalasia
got one of these.
[gasps] An Andalasian wishing wand.
A what wand?
[Giselle] An Andalasian wishing wand.
I've heard about them,
but I've never seen one before.
When your godparents are
the king and queen…
-[Sofia giggles]
-[spits]
Oh. [chuckles]
…they have to do something extra special.
♪ Presenting your wand of wishes ♪
♪ The most magical of tools ♪
♪ Use it for joy and happiness ♪
♪ Just be sure you know the rules ♪
Does anyone in Andalasia
ever just say stuff?
Not if we can help it.
♪ Here's the magic of Andalasia ♪
♪ Contained in
This wondrous wishing wand ♪
♪ We bring some magic from Andalasia ♪
♪ To this drab and most un-magic world
Beyond ♪
♪ This wishing wand ♪
♪ She will be so enthused ♪
♪ By what fun she can have ♪
♪ With this gift we brought her ♪
♪ But just remember
It can only be used by ♪
♪ A true Andalasian son ♪
♪ Or daughter ♪
♪ She's our true Andalasian goddaughter ♪
-♪ With this magic ♪
-♪ From Andalasia ♪
♪ When she longs for something
Heart and soul ♪
♪ She'll use the magic of Andalasia ♪
♪ And if she has questions
Just consult this scroll ♪
The scroll? Oh.
You just ask the scroll any questions,
and the answers appear.
Or I suppose, in this land,
you just read it?
[chuckles] How do you live in this place?
-Oh. How about that?
-[babbles]
You're a true daughter of Andalasia.
Hmm?
Okay, well, uh, if you don't have a wand
for a fake daughter of Andalasia,
-I'm gonna go change.
-[gasps] Oh--
And yes, I will look in your closet.
I'm sure there are lots
of fun options in there
for making a real splash at my new school.
Yes.
She sometimes says one thing
and means the opposite. [chuckles]
-Huh?
-I can never tell.
-It's-- Yeah.
-[babbles]
[Nancy]
Yeah, well, that's teenagers for you.
Are you okay?
-Oh, yes. It's fine.
-[Edward] Hmm…
I just--
[Edward] Hmm?
Is it sometimes easier
to live in Andalasia?
-[whirring]
-[grunts]
Oh. [chuckles]
Well, I wouldn't say easier.
-We have dragons and ogre rebellions.
-[Sofia whimpers]
See, in Andalasia the hardest part of life
is finding your happily-ever-after.
-Everything else seems easy.
-Mm-hmm.
This world is-- feels very different.
[chuckles]
Yeah. It's true.
Happily ever after is more
of a concept here than it is a thing.
Really? How horribly bleak.
[grunts, gasps]
Well, I say, that if this world is not
to your liking, then you must change it.
Well, honey, it's not always that easy.
Hogwashery!
If anyone can make something out of this,
why, it's our Giselle.
[Sofia babbles, giggles]
[sighs]
Made it.
Is that a sword?
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
Hmm.
Little tip: You should tell 'em,
"no bag, double wrapped."
And maybe leave the sword
at home next time.
-[inhales sharply]
-Don't listen to him.
You gotta do you.
After all,
you're riding this train over and over.
And over and over.
And over and over. And over and over.
And then you die.
It's just reality, man.
[conductor on PA]
Metro North to Grand Central Station.
Next stop, Poughkeepsie.
[student] Oh, I gotta go in!
Save me a seat!
I feel like a human get-well bouquet.
[chuckles] Don't be silly.
You look beautiful.
The flowers on your skirt bring out
the rest of the flowers on your skirt.
-Oh, great.
-[gasps]
[chattering]
-Oh, my.
-[Rosaleen] Very nice!
This is a big improvement from last year.
She really is involved.
-Congrats, you made it! [chuckles]
-Thank you.
Wow. You really do have a talent
for baked goods.
-It's just a little fundraiser.
-For, um, Monroe-fest? What's that?
It's the biggest event of the year.
Malvina organizes the whole thing.
-It's spectacular.
-Mmm?
There's also games and a little fun vote
for prince and princess.
[Rosaleen] Her son Tyson's won prince
three years in a row.
Even when he broke both his legs,
he still won.
-It's not rigged. I promise.
-Mm-mmm.
I think it sounds wonderful.
I love festivals. We have them
all the time where I come from.
-Mmm.
-Ah!
They were usually interrupted
by evil forces of some kind,
but when they weren't,
it really brought people together.
-Aha.
-I would love to help if you need it.
You actually should take her up on that.
This one time she made a forest
entirely out of M&M's
and had it delivered
to my class by pigeon.
-[Giselle] That's right.
-[Morgan laughs] Yeah.
No one beats her at this kind of stuff.
-Huh? Is that so?
-[chuckles]
[school bell rings]
Well, here we go.
Morgan? You're gonna be great.
Thank you.
-Hmm. [giggles]
-Tee-hee-hee.
♪ Just believe in yourself! ♪
-[student] What? Wait. What was that?
-[students giggling]
You know, Giselle, if you have time,
I'd love to buy you a coffee
-and hear more about your M&M masterpiece…
-Oh. [chuckles]
…and whatever else there is
to know about our newest Monrovians.
That would be so nice. Thank you.
[student 1] Hey.
-Excuse you!
-I'm living the full cliché here.
They must have an urgent selfie to post.
Hmm.
Hey, you're the new girl from New York.
Uh, Morgan.
And you're Tyson from cupcakes.
Ah, you met my mother.
[sucks teeth] Yeah,
I just try to ignore whatever she's doing.
She gets kind of intense.
Yeah, well, imagine if she was made
of magic and sang at the drive-through.
Huh.
-Yeah.
-[school bell rings]
Tyson! Come on!
-[friend 1] Dipset, bro.
-[friend 2] Let's go, man!
[chuckles]
-[student 2] Ew. Look what she's wearing.
-Whoa.
-Whoa. That's a lot of flowers.
-[student 3] Like, a lot.
[barista]
Extra large cappuccino with five shots.
-There it is.
-[barista] Hmm.
-Now, let me see…
-Hmm?
-Herbal tea…
-Oh.
Chamomile-- No!
Hibiscus.
You're right. He's right.
Oh, Edgar knows everything.
He's my eyes and ears.
[mouthing words] Thank you.
-[Ruby sighs] Oh?
-Wow, you guys move really quickly.
-We go wherever she needs us to be.
-Mm-hmm.
As you can see, Giselle,
our town is really just one big family.
And like a family,
everyone has their place in it.
You know?
And once you've found where you fit,
Monroeville can be whatever you wish.
[chuckles]
You know, I think you're right.
[crickets chirping]
Oh, I'm so glad you like it.
Do you think we should add music?
-Oh.
-[door opens, slams]
[gasps] Oh.
Hi, Morgan. How did it go?
It was fine.
[Morgan sighs]
Does this mean it didn't go well?
Well, no one talked to me all day,
so I got a lot of me-time. That was nice.
Oh.
Yes, that was sarcasm. My day sucked.
Well, this isn't anything
a little glitter couldn't fix.
It's old anyway. What's the point?
The point is, is that it's a memory tree,
and as we say in Andalasia--
"Memories are the most powerful magic
of all." I know.
I'm not really sure
it works the same way here.
-Morgan.
-[sighs]
I know you didn't want to come here.
But if you give it a chance,
it will get better.
What if it doesn't?
I should go back to school in New York.
I can take the train with Dad.
-It'll be fine.
-It's only been a day.
We just have to figure out
where you fit in.
We won't do anything, okay?
If I'm gonna do this,
then I have to do it myself, all right?
Okay.
I'm not a little girl anymore.
-I got this.
-Mm-hmm.
[exhales]
[gasps]
[giggles]
[bell tolls]
[grunts]
-[bell tolls]
-Hmm?
"Meet you at school.
I have a wonderful idea."
This cannot be good.
-[chattering]
-[Giselle] And there you go. There you go.
Vote for Morgan. She is new here.
And she makes a great friend.
-[student] Who is Morgan?
-[Giselle] I'm glad you like them.
There you go. Vote for Morgan. [giggles]
What are you doing?
Oh, well, I was just thinking,
in Andalasia,
we have festivals all the time,
and everybody knows
the prince and the princess.
And now everyone will know you.
Yes, but I told you
that I could figure this out on my own.
[gasps]
Why won't you let me do that? [huffs]
-Morgan. Morgan.
-[Rosaleen] Oh.
I'm sorry, Giselle, but you can't have
a table on school property
unless you're an official member
of a committee.
Oh, well, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Well, now you do.
-Ladies.
-Gladly.
Excuse me.
-Oh, these cupcakes look incredible!
-[pants]
-Oh.
-[Malvina] Take it all down. All of it.
[ticking]
[Robert] She's never been this late
without calling.
I think she's turned off her phone.
-[sighs] That's it. She's grounded.
-[typing on cell phone]
Do you remember when we made this?
She used to beg me for stories
from Andalasia every night,
and her favorite ones were always
about the Magical Memory Tree.
She used to love those.
I don't know what happened.
Oh, nothing happened.
Teenagers do this all the time.
That's all it is.
It's more than that.
I never sing the right song anymore,
and even when I make cupcakes,
everything goes wrong.
I used to be good at things.
[sighs] Things will get better.
Just give it a second.
[both chuckle]
Robert, are you happy here?
[stammers]
We just got here.
[sighs] Hmm.
When is the last time
that you were truly happy?
Uh, well…
It's not that I'm unhappy.
It just-- Sometimes I wonder if--
if time's just slipping away,
and I'll be riding a train over and over
and over again for the rest of my life.
[door closes]
-Oh, Morgan.
-What-- Where have you been?
-I went to New York.
-By yourself?
I've been riding the subway alone
since I was 13. Let's calm down, please.
Don't tell me to calm down.
-What were you thinking?
-I don't know, Dad.
I was thinking, though, maybe
you should have left me where I belong.
You belong here.
No, I don't!
Look, I know that you want to live in some
perfect fairy-tale land, but we don't.
-Okay? We live here…
-If you want to be mad, you be mad at me.
-…in this stupid town, and I hate it!
-But do not talk to your mother like that!
My mother?
Mm-hmm.
She is not my mother.
She's my stepmother.
-That's all she'll ever be.
-[footsteps depart]
Stepmother?
[Robert] She didn't mean that.
I think maybe she did.
[door slams]
I can't change that.
Giselle?
♪ Once upon a time ♪
♪ Back there in Andalasia ♪
♪ Rules were clear
And colors didn't fade ♪
♪ And once you found
Your happily-ever-after ♪
♪ Your happily-ever-after always stayed ♪
♪ And then I journeyed here ♪
♪ Where true love's kiss was waiting ♪
♪ Met my prince
Became his princess wife ♪
♪ But was my ever-after just temporary? ♪
♪ How I miss that fairy-tale life ♪
♪ Where you wake each day ♪
♪ And nothing's changed ♪
♪ And your daughter doesn't feel ♪
♪ Estranged ♪
♪ I thought I'd found a place ♪
♪ Where I could make things better ♪
♪ But all I did was change
Where I would fail ♪
♪ Oh, what do I do
If I don't belong ♪
♪ Where life can never be a fairy tale? ♪
♪ Where life can never be a fairy… ♪
[bubbling]
Oh, Pip! My old friend.
[gasps]
Oh!
-[in squeaky voice] Hi, Giselle.
-[chuckles]
Giselle, you look so sad.
I know.
I just wish--
Uh-huh? [chattering]
You wish what?
[sighs]
The Wand of Wishes.
You have a wand of wishes here?
[chattering]
[giggles]
[gasps]
-[Pip] Wow.
-[gasps]
That's the answer.
-I hope you know what you're doing.
-[chuckles]
[chuckles]
[whimpers]
♪ And so I make this wish ♪
♪ Where life is so confusing ♪
♪ And pain can cut you
Sharper than a knife ♪
♪ I wish that we all
Would live someplace where ♪
♪ Songs of the flowers
Ring in the air ♪
♪ And ogres and dragons
Are all that is scary ♪
♪ Give us all a fairy-tale life ♪
♪ I wish we had a fairy-tale ♪
♪ Life ♪
[chuckles]
I guess it didn't work.
Oh, well. Uh, that may be a good thing.
[sighs] Oh, well.
Oh, well.
I suppose tomorrow is another day.
Hmm. Uh-huh.
-Why don't you sleep over?
-[chitters]
We have some very comfortable twigs.
-[Pip] Oh, okay. [chatters]
-[Giselle] Yes. [chuckles]
I'm so glad you're here.
[Pip chattering]
[bluebird 1] Good morning. Good morning.
-[bluebird 2] Good morning, Giselle.
-[grunts]
[grunts]
[sighs]
Oh, it's not a very good morning at all,
I'm afraid.
[both] Well, then you just have to make it
a good morning.
You know,
you're absolutely right, friends.
-[wings flapping]
-I'll just-- [gasps]
Huh.
[Sofia giggles]
[chuckles] Oh.
You're extra giggly this morning.
[clattering]
[gasps]
♪ Get the table set ♪
♪ Your coffee's percolating ♪
♪ Can't talk now
I've got some eggs to fry ♪
Oh, my. [gasps]
♪ Whisk that omelet ♪
♪ I've got your smoothie waiting ♪
♪ Would you like your toast
Whole-grain or rye? ♪
[chuckles]
[vocalizing]
Morgan?
♪ This day is new now ♪
♪ There's work to do now ♪
♪ Scrubbing and sweeping ♪
♪ All the pleasures of housekeeping ♪
♪ Cellar to attic ♪
♪ I'm just ecstatic ♪
♪ Doing my daily chores
Let's sweep those floors ♪
Giselle! You're even more beautiful
than you were yesterday.
Oh?
♪ It's another day ♪
♪ Another quest ♪
♪ One more chance
To put my mettle to the test ♪
♪ What a sunny day
And what a yummy breakfast ♪
♪ You'll stay empty, Mr. Garbage Pail ♪
Oh, well.
♪ We'll big-bad-wolf it down ♪
♪ Then it's all hands on deck
Fast ♪
-♪ Rooms to dust ♪
-♪ And searching for the grail ♪
♪ Our life is almost like a fairy tale ♪
[Robert] Well, I'm off.
It's time for a new adventure.
A chance to prove my worth
and heroic fortitude
only to return home to you, my family,
glowing with a day's worth
of fully realized purpose.
Um…
-Be careful.
-[Sofia giggles]
And I am off too, but not without
my little helper. [chuckles]
Chores are an adventure all on their own.
That's what I always say.
[Sofia giggles]
[gasps]
[groans, in normal voice]
Those twigs were murder on my sciatica.
[spine cracks]
[laughs]
Hey, I'm talking.
Wait, how am I talking?
Pip, the wish I made last night,
it came true.
-What do you mean?
-We have a fairy-tale life.
Jumpin' jelly sticks! We got magicked?
[fairies giggling]
What to do?
Oh. [chuckles]
Well, will you look at that?
[chuckles]
♪ Look all around us ♪
♪ Life now will be
So full of song, love and laughter ♪
♪ And you can bet
We'll finally get ♪
♪ Our happily-ever-after ♪
-[villager 1] Good morning.
-[chuckles] Good morning! Good morning!
[villagers whooping, laughing]
♪ All over town here ♪
♪ Fun's raining down here ♪
♪ In Monrolasia
Life is just one big fantasia ♪
♪ Ladies are dancing ♪
♪ Hear every man sing ♪
♪ So, if you're lacking zest ♪
♪ Come be our guest
Be our guest ♪
♪ And you won't ever be depressed ♪
[villagers whooping]
[laughing, whooping]
[vocalizing]
♪ Every day is full
Of wonderment and whimsy ♪
♪ All that's magical and marvelous ♪
[vocalizes]
♪ When you have a life
That's truly Brothers Grimms-y ♪
♪ There's no sweeter way to live
And thus ♪
[vocalizes]
♪ It's this very merry ♪
♪ Extraordinary ♪
♪ Fairy-tale life ♪
♪ For us ♪
[vocalizes]
[fanfare playing]
[horse nickers]
[chattering]
[villager chuckles]
It's the queen.
Monrolasia has a queen?
-[gasps]
-A queen?
[villagers gasping]
-[gasping continues]
-[villager 2] Yes.
[villagers] Aah.
And she's a magic queen. [chuckles]
Those are always fun.
Eh, I ain't sure how fun she looks.
Giselle, how lovely to see you.
Out doing some last-minute shopping
for tonight, are we?
What's tonight?
-[gasps]
-[villagers gasp]
Your Majesty.
For the festival, milady.
Oh, the festival. Is that still happening?
Why wouldn't it?
No power on Earth could stop it.
It's my… little gift to my people.
-[villagers] Oh.
-[chuckles]
Of course, Your Majesty.
[Sofia babbles]
That's an interesting trinket.
[gasps] Oh, um…
[bell tolls]
[gasps]
-[bell tolls]
-[gasps]
Mmm.
Why don't you just focus
on your little party?
After all, baked goods
are what you do best, Your Majesty.
-[gasps, groans]
-[bell tolls]
That's wicked.
The wickedest.
Leaping lollipops, what was that?
[wind howls]
[bell tolls]
You know… [chuckles]
…I was just realizing that
this is her very first festival
in Monrolasia,
and we'll need to get you a new dress,
and… [gasps]
-…well, we better get right on that.
-Huh?
See you tonight, Your Majesty.
[grunts, groans]
[screams]
[splash]
Something is going on with her.
And I wanna know what.
-[villagers gasp]
-Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Everyone, out.
[villager] Out. Out.
[chattering]
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the… most powerful of them all?
Mirror?
[Mirror] Nope.
Mirror!
Wha-- Did you not hear the question?
I did, Your Majesty.
I just don't want to end up shattered
on the floor, if I can help it.
Just tell me who it is.
-[Ruby gasps]
-[Rosaleen gasps] But it's always you.
Oh, well, he must not understand.
We said most powerful, not the prettiest.
I mean, this guy, huh?
Apologies, Your Majesty.
I just-- I don't know what's happening.
I do.
It's that wand she's been so coy about.
It's dripping with magic.
Even a fool could see it.
-You two, get it for me!
-[Rosaleen] Hmm.
[gasps] But-- Wait--
You mean-- You mean steal it?
Uh, yes, Your Majesty.
But-- Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Oh, Giselle. What have you done?
Dresses certainly are different
than when I was almost a princess.
How do I look?
[gasps]
-Oh, Morgan. You look wonderful.
-[Morgan laughs]
What do you think?
-It's beautiful.
-Then we'll take it.
-[chuckles]
-You really don't have to do that.
I'm sure it's very expensive.
Of course, I do.
I've always dreamed
of sharing a night like this with you,
-and it's going to be perfect.
-[chuckles]
Now we just need shoes.
[both laugh]
[laughs]
[horse whinnies]
Hmm.
So, Miss Giselle,
we must find a dress for you too.
Oh, no. Thank you. I'm fine.
Nonsense!
These are one of a kind:
hand dipped in actual fairy dust.
You will twinkle like a star.
Oh, that is a very aggressive twinkle,
but I really don't need--
[bell tolls]
Hmm.
[babbles]
[salesperson] Miss Giselle?
Miss Giselle, is everything okay?
You know, I was just thinking.
I really do have a figure for fashion.
The finest hourglass
would shatter with envy.
Oh. [chuckles]
Let's try them all.
[both laugh]
[both panting]
Ooh. Oh.
[Sofia giggles]
[gags] What is that smell?
Oh, hey, it's me. You know why?
I fell into a gutter!
[gasps] Oh!
Geez, you buy the whole town?
Well… [scoffs] …it's not all for me.
Hmm. Is that so?
Picture our Morgan, the belle of the ball…
in this!
Huh?
[Morgan] Oh.
Well…
Well?
Ooh. Okay. [muttering]
-[babbles]
-[Rosaleen whispers] Over to the right.
[mutters, grunts]
-[Sofia giggles]
-[groans]
It looks… different in this light.
It's definitely air-conditioned!
Oh! [pants]
What happened? It's torn to shreds.
Why, it's hardly fit for a maid.
Not exactly how I would've put it.
[scoffs]
What? It was a little judgy.
-[Morgan] Well, perhaps I can mend it.
-[Giselle] No. No mending.
I got it. [grunts]
[Giselle] I'll just march right down there
and demand an explanation.
-[squeals]
-Okay, well, I'm off to market,
and then I'll have plenty of time
to get ready for the festival.
-[Morgan chuckles]
-Mm-hmm.
-Oh!
-Hmm?
Thank you for everything, Stepmother.
Stepmother?
[gasps]
Oh, no.
What?
[gasps]
-What?
-Oh! [gasps]
My hair, it's so high,
and my dress is so low.
And of course,
I want that dress to be made of rags.
People like me always do.
People like who?
What are you talking about?
Oh, no, Pip.
I'm afraid that my wish
is turning me into a-- [gasps]
A what?
It's turning me into a… [gasps]
[breathes shakily]
A wicked stepmother. [gasps]
What? Come on!
[gasps]
Oh, actually. Yeah. No.
No, no, I can totally see it.
Oh, no. [gasps] Oh, Pip!
[Pip] Uh, hey, slow down!
Where are we going?
[gasps]
Who lives in this rat hole?
Morgan does.
Stepdaughters always live
in attics or dungeons.
Oh, Pip, do you know what this means?
I am the villain of Monrolasia!
Well, you're not the only villain.
Well, that's silly.
There can only ever be one villain.
Not counting minions or pets.
Or villains that you don't know
are villains until it's too late.
[Pip] Well, Monrolasia might be different.
'Cause there's you,
and then there's that evil queen you made.
Who, Malvina? She's not evil. She's--
Uh, did you see that outfit?
With the big gestures and the crazy eyes!
Oh, no.
So, you better unwish that wish quick
before she, uh--
-[stomach rumbling]
-[groans]
-[Pip burps]
-Pip?
[grunts, groans] I don't feel so--
-[stomach rumbling]
-[burps]
What's wrong?
[grunts, burps]
[groans, screams]
[grunts]
-Oh! Oh.
-[Pip groaning, meowing]
[hisses]
[groans, hisses]
[screams]
-[grunting, groaning]
-[Giselle] Oh, Pip.
Wicked stepmothers don't have
cute chipmunks as friends. They have--
Cats! [meows] And evil ones! [yowls]
Oh, I can't be an evil cat.
They eat chipmunks!
Oh, I'm gonna be sick!
[retching]
[Pip retches]
Surely there's an adventure
out here somewhere.
[villager screams]
A bellow of distress.
[grunts]
Finally! [chuckles]
[villager 1] What are we to do?
[villager 2] I'm not going in there.
You go in.
[villager 3]
Well, I'm certainly not going in there.
Are you a dragon slayer?
I believe I am.
-[villagers scream]
-Ooh.
Never fear. I shall slay the beast.
I wouldn't if I were you.
It is very large.
-Oh.
-And cranky.
Hmm. A very large and cranky dragon is
just what I've been looking for.
Won't be a moment.
-Onward, my sweetness.
-[villagers chattering]
[dragon snarling]
[sword swishing]
-[screams]
-[dragon snarls]
-[grunts]
-[villagers gasp]
Have you done this before?
[chuckles]
Have-- Of course, yes, I have--
I have slain many a dragon.
[dragon snarls]
-[villager 4] Good on you.
-[villager 5] Oh!
[dragon snarling]
[villagers scream]
[screams]
-[all gasp]
-[groans] Ow. Oh, oh.
-[dragon laughing]
-Hot. That's hot.
I shall persevere.
I shall conquer the craven beast!
-[stone rumbles]
-I shall--
[villager 6] Hey!
No offense, sir, but you might want
to find another profession.
[villager chuckles]
[gasps]
Uh, what are you doing?
Nancy said if we had any problems,
all we had to do was ask.
Welcome to your magical
wishing wand experience!
-If you should ever have a question…
-Oh.
…just ask, and I shall appear.
-[laughs] Hello!
-Hey, we got no time for this.
[screams] Good kitty. Good kitty.
I'm sorry. My friend's a little anxious
because we need to undo a wish
as soon as possible.
Oh. Didn't like what you got, huh?
Well, I wished for a fairy-tale life,
and it made my town
a place like Andalasia.
And now I'm slowly turning
into a wicked stepmother.
And I'm her soon-to-be-evil cat.
-[groans]
-Oh! [laughs]
Oh, you changed the world.
What? You changed the world!
Do you know how much magic
it takes to make that happen?
-[meows]
-Whoo!
Where do you think
all that magic comes from, hmm?
Andalasia, that's where.
This is world-ending stuff.
This is definitely a wish to be unwished.
Good luck.
-[gasps]
-Uh-oh!
What we need to know
is how to unwish the wish!
Welcome to the magical--
Whoa, it's you. Okay. [laughs]
See, we always build in a certain amount
of time to reverse the wish.
You know, in case you change your mind.
Thank goodness you are not
all villain yet.
-Good.
-[stammers] Watch the tassels, please.
So, how far along are we? Let's see.
Stepmothers. Well, they're wicked.
Wicked good. [gasps] Mmm.
Check on that one. [laughs]
The other three are, well, vain…
I'm not vain.
I just look good in everything. [gasps]
There it is. Okay.
-Uh-oh.
-Cruel and ambitious.
[laughs] Yes, I would say your clock
has not run out yet.
-[Giselle] Good.
-What kinda clock do you mean?
-It could be anything.
-[Giselle sighs]
Have you seen
a flower dropping petals? Huh?
-No?
-Mm-mmm.
How about a clock
counting down to midnight
-with an ominous-sounding chime?
-[gasps]
I mean, it's pretty on the nose,
but it's a classic!
You know, that's not a litter box.
That's where I live.
-[meows]
-Not to worry, though.
-As long as you unwish it before midnight…
-[gasps]
…you'll be fine.
What happens at midnight?
On the last stroke of 12:00,
the spell is set,
and nothing will be as it was before.
It means your wish is permanent.
For all time, 'ime, 'ime, 'ime!
[chuckles] I did that for effect.
Permanent.
To unwish your wish, all you have to do
is use the wand, labeled "wand."
-[Pip] Where is it?
-Yes, yes, yes. It's right--
Uh… [gasps]
-It's gone.
-[bell tolls]
[gasps] Oh, no.
[laughs] Well, good luck with all of this.
You need it.
[Giselle] Oh. [sighs]
-Hurry! It's already--
-Two o'clock.
-[bell tolls]
-That means it's cruelty.
[chuckles] No, no, no, no.
We can't let this happen.
We have to fight it.
I'm not an evil cat. I'm not an evil cat.
I'm not an evil cat.
You stay here.
I have to find a way to stop this.
[groans] And I have to lick this,
for some reason.
Hmm.
Ugh. Aw, yeah, that's real bad. [groans]
It's all going to be okay.
We just need some magic.
As we say in Andalasia,
"Magic fixes everything."
Or breaks it?
But then you find more magic
to undo the magic,
-and then everything's fine again.
-Good day, madam.
[gasps] Oh. Well, at least we look fine.
[gasps] That is not important right now.
Speak for yourself.
But Robert will certainly appreciate it.
If he isn't slain by something. [giggles]
[gasps] Oh, no! She's right.
I mean, I'm right.
He thinks he's a prince. With a sword.
Who knows what he'll find out there?
Or Morgan.
Although, nothing ever happens
to young girls in Andalasia.
They just sing and pick flowers
and sometimes get trapped in a tower
or a dungeon or get kidnapped by trolls.
Or witches. Oh, my!
[chattering]
[villager 1] Oh, that's nice.
[villager 1 chuckling]
-Thank you.
-Oh.
-That's… quite a frock.
-[all laugh]
-[villager 2] What is she wearing?
Good morning, Morgan.
You ready for the big festival tonight?
Of course. Uh, my stepmother
even bought me a new dress.
She's never done that before.
-[chuckles] Everything's perfect.
-[chuckles]
♪ There's a festival in our future ♪
♪ We're all giddy with anticipation ♪
♪ I'll be hanging flowers
On scented bowers ♪
♪ To enhance the festivation ♪
♪ There'll be merriment in the courtyard ♪
♪ And waltzing even in the hallways ♪
♪ Won't it just be perfect? ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Don't you think
It will be just perfect? ♪
♪ Of course ♪
♪ Isn't it always? ♪
♪ It's another
Perfect Monrolasia morning ♪
♪ Shiny children play
Beneath a shiny sky ♪
♪ Every bird in every tree
Singing extra prettily ♪
♪ It's all perfect
So why aren't I? ♪
♪ I know my role
And every day, I play it ♪
♪ Who I really am
I never let them see ♪
♪ But I'm feeling, deep inside ♪
♪ Where the weird parts of me hide ♪
♪ Maybe perfect isn't perfect
For me ♪
♪ In me
There's hunger for adventure ♪
There's a longing for romance ♪
♪ And secretly I crave
A day that I could save ♪
♪ I could do it
If I ever get the chance ♪
♪ And on this
Perfect Monrolasia morning ♪
♪ There's a little thrill
Of possibility ♪
♪ 'Cause I've got a feeling
That maybe today ♪
♪ Just around that corner
Or out by the bay ♪
♪ Some kind of change
Could be coming my way ♪
♪ Something wild and imperfect ♪
♪ But perfectly right ♪
♪ For me ♪
[groans, inhales sharply]
-[murmurs]
-[chuckles]
♪ No, I never wanted
To be perfect ♪
♪ Just the chance to do and be ♪
♪ What's right for me ♪
[chuckles]
[goats bleat]
[villagers chattering]
-[clears throat]
-[squirts]
This fruit is very squishy today.
Well, I would be careful then.
The squishy dragon fruit
can be a little bit…
[snarling]
…grumpy.
[grunts]
[vendor] Sugar dates, figs and pistachios!
Can I help you, love?
Oh, yes. Do you have anything
that can reverse magic
that you didn't intend to use,
perhaps a poultice?
Or an unguent? Those can be very powerful.
No unguents, no.
[groans]
This one makes your eyelashes curly.
Um…
Oh. [gasps] Curly eyelashes? Why not?
No! We don't have any time for vanity,
we need to pull ourselves together.
Um…
[Tyson] So, I assume
you'll be attending the ball this evening?
Yes, I am. [chuckles] I'm very excited.
-I've never been to a ball before.
-Oh, no. No, no, no.
Stepmothers never handle this well.
[Tyson] My mother loves these parties.
I feel like I've been to a thousand.
That must be wonderful.
Sure. Sometimes.
Just not what I would choose if I could.
I understand that.
Well, um, since this is your first ball,
maybe I could show you around?
Make sure you have the perfect partner
to dance with?
Uh… [laughs]
Are there imperfect partners? [chuckles]
Oh, yes. Stick with me.
Your toes will be very happy you did.
[chuckles] Well, then on their behalf,
I thank you.
And I accept.
Then I am honored.
[chuckles]
Hmm.
[Rosaleen] I'll give it to her!
She likes me when I give her things.
-[Ruby] But I'm the one who got it!
-I'm the one that pulled you out.
Any wand of Giselle's
can't possibly be that powerful.
But, I suppose I should see
what I can do with it.
-Oh. [chuckles]
-Mm-hmm.
Let's see. I wish…
-Mm-hmm?
-[gasps]
-…Ruby…
-Oh.
[giggles]
…was a toad.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
[all scream]
[gasps]
[groans]
Oh, I'm a talking toad. I knew, I--
-[grunts]
-Oh! Oh.
-[gasps] Phew.
-Stupid chair!
[huffs]
Mirror! What kind of magic is this?
[chuckles]
Ask any question and I shall appear.
Well, that's an easy one.
It's Andalasian magic,
which means only a true son
or daughter of Andalasia can, um…
[chuckles] …use it.
-Aah.
-Mmm. [chuckles]
Hello. Who are you?
Grab him.
-[Ruby squeals] Gotcha!
-[Scroll groans]
Oh! Stop! Stop!
-He's a slippery little devil.
-[laughs]
-I'm ticklish over there. My tassels!
-Oh, so cute!
Careful of the fine print.
I'm sorry.
Did you say, "Ask any question"?
[chuckles] Oh, no. Away. Poof! Away.
Come-- Poof!
No, no, you're not going anywhere.
I've got quite a number of questions.
-Lots and lots and lots of questions.
-Mm-hmm.
So you're going to start
from the beginning…
[Scroll] Don't ask me.
…or I might have to do a little editing.
[scissors snip]
[humming]
That's quite the bouquet.
[chuckles]
They're gonna match my dress perfectly,
and they were growing wild
just by the market.
Aren't they beautiful?
The world is truly a miracle.
Oh, the most wonderful thing happened.
Tyson asked me to the festival.
Hmm. Thrilling.
But I'm afraid you won't be attending
the festival tonight after all.
You have far too many chores to do.
But I've done all my chores.
What about the carpets in the hall?
Awfully dusty.
And the windows? I can't see a thing.
And then there's the gardening
and the sewing and the mending.
And don't forget about the chimneys.
Filthy business.
Yes, perhaps there are a few
that I've missed.
-Oh, but surely they can wait--
-Are you speaking back to me?
No, of course not.
I would never do such a thing.
Perhaps you need
to remember your place here.
Until you do, you are not to leave
this room, except for chores.
And then only when I say.
But I promised Tyson
that I would be there.
Oh, come now, Morgan.
A boy like Tyson has plenty of options
and, frankly, better ones.
But not to worry.
You can enjoy your evening
from up here in your little perch.
I'm sure it will be just as magical.
[gasps]
That is sarcasm, isn't it?
Huh.
Not so hard to understand after all.
-Stepmother.
-Hmm?
Stepmother, please.
You can't-- You can't be this cruel.
Oh, I can't help it, dear.
It's just who I am.
No. No! [gasps]
No, you have to let me out!
You can't be this cruel.
-Please! Please, you can't do this.
-[pounding]
Stepmother!
[vendor] Apples! Juicy apples!
-[rumbling]
-Ooh.
[rumbling]
Giant!
A giant is coming?
A giant, it's coming!
-[Robert cheers]
-[villagers clamoring, screaming]
Best take cover.
-[grunts, laughs]
-[rumbling continues]
[grunting]
-[clamoring continues]
-[grunts]
Ah!
Rope! Ha! Yes!
What are you doing?
I'm gonna take this rope
and trip the giant.
And then he or she will be mine!
[giant growls]
[screams]
[grunts]
[villager screams]
[groans, grunts]
Oh, no!
[grunting]
Oh! [chuckles]
Oh, hey. It's all right.
No! [screaming]
-[groaning]
-Help me! I'm stuck!
-Oh!
-Help!
-Oh, no.
-Please! Help!
-I'm coming!
-[child screaming]
[screams]
[pants] It's okay. It's okay.
It's all done now.
The big bad giant is gone. [sighs]
Bella!
-Mommy!
-Oh.
Mom.
I'm sorry! [pants]
I turned away for one second!
-We are in your debt, sir.
-A true hero.
Oh, I wouldn't say that.
Thanks to you, our family is safe.
I'm forever grateful.
Hmm.
[sighs]
[dragon fruit snarls]
Oh.
[exhales]
Uh…
[whispers] Okay.
[grunts]
Going somewhere?
[gasps]
[stammers] No, it's--
It's not what you think.
-I--
-[Giselle] Hmm.
I just have to tell him
why I won't be there.
Stepmother, please.
I'll be home in no time at all.
Oh, you're right. You will be.
Because you're not going anywhere.
[gasps] Please! Please don't do this!
-Please--
-[gasps]
-[lightly] Morgan?
-Stepmother?
[in deep voice] Morgan.
Are you okay?
Never better!
Now we're going back up to your tower.
[bell tolls]
Oh, no. It can't be. Not yet.
What are you talking about?
Ambition. [gasps]
It's the last one, and then I'm fully her.
What is going on?
[bell tolls]
-Oh, Morgan. I'm so sorry.
-What is--
It's all my fault. [gasps]
I wished for a fairy-tale life,
and it's all gone terribly wrong.
-[bell tolls]
-[deep voice] Or terribly right.
[stammers] No. Wait!
Poor sweet Giselle doesn't know
what she wants, but I do.
-Stepmother, please just--
-Morgan, you have to listen to me.
[gasps] Oh, yes, yes.
Perfect little Morgan,
not so perfect now, is she?
[gasps]
Don't you dare!
Oh, I'll dare all I like.
Stop it! You're-- You're scaring me.
I know.
[pants] I wish I could do it myself,
but who knows what would happen
if I went over there like this? [gasps]
You have to go.
[gasps]
[chuckles] Yes!
Get help before it's too late.
[panting]
-And you have to do it before midnight.
-Do what? [pants]
Save us.
[screams]
Oh. [gasps]
Wretched girl! [chuckles]
-[Sofia crying]
-[gasps]
[crying continues]
-You three!
-[all gasp]
[Giselle]
You look like you're good with children.
My precious darling needs tending to.
See to it.
[all whimpering]
Mmm.
Oh, I feel superior to all living things.
I don't know why we were fighting this.
[Giselle] Indeed!
Who knew that being a villain
could feel so… liberating?
-Now, I just need to find that wand.
-[grunts, hisses]
[mug shatters]
[chuckles]
What have we here?
You know, stepmothers are many things.
But one of the things we are not
is powerful.
That's why we have to go through
all of these ridiculous manipulations.
We have no power of our own.
Now that Morgan's gone,
I'm not a stepmother anymore.
[Pip yawns]
So I think it's time
I took on a new role in this town.
I'd like to be queen!
Yeah, but there's already a queen,
and I feel like
she is really attached to the job.
[chuckles]
That should be easy enough to fix.
A villain like Malvina can't resist
a chance to show the world how bad she is.
Mmm. So, where are we going?
I say we give it to her.
And then I have a little job for you,
my pet.
Ooh. Do I get to be evil now?
-Oh, yes.
-[purring]
Oh.
Uh-uh. Oh.
[bell tinkles]
[Giselle chuckles]
-Hmm?
-[gasps] Mirror, mirror in her hand.
Who is the most blatantly insecure woman,
whose constant need
to ask her own reflection for validation
suggests that what she really needs to do
is to love herself,
in all the land?
[chuckles]
Giselle, a pleasure as always.
Yes, I imagine it is. [gasps]
Well, I was hoping that I'd run into you,
and look at this. It seems I have.
[chuckles]
So, what can I do for you then?
I thought it only fair
to give you a chance
to hand Monrolasia over to me peacefully
before any unpleasantness begins.
-[gasps]
-Mmm?
[laughs]
And why would I do that?
Because this town is mine.
I think we both know that, don't we?
Oh… [gasps]
-[grunts]
-Oh.
Sadly, I'm going to have to decline
your generous offer.
Having had a chat
with your little scroll friend,
it's clear that Monrolasia is everything
it was meant to be,
however that might have occurred.
Hmm.
Well, I tried.
But if you won't accept the offer,
you know there's only one thing
that can happen.
[Malvina] Indeed.
Dance-off!
You see what I gotta put up with?
One of us has to die.
Mmm. Say, midnight?
Sounds about right.
Again,
I'm so sorry to ruin your little party
with all of this messy
"destroying you" business.
Oh, Giselle.
You're hilarious.
[chuckles]
Delusional, but hilarious.
♪ Please don't fear that
You are upsetting me ♪
♪ Dear, I barely know you're there ♪
♪ Sorry, were you speaking?
You're hard to see ♪
♪ Like a smell that lingers in the air ♪
♪ Trying to be clever
That makes no sense ♪
♪ That's a role you haven't earned ♪
♪ You don't see your own insignificance ♪
♪ Well, it's time you learned ♪
♪ You may think you're bad
But, darling, I am badder ♪
♪ Really, sweetie, where's the thrill in
Being just a-- ♪
-♪ Has-been ♪
-♪ A wannabe ♪
♪ Villain ♪
♪ You're a garter snake
And I'm a big puff adder ♪
♪ Face it
I am so much badder ♪
♪ Than you ♪
♪ Surely you can see it's ridiculous ♪
♪ Two villains in one fairy tale ♪
♪ This town is too small
For the both of us ♪
♪ So off into the sunset
You should sail ♪
[grunts]
♪ I can send my minions
To help you pack ♪
♪ I'll be careful not to crow ♪
♪ Darling, I will miss you ♪
-♪ Alas ♪
-♪ Alack ♪
♪ But you have got to go ♪
♪ You can claim you're bad
But I'm a better badder ♪
♪ Nothing you've got up your sleeve'll
Ever equal me as a mistress of evil ♪
♪ I'm the heart and brains
And you, you're just the bladder ♪
♪ How can you believe you're badder
Than I ♪
♪ Nobody ever would bother to tell ♪
♪ A tale with Maleficent
And with Cruella ♪
♪ My cheekbones are sharper ♪
♪ My hair's much more high ♪
♪ So jump down a rabbit hole ♪
♪ Go climb a beanstalk ♪
♪ It's not au revoir ♪
♪ But goodbye ♪
♪ Someone really should
Put a stop on her ♪
♪ Up to me
To find a way ♪
♪ Maybe there's a house
I can drop on her ♪
♪ Mmm
Is a poisoned apple too cliché? ♪
♪ Drag her to a rooftop
And toss her down ♪
♪ A spell to make her disappear ♪
♪ And when she is gone
I will own the town ♪
♪ And everyone will cheer ♪
♪ She was sorta bad
But you are so much badder ♪
♪ Clearly that is why I have to
See that she lives happily never after ♪
♪ Once I sit alone
Atop the villain ladder ♪
♪ Everyone in Monrolasia
Will totally be in my thrall ♪
♪ They will say
"Oh, Queen, we praise ya" ♪
♪ Because I will be
Not just badder ♪
♪ Badder ♪
-♪ But the nasty ♪
-♪ Everlast-y ♪
♪ Flabbergast-y ♪
♪ Very, very baddest of them all ♪
[rumbling]
[grunting]
Huh?
Oh.
What happened?
The well!
Oh, no, no, no.
Why am I so pointy?
And my eyebrows are so perfect.
What the heck am I wearing?
Is this Andalasia?
Wow. This is not what I pictured at all.
-Morgan?
-Nancy.
What are you doing here?
I'm not sure.
Something weird happened.
Did it, by any chance,
include a giant hole in your sky?
[Morgan] A what? What the heck is that?
Last night,
that mysterious hole appeared in the sky
and started pulling all of our magic
into some other place.
[troll] Oh.
Okay, Morgan, tell us what happened.
Well, Giselle and I had
a pretty bad fight. And then, uh…
[Nancy] And then what?
-[gasps]
-[Morgan] I'm not sure, exactly.
But the last thing I remember is
Giselle acting really, really cruel.
And then she said something about
making a wish and that I had to fix it.
Oh, Edward. The wishing wand.
She must have used it.
But what could she have possibly
wished for that would have done all this?
Well, whatever it was, it turned our whole
town into some kind of fairy-tale place.
Just like Andalasia.
Morgan, a wish so big
that it changes a world
wouldn't need a little of our magic.
Why, it would-- It would need all of it,
every last bit.
Wait.
But everything here is made of magic.
If it's all gone,
then what happens to Andalasia?
If we can't reverse this,
everything Andalasian
will be gone forever.
I don't want Andalasia
to disappear forever.
-I know. I know.
-No.
There must be something we can do.
Giselle just needs to remember who she is,
and then she can fix all of this.
I know she can.
Remember? Edward!
Of course.
The magic of memories.
What? You mean Giselle's memory tree?
It's real?
It is.
And it's the strongest magic there is.
[door closes]
[fairies cooing, chattering]
[sighs]
-[Sofia babbles]
-[chattering continues]
Hello.
Who are you?
[fairy] We're your garden fairies.
-I'd turn around if I were you.
-Unless you wanna get thrown off the roof.
Hmm.
[babbles]
[sighs] Ah!
Seems like the babysitters
have had quite the day.
So have I, dear.
Hmm.
We're really going to need
something more regal than this.
And minions.
We'll definitely need minions
if we want anything done right.
Where did you say Morgan was again?
Oh. [chuckles]
Who knows?
-Hmm.
-Probably singing to a mouse or something.
But who cares? Tonight's about me.
Stop the carriage.
Whoa!
[Giselle] Robert.
Morgan wouldn't just disappear like this.
Unless something's happened.
Something's wrong.
I'm going to go find her.
Oh, well, another fruitless quest,
-but… [chuckles] …good luck with that.
-[grunts]
[Giselle] Drive!
-[driver] Hyah!
-[whip cracks]
[birds chirping]
Okay, I knew it was a tree house,
but that's a "tree house."
-We do whimsy really well.
-Huh.
I think the tree is over here.
[bird squawks]
That's it. That's the tree!
[sighs]
Oh, no.
It's dead.
Never fear. We will come up with something
very smart at the very last minute
that solves all our problems.
Edward.
What? That's how it works here.
There has to be something we can do.
You know, for a little girl with no mom,
seeing a princess hanging from a billboard
was magic.
I-I knew it was real.
I didn't even have to think about it.
Things were so much easier back then.
-[Giselle's voice] I'll never forget you.
-Whoa.
What was that?
You brought the flower back to life.
I did?
But how? I'm not magic.
No, but these memories are.
And they live inside you as well.
Which means their magic does too.
Morgan, you're the key.
That's what Giselle meant
by telling you to save us.
So, maybe if I can bring
some of this tree back,
the magic in it will get her to remember
that who she really is, is good.
Then she'll fix this.
I think we're running out of time.
But what if it doesn't work?
[Nancy] Morgan, it will.
You just have to remember
all the good in these moments
because you're a part of them.
Feel them, and they'll do the rest.
♪ Memories are magic, Morgan ♪
[young Morgan] Are you really a princess?
♪ Doesn't matter
How unmemorable they seem ♪
♪ Ordinary moments
Like a look or laugh you shared ♪
♪ Can bring a gleam of light ♪
♪ In your bleakest, darkest hour ♪
♪ Memories can save us, Morgan ♪
♪ When you add them up
They paint a picture of ♪
♪ All the love you've given
And the love you have received ♪
♪ And in that love, there's power ♪
♪ Love power ♪
♪ We can always choose to use it
If we dare ♪
♪ Love power ♪
♪ And we find it
In the memories we share ♪
♪ And we need it ♪
♪ Like the sun and light and air ♪
♪ When we need real magic, Morgan
This is where to go ♪
♪ Find the song inside you
That your memories seem to know ♪
♪ Let it grow
Let it glow ♪
[vocalizing]
[Nancy] Edward.
You go.
Someone needs to stay behind
to protect our world.
[vocalizing continues]
♪ Out of rock, there grows a flower ♪
♪ As a ray of sunshine melts
A cave of ice ♪
♪ So we'll sing it out
Until the world will sing along ♪
♪ What makes us strong? ♪
♪ Love power ♪
♪ Love, love power ♪
♪ It's like soaring on a magic broomstick
To the sky above ♪
♪ We fly on love ♪
♪ Love power ♪
♪ Love, love power ♪
♪ Just remember the memories ♪
♪ That show us the power ♪
♪ Of love ♪
I-- I think I know what to do.
[breathes shakily]
What is that?
It-- It's my memory tree.
I can bring her back.
I think I'm just gonna go get some air.
Whatever, dear. Back by midnight.
[grunts, mumbles]
[Rosaleen] I should be at that party.
Instead, I'm here,
-babysitting you babysitting this wand.
-[muffled muttering]
-[grunts]
-And all because she doesn't trust you.
Or maybe she doesn't trust you.
I'm not the one
she tried to turn into a toad.
-[Ruby] Well, maybe she likes toads.
-[Rosaleen chuckles]
No matter what reptile she turns you into,
I am her right-hand lady.
Which means that
you should be doing the dumb stuff.
And I should be looking fabulous
at the festival.
[Ruby] Okay, then go.
And I'll tell Malvina that
you abandoned the wand,
and we'll see who ends up a warty toad.
I would never be the warty toad.
-Look in a mirror lately? An honest one?
-[gasps]
-[Ruby] Ooh.
-[Rosaleen] Oh, it's gonna be like that?
-[Ruby] Uh-huh.
Well, I guess
we will both just babysit the wand.
I guess we will.
-Little advice. Get a life.
-[gasps]
She hates you both.
-Whoo-hoo!
-[shouts] Look out! Incoming!
-Hey, Scroll! Scram!
-[Ruby groans]
[Scroll] Watch it!
If there are no more questions, goodbye.
[gasps] Oh! [groans]
Let go of my tail!
Okay. Ladies, have you learned nothing?
Gotta be quicker than that.
-How is he so fast?
-[gasps] Oh.
Oh.
-We can get him down.
-Oh, hey, wait. Come on!
And away we go!
[both groan]
Hey, you ladies have been great,
but I got a ball to catch. See you later.
[chattering, laughing]
Do I look ready?
There you are, my pet. Any problems?
Nope. Turns out I'm good at evil.
Well, now comes the fun part.
I'm ready now.
Hope I'm not underdressed.
Oh, wait a second. What is this?
Ooh. Ooh, yeah.
Uh. Uh, hey! Wait a minute. I'm with her.
Folks, this is my stop.
Hello? Mr. Wig.
Forgot abou-- I'm with her.
I gotta get out of here. Hey!
Hey! Hey, what's happening? Wait a minute.
You forgot about me!
Hmm.
Morgan, where have you been? Are you okay?
No. Actually I'm really, really not.
-Can I get a lift?
-Of course.
Go! I'll be right behind you.
[whinnies]
Now, let's see.
I wish to be Queen of Monrolasia.
[exhales]
Ah.
[villager] Make way! Make way!
We have to get inside.
[applause]
I believe you are in my seat.
[all gasp]
You again.
[murmuring]
And I believe it's time we end this
once and for all.
Oh, yes. Please.
[screaming, clamoring]
[groaning]
[Malvina] Stupid chair!
[groans] Why does this keep happening?
-[rumbling]
-[gasps]
[clamoring]
Is this my mother's doing?
-[both grunt]
-[Morgan screams]
No, it's Andalasia.
It's breaking through.
[screaming]
Okay. Deep breath. Suck in. [grunts]
[screaming, clamoring]
I wish.
[gasps]
[laughing]
-[gasps]
-[Giselle cackles]
[grunts]
[grunting, groaning]
[chuckles]
[cackles] Guards.
Destroy her.
I wish.
[clamoring]
[laughs, gasps] Mmm.
They're just butterflies! Idiots!
[clamoring]
-Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
-Oh. [panting]
Ruby wants to tell you something
about the wand.
-[Ruby stammers]
-Oh, does she?
-[gasps]
-Hi!
It was her fault.
She's the one that should be the toad.
And you're the one who let the cat in.
You two are the worst!
-Huh?
-[both shouting]
-[Malvina] Hmm. [chuckling]
-[ribbiting]
Speaking of toads.
I wish.
[choking]
[grunts]
[screaming, clamoring]
[Morgan pants]
-Nancy!
-Robert!
Have you seen Morgan?
-Yes. She's here. She's fine.
-Oh, thank goodness.
My God, people are going crazy.
I know. I know. Listen, it's Giselle.
She's under a curse.
We have to save her so she can stop this.
A curse?
Let's go!
[screams]
[grunts]
[Robert] Morgan!
[Morgan] Dad!
Dad!
How have you fared? Oh!
I have searched both hither and yon.
We need to get inside. Let's go.
When did my daughter become so brave?
Now we save Giselle.
Time to be heroes.
[grunts]
[rumbling]
[chuckles]
[clamoring, screaming]
-Need a hand?
-[groans]
[pants]
-[Tyson] Mother, stop this!
-[Robert] Giselle!
[yelps]
[gasps]
-Hmm.
-[gasps]
Useless garbage.
No!
Giselle, no!
[Giselle's voice]
This is a very nice place.
-[Robert's voice] Yeah.
-[Giselle's voice] This is a date.
-She's very kind and very sweet.
-[Robert's voice] Yeah.
-[young Morgan's voice] Giselle!
-[Giselle's voice] I'm right here, Morgan.
[Morgan's voice] Hey, wait for me!
Mom, where are you going?
[Giselle's voice] I'm not going anywhere.
[Robert's voice]
You'll always be a princess to me.
[young Morgan's voice]
Higher! Higher, Mom!
[cackling]
[yowls]
Uh-oh.
What the heck is going on around here?
Uh, Giselle!
[Giselle] Oh.
[gasps]
Robert.
[Giselle chuckles]
[chuckles]
My sweet Giselle.
You've come back to me.
I'm so sorry. I don't want minions.
[rumbling]
[gasps]
Nancy, where's Edward?
He stayed behind to protect Andalasia.
[Giselle] Oh, no.
-Please, we have to hurry.
-[gasps]
The magic is disappearing.
We have to stop this
or everything Andalasian will die.
And that means that you…
will?
No.
No, I--
I can fix this.
[Malvina] Stop!
I wouldn't if I were you.
-[Malvina laughs]
-[Robert] Morgan.
Morgan! [pants]
-Mother, what are you doing?
-Oh, relax, darling.
It's just a little sleeping potion.
It was actually meant for Giselle,
but this'll do.
Malvina, you have to undo it.
[Malvina] Oh, and I shall.
Your helpful scroll explained
at the last stroke of midnight,
your wish is permanent.
And I like this world.
So you're going to drop that wand
and let the clock strike,
and then, she'll be free.
But if I do that, Andalasia dies.
And if you don't do it, she dies.
-No.
-Cease, evil witch.
Oh, Robert. Don't you think
you're being a little harsh?
Malvina, please.
This isn't you.
It is now.
Just as you wished it.
[gasps] No!
[gasps]
[Malvina chuckles]
Morgan.
[gasps]
[exhales]
[grunts]
[gasps] Oh. [pants] I feel weak.
Giselle. Giselle.
-[Morgan] What's happening?
-[groans, pants]
-Are you okay?
-[Giselle] I don't know.
-[Giselle gasps, screams]
-[Robert grunts]
No.
Isn't it marvelous when two worlds
come together in such… harmony?
[Giselle whimpers]
[bell tolls]
[gasps]
When the clock strikes 12:00,
the spell will be set.
[bell tolls]
No.
-This is not how it ends.
-Huh.
[Tyson] I'm coming with you.
Robert.
Some heroes.
[bell tolls]
-What are we gonna do?
-It can't strike midnight!
[bell tolls]
[Nancy gasps]
[sighs]
It's like a wish come true. [laughs]
-Please hold on.
-[tolling continues]
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
No, no, no. There has to be
something else that we can do.
-I just wish…
-No.
That piece of wand. Grab it. [pants]
Ticktock, ticktock.
-[bell tolls]
-[grunts]
-[Robert] Tyson, your sword!
[both grunting]
[Robert] Hold on!
[Morgan breathes shakily]
Morgan.
[gasps] You can't break magic.
Listen to me.
You have to make a new wish, Morgan.
My magic is almost gone.
Oh, according to your droll little scroll,
no one but a true Andalasian
can use that broken piece of kindling.
But go for it.
She's right. [stammers] I can't.
I'm not a true daughter of Andalasia.
You are a true daughter of Andalasia.
Because you are my daughter, Morgan.
♪ And I'll tell you ♪
♪ How I absolutely know ♪
♪ It's how I'd make a world for you ♪
♪ That never breaks your heart ♪
♪ Where you can grow and thrive ♪
[sniffles]
♪ And your every wish can flower ♪
♪ I will always love you, Morgan ♪
♪ I'm so proud
Of how I know you'll carry on ♪
No. [sighs]
♪ I've known a lot of magic in my life ♪
♪ But never anything as strong ♪
♪ Love power ♪
♪ My love for you has power ♪
♪ And you'll have it there inside you ♪
♪ When I'm gone ♪
No. [sniffles] No.
♪ My love will be there ♪
[whispers] No. No. [sniffles]
♪ Ever after… ♪
No. [cries]
♪ When I'm… ♪
[pants] No. No. No, no, no, no, no.
What do I wish for?
Please. Please don't go.
Please don't leave me.
-[groans]
-[Morgan] Please.
Giselle.
[cries]
What do I wish for?
[chuckles] Ticktock, ticktock.
Wait.
Where are the chimes?
Why isn't it midnight?
[gasps]
[both grunting]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[growls]
[shouts]
I wish I was home… with my mom.
[grunting]
[grunts]
[gears clacking]
-[glass shattering]
-[grunts]
[screams]
[gasps]
[grunts, gasps]
[Giselle chuckles]
-Oh, yes, sweet thing.
-[babbling]
Mom.
Morgan. [chuckles]
[gasps] Mom!
You did it!
I was so scared.
I know. [sighs] But you saved me.
You saved us all.
[Robert sighs] Good morning.
Oh. I had the craziest dreams last night.
-[giggles]
-Good morning.
[babbles]
[both chuckle]
He really doesn't remember anything?
Only the person who wields the magic
ever really remembers it clearly.
To everyone else,
it's sort of like a dream.
-[chuckles]
-[giggles]
Well, I can't wait for you to explain
to him how he sang with a garbage pail
-and defeated an evil queen.
-[Giselle laughs]
-Good luck with that. [kisses]
-[Sofia giggles]
[chattering]
I had a horrible dream about toads.
-Me too.
-[bell tinkling]
Good morning, Edgar.
Giselle, the usual?
Oh, yes, please. Thank you.
Good morning. I'm sorry to interrupt.
I just thought I'd say hi.
And I really wanted to apologize
for a lot of things. [chuckles]
I just really wanted Morgan
to be happy here,
and I guess I got a little carried away.
[chuckles]
Okay. Enjoy your coffees.
You know…
Um,
I have the tendency
to get carried away myself sometimes.
[chuckles] No.
It turns out we do have room on one
of our committees, if you'd be interested.
Mmm. Hmm?
I think our town could use
someone like you.
I'd love that. [chuckles]
-Oh!
-Oh, we're hugging.
-[Giselle chuckles] Okay.
-[Malvina chuckles]
-Not your chair.
-Oh, right. Nope. Okay.
Mm-hmm. Yep.
[Giselle chuckles]
[Pip] And so, a new story for Giselle
and her family began in Monroeville.
Without the magic this time.
Robert opened a small practice in town,
and never rode the train again.
Sofia sprouted up.
-And Morgan…
-[Tyson] Hey, Morgan!
[babbles]
-Um, I'll be back in a sec.
-Mm-hmm.
[Pip] Well, she was still a teenager.
-Stop looking at me. It's creepy.
-No, I'm just--
-Not looking!
-Gonna pour some--
-[Nancy] I am so sorry I'm late.
-[chuckles] Oh!
-There was a gaggle of hobgoblins…
-That's okay.
…in the woods today.
-They just wouldn't give up.
-[all laugh]
It took the whole village
to drive 'em out.
-[clears throat]
-Where is Edward? Did he stay behind?
Oh, no, no, no. He's here.
He's engaged in battle.
-Of course.
-Back, you wild beasts! Back!
[groans]
You're dead!
No, I'm not. You merely grazed me.
-You grazed me!
-[laughing]
I'm not dead.
Look, I have barely a limp!
-[chuckling]
-[Edward groans, sighs]
-[Nancy laughs]
-[giggles]
[chuckles]
Your tiny peasants are quite fierce.
-As are you, Robert…
-Oh, no.
…who so grandly helped save the day
with my sword.
Well, may your adventures
with my sword continue, my good man.
-Actually, Edward. I've hung up the sword.
-Ah.
I'm happy to say
I don't really need it here.
-Really? [chuckles]
-Yeah.
-What a tragedy.
Can I have it back?
-Yes. Of course you can.
-[laughs]
-Okay. Great.
-[Giselle] Shall we feast?
-[Nancy] Absolutely.
-What can I get you?
-But first, we have a very special gift.
-[Edward sighs]
Whatever dish you wish
will appear on this plate.
-Hmm?
-Oh. Oh.
That's all that it does. That's--
-Right? That's-- We're fairly certain.
-Yeah.
-Maybe you should make the wish.
-Yes.
-All right. [chuckles, groans]
-[Nancy] Oh!
[grunts] Excuse me.
I must defend my honor.
-I declare a do-over!
-I'll go deal with that.
-Here. Let me help you.
-Yes, of course.
I'm coming too!
[Edward grunts]
-[chuckles]
-[child grunts] Got you!
[babbles]
[chuckles]
What was that for?
-I just love you.
-Mmm.
And I couldn't wish for anything more.
♪ And some days are good
And some are not so ♪
♪ But none do we take for granted ♪
♪ 'Cause it's both the joys ♪
Ah! Toast.
♪ And adversities ♪
♪ Making these ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ And though here in reality ♪
♪ My ever-after may not be ♪
♪ At every moment happily ♪
-♪ It's even more ♪
-[chorus] ♪ Even more ♪
-♪ Even more ♪
♪ Even more ♪
♪ Enchanted ♪
[yawns]
[snoring]