Okay.
Okay, oh. Office
experience, which is great.
Okay.
So Emily, I do see
that you have something
on your permanent record.
Is that right?
Yeah. Yes, it is.
Oh. We haven't run
a background check.
We don't usually do that.
Could you fill us
in on the details?
Sure.
I have DUI, like,
a misdemeanor DUI.
What happened exactly?
I drove some friends
home from a concert
and I ran a red light.
Everybody was fine, but.
And you were intoxicated?
I was less intoxicated
than my friends, but yeah,
that's what happened, so.
Okay.
So this is your official
background check,
which I have read and
according to the state,
you were convicted of
aggravated assault in 2016.
Is that correct?
So, you do have
all my information?
Yeah, yeah. I'm afraid we do.
Okay. Okay.
Why would you.
Well, if you want us
to be generous with you,
then you need to be generous
with us and be honest.
Okay?
Okay.
This is a very important job.
You'd be handling
private medical files.
Right.
Right. You're right.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. Let's start over, okay?
Okay.
Can you tell us what
happened with the assault?
No.
No?
No. Why would you trick
somebody like that?
Oh! I did not trick you.
Yeah, you did.
What I did is very common.
That's a very common technique.
Oh, is that right? So,
you do that all the time?
If people chose to be honest,
then I wouldn't have to
do that all the time.
Well, you know what? Fuck this.
I don't even want to work here.
Emily, I'm sorry
you're upset but.
No, you're not.
Calm down, please.
I am calm.
And you asked me
why I want this job
because I got $70,000
of student debt.
There's your fucking
answer right there.
Yeah. You need to leave.
Yeah, actually. You know what?
Give me that too.
Okay, fine. Thank you.
Yeah, thank you too.
Excuse me.
There you go.
Yo.
Can I get that
dressing on the side?
So, this is the house
salad, dressing on the side,
then the chicken
churrasco, black beans.
Okay. Did we get
two rice orders?
Two rice. Two veggies.
Okay, good.
Hey, yo! Emily, yo. Are
you working tonight?
No, I just got off.
Do you want my shift?
My son has a baseball
game in Glendale.
His mother was
supposed to take him.
I called everybody,
like, everybody.
Dude, I don't usually
work downtown at night.
I know this. Big favor.
All right, I got you.
Thank you, gracias, for real.
Let me, yeah, yeah.
One second, okay?
Let me hook you up.
Text that number.
You can make like
200 bucks in an hour.
I swear to God.
What is this?
Dummy shopper.
You know what that is? Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's super easy.
You and me at lunch
tomorrow, right?
Yeah, I'll see you then.
All right. Be good.
Thank you. Come on.
Hey. Hey.
You got some mail.
Thanks.
Hi, yeah.
I paid $400 on the 10th
and it was never
applied to my balance.
$400.
It was applied to my interest?
Sorry. How much interest
is being added a month?
Doing what?
Excuse me, lady.
You can't park
here. You got to go.
All right.
Hey. Hi. Hi, hi, hi.
Yo. Sorry. Oh no, it's all good.
I just got here.
God, my life is so
fucking insane right now.
I can't even-Are you okay?
Yeah, no. I'm going to Portugal.
For work?
Yeah, I got to go
oversee this photo shoot
for a print campaign.
So we're going to Porto,
some little village
on the Spanish border.
Holy shit. Yeah, yeah.
It's only for 11 days but
11 days? That's awesome.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah. So how are you?
What's up? It's been a minute.
Are you still doing portraits?
Yeah. Like, yes and no.
I'm not painting at
all right now. Yeah.
Paint's expensive.
Yes. Yeah, I need a job.
Oh. Yeah.
Like a real job, like
a real job. Yeah.
Yeah. Just to like
pay my loans and yeah.
So I might go back to Jersey
and live with my stepdad
for awhile and save money.
No. What?
Is that what you want to do?
No, but yeah.
Okay. What if I got
you an interview?
'Cause I know that we're
hiring a graphic designer
and we're always
hiring assistants.
Yeah, but I thought you didn't
feel super comfortable
doing that.
No, I know. I know I didn't
but my boss loves me.
Like for real, she's
obsessed with me.
Yeah.
She said I have to like
tell her about my record.
That's like the whole thing.
Yeah. No, let me talk to her.
I'll tell her we went
to art school together.
I'll vouch for you.
I mean, it'll be fun.
Really?
You're not going back
to Jersey. Fuck that.
Okay. Fuck that.
Thank you.
Of course.
All right. Let's get a drink.
Yes. Are you drinking?
I'm drinking, but I don't know.
Yeah, I'll have wine.
I'll take it easy.
Whoa!
Oh.
No, no. Come on,
come on, come on.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, I'm drunk.
Oh my God. Fuck!
Hi. I'm here for the.
Let me see your
driver's license.
Who gave you our number?
Javier Santos.
Can you tell me exactly.
Wait.
Hello, Javier? Do you
know Emily Borato?
Moretti.
Boretto.
This kid is really cool though.
He acting like he
don't give a shit.
Man, he over here just.
Who here has been a
dummy shopper before?
Raise your hands but
only if you've done it.
You did?
Where? In L.A.?
Nah, Milwaukee.
Oh, Milwaukee.
What'd you buy, snow shoes?
Nah, like an iPad
Mini. Two iPad Minis.
Good.
So for everybody
else, listen up.
In the next hour, you
will make 200 cash,
but you will have to
do something illegal.
You won't be in danger.
You won't endanger
another person,
but you will be
breaking the law.
So if you're not cool
with that, I get it,
and you can go with any time.
Can I keep going?
Yeah, that's what we want.
Uh huh.
Good.
Grab a card, please.
In a few minutes you
will go into a store
and buy some merchandise.
Any of these flat
screens is okay.
Just buy one and
wheel it outside.
We pick up the merchandise
and we pay you.
And that's it for today.
These are stolen, right?
The information on
them is stolen. Yes.
What? Nah, man.
Fuck that. I can't
fuck with y'all.
Okay.
Look, if you're not
cool with this, great.
Take off and don't bother
calling the police.
We haven't done
anything illegal yet.
They won't even show up. Okay?
I'm cool with it.
Wait, hold on.
What's the problem?
No, it's just, how do
we know the cards work?
You don't. That's the hard
part, you have to trust me.
What if they ask for
a driver's license?
Mm.
Is that you?
Let's make some fucking money.
Yo! Are you gonna pay for that?
I'm sorry?
I said, are you
gonna pay for that?
I forgot. Sorry, man.
Tomorrow you have the
option to do another job.
It's a little bit
more complicated.
We'll text you at 1:00 PM, okay?
What do I have to do?
Kill someone.
Just kidding. We'll
tell you tomorrow.
All right.
Wait. Don't you want to know
how much you get paid for it?
How much?
2,000.
$2,000?
We'll text you,
yes? One o'clock.
Sure.
Right there. That's good.
I got it.
You text that number?
Yeah? Yeah.
For real?
Hey, did you do another job
for them, like, the next day?
Nah, but I was curious though.
I was
definitely curious.
Shit's broken or something.
What's up? Want me to get it?
Nah, I'm good.
You sure? I'm good.
God, damn it!
I got you.
I'm not trying to get fired.
Not on my.
Shh, chill.
Are we supposed to eat this?
Hey, what's going on?
Hey. Oh, are you at work?
Yeah, it's fine. Did
you talk to your boss?
Oh, I'll call you back. Sorry.
No, no, it's good. It's cool.
Okay.
Well, so we just hired
some people, apparently.
My boss is being super
weird right now and like.
Did you really talk to her?
What? Yeah.
You think I'm lying?
No.
Oh, fuck.
It's an hour away.
So, I got to go now.
What are you talking about?
Wells Fargo is a half
order, you don't need me.
Nah, you can't ditch out
in the middle of lunch.
I'll throw you my
delivery fee. Okay?
That's 30 bucks right there.
What? Am I driving your car?
I'll take you back to the
kitchen, you grab your car.
Whoa!
These are black cards. They
don't have limit, no limit.
And these, take these, okay?
Just listen to me
and you'll be fine.
Do what I tell you to do.
Go to the Southeast
corner of the Plaza.
You'll see a white door,
they'll buzz you in.
If you don't know
Southeast, use your phone.
It's just you.
Okay? Okay.
With a purchase of this size,
the bank will call the vendor,
but that takes eight minutes.
So once they run your card, you
have eight minutes to leave.
Eight minutes or
they know it's fake.
How do I know this
is going to be safe?
If you don't want to
do it, don't do it.
Okay? It's up to you.
Hey. Hi.
How are you? Good.
Come inside.
Please, come in.
Okay, so you want to
test drive it, huh?
No, actually my boyfriend
drove it yesterday,
so I'm just here.
Here to pick it up.
Oh okay. Sit down.
So, you don't want
to see the car, huh?
No. I don't need to.
He, like I said, he
drove it yesterday, so.
It's a little
unusual for someone
to buy a car without seeing it.
Mm.
Okay. Let's do it.
How do you want to pay for it?
Do you have a cashier's check?
Yes.
I've got.
Okay.
And.
And the rests of the card.
Okay.
Let me see your
driver's license.
Sure.
Jennifer, huh?
Jen.
Okay. Just a moment.
Takes a few seconds.
It's taking its time.
Please sign.
There you go.
Thank you.
Hold on a minute.
I need you to fill
out this form.
This is a waiver that
states we're not responsible
for any mechanical
issues after today.
Sure.
Take your time. There's no rush.
We just got this car, you know?
Oh yeah?
Yeah, from Mexico.
You don't mind do you?
No.
Oh, but it's a nice car.
So your name was what,
Jennifer or Jen? Jen?
Sure. Yeah, Jennifer.
I like Jen.
Oh okay. You like Jen.
Yeah, Jennifer, no.
Jennifer makes you too old.
Oh, we wouldn't want that.
Hey, get my number.
That's the car.
You like it?
Yeah.
Get my number.
Yeah, I think I
got his number too.
There you go.
Thank you very much.
Enjoy, yeah.
It fits you nice, huh?
Yeah, yeah. You look nice, yeah.
Drive safe.
Just one moment, please.
Hey, we just need to
go back to the office
for just a second.
Why? What's wrong?
Nothing. We forgot one thing.
It's just my fault.
You can't tell me what it is?
It's not a big deal, you know?
So just, can you turn
off the engine, please?
Turn off the engine.
Hey, hey! Don't!
Pull over! Pull the
fucking car over!
Fuck.
Oh, what the fuck
did I just told you?
Hold on. What's this?
Oh shit.
Two grand. Let me see it.
Okay. Okay.
Come on. Let's go! Okay!
What the fuck are
you staring at?
Give it to me.
What happened?
Dude fucking attack to
me. What do you think?
Let me see.
No, don't touch me.
I just want to help, okay?
I thought it was safe.
That's why you paid somebody
else to do it, right?
Fuck off!
Hey. Are you okay, huh?
Hey, hey. Breathe.
It's okay. You're okay.
Okay, lean, lean forward.
Lean, lean, lean forward.
Okay, good. Come on.
Okay.
Are you okay to drive?
You can't make
money another way?
You can make money another way?
Make a left up here.
Here?
Here.
Okay. You're welcome.
Hey, wait, wait.
Do you want this?
Yes?
Yes. Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Is your face swelling?
What?
Your face? You need to
put ice on it, okay?
Yeah, I know.
Right away.
But you need to use
the ice cubes. Yes?
Yeah. You think, I don't
know how to do ice?
I did not say you don't, okay?
I could help. I could
come up and help.
You want to help put
ice cubes on my face?
Sure.
Here. Thank you.
Put it right on your face.
You don't have to do that.
I told you there isn't any left.
I know.
You got no other booze.
Excuse me, no. It's there.
Excuse me.
Did you make these?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Check it out.
I'm going to buy this
place and fix it up.
40 units, just like
this, rental properties.
My man, Rahad is
going to sell it to me
after he's done renovating.
You're going to buy this?
I am.
How much is it?
It's a little down payment.
You make that much selling TVs?
Sometimes TVs, sometimes
other things as you know.
How much can one person make
if they did what you do?
What I do?
No, I was just wondering.
I mean, I already did it twice.
You could show me how to do it.
Why? What's in it for me?
I don't know, how
about a free car?
Here.
Keep it. Now you have my number.
Adios.
Hey, I'm sorry about
yesterday. All right?
Did it go okay?
Marco wants to talk to you.
Hey.
Yo, what happened yesterday?
It was an emergency,
okay? I'm really sorry.
Why didn't you call?
I should have.
Well, I got to cut
your lunch Wednesday,
Thursday, and Friday.
If you want to
double up on nights.
What, what? Starting this week?
This week. Yeah.
No, you can't take
me off the calendar
with no warning, Marco.
I'm sorry, are you an employer?
No, you're an
independent contractor.
So quit talking like you got
rights and go back to work.
Oh my God, dude. We have rights.
Just because we're not employees.
Look, this isn't
a union in house.
Call your shop steward
then. All right?
You got a union shop
steward, call them,
if not go back to work.
So I can give you numbers, but
I can't make cards for you.
I do not have the time.
But it's easy.
Watch.
Here's the numbers.
Here's the cards.
Okay.
Now, you scan the magnet.
Now you try.
Fucker.
When you did it,
it looked so easy.
Okay, wait, wait. Look, look.
Pull it hard like this.
We sell to a couple of vendors.
They keep us on
payroll like salary,
but you can sell online,
Craigslist, whatever.
Yeah, that's a bad idea, right?
I mean, none of this
is safe technically,
but if you listen to exactly
what they say, you'll be fine.
Don't mess with ATMs. Okay?
Don't meet customers
at your home.
And the most important thing,
don't go to the same store
more than once in a week.
You'll be dealing
with lots of cash.
What do you use for protection?
Pepper spray.
No good. I got
something for you.
Whoa, what do you mean?
What is that?
This.
If you make less than
$5,000, keep it, you're done.
Okay. And what if I make more?
If you make more?
Yeah.
Then you hit me up and
we'll take things further.
Shit.
Hey, Michael, are
you still coming?
So, it's $600?
Six? No, it's $300.
No, $600.
You said three online.
No, no, I texted you
six. I'll show you.
$300.
For real man. We're
in broad daylight?
Oh, what's up? You
gonna call the police?
I mean, we could just
steal the shit for free.
All right. All right.
$300.
Sure. No worries.
Come on, now. Where
are you going?
Hold up. Hold up.
$600, yes or no?
$350. Hey, where are you going?
What else you got?
Cool, man.
Thank you.
So, fucking insane.
It's like my favorite
color. You know it's green?
And so I thought, why
can't I have a color party.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay, so you got my email.
So you know everything
you need to do.
The only thing is
he's crate training,
so he has to sleep in the crate.
Okay, got it.
He doesn't like it.
But just, you know,
shove him in there.
Hey buddy.
Hey, I'm sorry about the job.
It's fine.
I can hook you up. I
know I can hook you up.
I just got to wait for
the right time, you know?
Totally.
But we can talk about
it when I get back.
Okay.
Okay. All right, baby.
Mama's gotta go to work.
I'm going to go to Portugal.
Yeah.
Love you.
I'm really gonna miss him.
Aww.
And you too. I love you.
Thank you so much.
Okay. Be safe. Yeah, you too.
If he's bad, you know, you
just smack him.
No.
Okay, I'm going to hook you
up with more numbers. Yeah?
Bigger accounts. Bigger limits.
Okay?
Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Sit, please. This could
take a minute. Okay?
I like your office.
Oh yeah?
Yes. The Feng Shui, it's just.
Yeah, it's good,
because I installed
all the lights myself.
I did the lighting design.
Oh, is that right? Yeah. Yeah.
It's good. I like it.
Okay.
I fucking hate this
place. I hate it.
But just a little more.
Well it's only temporary, right?
This is my cousin Khalil.
Khalil, this is Emily.
Nice to meet you again.
Nice to meet you too again.
Oh, she forgot her phone
at the meeting Thursday.
So, she came to.
You left your phone?
Yeah.
Just give me one second, please.
Yes? Okay.
I'm sorry I was late. Okay?
I'm gonna take you for a walk.
I'm going to feed you.
'Cause that's what
I'm supposed to do.
Hello?
Yeah. It's still available.
Yeah. I'm just in a
different spot right now.
8216 Core Team Place.
Hey, excuse me.
Hey. Hi.
We almost caught, we
were across the street.
Look, I'm Chip up
here for the Samsung.
I mean, you know, we
drove all the way across.
Yeah, yeah. Cool, yeah.
Just stay right there,
and give me one second.
No, no. We came all
across town, man.
And, you know, I just
want to get it and go.
One second.
Is it right there though?
No, it's not. I'll be
right back, all right?
Let me give you a hand.
Yeah, I'll be right
back, all right?
No, no I'm just
giving you a hand.
Stay still. Stay still!
You feel that?
Yeah.
We know what you're
doing? We know what's up.
You do what I say or I'll
slit your throat. Okay?
Huh? Yes!
Okay? Do you want understand me?
Yes.
All right. Where's the cash at?
I don't have any cash
here. I swear to God.
Hey! Hey, hey, this
could be super easy.
Just tell us everything.
That's all you got to do.
There's a safe in
the bedroom closet. All right?
Bedroom on the left, on the
right. Bedroom on the right.
Hello.
You're just the cutest.
You wanna go for a ride?
Good boy.
What the hell is that?
It has a combination lock on it.
Okay, open it up. Let's go!
Okay.
Oh my God. Are those hundreds?
It's gotta be like
10, 15 grand in here.
Bag that shit up.
Let's go. Let's go.
I'm gonna borrow
your dog, bitch.
Yeah. Are you scared of me?
Hmm?
Yes.
Yeah.
We know where you live.
No.
No, no, no!
Hey.
Chip, what the hell? Chip?
Get out of the car.
No. Get out of the fucking car!
Wait, wait, wait.
Please, no, no, no!
Stay still. Okay?
Pauline Carper,
1186 Mirada Drive.
Yeah, yeah. Right?
Glendora. That's where you live?
Yeah.
Okay, you might
know where I live,
but I know where you live too.
You understand? Yeah.
You understand what I'm saying?
Yes!
What's up?
Oh, you look sexy.
Thank you. Hi, my baby!
I missed you.
Thank you, fuck, so
much. How was it?
How was what?
Barton.
Oh yeah, he's no problem.
Oh, thank God.
He's normally such
a fucking asshole.
Oh, not with me.
Emily, this is Taylor.
The Taylor from work.
Oh. This is Brendan.
They do our copy writing.
Guys, this is Emily.
Emily and I went to high
school together in the 973
and we went to art
school together, so.
97, what is that? An area code?
Newark.
Okay. Well I'm scared now.
You really should be.
You should we scared.
Taylor? Oh, okay.
You guys.
What kind of art do you do?
Um.
Sorry, Liz told me
you're an artist.
Oh yeah, no I, yeah, no.
I haven't done anything
in a long time art wise.
Oh, okay.
All right. What do you do then?
Credit card fraud.
Hey, are you Emily?
Yeah.
There's a guy outside
looking for you.
Hey, I didn't think
you got my text.
I wasn't far away, so.
Hello.
Hi.
This is my friend, Youcef.
Hi. Liz.
Oh, hello. It's very
nice to meet you.
Thank you. Thanks for coming.
Liz, yes? Liz?
Yep.
Is it your birthday, Liz?
No, I just got back
from a trip, so.
I'll be on the dance floor.
All right. We'll see you then.
Do you know all these people?
No, not really.
Nobody?
No. They all work with
Liz at the ad agency.
Do you want me to pretend
to be your boyfriend?
Sure. Okay.
Like this?
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay, so Sarah just put
in her two week notice.
My boss just texted
me right now and asked
if I know anyone, like,
this just happened.
Do you still want to interview?
Yeah. Yeah, definitely.
Yes. Yeah.
Just come by.
Can you come by the office and
I'll prep you on everything
like Tuesday at 11?
Yeah, definitely.
Definitely, yeah.
Okay. What did I tell you?
Yeah, girl.
See you in the back.
Oh, they finished the painting.
Good.
See, what I want to do is I
want to shorten this wall.
Yes? Put the bar here.
So the living room
and the kitchen
is like one big open space.
Nice. Yes?
For all four units,
we'll do the same thing.
We're going to put this up.
Yeah, but do you
own this place yet?
Soon.
Si.
So if you had some
money, what would you do?
Pay a loan?
Yeah, I would definitely
do that first.
What about your art?
Would you do your art?
Yeah, I would make art for sure.
I would paint. I love painting.
It makes me happy.
What else?
I mean, I don't know.
I just want to be
free, you know?
I just want to be able
to experience things.
I want to travel.
I want to live in another
country for awhile.
Like, I got a long list, like,
I really want to go
to South America like.
So, go. So, go.
You can go.
Yeah, no. I can't just go.
Sure. Sure you can.
I did. I left my home
and it was crazy.
Do you miss it?
Yeah, sure. Of course.
Now you're here.
Now I'm here.
I was hoping you could do
something for me like a favor.
Yeah? I'd owe you.
I swear to God.
What is it?
Don't freak out,
seriously. I'd owe you.
Okay?
Okay.
Say yes.
No.
Maybe you button
up your sweater.
Really?
Please, yes.
Hey, mama.
So happy to see you.
So, happy. Ma.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Three kisses.
Ah, come on in.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, not this.
Yes. No.
Ancient Lebanon tradition.
Really?
No, that's Italiano.
She just wants to drink
that shit with somebody.
That's not Lebanese.
I'll drink with you.
Oh, of course.
He cannot drink.
He takes tiny little shit sips.
I don't take little shit sips.
Tiny little baby
sips. I show you.
Tiny little baby sips?
Like this.
No ones' even said that.
Okay.
Here we go. Here we go.
One, two.
You don't even do it!
Come on, one, two.
Don't worry about me.
One, two, three.
Ooh! It tastes so bad.
He buys me an apartment.
Have you seen much
better than here?
I have seen, it's very nice.
He makes promise all his
life, now he does it.
He will become
successful businessman.
I know this. I know.
He does what ever
it takes. My Youcef.
So what do you do in life?
I'm not sure yet.
You don't know? It's okay.
You will figure out your
gift. God will give you gift.
My gift was making man.
Maybe, Emily the teacher.
Emily the mother.
Emily the something.
Very nice. Really nice day.
Ah, mama. I missed you.
I have more things in the
oven. Sit down, sit down.
I didn't know you were coming.
I'm just in a neighborhood.
I hold a video.
What's that?
Ah, show him.
Right there, huh? Same
store twice in one week.
So they put it on the website
like that. Linden police.
Did you drive your own car
with your own license plate?
I don't think it means anything.
No? Well, it's Emily, right?
Right.
If they find you, they
might find us. Understand?
Huh? Sure.
You understand? I understand.
Okay. Look, maybe
we go to somewhere.
No. You lied.
You told me it was a
one time thing with her.
Are you fucking
her yet at least?
That's enough.
Okay. That's enough.
At least one of
us is benefiting.
Excuse me?
Yes.
What'd you just say?
You cannot hear well?
Yeah, I heard what you
said. Say it again.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
I like her. She has
bigger balls than you.
I have wonderful things
for you to eat, eat.
What is happening that
nobody's eating here?
Oh, yes.
Wow. Those look good.
I want people to eat
and feel calm, happy.
Emily?
Hi. Hey.
Hey!
Oh! The blazer, bold choice.
Oh yeah. Is it too much?
No, I love it.
It's the only jacket I have.
It's very 80s.
So this is how I
do the scheduling.
It's just one Google doc
for the entire company
and basically it's open format.
So anyone can go
in and make changes
but realistically
nobody does that.
So I'm kind of in charge of
keeping everything on point
for about 50 employees, right?
I think it's 55 now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Including assistance and
everything like that.
So basically it's going
to be these six columns
that you want to make sure
that everything is correct.
This last column is going
to be the most important.
And by Friday, everything
needs to be pretty much set.
So you're going to need.
Now, you're gonna
kill the interview.
E-mail all the bosses,
CC every Assistant,
all that good stuff.
Thank you so much, Sarah.
Yeah, of course you.
I'm gonna miss you.
Oh, I know, I'm gonna
miss you guys too.
Hey, you want to get lunch?
Right now? Yeah.
Yeah. There's this ramen
place around the corner.
It is ruining my
life. It's so good.
But I just need 10.
So, I'll be right back.
Yeah, cool.
Hey.
Let's go.
What happened?
Let's go. Let's drive.
Hey, you're bleeding.
Here. There's some
tissue in here.
Drive the car.
All right, fine.
I'm fucking done.
I'm done with Khalil.
So, quit.
Five months, five months!
He hasn't paid me a thing.
He's not paying you?
And now Rahad calls and tells me
he needs the down payment
for the apartment.
He needs it now, that
there's a cash offer
from a Chinese company.
I tell Khalil, you
know what he say?
You know what he say?
He says you work with Emily
now. Why you come to me?
So, look.
Listen, tomorrow, first thing,
I'm hitting the storage
units then the office.
I'm going to clean up all
the cash that's there,
then the bank account.
We have a business account.
I'm going to empty
it as much as I can.
Jesus.
Are you in?
Am I in?
We're working together.
Yeah, but that's like a
whole other thing. Okay?
I don't know if I could,
I don't even know what
you're talking about.
Even if I do this alone,
he's going to blame you.
How much do you want?
Oh my God. So you're
just going to rob him?
Yes.
You take a cut.
All your debts paid.
You can travel. Get to
a new place, whatever.
But listen, if you're
going to do this,
you have to be in for real.
For real.
No. Stay here.
No, I gotta go to an interview.
Hi.
Ah, there she is.
Hey, it's so great to meet you.
Hi. Thanks for coming in.
Good to meet you too.
Thanks for having me.
Ooh, I like your accent.
You're clearly not
from the west coast.
No, I am from New Jersey.
Where?
Bayonne.
Hoboken.
Oh, nice.
Yeah. Where'd you go to school?
HBS.
Junior Senior,
Ninth and Clinton.
Oh yeah. I know Junior Senior.
So you're familiar
with the company.
I don't have to go through
the whole sales pitch.
So you left college
before you finished?
Yes.
Why?
I got a felony conviction.
So why didn't you go
to school afterwards
or a community college?
I wanted to, but you know,
I had legal fees, and student
loans, and living expenses.
I had to take care of my
grandmother, so I had to work.
Okay.
All right.
So what we're looking for
here is a design intern.
Does that sound
appealing to you?
Definitely. Yeah.
Good. Yeah.
Sorry. Is that a,
you say intern,
is it a job or an internship?
Well, all my
assistants are interns.
So is it, sorry. Is
that a paid position?
Not at first.
The way it works is the
first five or six months,
you get to know the business
and if you do a great job,
then I'd love to
discuss it with you.
Right.
Sorry. I'm just trying to
wrap my head around that.
So what are the hours?
Regular hours.
You do realize this is a
very competitive position?
Yeah, sure. I understand that.
What I don't understand is
how you feel so comfortable
asking someone to
work without pay.
You know, when I was your age,
they told me all I could
be was a secretary.
Okay. But secretaries get paid.
That's not the point.
Well, when you were my age,
do you have $60,000 of debt?
How about this?
When I was your age,
I was the only woman
in a room full of men.
But you had a job.
Okay. You know.
You were getting
paid. Am I wrong?
I don't have the time for this.
Clearly you're a bit spoiled.
Spoiled.
Let me be frank with you.
You don't belong here
because you think everyone
is out to get you.
None of us are out to
get you, especially me.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I'm trying to help you.
This was a fantastic,
Liz. Thanks very much.
Thank you. No more
talking, just leave.
Thank you so much for coming in.
Hey, if you want to
tell me what to do,
put me on the fucking payroll.
How about that?
Sorry I'm late.
You okay?
Yeah.
You sure.
Are we good?
Yeah. We're good.
Okay, good. Trucks
coming in 15 minutes.
Youcef Had dad. H-A-D-D-A-D.
Address?
1087 Van Nuys Boulevard.
Can you tell me if there's
been any activity on my
business account in the
last 48 hours, please?
Is this a shared account?
Yes, it's the shared
account. Khalil.
He did? Okay.
No, I don't need to.
Thank you.
He robbed me before
I could rob him.
You should go.
Hey.
It's going to be okay.
Twice in one week.
You hit the same store
twice in one week
even after I told you the rules?
Oh, so this is my fault??
He was going to do
this to you all along.
I don't know about that.
I do know. I don't know.
Yeah, you put up with his shit.
You didn't fight
back soon enough
and you let him take
advantage of you, okay?
Who's fucking fault is that?
Hey! Hey, did you fucking hear?
Did you hear? I just
lost everything!
I am have nothing! Two
years of fucking work!
Yeah. Okay.
Come on, please. Get
the fuck out, please!
Hey, careful! Nice.
Where is he?
Santa Clarita with the
Armenians, Robert and.
Yeah? Mm hmm.
Is he there right now?
Let's go talk to him.
It's a different situation
now. I need to think.
Is it? Explain it.
He's not alone and these
are very serious people.
No, no.
We're serious people. Okay?
He should be scared of us.
Motherfuckers will just
keep taking from you
and taking from you until
you make the God
damn rules yourself.
That's what this is about.
Am I wrong? Am I wrong?
Now, you told me I was going
to get a cut and I want my cut.
So let's go right now.
Right now?
He thinks you're a pushover.
He's not expecting you to fight
back. That's an opportunity.
You're a very bad influence.
What's up? You're
working on your day off?
What was it for, your
assault conviction?
It was just a guy I was dating
and we fought all the time.
One day, I just,
you know what my mistake
really was though?
I didn't go far enough.
I didn't really scare him.
You know, 'cause if I had,
he would've never
called the police.
Don't follow me to close.
Hi, how's it going? Khalil?
What is this?
I got a order, food
order for Khalil Had dad.
Is this the right place?
All right. Just pass it through.
Yeah. I don't think
it's going to fit.
It's a big order. Let's see.
Let me check it out.
Do you want me to
just bring it inside?
No. No. Just.
Look, I got to go. Okay,
I got another order.
Okay. Hold on.
All right.
Ah, What are you doing?
Hey, shut the fuck up
or I'll zap you again.
No, no, no. Shut up.
How many people are inside?
I don't know? How many people?
I don't know, all right.
How many people?
Six or seven! I don't know!
Where's Khalil?
In his room. I don't know.
I don't know what's going
on. I don't know anything.
Unlock the phone. Go ahead.
Okay. Just let me go, please.
All right, chill out. All right?
We're just going to park
your car down the street.
All right, you shouldn't have
been here. It's your fault.
Wait! No, no, no!
You already know. Come on, man.
Let's go. Don't forget the keys.
He's not in there.
Wait! Wait!
What are you doing?
Okay, now you're
going to do what I say
or I'm gonna slit
your fucking throat.
Do you understand?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You took his money.
Where is it at?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Where is it at? Tell
me where it's at!
There's no money here.
What do you think, I
withdrew all that cash?
You can't do that!
Please, I'm going
to bleed to death.
Tell me where it's at
and I'll let you go.
There's nothing here! Go look!
You're crazy!
No, no, no, no, no.
I think you're lying, okay?
I'm going to count to three
and then I'm going
to slit your throat.
One.
There's really
nothing here. Okay?
Two!
There's no money here!
Three!
Okay, in the fridge.
There's cash in the fridge.
Can you breathe? Can you talk?
Call an ambulance.
I got you. Good, good.
You're all right.
Okay. Okay.
All right, where are your keys?
Give me your keys.
What?
I need your keys.
I need a doctor.
I know, I'm going
to get you a doctor
but I need your fucking
keys, all right?
What happened to him?
Did you kill him?
No.
Hey, stay awake. Okay?
I'm going to get
you to a hospital,
but I need your fucking
keys, all right?
What did we do? What happened?
Fuck.
Fuck! Shit!
I'm sorry.
Here, right?
Searching!
Go, go, go, go. LAPD!
Clear.
Got them?
Clear that room.
Clear.