There's a big gap.
It seems like the only route,
let's keep going.
You okay?
It's about right.
Can't ever be easy.
Okay.
- One.
- Be careful.
Two, three.
You okay? Okay.
Oh, my God.
You're better.
Okay.
- Shit!
- Whoa, you're good.
You're good, yeah? You're good?
- No.
- Okay, you've done way scarier than this.
Remember AJ Hackett, Snake Dike.
Stupid singing competition.
God, you married this sad sack,
for Christ's sake.
- Yeah? Okay.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
Come on, I caught you
That's my girl.
Ew, gross. You guys get a room.
There's comes Ethan Hunt.
Careful, H, there's loose rock
around the elbow.
Worry about your ropes, bitches.
I'm fine.
Try to keep on.
Taking your time there, hot-shot.
Hunter, you show-off.
Dan!
Hang on Dan, hold on, I'm coming.
Dan, are you okay?
Just hold on, I'm coming down.
Come on, come on. I can't make to it.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, Becky, Becky.
I just need a little more line,
can you uncut? Are you secure?
- Are you secure?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm secure.
Just uncut, and I'll be able
to swing to the rock.
- Okay.
- I think I can reach it.
Ready?
- Can you reach it?
- Just, just one second.
I think I can make it.
Hold on Dan, I'm almost there.
I just need more momentum.
Okay.
No!
Dan!
51 WEEKS LATER
Hey, this is Becky and Dan,
leave a message.
Hey, Becky, it's me.
Look, I've tried to console you
every way I know how.
But I... I can't help you
if you don't pick up the phone.
Sweetheart, I'm worried about you.
So whenever you stop
hating on me, I am here.
CREMATED REMAINS
DAN
Hey, what's up?
This is just a voicemail,
you've reached Dan.
Just leave a message
and I'll hit you back when I can.
Get it on for the the beep.
Hey.
I miss you.
Dad, what? Are you stalking me now?
No, I just don't know what else to do
because you're not answering your phone.
Take a hint.
I think this is getting
a little bit ridiculous.
Ridiculous?
You told me I shouldn't be so broken up
about him because he was an asshole.
No, I said that maybe he didn't belong
on this pedestal
that you were putting him up on.
That he wasn't this martyr
that you've been making him out to be.
This is how you console your daughter?
I just want you
to be able to move on with your life.
I don't wanna move on, I miss him.
Every day, I miss the way he looked at me.
I miss the way he made me feel.
- Sweetie.
- Don't.
Don't what?
What do you think you're doing, Becky?
- I'm getting away from you.
- You are not driving. Stop it.
Fuck off!
You don't get to talk to me like that!
Your mother and I,
we raised you better than that.
So, getting shit-faced
and pushing the people away that love you
is not gonna work.
All right, look, a horrible thing
happened to you.
But you have to start
living your life again.
All right? There's a whole big
wide world out there that needs you.
And believe it or not, I need you.
Let me give you a ride home.
I'd rather walk.
Let me ask you something.
If roles reversed,
if it had been you
that had fallen that day,
You think Dan is standing out here alone
drowning in booze, grief, sorrow,
whatever the hell this is.
He's not.
And you damn well know it.
Goddamn it, Becky, I need you to try.
Do you know what I need, Dad?
I need you to leave me alone.
Goddamn it.
DAN
The number you have called
has been disconnected.
No.
♪ She's my cherry pie ♪
♪ Cool drink of water,
such a sweet surprise ♪
♪ Tastes so good,
makes a grown man cry ♪
♪ Sweet Cherry Pie, yeah ♪
♪ She's my cherry pie
Put a smile on your face, ten miles wide ♪
- Hi.
- Hey.
You look...
- Awful.
- Yeah, like really freaking awful.
Come here.
So, what brings you back?
You're finally ready to rest?
I'll rest when I'm dead.
I have something that's planned,
and I need a partner in crime.
Look, your Dad called me a few weeks ago.
He didn't know who else to turn to.
And he said that you were in a bad place.
- He had no right to do that.
- He's worried about you.
It's coming up on a year,
he doesn't want you to be alone.
Look, the only thing that drives me
crazier than Dan's boxed ashes
collecting dust in there
is my best friend stuck in here with him.
So, I have something
that I wanna pitch you.
You're not gonna like it,
but just try to keep an open mind.
Look.
The B67 TV tower.
It's only a six hour drive from here.
I was planning
on climbing it this weekend
and I wanted to see
if you'd climb it with me.
I would be an adventure, like old times.
And you could scatter Dan's ashes on top.
I just... I haven't climbed since...
I get it.
But if you don't confront your fears
you are always going to be afraid.
What is it that Dan used to say?
Don't die if you wanna to live?
Or, keep living even if you're dying?
Shit, I feel like
I'm messing this pitch up.
No, I'm sorry, Hunter, I just... I can't.
It's like a "no,"
I can't do it. I'm sorry.
You're gonna be okay.
- I can't.
- Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
Morning, Princess.
What's wrong?
If you're scared of dying
don't be afraid to live.
That's what Dan used to say.
Let's do it.
Let's climb your stupid tower.
Oh my gosh, Becky baby, I'm so excited.
♪ She's my cherry pie ♪
♪ Cool drink of water,
such a sweet surprise ♪
I've never actually seen this video.
Shit, I was really ripped.
Yeah, you're awesome.
That is the Becky
that we need for this trip.
Holy shit, look at your beaming face.
Who is this in the photo with you?
I don't know, it's an old date.
- Who is it?
- Nobody, just give me my...
Hunter has a boyfriend.
It's nothing, just some guy.
Oh, that "some guy" sure knew
how to tickle your whistle.
DAD
Yo, what's up, guys?
Danger D, I'm back in the States, yo!
Super bad-ass.
Okay, in my defense,
I may act like a total dick on camera,
but it's worth it.
I get paid for this shit.
It's enough to keep me traveling,
and you know me,
I have to be doing dangerous shit
to keep my blood pumping.
So, I might as well wanna try this gig.
I'm just saying,
if you're gonna be a YouTuber,
Why not be yourself? You are awesome.
- Natural born click bait.
- No.
What we're doing here, this is click bait.
Excuse me?
Do you have somewhere
I could charge my phone.
Power ain't free, ma'am.
And do you know where the B67 TV tower is?
We can't find it on the map.
You don't need a map.
You see that light way up there?
This's your tower.
That's insanely high.
What's with the light, I thought you said
it was out of commission?
So aircraft can see it.
You know this was once
the tallest structure in the US?
And now it's just this old relic.
They're gonna tear it down this winter.
Becky?
Becky.
- What?
- Give me your phone charger.
What are you doing?
A very cool life hack.
Now I'm just gonna line up the prongs
with the elements in the lamp.
And...
How's that for a dumb YouTuber?
Hey, honey.
Did you sleep well?
I love you.
You're not gonna say it back?
I am saying it.
One, four, three.
I love you.
Hey, come on, Bex, the sun's up.
What's up "El Capitan"?
I don't know, but something's up,
Sports Illustrated.
Tits for clicks.
Are you live streaming?
No girl, We'll shoot now, post later.
Okay, I don't wanna be in it.
Hey, guys! Danger D here.
And I have somebody
very special for you to meet.
Say hello, Becky C.
Hi.
And we have something
totally bat-shit crazy for you guys today.
The B67 TV tower.
This bad boy is over 2000 feet tall,
and your home-girls are gonna
be climbing to the tippy tippy top.
But don't worry, Becky C,
because you're safe...
Watch out!
Holy shit!
Eight more lives remain.
NO TRESPASSING
DANGER OF DEATH
Shit.
Looks like we're walking from here.
- How far?
- I don't know.
Like a mile, maybe two-ish.
REMAINS
Damn, it's hot.
You'll cool down
once we get some air time.
We got enough water you think?
Water check, harnesses check.
Super bad-ass 4K drone check.
Selfie stick, only essentials.
Food?
No, I'll be back in time before lunch.
Oh, Jesus.
Holy shit, they're big.
It's still alive.
Get off of him!
Hey! Shoo! Shoo.
- Just go.
- Go.
Poor thing.
Pricks.
Survival of the fittest, right?
You'd do the same
if you were starving out here.
Feeling peckish.
- Hunter.
- What?
That's funny.
Holy shit, 300 likes.
Oh, wow.
350.
I wonder how many
of your followers are serial killers?
Holy shit.
Looks a lot bigger up close, right?
It is sick.
This is awful.
Hey, guys, Danger D here,
and we are at the foot
of the stomach turningly massive
fourth highest structure in the US.
We're gonna begin our grueling journey
within 1,800 foot ladder climb
inside a steel cage.
And then, after the cage we have
a 200-foot vertigo-inspiring mast
to the external ladder.
Your girls gonna be wide open
to the elements.
And then, beyond that,
we have the precipice, the ledge,
the top of the world.
Hunter.
I'm sorry, I can't do it.
Babe, of course you can.
No, I really can't, I'm like...
I'm petrified, and I'm shaking.
I'm here.
Take a breath.
After Dan died,
I was afraid of my own. Shadow.
But I pushed through.
I overcame the fear, I took control.
Do not let this fear consume you.
Come at it head on and kick its ass.
If you can beat it, you can beat anything.
And I am right here
beside you the whole time.
You are so much stronger
than you think you are.
So shut your shit, and let's do this.
God, Hunter, you know that's the kind
of shit you should be posting on Instagram.
Come on.
Damn it, this is so cool.
Holy shit. Look at this.
Damn it, Hunter,
you are such an asshole.
What are you getting us into?
Don't worry.
We've got 50 feet of rope between us
We are clipped in and we're all good.
Okay.
One leg at a time
and let me know if you have to rest.
Okay. Okay.
See? It's easy.
Sure.
You're doing a great, come on!
You okay?
No.
You're doing a great, come on.
Hunter?
- Hunter?
- Yeah?
Can we rest a moment? I need a drink.
Of course.
The skylines mean we're half way up.
Perfect spot.
Do you wanna do something crazy?
What?
Half way up, that means
we've climbed about a 1,000 feet.
So, we've climbed the height
of the Eiffel Tower.
Please don't say shit like that, Hunter.
There's the motel, and the diner.
Now way, looks like a little toy town.
Let's just get this over with.
Yeah.
Come on, catch up.
That's it, Becky, you're doing amazing.
Come on.
Come on, Becky.
Okay.
This is the end of the internal ladder.
Each step at a time, okay? You got this.
The next two hundred feet is external.
I'm not gonna lie
it's gonna get a little bit crazy
when we're out of the cage
in the open, but don't panic.
Shit.
Hunter?
Hunter? Hunter?
Becky, you gotta come up, it's so sick.
Okay.
Hunter?
Out here, it's just like 200 feet more.
That's all.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
Just look up, only up.
You're doing great. You got this.
Okay.
Yeah, you're killing it.
You okay?
Remember, only look up.
What the hell are we doing?
Hey, stop over thinking.
How?
I don't know, concentrate on something else,
like, sing a nursery rhyme or some shit.
Okay, okay.
♪ Ring-a-ring-a-rosies,
a pocket full of posies ♪
♪ A tissue, a tissue, we all fall down ♪
I wouldn't have picked that one.
Wow.
Okay, Bex, this is gonna look
a little bit worse than it is.
What the hell, Hunter?
Let's just go back down.
Becky, if I let you
go back down, fear wins.
And I'm not going to let that happen.
It's okay, Bex.
It's okay.
I've got your weight.
Thanks, okay.
Okay.
Reach with your arm.
Okay, smooth our sailing to the top now.
You've got this.
I actually really do hate you, Hunter.
Hey, does this ladder feel a little slack?
Stop, you dick, Hunter!
Sorry.
What was that?
Come on, we're almost there
- Come on.
- Okay.
Becky, you're not gonna believe this,
you gotta pull up here.
I'm coming.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Hunter.
Hey, trust me.
Okay, okay.
Becky.
I'm here, oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
We did it, Bex.
I knew you could.
Here we go!
On top of the goddamn world.
Do you want to try?
Shit, Hunter, stop.
Just focus on getting a good shot.
I didn't wear this stupid bra for nothing
No.
No, Hunter.
Fly it around.
Take your time.
Okay, oh my God.
How did it look?
Insane. Insane. Crazy.
Let's get this bad boy back.
Holy shit, so sick, dude.
Okay, now the ultimate, Bex, your turn.
What? No.
Do you wanna kick fear in the dick or not?
No, no, Hunter.
The old Becky would have done it.
- Just saying.
- Dude.
Here, I'll hold your hand
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Shit.
Come on, come on.
You can do this.
You can do it.
Okay, okay.
I got you.
Okay.
You can trust me.
- Okay.
- I've got you, Bex.
Oh, my God.
Careful over the ledge.
Take it easy.
Okay. I've got you. I've got you.
Okay.
Open your eyes.
Look up.
Okay, just one more.
Come up.
Oh my God, I did it.
You did it, you idiot.
Yes.
- Look, look how amazing these are.
- Oh my God.
Next time you are ever afraid of anything
I want you to look at these,
And know that you have nothing
to be afraid of.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You know I'm proud of you.
Dan would be too.
Yeah.
Okay, okay, it's time.
You and I, we're one, Dan.
And whenever I needed to laugh
you'd told me one of your shit jokes.
And whenever I needed
a shoulder to cry on it was yours.
And now you're gone and uhm...
I don't feel whole anymore.
I miss you, just so much and...
I love you.
Goodbye, Dan.
Hey.
Sorry.
I just didn't expect
it to tip me like that.
Yeah.
It's been so far away for so long.
It just didn't really feel real
until then.
Come on.
Let's get back down on Earth, okay?
I don't know about
you but I really need to pee.
I needed to pee
since we passed the Eiffel Tower.
You okay?
Okay, home time.
Home time.
- Harnesses?
- Harnesses.
Think of the ice cold beers
waiting for us.
Oh, stop.
I've got you.
Okay, slowly.
Okay, I'm just gonna sit here.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Hunter!
No!
Oh my God, oh my God, holy shit!
- Don't let down!
- No, I've got you.
Hunter!
Oh, God, please don't let go off me.
Don't let go.
Bex?
I've got you, Bex.
I can see the ladder.
I've got you.
I just died almost.
Oh, my God.
- Did that really just happen? Oh, my God.
- Jesus Christ.
I wish we'd filmed that.
You're here.
Let's get back on the ground
before I actually peed myself.
Yeah.
Okay, take two.
Okay.
Oh, no.
The ladder, it's gone.
Hunter, how are we gonna get down?
- Shit.
- Please tell me there's a way to get down.
There's nothing on the pole
I can get a foothold on.
No.
- Oh, no.
- No, no, no.
There must be something.
No, shit, I don't have a signal.
I don't get it either.
I'm sure there's something.
I'm sure it's just really spotty up here.
No, we're too freaking high,
there's no signal up here.
It'll be okay.
Freaking out is not gonna help anything
right now, so just take a breath.
We're stuck on the pizza-size platform
in the middle of nowhere., Hunter.
Becky, freaking out
is not gonna help anything.
It's not gonna help, okay? It's okay.
- I'm sure we can...
- Wait, Hunter, Hunter, look at this.
Oh, my God.
Binoculars, that's amazing.
Okay.
We have a flair.
- Okay.
- This is great.
OK, great.
Oh, shit, our bag is down there.
Oh, man, our water is in there.
Shit, we're gonna die of thirst.
No, no.
We don't have water, that is how
you die when you're stranded.
The noise, the noise that this thing made
when it crashed,
there is no way nobody heard that.
I am sure that there are like
multiple calls to 911 as we speak.
Do you really think so?
Yeah.
Yeah, the cavalry is coming, okay?
We just have to wait.
Okay. Okay.
Holy fuck.
- What, what?
- Becky, your leg, oh, my God.
What the hell? I didn't even notice this.
Whoa.
Give me your leg, let's do a tourniquet. ♪
- It really hurts.
- Are you okay? I know, I'm sorry.
- Can you warn me first?
- Okay.
- Count to three or something.
- Okay, one, two, sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I know.
- Oh, man.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, I mean, I'm like okay, it's like...
I really need to pee.
- Just go.
- No.
- No, it's fine, I can hold it.
Just getting comfortable.
Can you go any any further?
It's like spraying.
- Okay, careful over the edge.
- I'm trying.
Stop looking at me.
Oh, God, that's a relief.
I'm just grateful you didn't need to shit.
Okay, we should find a way
to get comfortable
cause I think
we gonna be up here for a while.
All right?
All right.
Do you really think someone's coming?
One million percent.
Hey, Danger D, what's happening, guys?
I'll tell you what's happening, Becky C.
We are stuck at the top
of a 2,000-foot tower
with no way out.
And I shot some of the best
goddamn footage of my life
and no way to upload it.
That's what worrying you
about the situation?
It's quite ironic.
Don't worry, you'll still be famous
if you fall.
As the girl who died taking a selfie,
now that is ironic.
I would like to be remembered
for my life, not my death.
Thank you very much, #life over death.
#beckyisadickhole
Hashtag, Hunter says she's doing
this YouTube thing for the money,
but really I think
she's just a like-whore.
- It's not like that.
- Okay, what is it like then?
Come on, show us who you are,
show us Shilo Hunter.
Tell us why you vlog.
Okay, firstly, you're an asshole.
Yeah.
Secondly,
And this is gonna sound stupid
but I do this because of Dan.
What happened, it just made me realize
that life is fleeting.
And I want to spread that message
that life is short, too short
so you gotta use every moment,
you gotta do something
that makes you feel alive.
That was amazing.
Wow, I mean, I told you
you should just be yourself.
That was really great.
Should I kill Danger D?
I'll help you bury the body.
Oh, shit, there's like an old
RV thing down there.
Can I see?
Just past the gate, a little over.
Yeah, that looks abandoned.
It's been five hours,
if anyone called 911 they'd be here by now.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Hold on, Becky,
we don't get service up here,
but we definitely did down there,
remember?
Remember, I got all those likes?
Shit.
Okay.
Okay, so we don't know
at what point we lost service,
maybe it was just up here
because of some like interference
with the broadcast antenna.
I think you're definitely
onto something, Hunter.
Okay, we have 50 feet of rope.
- We can try to fish for coverage.
- Yeah.
I just need something to secure this with.
- My hair tie.
- Yeah, perfect.
Okay.
Can you message emergency services?
I don't think so,
but I have over 60,000 followers.
Okay.
Help us, stuck on B67 tower, call 911.
It's ready to post.
We should hear it when it sends.
Come on, come on.
Okay.
Let me see if I can get it lower.
Just be careful.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Come on.
That's the end.
- I didn't hear anything.
- I didn't either.
I don't think it posted.
Okay, maybe I can get it lower.
What do you mean...
I've got it. I've got an idea.
Careful, Hunter.
I feel solid.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- Shit.
You're full of shit, oh, my God, Hunter.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
Careful, shit.
I can not hear anything no thing
Okay, you need to come back up.
Shit.
I got it.
Did it post?
No.
- What do we do now?
- I don't know.
Wait, hold on. We know
there's a signal at the base, for sure.
Yeah.
What if we just drop the phone...
But what if my phone
just shatters into a million pieces?
Not if we reenforce it somehow
so it doesn't, like the egg drop challenge.
Yeah, okay, shit.
We just need something to put in it.
Yeah.
This...
It's melded on.
My shoe is too clumsy.
- Your shoe?
- Yeah, perfect.
Okay, got it.
We need some padding.
Can we use your sock?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
We still need something more substantial.
Oh, Hunter, your push-up bra.
That is more substantial.
- Yeah.
- I'm trying to get this thing off anyway.
Thank you, VS.
Okay.
Hope it's strong enough.
Shove it in, okay.
Okay.
Here comes nothing.
- Did it work?
- I don't know, I can't tell.
Do you see anything?
No, nothing.
Don't worry.
They're coming.
Holy shit, there's a freaking guy.
- What?
- Oh, my God, yes!
And a dog too.
Hey, hey, help us!
Up here!
Look, I sent you the check, man, come on.
I need that...
Up here, boy.
Parker, come on, boy.
No no, no.
Shit.
Let's go
Goddamn it, they're getting away.
Parker?
He saw the shoe.
Hey, up here!
- Hey!
- Look up!
No, no, no, turn around.
- Turn around, where are you going?
- Shit.
Shit, shit.
Help!
Wait, wait, do not fire the flare.
He's not looking.
This might be our only chance.
No, no, no, he stopped looking.
Wait, hold on, there's somebody by the RV.
He's setting up a grill or some shit.
And we'll fire the flare when the sun
goes down, in like an hour.
We've only got one shot at this.
Oh, damn.
What?
They're making ribs.
- Oh, no.
- And they have a really cold beer.
Stop.
These guys are definitely a couple.
Dirty weekend away.
I'm jealous.
Hey, they're finishing up.
It's now or never, fire the flare.
Is it dark enough?
Uhuh.
Okay.
- Shit.
- Shit, what the hell. Why is it not firing?
I fired it, I cocked it,
but maybe there's a safety here...
Shit, okay, they're going in,
you have to do the flare now.
- I'm trying.
- Get it to go.
Okay, I got it, I got it.
Hey, Randy, come check this shit out.
Okay, give me your phone.
Okay.
Hey, sons of bitches, out here!
Holy shit, check this out.
Up here!
They're looking at us.
- What?
- They can see us.
Oh, my God!
Shit, oh, my God, let me see. Let me see.
Oh my God, they're coming.
Holy shit, they found the car.
They found our car, they found our car.
They have a crowbar.
They probably can open the gate.
- Okay.
Wait, what the hell?
Wait, what's going on?
They stopped.
- What?
- Quit chatting, open the freaking gate!
No.
No, what the hell?
They stealing my freaking car.
- What?
- No, you sons of bitches!
- No!
- You asshole, what the hell?
- No.
- I have to see this.
Oh, my God.
- No!
- Assholes!
Okay, new rule.
If somebody falls off the tower
they bring the cell phone with them.
And call for help on the way down.
And maybe post that video.
I'm kidding.
Yeah, my leg, I could eat Aspirin
like Skittles right now.
Yeah, looks like
it's getting a little funky.
You could use some washing, here.
Sorry.
We'll just keep it wrapped up.
What's wrong?
Dan could never say
the words "I love you."
143.
Becky, I...
How long?
Four months.
It was a huge mistake.
I'm sorry, I am so, so sorry.
For sleeping with my husband
or me finding out about it?
For falling in love with the same guy.
Who made the move?
- We were both super drunk.
- Who?
He did.
But it was a huge, huge mistake, Bex.
No.
Mistake is a kiss or a one-night stand.
You said you'd loved him, so...
It got out of hand.
I tried so hard not to
but I fell for him.
He listened to me, he was...
He was just different than every other
douche bag that I've ever dated.
And I had never felt that way before.
And then you asked me
to be your maid of honor
and it all hit me like a ton of bricks
how messed up this all was.
I loved him but...
But I love you more so I ended it.
It was just so hard
seeing you guys together.
And after Dan died, I...
I just didn't have the strength
to be there for you.
To be strong enough for you, so...
So I ran away.
And now you hate me and I don't blame you.
And now we're stuck
on this stupid freaking tower
in the middle of freaking nowhere,
and it's all my fault.
I am so, so sorry.
What's that?
I set it when we dropped
the phone down yesterday.
It's been 24 hours.
I think its time to accept that either
your 60,000 followers don't give a shit
or your phone is down there
in a million pieces.
Okay, well, we've got
one more shot, your phone.
Yeah, no padding this time though,
even less of a chance.
And if this fails
we really don't have any hope.
How long till we die of thirst?
It's just killing me that our water
is just right down there in that bag.
Yeah, with the drone.
We could have used that
to get help.
We could have flown it back to our motel
with a good old-fashioned note.
Hey, maybe I can get it.
What do you mean?
You said it was too smooth, no footholds.
Yeah, but when I hung
my cell down yesterday
I think the rope
was long enough to reach it.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I seriously think I can get it.
Hunter, I don't think this is a good idea.
Becky, I don't think we have a choice.
Every hour that passes the weaker we get.
Besides, maybe I get lucky and I'll fall.
Hunter.
Be careful.
I'm sorry, Bex.
I love you.
Okay.
Hunter, are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, all good.
Okay.
Hunter, be careful.
Shit.
I can't quite reach it.
Just come back up and we'll tap it lower.
Come on.
Shit.
I think I can drop myself lower.
What?
What the hell are you doing, Hunter?
Hunter?
Shit.
I think I can swing to it.
Hunter, no, Hunter.
Come back up.
Hunter, no!
Hunter!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Is there a way down?
No, the ladder ripped all the way off.
Water.
Oh, my God.
Wait, Hunter,
how are you gonna get back on the rope?
Shit.
Can you reach it?
♪ Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ Humpty Dumpty had a great fall ♪
Shit.
You okay?
Yeah, I have an idea.
Okay.
I'm gonna try to hook it on with this.
And then we're gonna work together
to pull me up, okay?
That's amazing, that's
some good MacGyver shit right there.
Come on, please, come on.
Please, come on.
You did it!
Okay. Okay.
I'm gonna jump onto this.
I'm gonna need your help to pull me up.
I think I'm ready, Bex.
Okay.
Okay, come on, come on
Come on, you can do it.
Shit.
Hunter, are you okay? You okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Let's do this fast and quick, Becky.
- We'll work together to pull me out.
- Okay.
I climb, you pull, okay?
Okay, now.
I can almost reach the ladder.
Almost there, Bex.
Okay.
Becky, I landed on the bag.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
I hurt my hands, real bad,
I don't think I can climb.
You're gonna have to pull me up, okay?
Okay. Okay.
I got you.
Shit.
No, are you okay?
Yeah.
I thought you died there.
I'm not going anywhere, Bex.
Yeah, that was scary.
We should ration it.
Yeah, you're right.
Is there food in there?
No, it's just your cherry lip balm.
I don't think you can eat that.
Okay, it's getting dark.
I think it's now or never on that drone.
I think we need...
We need to write a note.
Okay, the receipt from the diner.
Pen, do you have a pen?
Eyeliner in here.
Aren't you glad I brought makeup now?
Help.
Stuck on top of B67 tower. Call 911.
Okay.
Yeah, perfect.
See that?
That's the road where we almost got
wiped out. It leads to the motel.
Let's do this while we still have light.
Okay.
Okay, just keep it straight
and follow the line of the rode...
Okay.
Okay, we're almost past the gate.
- Oh my God, no, no.
- What?
- The battery, it's running out of juice.
- Shit.
Hit "retrieve." Has it gone too far?
- Is it gonna make it?
- There's no chance.
- Are you sure?
- It's not even at the gate.
Oh, shit, it's falling.
Hit "retrieve," hit "retrieve".
Okay.
- It's coming back.
- Fly it high.
Give it your best shot
to get it back to us.
Come on, just get it higher,
higher, higher.
- Just get it higher.
- I'm trying.
We'll grab it when it gets close.
Okay.
Okay, grab it, Bex. Get it!
Nice, great job.
We have a charger,
but we don't have any power.
Maybe just turn it off
and once it's rested it'll have more juice?
It's never gonna be enough, Hunter.
What are we gonna do?
Hey, we're not gonna panic.
We're gonna stay calm.
We're gonna figure it out.
Okay, there's gotta be a way.
Are we gonna die?
No, we're gonna be okay.
Hunter? Hunter?
Where are you? Hunter?
Hunter?
Hunter, where are you?
Hunter.
Hunter?
Becky, it's okay,
you just had a bad dream.
You're nice and safe.
Two thousand feet up
in the middle of nowhere.
I have an idea.
How to charge the drone.
Your dumb life hack.
Becky, you're freaking genius.
I think it's light enough now.
Let's do it.
Okay, it's a standard bulb fitting,
it's gonna be hot.
It's 30 feet
but it's gonna feel like a thousand.
- Is your leg okay?
- Yeah.
It smells, but it doesn't
hurt anymore, it's fine.
Okay.
You can do this.
- Yeah.
Keep going, Becky.
You can do this, Becky.
I can't.
It's okay, it's okay.
You can do it, Becky.
You got it.
It's okay, it's just like pole dancing.
Okay, "Cherry Pie."
♪ She's my cherry pie ♪
♪ Cool drink of water,
such a sweet surprise ♪
♪ She's my cherry pie ♪
♪ Cool drink of water,
such a sweet surprise ♪
♪ She's my cherry pie ♪
Becky's my cherry pie.
Yes.
Okay. Okay.
Yeah.
You did it, my cherry pie!
Okay.
- Okay.
- Remember it's hot.
Okay. Okay.
Be careful.
Okay, just think back to the diner.
You'll gonna wanna align
the prongs of the charger
with the element in the bulb socket.
I don't think it's long enough.
I think the back prong doesn't reach.
Okay, you're gonna need something small
and metal to carry the current, like...
Like a screw or something
you can jam in there.
- There isn't anything.
- Jesus.
It's working, it's freaking working.
Holy shit, my hero.
Okay, we're gonna need a full charge.
I don't know, it just has four lights.
Okay, we have to charge it all the way,
give ourselves the best shot.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah, I got this.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hang in there, Bex.
Passed half way.
Here about me
It's okay, it's okay,
Becky, you've got it.
Three lights.
Come on, Becky, you're so close.
Get away from me!
You did it.
Jesus, I'm so proud of you.
Why didn't you catch the bag?
Babe, you're okay?
We need to fly that thing
when the motel is the busiest.
Check out, 10 a.m, just a couple of hours.
Yeah, he was right about Dan,
he was just trying to help me.
And I was so horrible to him.
If there was anyone
I could text it'd be him.
Just to tell him I'm so sorry.
I love him.
I'm tapping outta here.
Stay with me,
try to keep your mind occupied.
Tell me something, something
that you and your dad used to do together.
We would watch wrestling.
WWE.
Yeah, I forgot you guys were into that.
Yeah.
We both like it, you know.♪♪
He always said I'd be world champion
with my fighting spirit.
I always felt so close to him
when we were watching it.
Name some of your favorite wrestlers.
Stone Cold - Steve Austin.
The Rock.
What was Cactus Jack's name
when he was wearing a mask?
Mankind.
Wait, I thought you said
you didn't watch it.
I didn't.
Keep going, you need to stay awake.
Batista.
Sub. T
Okay, it's check out time.
Here it goes.
Just keep that shit straight,
follow the line of the road.
Come on, you son of a...
We've passed the point of no return.
How's the battery? Should I retrieve?
No, keep going.
Come on, come on, just follow the road.
Oh, shit.
It's gonna work.
Oh, God.
No. Screw your truck, get the drone!
Get it!
No, no, come back.
No, no.
No, come back.
Come back.
No.
Fuck, no!
Is this a storm?
It's kinda beautiful from up here.
I can't survive another night.
Becky, don't talk like that.
I just want to sleep.
You can't sleep.
The vultures, they can smell your leg.
They're waiting for you to give up
so they can attack.
Survival of the fittest.
You need energy, we should eat something.
What?
We're 2,000 feet up
in the middle of the desert
There's no food up here.
There is always something.
It's hopeless.
Let's send another message.
We can pad the cell better this time.
With what?
Give me your shoe.
- I can't.
- Why?
It's not up here, is it?
What?
It's down there.
It's on your foot.
Yes.
But I am...
down there, remember?
I fell.
You can't have the shoe
because I didn't catch the bag.
I bled out.
You didn't really think your scrawny ass
could pull me up, did you?
You pulled the bag up.
I guess you were just too afraid
to realize that you were up here
all alone.
Hi Dad, I wanted you to know that I...
I found my fight again.
Please leave your message.
I wanna live, I wanna go home.
But I'm not gonna make it.
You were right about everything and I...
I'm sorry, Dad.
Becky, call me when you're ready,
I'm here for you, Dad.
By the time you see this
I'll be gone.
I love you.
Thus
You need energy, you should eat something.
Survival of the fittest.
I can pad the cell better this time.
Give me your shoe.
Hunter.
God, I love you.
Help, stuck on the B67 tower,
I love you Dad, Becky.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, but I really have to
make sure this gets through.
God, God, I'm sorry.
You can't walk here.
Becky, Becky?
No, no.
Dad? Dad? Dad.
Jesus, I thought that was you.
Dad, I love you.
And I'm so sorry.
It's okay, I just want you to be okay.
I am, you know. I'm gonna be okay, really.
Let's go home.
Life is fleeting.
Life is short, too short.
So you gotta use every moment.
You have to do something
that makes you feel alive,
and that shit,
that would spread that message
far and wide.