YUMMY MEAT
Nikuko is my mom.
Drink up, fellas!
What's your height, Nikuko?
Hey, don't ask a lady
questions like that!
She's 151 cm tall.
67.4 kg light.
In number puns,
that's "No work, no fun."
March 4th? That's "Sounds swell."
8812?
"Gimme a leaf."
Right?
She loves number puns.
When you "MINGLE" with a "BEAST"
you get "SLY."
When "YOU" get too "BIG"
you get "STINKY."
She loves kanji puns even more.
Nikuko grew up in a small town,
and made the big move to Osaka at age 16.
She started working at a bar.
That's where she met
The Casino Dealer.
What a classy guy!
But when he screwed up at work,
he skipped town, leaving Nikuko
to deal with his "huge" debt.
She worked herself to the bone,
but she paid the debt off.
Then she moved to Nagoya.
She was 27 years old,
and all worn out.
That's where she met
The Barman.
He was working his way through college.
That sounds tough.
Of course, he was no student.
But Nikuko fell for it.
He went through her money
like water.
She only caught him cheating
during his eighth affair.
Leaving everything behind,
Nikuko headed for Yokohama.
She was 30 years old,
and all worn out.
That's where she met
The Married Office Worker.
He parts his hair?
What a stand-up guy!
Of course, he started
borrowing money from Nikuko.
It was for his divorce.
Love you!
At first, he needed 500,000 yen.
Then he needed more.
When it reached three million,
Nikuko learned his wife was
pregnant again.
Furious, she raced to his house.
But when she saw the kid's bike,
she walked away from it all.
The kid hasn't done anything wrong.
Nikuko has the sweetest of hearts.
Then she headed to Tokyo.
She was 33 years old,
and all worn out.
She started working at a deli.
No more bars for her.
She wanted to steer clear of shady men.
But then she met
The Novelist.
He looks troubled!
It turned out this guy really was
an aspiring novelist.
But he never wrote a line.
All he did was buy books
with Nikuko's money.
But unlike the other guys,
he never fooled around with other women.
Nikuko cared a great deal for
The Novelist.
And I didn't hate him
as much as the others.
What I liked most was
the books he bought.
My life was pretty miserable,
but they provided
a faint source of light.
For the first time ever,
I started to paint
a vague picture of the future.
I thought the three of us might
live here together forever.
- But one day, he suddenly disappeared.
- I'M GOING HOME TO DIE
Nikuko panicked.
We leapt on a northbound train,
hoping that's where he lived.
"MYSELF," "HEART" and "CHICKEN."
That's how you write "WORRY."
She ate four meals on the train.
Four whole meals!
Then we arrived in some port town.
It was snowing.
She was a giant matryoshka
looking for a lost man,
dragging around an eight-year-old girl
in the middle of a blizzard.
The rumors spread quickly.
It was such a small town.
She never found him.
When "RAIN" needs a "BROOM"
you have "SNOW."
She was 35 years old,
and all worn out.
She decided to live here.
That's the story of "The Meaty Lady,"
my mom Nikuko.
FORTUNE
FAVORS
NIKU
(MEAT)
FORTUNE FAVORS NIKU
FORTUNE FAVORS LADY NIKUKO
What's that?
Gee whiz.
Go beyond!
Morning!
What's the time? Morning?!
Kikurin!
Wake up! Kikurin!
You gotta eat school
and go to breakfast!
Huh?
You gotta eat school...
And go to breakfast...
Hm?
Something's not right.
You gotta eat breakfast,
and go to school,
- then eat some more.
- Nikuko.
Morning.
Morning, Kikurin.
That's actually a sad song.
It's ready!
Bless this food!
- That was yum.
- Finished already?
- I eat meals like that for breakfast!
- That was breakfast!
- Isn't that the saying?
- Oh, I nearly forgot.
- Eat breakfast for breakfast...
- Sign this for me.
Sign it? Why?
It's for my swimming lessons.
We need parental permission.
Okey doke!
I eat permission slips for breakfast!
Even when I'm full.
Not there, Nikuko!
What?
That's where my name goes!
Student Name, Misuji Kikuko
Oh no. I screwed up.
I'll have to write your name
where it says "Parent."
Then I'll add some arrows like this.
We use different kanji, but we're
both called "Kikuko." What a mess.
Go get 'em, honey.
See you later.
MISUJI KIKUKO KIKUKO
(aka KIKURIN) (aka NIKUKO)
Our family name looks like a girl's name.
It's like three women live here.
Hey, cut it out!
Maria!
Kikurin! Morning!
Hi. Did you wait long?
Nope! Let's go, Kikurin!
Don't run on our bridge!
- Nakajima.
- Here.
Nogami.
Manaka.
Misuji.
Misuji...
MISUJI
This is misuji.
It's the tastiest part of
the oyster blade.
- Yummy!
The Misujis are eating misuji!
Old Sassan's misuji is so darn tasty...
Stop it!
Why am I daydreaming about
"The Meaty Lady"?
- Everything's a mess.
- PERMISSION TO SWIM I'M THE MOM!
It's too much!
Sassan!
Nikuko! See you at the grill later.
You betcha!
UWOGASHI GRILL HOUSE
YUMMY MEAT
Rock paper scissors!
Ready, go!
Kikurin.
- Yosshi.
- Hozumi.
- Akechi.
- Risa.
- Sayaka.
- Nakaji.
Hmm.... Maria.
Hear that pause before she chose Maria?
The girls in my class play basketball
during our lunch break.
Even the girls who don't play watch,
cheering along on the sidelines.
I think nobody does their own thing
because they don't want to be
left out of the circle.
Come on.
Time to go back.
What a goody-goody.
I'm definitely right!
I'm not so sure.
I am!
There's no doubt about it!
Kikurin! You know it's true.
Like I said. I don't.
Come on! Don’t lie!
- Kanemoto definitely likes you!
- What do you mean?
That's why she always picks you first!
- But they do rock paper scissors.
- Yeah! That's wrong too.
It's totally unfair!
You want to play on Mori's team, right?
Well, I don't care which team,
as long as I get to play.
Either way, ever since you
transferred here, I've been...
Dammit.
It's those dumb boys again.
They're here every day.
I bet they're sweet on you.
Ew!
That's gross!
Way too gross!
See you, Maria.
Hey!
Leave us alone!
Kikurin! Bye bye!
MIZUKAWA SHRINE
Excuse me, young lady.
I am absolutely full of history.
Would you fancy some details?
"The Sexy Shrine" talks too much.
I have no idea why it's called that.
I could smell summer in the sea air.
- Want some more meat?
- Two plates of loin, please.
- Loin, two plates!
- Loin!
Here's your second round of rice, boys.
You sure know how to eat.
- More, please!
- Wow!
Kikurin!
Hi... everyone.
Hi there!
Kikurin! Over here!
This table's free!
- Loin's ready!
- Right up!
Meat, meat, meat!
Here's the loin meat
you couldn't wait for!
The All-Seeing Dalicia's
Special Psychic Show!
- Welcome to the show...
- Hey, Kiku.
Tonight's staff special.
Fried noodles with meat!
Thank you!
- Like it, Kiku?
- It's great!
Will I see, or not?
I see all!
- You did wrong in a past life!
- I did?
You killed sacred white snakes.
- I don't recall that...
- What a sucker!
Of course not.
It was your past life!
What will happen now I'm cursed?
- Your forehead will fester!
- She's too much.
You have such a round forehead.
It's going to fester.
How can I stop the festering?
- Sushi.
- Sushi?
Kikurin.
That foreign fortune teller is on TV
so much these days.
You're right.
She's on all the time.
Her name's Dalicia.
She's always right.
She says the craziest things.
Before you got here she drew
a picture of some guy's dead father.
It took a few days,
so they had to edit it,
but when she finished,
it looked just like him!
- It was a collage!
- Why?
It was exactly like him.
No way. A collage? Days later?
That sounds shady.
- I bet she sees everything.
- I bet she doesn't.
What have you been reading lately?
Salinger.
Salinger?
That sounds like a superhero ranger.
I bet the print's small.
You're so smart.
Kikurin, you're so smart!
She's smart and cute!
Thanks a bunch.
- Way to go, Nikuko!
- It's "Kikuko," actually.
- Nikuko!
- Coming!
- Can I get you more meat?
- Your fates are sealed!
In your past lives!
Past lives...
If we really do have past lives,
I wonder what Nikuko's was like.
She has such a hard life now.
Did she do something that bad?
Good night!
THIS IS THE LAST ROLL!
Nikuko is bad at starting things off.
It's all stuck together.
I don't know which way to peel!
Try sticking tape onto it?
Her problem isn't just with objects.
She's bad at starting relationships too.
She doesn't know what she needs,
let alone the needs of others.
PROBLEM CHILD
People get annoyed with her,
make fun of her, or they deceive her.
Wherever she goes, she's 100% Nikuko.
I'd like to ask Dalicia.
If she really can see all,
what did Nikuko do in her past life?
And I also want to ask
what kind of life awaits us.
Some girls in my class
got their periods.
Some wear bras too.
My body's the same as it's always been.
I'm scrawny, my chest is flat,
and my legs look like twigs.
Still, I like my body.
I hope my chest never grows,
and my period never starts.
THREE FOR 150 YEN
THREE FOR 180 YEN
This would drive Nikuko wild.
No way!
She'd get even meatier.
Hey!
What color are your shoes?
Black.
Thought so!
Damn, that's scary!
From then on, I observed him
whenever I could.
But he never made any weird faces
while I was watching.
Huh?
The kid at the back?
The two laughing are
Matsumoto and Sakurai.
Behind them is Ninomiya.
Did he do something?
No, I was just wondering...
Oh? You're sweet on him?
Of course not.
I remember now.
Matsumoto, Sakurai,
and Ninomiya, right?
This was a first.
I'm not "sweet on him"
like Maria said,
but I think I'll keep an eye
on Ninomiya for a while.
Rock paper scissors!
- Kikurin.
- Yosshi.
- Hozumi.
- Akechi.
- Risa.
- Sayaka.
- Nakaji.
- Maria.
What's Maria's problem?
- Bye, Kikurin!
- Bye bye!
Dammit!
I'm a mess.
If I didn't know Nikuko,
I'd think it's a crime scene.
Uwogashi is closed today.
It's Nikuko's day off.
She probably sorted through the laundry,
hand-washed my gym clothes,
then started to prepare lunch,
but halfway through,
sleep got the better of her.
RICH AND MEATY
Nikuko.
Food's ready.
Wow! Meat spag?
I missed you!
Are you talking to me,
or the meat spag?
Bless this food!
I love your meat spag, Kikurin!
It's not me.
It's the can.
Then I love your can, Kikurin!
You're nuts.
What are we gonna do today?
What can we do?
It's pouring.
Who cares?
When else do we get the chance
to hang out?
What's wrong?
Got stuff to do?
Not really, but...
Perfect!
Wanna go see Penta?
- Why not?
- That penguin makes me sad.
And it's "Kanko," not "Penta."
How come?!
Penta is super cute.
Nikuko adores that penguin.
Even though she gets its name wrong.
Alright, let's go.
Yippee!
Penta, Penta, Penta!
SEXY MIZUKAWA SHRINE
Why are those monks pink?
You won't bump into any classmates.
There's no chance.
Kikurin, you say something?
Nope.
Everyone in town knows Nikuko.
"The cheery plump lady
who wound up living here."
She stands out in this little place.
What's more, she's my mom.
Such wonderful history, young lady.
Kikurin, you say something?
Nope.
I was relieved when the bus came.
Part of me had been wishing,
"I hope nobody from school sees me."
The next stop is Noda Housing Complex.
NODA HOUSING COMPLEX
Please be seated.
The next stop is The Aquarium.
THE AQUARIUM
Did Ninomiya really not notice me?
The rain stopped.
- "SUN" and "BLUE" make "SUNNY"
NEXT STOP: KOTOBUKI CENTER
- Hey Nikuko.
- What?
What's this "Kotobuki Center"?
Kotobu...?
Some kinda center, right?
Forget I asked.
One adult, one child.
Come on in.
You're a cutie.
Thanks.
The whole place is yours today.
Yippee!
Yay, yay, yay!
Which of us is the child?
KANKO
Death to you all!
Penta!
He's so cute!
Death to you all!
Hey, want to come over?
- Today?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, sure.
- Yippee!
I'm so glad you're coming!
I invited Mori, Yosshi, Sayaka,
and Akechi today too.
What's wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
You're so weird!
That's Mori's dream team.
That's life.
I don't wanna go.
I speak with Nikuko's accent when
I think out loud. What's with that?
Welcome back, Kikurin.
Look what I found.
Three for just 130 yen!
How cheap!
Yoshitoku makes great discounts.
They sure do, at Yoshitoku.
Kikurin, how was your day?
Ordinary.
Ordinary?
Ordinary is the best of all.
Come for dinner around 7.
I might go to Maria's.
Oh yeah?
You'll have dinner there?
But I might not go.
You won't?
Well, I dunno.
She invited you?
Don't wanna go?
It's not that I don't want to.
It's just...
If I go, I'll have to listen to Maria
badmouth Kanemoto.
Then she'll say I should
join Mori's basketball team...
I won't be able to say no.
Don't go then.
Say you caught a cold or something.
I'll do that.
If I feel bad, you'll call her for me?
No, it's cool.
I called her straight away.
Sorry Maria.
Don't be. I hope you're okay.
Get some sleep.
I will. Thanks.
I felt bad about making Maria worry,
but it was a weight off my shoulders.
Kikurin.
Got a second?
Kikurin, I'd like to ask you something.
What is it?
What do you think about Kanemoto?
What do I think?
It seems like
they made a decision yesterday.
How am I going to handle this?
She's good at sports.
I envy her for that.
That's not what I mean!
Do you like Kanemoto?
Like her?
Isn't she bossy?
Come to think of it,
I've never really talked to
the other girls before.
It was Kanemoto's idea to choose teams
when we play basketball.
- It was?
- It was!
And she only ever picks her favorites.
The others get left out.
Don't you feel bad for them?
Mori doesn't want to choose.
But she has to,
because Kanemoto forces her.
She does?
You wouldn't notice.
Because you're Kanemoto's favorite.
Next lunch break,
when she asks us to play,
we’re going to turn her down.
So Kikurin,
play with us instead!
But I...
Are you betraying me?
No, I just...
Then play basketball with us!
If we do it Kanemoto's way,
people will always be left out.
Kikurin!
Please!
I just...
Forget about it.
Let's go, Maria.
Fine.
Who wants to play with us?
Those who never get picked
can play too!
Uh-oh.
It's a chick fight!
So, who's coming?
Let's play.
Let's go!
Kanemoto didn't even flinch
under Maria's pressure.
She played with those who stayed.
I can't choose.
It's not right to leave people out,
but is what Maria's doing right?
I can't say it's wrong.
Even if I had a solid opinion,
I couldn't share it.
I just want to accept theirs,
and run away.
When I transferred here,
Maria was the first to talk to me.
She was kind, looked out for me,
and genuinely liked me.
I doubt she'll ever
walk home with me again.
SEXY MIZUKAWA SHRINE
I'm late! I'm late!
For a date I don't even have!
The world is a hazy white.
I spent seven years buried,
just to die aboveground!
Fried noodles!
Beef kebabs!
Frankfurters!
Kikurin!
What?
No summer kimono?
I couldn't be bothered.
What a waste!
You'd look great in one.
How true. You would.
You are so cute!
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah right!
Come on.
Come try your luck!
Come get it!
They both smell great.
There's Maria.
All by herself.
Isn't that her mom?
- Maria's so tacky.
- She's lame.
Maria ended up being
kicked out of Mori's group too.
She was probably too selfish,
and pushed too hard.
I wondered what I should do,
but I couldn't do anything.
I still had mixed feelings for her...
I'm coming!
Oh, Kikurin!
Hey!
Having fun?
Are you?
That's your mom, right?
Yeah.
- She keeps herself young.
- True.
You think so?
What an idiot!
- But you look nothing alike.
- True.
- You think so?
- Yeah. Nothing alike at all.
When Nikuko's drunk, she squints her eyes
and gets droopy eyelids.
Okay, let's see how
your okonomiyaki tastes.
What pressure!
If I don't like it,
I'm getting a refund.
She starts to slur her words too.
Oh no.
He's just her type.
This is how she always falls
for the dirtbags.
Does the summer heat make her
a pushover?
Nope.
She's a pushover all year around!
Misuji?
Ninomiya...
That's better.
I waited all that time,
just for this?
The new term started.
Mori's and Kanemoto's groups
went back to normal.
Only one student was left out.
It was Maria.
Ninomiya...
Misuji.
You know my name?
Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- Looking at this.
- You?
- I went shopping at Yoshitoku.
Oh.
"Batou Kannon"?
The Guardian of Horses.
- Why were you looking at it?
- Well...
It used to be closer to the beach.
The beach?
There was a tsunami,
ages ago.
Wow, right?
- How do you know that?
- I looked it up.
- I saw you on the bus before.
- Yeah, I know.
He knew?!
You went to the aquarium.
- Was that your mom?
- Yeah.
You look nothing alike.
Not one bit.
Where did you go that day?
Kotobuki Center.
- What's that?
- Beats me.
- What do you do there?
- I'm making a model.
- A model?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- My parents make me.
- They make you make a model?
- Yeah.
Why?
They say I need to
focus on something.
- What kind of model?
- Not telling.
It's a model of the thing
I care about most.
Why do you need to focus?
You know how I pull those faces?
Yeah, I noticed.
Like when you stick your lips out.
Yeah.
I can't stop doing that.
So, today's the day I go to the center.
Will you make your model?
Yeah.
Join me?
Just kidding.
- Are you going to walk?
- I have things to look at on the way.
Go beyond!
- When did you start doing it?
- I don't know.
I just did it.
I see.
I thought everybody did it.
I thought pulling faces was normal.
But that wasn't the case.
I think I know how it feels.
The truth is,
I've been imitating Ninomiya.
It feels great when you make a face.
It's more like
something I have to do.
I'll show you my secret place.
This way.
Your secret place?
Where exactly are we?
Everybody lives down there.
Isn't it amazing?
Everything looks like a toy.
You can see your home.
You know where I live?
Do those two know this place too?
Those two?
Oh, Matsumoto and Sakurai?
- Yeah.
- Nope.
This place is for me only.
Is that so?
Go beyond!
KOTOBUKI CENTER
Will they let me in?
It's cool.
Welcome to Kotobuki Center.
Please tap in with your card.
What is this? A robot?!
One moment, please.
Why does the robot sound just like
the aquarium guy?!
- Hello Ninomiya.
- Hi.
Is this a friend of yours?
- Hello.
You can wait in the classroom.
I could tell Ninomiya was showing off.
He'd been waiting to
show someone this place.
I'd want to show off too.
Are you close with
Matsumoto and Sakurai?
We've been in the same class
since Grade 2.
They're just always there.
Do they know you come here?
They do.
They do?!
So this isn't a secret?!
Things are screwed up
with the girls in my class.
How?
You know Maria?
She wears frilly clothes.
She's cute.
Seriously?!
She dresses like a princess,
and she's feminine.
It doesn't suit her!
She has no idea how she looks.
She doesn't even realize the other girls
diss her for those clothes.
They diss her? Poor thing.
She's the one who started it!
She did?
Maria wanted to be
the center of attention.
That's why she tried to divide
Mori and Kanemoto.
But in the end,
she was the one left out.
It sucks to be left out.
You two were close, right?
But Maria was the one
who badmouthed me first!
All because I didn't
go along with her plan.
What plan?
Like I said, she had a plan to become
the center of attention.
She badmouthed me,
then she laughed at me
on the bridge after school.
That's why...
That's when I realized.
She got what she deserved.
Nobody thought as badly
about Maria as me.
I had no idea I was so mean.
So mean, and so nasty...
Here you go, Ninomiya.
- Thanks.
- Let me know when you're done.
Misuji, check out my model.
It will blow you away.
I went to see her.
Maria cried.
We both apologized for
what we'd done.
My bad, honey.
Your honey is bad?
Done!
Your rice balls are way too big.
- The more the merrier!
- You're nuts.
The closer we got to autumn,
the bigger Nikuko got.
Then, when autumn finally arrived,
the late night phone calls began.
Nikuko yells,
even when she whispers.
But this time,
she actually kept it down.
Was it that okonomiyaki vendor?
The calls came Tuesday nights.
I saw a dream each week.
A dream, that wasn't a dream...
Or something like that.
But I saw them!
I can't wait for my packed lunch!
Today isn't "Packed Lunch Day."
It's "School Sports Day!"
I'm gonna kick butt!
SCHOOL SPORTS DAY
The next event is Gymnastic Formation.
Kikurin!
- Did you see a flash?
- Yeah.
That's an ultra C move!
Way to go, Kikurin!
You're so good!
As the boys fought the Cavalry Battle,
I searched for Ninomiya.
I secretly rooted for Ninomiya.
I wanted him to win
and pull a face!
What's that?
You were pulling a face.
- Yeah, it feels good.
- What?
You're loopy, Kikurin!
Again?
Ask before taking photos!
Hey Kiku,
you sure know how to run.
Kikurin's super good at sports.
My big race is coming up soon.
The Scavenger Hunt.
- Scavenger hunt?
- I'm gettin' butterflies.
What's wrong, Nikuko?
Those are mine.
Restroom!
Why take the rice balls?
You're way too nervous!
What's with her?
Kiku.
Dig in.
Thank you.
Wow.
This is like a textbook version of
"School Sports Day."
The next event is for parents.
The Scavenger Hunt.
All participants,
please gather at the gate.
Is everyone ready?
On your marks...
Oops. Sorry.
- Sorry.
- Let's try again.
Wait for it!
Sorry.
Nikuko!
Calm down!
On your marks...
Ready...
He finally got to shoot!
Watanabe's grandfather must find
a jacket!
Hotta's mother must find
reading glasses!
Misuji's mother must find...
a novel!
A novel?!
Novels are books!
Kikurin knows books!
Salinger?
Anybody got Salinger?
A novel! Kikurin! Salinger!
Madam!
Take this.
"The Pass"?
Thanks!
Thanks so much!
Thanks a bunch!
Nikuko!
You won last place!
Last place?!
A season yearned for never comes.
Everyone said this year's winter was odd.
It usually snowed from late November,
but the snow never came.
How's your mom doing?
She's doing fine. Great!
Oh, Kikuko! I saw your mom
walking around the other day.
Sorry about that.
No need to apologize.
Of course she walks around!
After the sports day,
Nikuko became a town celebrity.
You're back!
I am.
Guess what. The lady at Yoshitoku
asked how you were doing.
I'm a celeb now!
A celeb?
I'm not sure that's a good thing.
Why not?
You gotta make people notice you.
They say bad things about you too.
All the better.
They can call me
"The happy fat lady at the grill."
They can call you
"The pretty kid, so unlike her mom."
But I am Lady Nikuko,
and I love it!
I knew that face.
She had good news.
Was it the okonomiyaki vendor?
Kikurin, how was your day?
It was just an ordinary day.
Ordinary?
Ordinary is the best of all.
What's your idea of "ordinary"?
Ordinary goes like this.
You eat, poop, study, work,
bathe, then go to sleep.
And fart.
If that's your idea of an ordinary life,
- nobody in the world leads one.
- How come?
Because nobody can live such
a monotonous and uneventful life.
Is that how you'd describe our lives?
You call this "ordinary"?!
We eat, poop, study, work,
bathe, fart and sleep.
Then the whole world does.
I don't think so!
Some people have no food to eat.
Some have no place to live.
You sound like a teacher.
I saw it on TV!
Nikuko!
Eat this.
I give up.
Nikuko has no idea how I feel.
If it doesn't work out with the new guy,
we'll end up moving to the next town.
Would that happen to be
smoke dried tuna?
It's sweet potato.
You want some?
- What's up?
- I'm eating sweet potato.
Way out here?
What do you mean?
It's right next to our place.
The port's not next to your place.
Your place is next to the port.
Right.
Where's Nikuko?
Getting ready.
She'll leave soon.
Oh yeah?
She's put on more weight lately.
She's always eating.
Sassan...
Does her boyfriend come to the grill?
Does she have a man now?
Well, I don't want to know,
so I don't ask,
but she's been beaming
since the festival.
I thought she might be dating
that blonde guy.
Blonde guy?
What is he again?
A vendor, or something.
I don't really remember.
What a lie.
I remember clearly!
Doesn't ring a bell.
I haven't seen him.
Really? Then they must meet
somewhere else.
There's no need to hide it.
I don't think she has a guy.
Whatever. I don't mind.
Okay, gotta go.
Kiku.
Tonight's staff special
is going to be misuji.
What?
Misuji?!
Yummy!
He sometimes treats the regulars
to misuji.
It's tasty beyond compare.
I can eat a bowl like this
in one go!
This tastes so good!
What's the difference between
the name Misuji and a bridge?
One sounds like meat,
the other's where you meet.
I should've kept that to myself.
Maybe that joke was
a little undercooked.
Kikurin, you say something?
Nope.
- Like it, Kiku?
- It's unreal!
Consider it my early Christmas present.
Yay! Merry Christmas!
What's the difference between
a party at Uwogashi and Christmas?
One takes the cake,
the other needs a cake!
You guys are cold!
Did someone turn on the AC?
Maybe that was me.
Nikuko's in high spirits,
but I'm not quite in the mood.
I think I know why.
We might be leaving town again.
For some reason,
I had that vague sense of anxiety.
- Pull it together!
- I drank too much.
Can you make it?
Good night.
Nikuko, we're going!
I'm a baby so I can't walk...
No baby's as big as you!
What were you like as a kid?
- I was really frail.
- You're kidding.
It's true!
I slept all the time.
Then my pop died,
and my mom had to work.
Grandma took care of me.
- What was she like?
- She died.
- When?
- Junior high.
- I cried my eyes out.
- I bet.
She was like your mom, right?
Yeah, Mom got a boyfriend...
- I was so lonely!
- You're heavy!
But Grandma said she'd stay by my side
even after she died, so I was okay.
- I still am.
- How's that?
I've got you,
so I'm not lonely at all!
I'm so glad I got you, Kikurin!
Hey Nikuko, look!
Wow, it's so pretty.
The stars might fall
before any snow does.
You're right.
When a "SUN" is "BORN"
you get a "STAR."
The next day, I woke up in pain.
Could it be food poisoning
from the misuji?!
No, or I'd have the runs.
Sassan lets us live here cheap,
as long as we don't get diarrhea.
That's the only condition.
It's not food poisoning.
It can't be!
Huh?
Your lips look kinda blue.
- Well, today is a bit chilly.
- Caught a cold?
No, I'm fine.
Ow!
It's getting worse.
But if I tell her...
- THE KIKURIN SHOW
- What's wrong?!
My stomach's never hurt so bad!
Oh no!
Was the misuji bad?!
No way can I tell her!
Sorry, I have- -
She beat me!
- That was quick!
- We need more paper.
I need to go too.
Kikurin, I'll buy some toilet paper,
and bread,
and a bunch of other stuff.
Yes! I can take medicine.
Kikurin, you okay?
- I'm okay!
- You sure?
I wish she'd take a hint,
but that's one thing she'll never do.
Alrighty, I'll go then.
Catch you later!
We've got nothing!
I hate this place!
Darn... It hurts!
It hurts like heck!
She was beautiful.
Whenever she felt blue,
she gazed at the river.
One day, she left home.
Armed with nothing but her looks,
she found a new river.
CABARET PHUKET
Each time,
she found a new name.
she left everything behind.
When she had almost forgotten
the name she was born with,
she took the name "Miu."
Hey there.
Got time to talk?
Don't barge in like that!
My bad, honey.
It's raining outside and I'm bored.
I thought we could chat.
Why not?
Why not.
The woman called herself "Daria."
The only thing we have in common
is our size.
Gee whiz.
She left home in her teens,
and is trying to pay off a lover's debts.
Worse still,
the boyfriend ran away.
Sure you're not being scammed?
Probably.
Are you dumb?
Yep!
How much do you owe?
So much,
your eyes would pop out!
But hey, I'm still alive.
Miu!
You got a customer.
Coming!
- Later then.
- Take care now!
Daria and Miu moved in together,
and they began fending for each other.
It's ready!
Bless this food!
Daria adored Miu,
like she was her little sister.
Miu came to regard Daria
as her big sister.
- Sis, use this for me.
- What's that?
One of my clients is a good tipper.
Then you keep it.
You should plan your daily expenses
each month.
Then you'll never spend too much.
I can spare this much.
We both want to repay our debts
as quickly as possible,
but being too stingy can't be good.
I can afford to pay a bit extra.
You know what?
It seems I can't have kids.
Keep the money.
Miu...
Do you wanna have a baby?
I never thought so,
but now I know I can't,
it feels a little lonely.
Huh?
Miu...
Oh, sis!
Quit that funny face!
I'm glad you're laughing.
She flipped!
- Hey, I'm upside down.
- Calm down, sis!
Miu was tough.
She raked in the tips,
and ultimately paid off her debt.
Put them in.
It's so swanky.
It smells great!
Just like cake, yeah?
It's ready!
It really is like cake!
Well, today is Christmas Eve.
It's a Christmas cake!
Bless this food!
It's so good!
I'm glad.
Sorry, sis.
Miu had a funny feeling.
Her period hadn't come
for a long time.
On that sacred night,
she became certain.
Sis!
Yeah?
I'm pregnant.
For real?!
Does anything exist in the world
that we can believe in totally?
Even if such a thing were to exist
we’d pretend not to believe
People who shed melancholy tears
are beautiful, supposedly
People who laugh while holding in tears
Why do men wander the world
in search of female company?
Why do women doll themselves up
in hope of male company?
I’d like to join forces with deadbeats
and walk side-by-side amiably
Deadbeats also might join forces with me
and walk side-by-side affably
If everybody could see into the hearts
of those who fight endlessly
The hearts of those fighting endlessly
surely wouldn’t burn so brightly
I used to fear hurting and getting hurt
but now that’s far behind me
The power of people to hurt and get hurt
is part of our history
Miu!
- My baby's a girl.
- A girl?
That means she's not a boy!
Can I name her after you, sis?
Kiku, you're awake?
You okay?
You don't feel sick?
I'm okay.
They say you had appendicitis.
- What about the grill?
- Don't worry about that.
You toughed it out?
They say you nearly
gave yourself peritonitis.
Did they operate on me?
They did.
So you have to stay still.
Where's Nikuko?
- Getting details about your admission.
- I have to be admitted?
Of course you do.
Just for a week or so.
A week...
I'm sorry.
Why apologize?
I'm so sorry.
Kiku.
Kiku!
Why did you tough it out?
Kiku, look at me.
Don't tell me
you did it because of me.
Because I said you mustn't get the runs?
Is that why you toughed it out?
So that was why.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Why couldn't you tell me?
Because...
Because of what?
Because I wasn't supposed to be born.
MISUJI KIKUKO
You're alive, aren't you?
Get it? You're alive.
You'll make mistakes your whole life.
Don't be scared of them.
You could act more like a kid,
but "acting like a kid" is
just a thing adults made up.
The only thing we should act like
is ourselves.
But in the same way no kid is perfect,
no adult is perfect either.
So no matter how hard you try
to be a proper adult,
you're going to struggle and mess up.
There's no doubt about it.
The best you can do is
prepare yourself for it.
Mess up while you're still a kid.
Cause trouble. Get into trouble.
Get some emotional scars.
And go on living, okay?
It's okay to cause trouble.
I won't go easy on you.
We're not strangers.
You got that, Kiku?
I'll scold you,
because we're family.
And that means you can't
tiptoe around me either.
Everything will be okay.
Kiku.
You were supposed to be born!
What the heck?!
This really snaps shut.
Calm down.
Is this all you brought?
Thanks a bunch.
Thanks- -
See you, Kiku.
I'll be back.
Thanks a bunch.
I owe you.
So much.
I owe... Oh, Kikurin!
You okay?
Are you in pain?
Do you feel sick?
Kikurin!
I'm fine.
You are?
You had an operation.
You're gonna have a tiny scar.
But you're safe now.
It won't hurt anymore.
- I'm sor- -
- I'm sorry!
I should've realized you
had a sore stomach.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Looks like we're moving again.
Go beyond!
- Nikuko.
- Yeah?
What is it?
Does it hurt?
No. I know...
Know what?
You're not my mom, are you?
Kikurin...
Actually,
I've known since I was about four.
You're that surprised?
We look nothing alike.
Kikurin...
And I saw that photo.
The one with you and that lady.
She's my mom, right?
Of course I figured it out.
We're the spitting image.
And one more thing.
Yes?
You're on the phone a lot lately.
Don't hold back because of me.
Call whenever you like.
You know I'm grateful.
You brought me up. All the way.
And I'm not even your kid.
And I'm gonna need you
for a while longer too.
I truly am grateful.
So, never hold back on my account.
It's the okonomiyaki guy, right?
The okonomiyaki guy.
What's that?
A scary movie?
No.
He's your new boyfriend, right?
It's nothing to hide.
I want you to find
your own happiness.
I mean that from
the bottom of my heart.
What boyfriend?
Isn't he the one you call at night?
Rather not say?
Kikurin, promise you won't freak out.
Promise!
I can handle it.
Those phone calls...
They're from your real mom.
Are you freaking out?!
But listen.
It's true. I swear.
She really loves you.
And you know what?
Miu got married.
And finally, she got pregnant!
Miu grew up,
and found someone who loves her,
and now she realizes
how precious children are.
But that doesn't mean
you weren't precious to her.
She wanted you so much.
It's true!
She cried about how much
she wanted a baby.
But she was too young
back then.
She was scared.
But now she's older,
and pregnant again,
she said she realizes
how awful she was to you.
She says she realizes
how precious you are!
She realizes how awful she was?
So she abandoned me?
And my mom's name is Miu?
Don't worry, I can handle it.
So, who's my dad?
She doesn't even know herself.
I can handle it.
What else?
Well, Miu and I were
living together.
One day I came home,
and you were alone.
She was gone?
She ran away.
She didn't run away!
She just got scared.
That's all.
You were precious to her.
You really, really were.
That's right!
Look at this.
This is the letter and money
she left behind.
- She left this, and some breast milk.
- PLEASE TAKE CARE OF HER
She did the best she could.
She didn’t abandon you.
She was hurting.
And she was so young.
And she's never stopped
thinking about you.
She said so herself.
So what?
What's with the phone calls?
Well...
Does she want to see me?
No. She just wants to know
how you're doing.
She wants to know you're okay.
She said she searched for us,
all the land over.
She even...
She came to the sports day!
She did?!
That was her!
You took rice balls to the restroom
that day.
- Yikes...
- Cut it out.
Were they for her?
How did you get so sharp?
Miu came all the way from Kobe.
Just to see you
at your sports day.
And then, when Miu ate the rice balls,
she started crying.
You looked so pretty,
and had grown up so much.
She was so happy,
she bawled her eyes out.
So I told her.
"I don't know if Kikurin's happy or not,
but I'll do whatever I can for her,
with all of my might."
But if you wanna see Miu,
or if you wanna live with her,
just say so, okay?
You know what I'm like.
I'm a poor excuse for a mother.
But Miu is married to a rich guy
and seems happy now.
If you say you wanna live with her,
I know she'll be happy.
Yeah...
That would be sad for me,
but if it...
makes you happy...
Nikuko is such a fool.
Such a total and utter fool.
Nikuko.
Kikurin!
I don't want to be like you.
It's not just your looks.
You say and do dumb things too.
But even so,
I love you, Nikuko.
PROBLEM CHILD
Cheer up, Mom!
You can do it!
Feel better?
Way better.
- Thanks honey.
- Mommy!
I love you!
I love you so much, Nikuko.
Kikurin!
I love you, Nikuko.
I love you.
Wanna eat some noodles?
Kikurin!
Do you want noodles, or not?
Nikuko kept crying,
on and on and on.
Kikurin, get well soon!
Thank you!
This is for you, too.
- It's a great movie.
- Thanks!
Kikurin...
What's this?
That's...
The hospital gave special permission
for Nikuko to stay with me.
And the day before I went home,
Ninomiya came to see me.
- What's this?
- The bill.
Apparently you only pay
when you leave.
But Nikuko tried to pay
the day I came.
You have a great mom.
- Ninomiya.
- Yeah?
- You really are weird.
- Huh?
Do you hide your weirdness
from everyone else?
I don't have to worry about it
when I'm with you.
Why not?!
Because you're weird too.
I'm weird?!
How?
You talk to yourself so much.
When you see a seagull you say,
"Go beyond!"
When you see a lizard you say,
"I'm late!"
You always yell stuff.
And you do the same pose!
You're way weirder than me.
But saying those things
makes it more fun.
You're nuts!
Are you still making your model?
Did you finish it?
That model won't ever be finished.
Misuji.
It's snowing.
Why does this light feel so familiar?
It's like the light I saw then.
That glimmer of hope.
And...
Ninomiya's model that day.
His model was of
a tiny seaside town.
It was full of the present day,
past memories, and dreams for the future.
Everything became enwrapped in light.
The light overflowed and rose to the sky.
Then it showered down on
this little port town.
The snow probably
won't melt till spring.
Kikurin, what did you pray for?
Hey, it's bad luck to tell others.
When I prayed, my mind went blank.
All I could say was, "Hello."
You're so silly.
What a waste.
But I know what you mean.
It's so sea-ish!
What kind of comment is that?
Ta-da!
What's that?
A New Year's treat.
Red and white sweets!
I got them at the shrine.
My stomach hurts.
You're still not over it?
Don't worry.
This is a different kind of pain.
Whoa. They're both red!
- Nikuko!
- What?
Kikurin...
Congratulations.
Nikuko: Shinobu Otake
Kikuko: Cocomi
Ninomiya: Natsuki Hanae
I’ve been searching for you
On the first day I met you
I couldn’t express how I truly felt
Your face turned serious
and you cast your eyes down
While I gazed at you helplessly
I’m bursting with love for you
A beating in my heart I can’t hide
It all happened by chance,
so suddenly
All I do is smile with you, my love
as days go by uneventfully
What I can’t express
becomes a serenade
In the sky on a lonely night
a star twinkles brightly
If you’re watching it too,
let’s talk a while
I’ve been searching for you
Beneath the same sky
I’m so glad we found each other
We may not always see eye to eye
But I always want you to know
Words can never surpass
what I feel in my heart
All you do is smile with me, my love
as days go by uneventfully
We call each other’s names
to make sure we’re still there
In the same place, same time
we mean so much to each other
In the days to come
let’s find that meaning together
I can never express
how much I love you
So I’ll make sure my destiny with you
is carried by this melody
I can only pray it gets through
I'll smile for you when you're sad
Because I’ll always be by your side
Never forget the joy you always bring
On days when it rains
I’ll always open an umbrella
Let’s walk together
shoulder to shoulder
When I’m sad and start to cry
I know you’ll smile for me
Stay with me always
through tears and tomorrows
I hope that beyond our goodbyes
we’ll still be able to smile
The rain will lift before we know it
We met by chance
By chance, you’re beside me
But not by chance,
because I’ve been searching for you
MY MOM
PROBLEM CHILD
My daughter said,
"I'll look after you when you get old."
I was so happy.
She said, "I'll change your diapers."
I was about to cry, then she said,
"But do your own wiping."
- How can she not wipe?
- He never shuts up.
-I'm done for, too.
The End