Come on!
FREE FALL
The early bird catches the worm.
Get in closer! Closer!
Get him!
Go!
- What the hell? - That's it for today!
- Wanker! - What did you say?
You got shit for brains? It's an exercise!
Problem?
- No. No problem. - In my office. Both of you.
Shit.
And?
And what?
- What did he say to you? - What do you think he said?
If I screw up again, I can stick my exam where the sun don't shine.
Exactly
Quite a poet, that Brandt.
Got a light?
Sorry about earlier.
Are you nuts?
No way.
What?
It's dead.
Dead as a doornail.
Are you crazy? What if they catch us?
- Pussy. - You calling me a pussy?
I'll give you pussy.
Shit!
Let's get out of here.
Shit.
Come on.
It was our job to escort the visiting fans.
Our goal was to keep rival visiting fans and groups of fans
away from each other.
There was an aggressive attitude
not just towards the visiting fans but also the police officers.
And various errors were made on the way to the station.
Firstly, there were communication breakdowns.
Breathe evenly.
- I'm gonna puke. - Well, not bad for a start.
Come on! Keep it up!
Pussy.
How did you end up a cop?
Ever heard of infiltrating the system?
What? You're an anarchist?
Keep it in.
Are you nuts?
It was just a joke.
Chill out.
Let's go.
Come on.
We missed you.
I missed you, too.
Now?
Okay...
Hello, baby...
I'm Auntie Claudia and...
And when you watch this on your 18th birthday,
- I hope this top still fits me. - So do I.
That was your witty Uncle Frank and...
look, here's your granddad.
- And there's your grandma. - Hello.
And this lovely lady...
is your mum.
I can't wait to finally meet you.
And this bump... that's you.
There's Daddy. This way.
Say something to your son, Daddy.
I'm really proud of you.
And I think about you all the time.
And your family and your dad will always be there for you.
Am en! So, back to work.
Come on, I'll show you the garden.
How was training?
How do you think it was?
I mean how were the chicks?
Or have the paternal hormones damaged your eyesight?
Not everyone's a randy bastard.
Look who's talking.
We can't get through. Prepare to go in!
I repeat: prepare to go in!
Got it.
Okay, let's go get hailed on!
Yes, yes, yes...!
- Oh, that was so close! - We're hot on your heels, guys!
So what's it like living next to your future in-laws?
I can almost watch his dad taking a leak.
- Well, don't look a gift horse... - it's no gift. We'll pay them back.
- Show us what you got! - It's not looking good.
Quiet, please. The master needs to focus.
- The master's over here! - Exactly.
Are you okay?
As long as my parents don't burst into our bedroom...
When you go back to work, you'll be able to drop the baby off next door.
You're starting to sound like your mother.
Bettina!
You cow!
Come here!
Benk? Here.
Borgmann?
Eitenbichler?
Engel?
Lieflander?
- Passanen? - Yes.
- What about Engel? Isn't he coming back? - Well, he's still enrolled.
- Possner? - Here.
- Schneider? - Here.
Makes you impotent.
Don't you ever read the package inserts?
Thank you.
Brandt made a huge fuss again.
I think he really missed me.
See you around.
Another jog in the forest?
I've had enough for today.
I nearly forgot what a great runner you are.
I just wanted to say hi.
I love you, too.
Okay...
Ciao.
Bettina...
Breathe evenly.
- Evenly! - Stop it!
Stop it!
Why are you back so early?
I wanted to see you.
Are you okay?
We finished up early. Aren't you happy to see me?
Sure! Of course I'm happy!
How's training going?
Okay.
"Okay?" Do I have to drag every word out of you?
How do you think it's going, Dad?
It's going well.
He doesn't tell me much either.
I shared a room with a nutcase when I did my training.
We had eight to a room in our day.
Never a boring moment, I can tell you.
And how's your new "bedfellow"?
- We haven't thanked you properly yet. - Marc.
No, seriously.
Thanks for making it possible.
So, here's to the house and to good neighbors, of course.
And to everything that's yet to come.
- Bettina. - Cheers.
To you two... you three.
- Morning all. - Morning.
I'd like you to meet your new colleague, Kay Engel.
He'll fill the vacancy in our unit.
But Eiden, you promised Limpinski a woman!
Borgmann, take him under your wing, will you?
You already know him from the academy.
Welcome to the unit. Here's to good teamwork.
Welcome.
So, is he any good?
- Dunno. - I thought you knew him from training?
So?
Get a move on.
What are you doing here?
Nice to see you, too.
Did you guys see Britt in action just now?
- Wouldn't mind being locked up by her. - Can't you talk about anything else?
- Or do you get off on it? - You don't?
So what do you think of her? Pretty hot for a bird in blue, huh?
- Amazing tits. - Amazing tits!
Hilarious. What is this? Kindergarten?
- No! - It's not looking good for you guys.
No! Let's play another game.
- Beginner's luck! - That's it.
The next round's on you.
There's Britt! Hello!
This is a surprise. Hi, everyone.
- Hi. - This is our new guy, Kay Engel.
- Frank's wife, Claudia. - Hello.
Hey.
And Marc's girlfriend, Bettina.
- Nice to meet you. - Hi.
Pretty scary, huh?
- So... wanna join us? - We don't want to intrude.
- We're starting a new game, anyway. - Exactly.
- Okay, then. Why not? - Great.
So...
now you know.
Weird evening.
Why didn't you tell me someone from the academy had joined the unit?
Don't know.
He already bugged me during training.
How's that?
He seems really nice to me.
Change partners.
Attack!
What the hell?
Next.
- See you in the canteen? - Sure.
- Okay, see you in a bit. - Okay.
- It was a dumb idea to come here. - No shit.
Anyway, if you do want to go jogging sometime...
Bettina.
Everything okay?
It was really nice.
And breathe in again.
Hello. Just join in. And breathe in again.
Sorry.
Good. And then carry on breathing normally.
Bettina... Don't make such a big deal out of it.
Don't make a big deal out of it? You've gotta be kidding!
- Don't shout. - I'll shout when I like.
Do you know how awful it feels to sit there alone, like a single mum?
- I just lost track of time. - What's up with your cell?
- I phoned you over and over again. - I left it in my car.
Your mum had to take me in the end. Thanks a lot!
But I couldn't explain why her son had to go jogging in this shitty weather.
I have to pull my finger out or I'll fail my exam.
I messed up in running.
Why didn't you tell me?
Hardly surprising, the way you smoke.
Morning.
Did you sleep well?
- Don't you want to answer it? - No, let's eat.
Come on.
Just answer it.
Hello?
Hey, I can't talk now. I'll call you later.
- Who was that? - Frank.
Aren't you going to eat?
Want some tea?
Breathe evenly.
Pussy.
Ever thought of just leaving it all behind?
Taking off and starting over.
No, not really.
In case you ever need some space.
I'm sorry.
It just feels weird with the baby.
Don't be stupid.
Okay.
Shit.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I tried.
Loads of times.
I'm sorry.
Is everything okay between us?
What could be wrong?
What?
Marc!
Bettina.
Stop it!
Stop it - Why?
Stop it, Marc!
I told you to stop it!
I'm sorry.
I...
- I haven't been myself lately. - Tell me something I don't know.
Is that why you stink of alcohol?
- I thought you were on duty. - We had a few beers in the canteen.
- You think I'm seeing another woman? - Well?
Are you?
What? Do you want me to swear?
Okay.
You're not seeing another woman.
That makes everything okay?
Hey... I'm sorry.
Everything looks just fine.
There's enough amniotic ﬂuid.
The blood ﬂow looks good, too.
So, you can get dressed again now.
There you go.
Thanks.
I'll just check the blood sugar levels.
Thank you.
Do you have any contact with Kay Engel outside of work?
- What makes you say that? - Just answer me.
- We go jogging together sometimes. - You don't go on your own?
I thought you couldn't stand him.
I've got no one else to jog with.
Let's go.
Aren't you going to tell her sometime?
I've got to go.
For he's a jolly good fellow For he's a jolly good fellow
For he's a jolly good fellow And so say all of us!
- This is for the little rug rat. - Wow!
Thanks, Frank.
Thanks, guys.
Congratulations, Marc.
Congratulations!
Got a photo? I want to see him.
There he is. Look.
You can see he's not yours!
All newborn babies look like that. Here, look at that chin on him.
- I'm jealous! - Do I hear wedding bells?
Whose wedding bells?
You and him, of course. Jealous?
What? No!
- Congratulations. - Thanks. Look.
- So, Marc. Cheers! - Thanks, guys.
- Thanks. - Cheers! To you!
More anyone?
We're just giving you a little wash.
Shall I hold your hand? You can hold tight.
Is that nice? Is that nice?
Do you like that?
I've got him.
I've got you. I've got you.
- I've got you. There we go. - You're all wet now.
I've got him.
Shit.
Are you nuts? Kay! I nearly crashed into you.
What the fuck are you doing?
Nothing for days! Not even a fucking text.
I'm a father now. Don't you get it?
Shall I just abandon them?
- I didn't mean it like that. - what then? Huh?
Stop kidding yourself. Just admit that you're gay.
It isn't easy for me...
I'm not gay, Kay. Got it?
It was just a one-off with you.
So stay away from me.
Stay away from me, Kay.
He's asleep.
What's up? Everything okay?
I don't know.
Was Was.
Lately I've just had...
the feeling that I'm suffocating.
It's like...
I don't know.
It's just so stiﬂing.
Do you know what I mean?
You wanted us to move in here.
What did you expect?
Hey, honey...
We'll get through this.
We have each other.
So that's the schedule. There is one other thing.
I hope I don't need to remind you: we will not tolerate discrimination.
This applies when you're on duty and with your colleagues, of course.
And I hope you won't forget this.
Have I made myself clear?
I want this unit to set an example.
If you have any questions, feel free to come and talk to me.
Hey.
- What's up? - I have one word for you: cocksucker.
That was my reaction, too. Imagine Britt's face!
They picked Engel up in some gay bar last night.
Completely wasted. He's been screwing us over all along.
- Quite literally. - We get it, Limpinski.
Well, it's true, isn't it?
What's a gay bar with no bar stools?
A fruit stand.
Isn't that right, Gregor?
This is a surprise.
That raid had been planned for weeks.
Is that all you have to say?
Are you losing it?
You want to blackmail me with that shit?
Blackmail?
You fucking asshole.
Did I ask you to come here and fuck up my life?
Did I make you suck my cock, huh?
- Go on, hit me! - Yeah? -Yeah!
Yeah?
What were you doing there anyway?
Fucking other guys?
I'll fuck whoever like!
What's your problem?
Nothing but "Me! Me! Me"!
"Me!" But what about me? Marc.
What about me?
Don't you get it?
I love you.
Marc!
Leave me alone.
Please!
I'm not sleeping with anyone else.
- Schnitzel and chips. - Goulash, please. Half a portion.
Thanks.
Goulash.
What? I won't let this faggot grab my balls.
Stop it, Kay!
Getting all horny, huh? Who's the fag now then?
Engel! Stop that now!
Shit!
It's okay.
Seriously!
Fucking hell.
You okay?
- Let me take a look. - It's okay.
Fucking morons.
You know who started it, don't you?
Did you see what happened?
You have to report it.
Come on, you know I'll get the ﬂak for that shit then.
You can't be serious?
When you're squad leader you can report this shit.
But don't tell me how to do my job.
Got it?
- I'll take you to hospital. - I'll get a taxi.
Shit!
- What are you doing here? - Is it broken?
Let's have a look.
- Ow! Are you crazy? - Ah, it's nothing. Pussy.
You'd better go before my mum gets here.
I'm gone already.
Fuck!
Shit!
Mum!
Mum! Wait a minute, Mum!
Let's go.
When did it start, Marc?
We didn't raise you to be like that, Marc.
How did you raise me then?
To be like you and Dad?
Bettina was right: moving in was a fucking bad idea!
Why didn't you tell me he was gay?
- How should I know? - You just notice these things.
I mean, you share a room at the academy.
You go running together.
You go jogging together?
So what?
Is this an interrogation?
- Aren't your parents joining us? - Doesn't look like it.
Is your mum okay?
She was acting all strange last night.
I don't know.
OW! Shit!
Come here.
Okay.
What's up?
What are you looking at?
Look at that.
So, watch out, kids. Move over.
And...
Schnapps for you strong guys.
- To us! - Thanks.
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
- So, cheers! - Thanks, guys.
- Cheers. - Cheers!
What's he doing here?
- Have you adopted him? - We're not all as homophobic as you lot.
- What's it like with a homo then? - Great. Jealous?
Of that faggot?
- Nice you made it. - Yes.
Thanks for the invitation.
What are you doing here?
Do you know what we're celebrating today?
I'm invited.
Look, we have nothing against you or homosexuals.
But stay away from our son.
- You don't understand. - No, you don't.
They just had a baby. Do you know what that means?
I love your son.
- How can you say that to my face? - What's going on here?
I think it's better if you go now.
- You're ruining everything! Everything! - Mum!
Is there something I should know?
- Marc. - what?
- You shouldn't have invited him. - Who? Kay?
So now it's my fault you're all acting so strange?
- Did he hit on you, too? - Are you crazy?
I'm crazy, am I?
- Come on, Bettina. I don't want to argue. - Then talk to me!
Tell me what's wrong.
What do you want me to say?
Kay?
What the fuck were you playing at yesterday?
Are you fucking insane?
Kay?
Shit!
I've looked better, huh?
Limpinski?
That fucking asshole.
You have to press charges.
Come on, you know how it works.
Maybe you should get another transfer.
And what about us?
Bettina.
- What are you doing? - I'm going to Claudia and Frank's.
The house is all yours.
I want you gone by the time I get back.
Can you tell me why?
Because you're a liar.
I talked to Frank.
All those night shifts.
You weren't even there.
You've been acting so strange lately.
All those lies!
All that sneaking around with Kay.
I don't know you anymore.
What am I lying about then?
Bettina!
Don't...
Bettina. Please don't go.
Will you stay if I tell you the truth?
I'm almost scared to hear the truth now.
I want to talk to Bettina.
She doesn't want to talk to you.
- Claudia. Please, just let me in. - Frank?
- Yes. - Come here a minute.
What's up?
I think it's better if you go.
You can't be serious...
- I'm sorry. - Frank...
- Come on, let me in. - No.
- What the fuck is this? - Please, Marc.
Bettina!
- Bettina! I want to talk to you. - Don't make it any worse.
Please, Bettina!
It's okay.
Bettina...
I don't want to lose you both. Please.
I had an affair with him.
I don't know how it happened.
- You know I love you. - Then you'd never have fucked him.
- Are you gay? - No, I'm not gay.
What are you then, Marc?
What are you then?
Please, Bettina.
Hi.
Hey... Bettina.
- What are you doing? - Tell me how.
- Bettina! - Tell me how you like it.
- Stop it, Bettina! - Do you want it from behind?
- Stop... - Do you like it like that?
Bettina, stop it!
I can't even be properly jealous!
Hey, he?-
Bettina.
Shit.
Shit!
Kay?
So that fag just did a runner then? I don't get it.
Why did he come here anyway? He only knew you.
I wonder what other skeletons were in his closet?
Shut the fuck up, Gregor!
What's up with you?
Did Engel fuck the sense out of you? Wanna have a suck?
- You'd like that. - Was something going on with you two?
Jealous?
Well, fuck me.
That's disgusting.
Have a feel. You fags fuck anything that com es your way.
- What's your fucking problem? - Liked it, huh?
Is that the best you can do? Pussy.
Why the fuck are you smiling?
- I won't let that faggot hit on me! - You've had it now!
Are you okay, Marc? Get up.
- Frank! - Beat it.
Get out! Go!
Marc...
Shit!
Shit.
I can't go on like this.
Me, neither.