[Music]
[Applause]
don't see no one taking that house yet a
while nor me
[Music]
Namie it works
Nancy hey honey
they're coming along now I saw the cab
down the square
[Music]
[Applause]
but afternoon get outs again though good
afternoon
[Music]
beautiful voices
those are the melons from number 12 yes
I thought we might call on them not in
London it wouldn't be correct my dear I
said No
only two maids
[Music]
hi
see mr. ruff John over there will edible
excuse me sir the message from the vet
about the mayor he says alright sir I've
seen a ghost cub what here's it the
ghost of a man out of my past oh you
mean when you were in the police forces
most of my ghosts are criminals but this
one wasn't I know the story of the house
he lives in
I was on a case there once when I was a
young peeler Louie ba the nephew of old
Alice borrow that was murdered 20 years
ago Louie ba a foreigner he wasn't very
cut up I remember funny should come back
212 Pimlico square after all these years
12 Tim to kill squares mr. Mallen's
house nonsense Louie bar right face
right house no you were wrong sir
impossible what you know about it anyway
well it's the parlor maid sir you see
she's a friend of mine the family's name
is Mallon and they live at number 12
yes sir leastways part of it Nancy says
they don't use the top two stories but
queer Nancy says means less dusting for
her though mrs. Malins queer to query
shame hmm what way well she sort of odd
in her mind she does strange things
Nancy says mr. melon gets very upset he
goes out every night it's a bit queer
please yes does sound queer I want you
to see as much of her as you can what
the mayor sir no no no your Nancy oh
she's not mine's not only one of the
pebbles on the beach so to speak well
you play after I want to know everything
that goes on I believe I'm going to be
very interested in number 12
a dirty evening for a stroll sir a lot
of dirty things in London
[Music]
nr
what are you doing nothing Paul don't
wake up are you doing Bella thought I
heard them up in man
now why didn't you ring for Nancy to
find out I thought it would mean two
journeys freeing for Nancy better what
do you suppose the Serbs are for to
serve us I suppose dead
Nancy I rang the muffin men
oh don't you a good team um I was just
bringing it up oh then it's too late for
muffins not at all my dear not at all
Nancy spread the cloth the Nativity
things go down and get the muffins cook
the muffins and bring up them up in the
same idea is all quite simple
not the gasps Nancy yes it
you're looking very impudent and pretty
tonight Nancy ma broke my heart
I don't know I'm sure sit where do you
get the color fair cheeks Nancy could
you not give the recipe to mrs. Mellon
Oh No natural will it be all your
barking say yes Nancy that'll do for the
present caller so I do anything to my
face so ask for her assistance if I did
well then I was only try so humiliating
for me that girl laughs at me enough as
it is or not suspect you know perfectly
well how you imagine things don't say
that I have been better the last to wait
some time what you mean you know very
well what I mean that I've been trying
so hard and I have been better because
you've been kind to me
I'm perfectly all right even your be
patient and gentle ISM of course Mario
shall I stay in this evening what do you
what shall we do tea first
[Applause]
[Music]
what is it I've just noticed something
if you put it right when I'm not looking
every see no more about it
what's the matter I don't understand
well don't turn your back look on the
wall behind you
[Music]
pictures gone again
yes where have you hidden it this time
didn't take it why should I take it it's
no use to me why should you take other
things pencils knives hold on fella
where's the picture didn't take it I
swear I didn't come get the picture
I'd know if I touched it I'd remembered
I've been better lately you've missed
nothing today is two weeks I've been
well I've had no headaches no dreams why
should I take
so you didn't know where it was promise
you I didn't never supposed it was here
because it was found here twice before
why do you persist in lying to me Bella
it's the truth they love you're not
lying there's only one alternate if
you're losing your wits no control
living of your hands you have to better
go to your room good god help you need
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm going to appeal to poor please
please don't be angry with me I've never
lied knowingly to you if I took the
picture or your ring or your pencil I
didn't know you must bear with me Paul I
don't know how much longer I can keep my
patience
[Music]
eavesdropping Nancy yes sir I didn't
hear anything I was just carrying the
matter your mistress is a very unusual
woman quite strange you know you mustn't
let things you hear and see in this
house upset you you're a young girl
inexperienced you are inexperienced
aren't you friends are you mean
thank you
[Music]
isn't it a lovely day Paul just look at
the sunshine out in the square mm um
where's my letter what letter I haven't
had one for such a long time I do hope
it's from cousin Vincent it isn't here
Why should there be a letter for you
Nancy told me there was one
oh she did she did but you've been
through them yourself dear you see
they're all addressed to me had so hoped
there must be a little nine o'clock good
morning bad he said good morning good
morning miss they don't fit up
[Music]
I'm sorry to
I will read from the hundred and twenty
seventh son except the Lord build the
house they speak with their enemies in
the gate let us pray
I'm the girl squared I was after
number 14 s the only empty house in the
square I'm afraid we are these soul
agents my pipe whirring yo
faces south a little early runs along
the back nothing to block out the light
we'll have some difficulty I'm afraid
mr. Roth why is that
the remainder of the lease of number 14
is in the hands of mr. melon of number
he's already refused three good offers
Tamela rule number 12 why won't he let
you know I've often wondered a queer
profession man mr. Roth soon near to so
many people's lives and yet always on
the doorstep as it were yes indeed a
fascinating study human nature mr. Oh
fascinating you don't think there's much
chance of that house being really in the
market if you want to make an offer do
so by all means I sometimes wonder if
it's the noise he's afraid of the wife's
a delicate woman just had a breakdown I
understand a charming creature I've seen
her often walking in the gardens of the
square with her dog garden sounds very
pleasant with a charm
[Music]
savages hope in a personal you'll come
and sit down over here
oh no I'm all right oh you can't
possibly tell if you heard until you've
had time to think it over there's
medicine at you and you've soft bones
like those little rascals would mind to
go and complain to the nurse fond of
children I see I got them your own no
that was good well you haven't counted
all your bones yet don't worry about me
I'm old enough to be a father not what
they used to be who want children huh
I should be ashamed if I couldn't build
a better hoop than that wouldn't you I
never bothered about hoops I was brought
up in the country and so was I what
about Devon sure Devin sure what I lived
with some cousins near Xmas no Xmas very
well their name was Alice water well
don't go yet I was just getting
interested poor little devils I'd like
to give them a taste of Devon yeah yes a
grass bank to roll down some nice clean
mud well thank you for being so kind
toy shop something those little objects
to play with there is a toy shop across
the road
oh what a lovely idea they do look so
miserable now you'll have to come along
too of course that's the whole idea must
have a woman about where Brett's are
concerned you know I mean they'd run a
mile if I would have so much as called
him to camp I'd love to see them enjoy
themselves but my husband is out and he
won't be back to the TT learn you
Rebecca in time to have it with it don't
want to be silly but I don't know you
know this is charity man at blows
convention out of the window hey hey I
mean you children out there in the
street I'm gonna be afraid
I've got something for you
[Music]
did you make some toys to play with it
is such a shame you can't go into the
square this gentleman thought well
there's a toy shop over there tops if
you like Oh hoops let's go shall we
[Music]
we've kept the wrong shop bands and ice
cream what they want do you think
Michelle Johnson's make them all sick
doom a world of good
well you know what you want don't you
come on blondie you were named ugly
cause anymore
anything you like in reason that's right
[Music]
and what exactly can we do for you knock
his block off you who kind of control
yourself in your own home
to reach such a thing with a complete
stranger who's the children for a horde
of noisy street urchins when you know
the only hope for you is rest and quiet
put the dog down you're not listening to
me I am what are you going to do before
I can't stand the dog in the drawing
room I'm very fond of her pour some
natural fuss you make over it sometimes
I wonder if you even want to be like
other people why did you ever marry me
Paul but I'm married to Bella you were a
normal woman so I thought it's only
since we came to this house that I I've
changed I never wanted to come here
it was my money that made it possible
for you to buy it
is that why you married me Paul you have
changed Bella what's made me change
what's made you change Paul because you
have in the way you treat me
I believe it's ever since that day when
I I found that old envelope addressed to
Louisa that was the first time that you
were angry with me like this that I told
you I had forgotten that incidents my
only anxiety has always been to get you
well I must get away from here I never
were well till I get away from this
house all I could my cousin's the else
waters it would be lovely to smell
Devonshire again your cousin mr. Vincent
arse watered the effrontery to oppose
our
marriage but that's over and done with
Vincent won't mind now would I mind
I have no desire to reopen our
acquaintance besides I don't care to
drag strangers into our troubles they're
not strangers they're my own people
they're all I have I want to see them I
I will see them if you see anyone it
will be a doctor no no not a doctor poor
life huh well I'm better please leave me
alone but I don't see how I can take the
responsibility for you any longer don't
cry you spoil your looks and I wanted
you to look very beautiful
- have you any objections to being seen
out with your husband's why are you
going to take me out there's a charity
concert tonight at Winterburn house I
could get tickets and already
winterville consistent you take me I
shouldn't show it Maria provided you
promise to control yourself to behave as
you know I'd wish my wife to behave I
promise I will have you know pretty soon
my dear there are where the cameo brooch
I gave you but we got engaged
[Applause]
[Music]
I broke please Nancy the big cameo yes
ma'am
[Music]
snotty mm yesterday look underneath
[Applause]
perhaps I left it in another dress
[Music]
well ah time to start Nancy my temper
which one mum well which one do you
think couldn't say I'm Sherman
[Music]
what a very lovely purse
[Applause]
but not that brooch I would have worn it
you know how fond I am a little meetin
didn't go with this dress but I wouldn't
presume to criticize your taste but you
has it quite right come on hold that
[Music]
it's a quarter to eight better I think
I'm making it worse my hands quite shaky
with excitement
[Music]
there's the cat
I think I'm going to enjoy myself
tonight
[Music]
mr. and mrs. Blair brings a noir and mr.
Ryan
mr. and mrs. Vallon how do you do how do
you do we introduce my wife how do you
do how do you do a very good cause is
Haley printer miss Fritton
mr. Arlen miss Rowley charming quite a
collection
you're the most beautiful of all
[Applause]
I hope this tool is right
[Music]
I don't know anything about it my house
didn't put it there I swear
[Music]
lady winter Vaughn I do apologize my
wife let me send for a doctor don't
think it's nothing unfortunate to come
along Oh
[Music]
speak to me don't sit there silent I
can't stand it hit me help me do
anything but she just sits peaked
[Music]
well how can you torture me like this
and have your not tortured me you make
my life a misery at home and now you
shame me in public at least let's keep
your stealing and pickpocketing and
lying to ourselves
I haven't lied you I didn't take your
watch what about the brooch the one I
asked you to wear tonight the one that
didn't go with your dress it's upstairs
in my room more lies it is it must be
it's only mislaid poor you've hidden it
away in one of your mare dreams I have
not if it's gone someone else has taken
it someone else we see about someone
else
Elizabeth Nancy and after the drawn room
at once please
poor please don't question servants in
front of me oh dear dear what's happened
now mistress been playing him up again
our stairs your basket stopped
innovating yourself come on oh please
don't at least let me look again first
it may have fallen behind the dressing
table let's talk this over between
ourselves
please please don't let the servants
know daddy shut the door please
Elizabeth coming to the road you know
the cameo brooch you're mr. supple wears
yes sir
you Nancy yes sir it is missing do you
know anything about it I want you to
think carefully before you're answered
is with
no sir I don't you will please kiss the
Bible and talk of your to thoroughness
you Nancy have you ever touched the
brooch no say of course I haven't
thank you you may go
be careful what you do don't commit
sacrilege as well this is no secret I
swear by Almighty God that I neither
took your watch nor hid away the brute
you are bad unhappy creature and you'll
get worse that you died raving in an
asylum
[Music]
where the devil are you gonna answer I
can't see it somebody let it to the
poster I expect him to meet somebody on
your way to the first layer gentlemen
friends sir suppose well I really
letters come in a film a video don't
ever look at your hair hey good sit
anything more you want to perhaps don't
close civilian
there anything you want
there can she do that for you Marilee
you're jealous of your mrs. Nancy huh
she's a poor thing it's better than one
of us we get eggs ain't it yes dance
every if it is
you're mine now aren't you cuz you want
me how do you want me I've always wanted
you when do we meet I'll let you know
not tonight I have to go out again
goddamn now there's a good girl very
well
you should be master for a bit longer
goodnight - lordship
that you come yes
all quiet when constable passed about
ten minutes ago sir I reckon they can't
get back from that concert before 11:00
and give me time to find out what he
gets up to and number 14
everything is sir they really meet Nancy
when she comes out of 9 o'clock to post
the letters well she never came well
we'll have to risk it you're worried
about if Nancy does come out squeeze I
dry of information on him
[Applause]
[Music]
good evening then see you later la
salida wait
such goings on master made us wear
things kiss in the Bible in all still
but I thought they were at the concert
oh they came back any must met another
route come or not gonna take the letters
well let me take them for you it'll save
you the trouble
I like a bit of air and a change
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
it's alright now I'm having Elizabeth
there is someone upstairs someone moving
there man
don't take on so there isn't anybody in
the house only you and me you mustn't
let yourself imagine things come into
your room and drink your milk but I
don't imagine things Elizabeth it's true
you couldn't handle it
moment ago there was on the gas steam
does it does when someone turns on
another light in the house did you turn
on another light Elizabeth no ma'am
there's no one in the house but us
Nancy's out and the master did let's go
there there ma'am
there's only something wrong with the
pipes you must have dropped off and been
dreaming you heard something that's
right Elizabeth dreaming I dream things
when I'm awake I'm going out of my mind
Elizabeth oh you mustn't say such things
you know well the master did say
something better I once knew a girl who
died in a lunatic asylum
that was how I first knew if there's
anything I can do man
thank you Elizabeth
just anything anybody
[Music]
here come the letter from Australia said
Australia give it to me
cub
I really have a remarkable man yes sir
it's my memory amazing they still have
it for the museum when I die any luck
they should help us
when's Nancy's next night out well
tonight sir yes I wish it was mrs.
Malins instead still it all goes to show
that I'm on the right lines as usual all
I want now is evidence evidence of what
sir I'm certain that he's Louie Bella
and I'm assured idea of what he's up to
in an house can't prove it of course the
only one who can help us is that poor
woman and she's crazy she will be she
stays there much longer does she know
that he's not Malin don't think so
but she knows something that's a danger
that's why we've got to get it away from
him out of that house that's easier said
than done sir what is it I'd like to see
the governor it's a stranger sir shall I
take god you're here sir come along II
I'm sorry so I didn't know he's a friend
never seen him in my life before you mr.
Brown that's right
I got your letter I'm mr. Vinson dams
water from different carbono gonna sit
down sir
I've got a lot to talk to you about your
boots it mm-hmm
this man isn't their own yes sir
I think she's got a new dike sir did you
have a note I'm M assist man did not
have a headache Nancy hardly ever sir
and when is your next even in oh it's
Nancy
do not say and where do you usually pass
the evenings with your gentle friends
Nancy well commander square said are in
the park perhaps it would be departing
too much from tradition if you were to
come with me to a music hall oh do you
mean it
always mean what I say I shall meet you
at 7:50 at the corner of the square
you're a ramen I bought you is never
gonna do nothing it'll do Nancy answer
the bell
what name should I say to cousin mr. how
do you do how do you do will you come in
here for a moment see that mrs. Mellon
is not informed of this call if he could
say I hope you'll forgive me for calling
at this hour but I happen to be in
London and I'd help to see Bella I'm
sorry but my wife is unable to see you
mr. Bao this is little difficult to
explain but you may remember that at the
time of your marriage there was a slight
friction between us
I was peculiarly alive to the my
sister and I have long regretted these
differences they've kept us separated
from Bella too long
in Europe in yin we're anxious to see
her again never stay with us in Devon so
the air always used to do her so much
good down there you are under the
impression she's ill well and what has
given you that impression she was never
strong I am the best guardian of my
wife's health all the same I should like
to see my cousin when I was with me when
we heard you arrived if she had wished
to see you she wouldn't have asked me to
speak to you down here she refused to
see me
the inference appears to be perfectly
clear I don't think I like your tone
melon you're under no obligation to
listen to it mr. OHS voter
I'm not going to leave this house until
I've seen my cousin you propose to
interfere between a husband and wife
that would require physical force mr. al
sponsor yes he will you please show this
gentleman out yes
[Music]
Vinson
oh I've just seen Vincent out in the
square has he been here yes he's been
here let him go without seeing Paul why
didn't you tell me so you did write to
him right against my express orders you
went behind my back and complain to your
cousin's but I didn't I've never written
to them how did you know this address
I don't know oh that's you it to be an
ill I don't know what else did you tell
him nothing I never wrote what lies
about me have you told him Paul if I had
written which I didn't do you suppose
I'd have said a word to my cousin's
against my husband no think I can't
trust insane ravings of a madman disease
you are sweet animal
oh I'm desperate if I do the things you
say then I am going mad it's when you're
angry with me like this my head aches my
mind gets tired we must help me Paul if
you would have flicked it I would be
gentle I should love you more how can
you he was not to be it's only since we
came to this house everything's changed
it must be because of that envelope I
found who was Louie beau
there's no such person as Louie why
should that have changed our lives just
a name on an old envelope it's never
even an umbrella that was the beginning
of your madness then I realize you were
a half-witted creature prize for my desk
and my papers but this is the end
you understand you made your dangerous
you're going to see a doctor madam
no more than one doctor tomorrow morning
and I can't understand this my cousin
not wanting to see which is his wife I
couldn't force him to let me see her but
surely there must be something we can do
to help nothing you can go now it won't
let him get really afraid of your
interference this cameraman will take
you back to your tale is very kind but I
hate leaving to deal with all this after
all I am her cousin well I can perhaps
use methods that you can't I may need
your influence to get a warrant if I
can't get my evidence good but he won't
risk anything that'll lead to an inquiry
afterwards in the meantime you know
where to find me Anderson's hotel Jim
Anderson's a tail come on mr. Russell
it's mrs. Malins what he's gonna have a
certified in the morning how do you know
well Nancy heard I was going out
visiting boy well I waited and I saw
Nancy and mr. Mallen get into a cab
whoever they gon tell well I heard him
tell the driver to go to Canterbury
Music Hall this is our chance where we
go save your breath you'll need it later
on
[Music]
random year until number three weeks
four days five hours unless I went to 40
one of nature's aerosol hours mr. Athena
only my new foster deep sensation in the
region
[Music]
for each venue that's gonna be one long
holiday for you after tomorrow
[Music]
Oh Elizabeth it's you help me to move
this my brooch may have dropped behind
you oh yeah find my brooch you may not
send to the doctors for gentleman to see
you ma'am I will tell him my husband
isn't him assume he wants to see ma'am
not the master and he says it's urgent
[Music]
what are you do mrs. Mellon you but I
thought this time we met your husband
interrupted us very well this time I
don't understand
yeah you will indeed ma'am very shortly
now you just sit down make yourself
comfortable
hey you're supposed to be going off your
hands you I know more about what they're
going to do the new gue at the present I
hope you'll excuse my back
[Music]
[Applause]
the whole of this house was ransacked
the merderet searched for those rubies
all through the night and the opinion of
the police was that he found him and
vanished with him they never caught him
no but suppose he didn't find those
rumors after all suppose they were
concealed in the walls or the floor of
old Ellis Burroughs bedroom which was
the room of our viewers mrs. Mellon
footsteps what footsteps the guests
slide going up and down
[Music]
what's matter but there's a little
tender starting rapid enough come along
now
that's what's made me sure my mind is
going lying in my room watching the
guests slide listening for someone in a
place where no one can go will you stick
in along the roof from the empty house
next door what I'm saying it fits it all
fits to me I found an envelope addressed
to him when we first came here that's
what started me I've got it I solve it
I've saved you
God what a marvelous man I am what are
you talking about
you're mr. Mellon is my mr. Louie burrow
a criminal maniac who murdered his aunt
and steals back to his own house at
night still searching for those rubies
he couldn't find 20 years ago and every
time he lights the gas up in that room
so it dims down here sir I hear his key
in the door few minutes afterwards I
can't stand it my mind
oh you're not going out of your mind
mrs. Mellon you're slowly and
methodically being driven out of your
mind
why because quite Paxton's you got into
his identity and that made you dangerous
to him he couldn't get rid of you by
ordinary means for fear of an inquiry so
he's driving you mad in order to
discredit anything that you say as the
ravings of a lunatic thank god you're
not married to him not married to
certainly not he married another lady
long before he met you and she is still
alive
I dunno I've been finding out things
about mr. Louisville where is this woman
but the general Australia at three
months away by then it'll be too late to
save you
that's why you've got to give me the
evidence we need whatever any proof of
Louie Bowers identity I don't know where
to find it so you can tell me where to
look yes but in here you don't
understand to me is still my husband I
couldn't betray my husband you mean the
man who betrayed you into thinking you
were married to him that's different
it was before I knew him we've lived
together as husband and wife if I
betrayed him I'd be betraying myself
even though I tell you that this moment
he's sitting in a music hall with
another woman your parlor maid - it's
hard to take everything from you
but I'm afraid it is you will straight
in and a follow you in a moment what you
gonna do
Oh take a little stroll when we go out
again I'll let you know
[Music]
he keeps his papers in there haha this
is where we start but it's not good that
means there are probably some things
inside that are very interesting do you
mind if I take my coat off I always work
much better with my coat off
saucy shirt isn't it what are you going
to do there's only two things I've ever
wanted to be a gardener or a burglar
both of nice quiet occupations versus
tougher than I thought you mustn't force
it Fredo
have to but what should I say when he
comes back don't you realize it tonight
or Never
tomorrow he wants to get you certified
if we go back we're lost
we must gamble on finding something now
are you with me all right force it would
be quick there's no hurry mum he's quite
happy where he is I don't like these
violent methods makes me feel like a
dentist on a blank sofa give me the keys
supposed to keep his papers in here
look he's back he's upstairs
how long is he usually stay he'll eat
time and our art in minutes well one
longer than that let's jump what I'm
afraid we should have to risk it come
along I can't see it my dear shot go
right up to your room lock yourself in
and don't come out in any circumstances
until I tell you you're not going you
won't leave the house course but
Elizabeth oh don't you worry about it
whispers I've squared uh-huh I remember
you're all right so I was just stay in
your own
[Music]
man up
I brought you milk go upstairs and tell
mrs. Mayer and she's to come down here
at once just like that sit very good sir
are you the inner master said you to
come to the drawing room at once
she wrote to answer she's got the door
locked I tried it alright man to go to
bed well I've got to let the dog out
first you need to worry about the dog
go to bed
but the gun but Yahtzee way well you
kindly remember that you're not a guest
in this house
hello I have your dog here I found it in
the drawing room but you know it's an
hour what dog
you said you had interview her I haven't
seen your dog none of your dreams that
the one about you didn't break open my
desk dream don't tell me it was a dream
that he never came okay tell me about
this dream of yours a dream that a man
came here I know you dreamed but tamatha
man was right part of this curious dream
who are you apparently a mere figment of
this lady's imagination how did you get
in
whoa we ghosts don't have to bother
about doors if you don't tell me your
business I'm to call upon another ghost
the ghost of the man who murdered Alice
Barlow in this very room I have no idea
what you're talking about
thank you mr. Joey Bauer
my name is melon I know it isn't you've
been listening to my wife's insane
ramblings correct except that she isn't
insane nourish your wife who dare to
break into my house you tamper with my
desk where you and I know lies the
evidence that you are Louie Bower here's
what you want it'll give me great
pleasure to see you make a fool of
yourself before I throw you out of the
house hmm
seems to be nothing here Mike roach
and it's true you did hide my things you
laid traps for me and said that I lied
to you
I found the Grouch on earth today and
put it aside until I could give it back
to you give it to me
this isn't your brooch I gave it to my
wife as an engagement present
where'd you get it from it's secondhand
how do you know there's an inscription
in it where where inside it's a trick I
discovered it by accident
show me - hey B what are these or some
sort of stones in stones well where are
they quick they were loose so I took
them out and put them in here there you
are
Alice borrows books Alice borrows rubies
20,000 pounds worth this brooch and
these rubies are going to send you to
the gallows give them to me
get out the room quickly
little hold him we shall need an mo did
you get my message through to mr. Dallas
Walter yes all right well you go for the
police now and hurry
well very good sir it's all over now
ma'am you can go along up your own I'll
deal with the servants
I want to speak to my wife don't you go
up to your own I too want to speak to my
husband
no y'all only be torturing yourself I
want to speak to him alone very well if
you insist
and that's the poser I'll hear you if
you call quick rubies rubies how you
lusted for them okay look better hurry
get the knife then the draw cut me free
and give them to me okay you better cut
the rope here take the knife
life hotknife are you suggesting this is
a knife I have in my hand have you gone
mad my sane husband there was a knife
but I lost it I always hide things away
because I'm mad Vera what are you saying
really you killed a woman for me you try
to kill my mind you made me mad woodless
is an animal you said now you're
helpless and I made
[Music]
[Applause]
Jim better let him hold
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
you