This world is ridiculous.
Human relationships are annoying.
Love is not enough to make
this world a better place.
Fah?
Your bride looks loaded.
So give me back the 5,000 you borrowed.
Look at you.
You ate the whole plate of fried shrimp.
I don't want to keep doing this.
We should break up.
But we can't, Ball.
Don't you remember?
We are bound by destiny.
It can't be.
So give me back the 5,000 you borrowed.
WATCHARA APARTMENT - INVOICE
Don't pretend to forget.
Why ask for it now?
This is a wedding.
We don't have money with us.
One thousand baht!
Hello!
Mr. Charas.
She knows me.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
Let me see how much.
How could you? 200 baht?
From the whole family, 200!
That's tough.
I'm one of those
who was trapped in destiny,
holding onto something I can never have.
Chasing tirelessly,
knowing I have no chance,
I still manage to make a mess of my life.
Hello, Mother.
We can't be together.
Why not?
Your family health... there's a high risk
of diabetes and hypertension.
I don't want my children to risk it.
Don't you remember our destiny?
With this medical test,
it would be beyond destiny.
Where is the bride, doc?
I only saw the bride's mother.
What did you call me?
I'm the bride.
Can't you tell from my gown?
This is haute couture from France.
Who invited you?
Doc did.
He told me that he has gonorrhea
and he hasn't recovered yet.
Now he is getting married.
Congratulations.
You had me tested and everything,
and you have venereal disease?
Why am I serious about destiny?
Maybe because my writer mom
narrated this in her romantic novel,
"When Destiny decides Love"
I read it from cover to cover.
It made my young self
believe and become deeply attached.
A short plain Jane like you...
has had three ex-boyfriends?
Oh my, oh my...
What my should it be?
My rock.
Don't tell me that your third
is that rocker
who chatted you up at the shop?
Yeah, that hot rocker.
First I thought you were the one,
but you really weren't.
You live a strange life,
different from ordinary people
like my friends and me.
How did you know he is getting married?
Did he invite you?
No, someone told me.
I hope you're not thinking of going there.
She won't.
Those rockers are a different species.
Stay away from them.
But in reality,
there are tens of billions of lives.
Destiny doesn't have time for all of us.
Looks like the wrong wedding.
Oh, that queer tricked me!
Just for cheap cosmetics, huh?
Easy. Easy.
Two jugs of beer.
Yes, ma'am.
Why order more? You're drunk.
Let's go home and rest.
Bas, take her home.
I'll stay and drink more.
For what?
For wrecking the
after-party of that queer.
Hey.
Are you kidding?
I'll do what I said.
SUVARNABHUMI AIRPORT
Is it the same guy
that's picking you up?
Of course.
Bas. You miss me, right?
So much, Tae!
Come save your best friend
from the hands of devil now!
What is it about?
Talk like normal human, will you?
I can't keep up with your queer slang.
Fah is drunk?
Who took her out to drink then?
We were worried that
she would wreck the wedding,
so we convinced her to drink some beer.
Thought it'd be a little bit,
just enough for her
to get sleepy and go home.
But she kept drinking in the bar.
Then she went to pee,
and never came out of the toilet.
Beer is trying to
find her in the wedding party.
I don't know how it goes.
You're dressed formally.
It must be for the uniform-themed wedding.
I just found out
there are two wedding events.
Hope you didn't go to the wrong one.
Zen, you are cheeky.
After realizing it's not that party,
you left me.
I thought you'd like it.
Music!
Singers, wait.
Where is the bride?
Let your ex give you a toast.
Who brought this hippo on the stage?
Where is the bride?
Ton, where the hell are you?
Come out so I can give you a toast.
Pull her down, hurry.
-Ton.
-Fah.
Stop. Don't say anything.
I'm sorry, Hippo.
You are in the wrong party.
Your ex is in the other room downstairs.
Come on.
Oops, my bad!
Sorry. I'm your biggest fan.
Come on, this is embarrassing.
Where are we going?
Just tell Fah I bought the souvenir
for her mom.
If she wants it,
be nice and don't come around.
Hey Bro!
Bro, come hide over here.
-What?
-Hurry or our team's gonna lose.
What team? I'm not a guest here.
Oh, damn it.
What a troublemaker.
Hold on!
Tae, don't shout at us.
I didn't want to lose her.
But she's just gone.
She always causes trouble.
Zen.
You said you'd stay for the after party?
Of course, but I found this bag.
Someone must have dropped it.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Can I buy that stuff in the bag?
It's not mine.
I'm looking for the owner.
It's mine!
I left it a while ago.
Can I take it back? Please.
Wait.
You just said
you wanted to buy it.
Now you're the owner?
Which is it then?
You don't believe me?
Kobori!
Hey!
"NO DRUNK DRIVING" CAMPAIGN
Who put the light sign there?
People may run into it.
So we know who's drunk.
They won't need the breathalyzer.
Let me have you tested.
But I'm not the driver.
Don't have me tested.
George is driving.
Test him instead.
How much should I laugh at this gag?
What's your name?
Officer,
-can I borrow your phone?
-Why?
-To call my friend.
-Where is yours?
It's dead.
All right, what's the number?
Zero, eight, four,
six, six,
five, two, one.
Unable to press number one.
Can I press number two instead?
You are so funny.
One can't be lonely around you.
Wanna kill loneliness?
Then let loneliness kill you.
Once loneliness is dead,
you've killed loneliness.
How much should I laugh at this?
Someone bailed you out.
You can go now.
He bailed me out? Are you sure?
Stay if you want.
No. No. No. No.
-My car key?
-Outside.
Thank you.
Hey.
Time proves what's right,
but kaffir leaf is a spice.
The first one because of fried shrimp.
The next one because of health.
And the last one is a queer.
Really?
How's my love life?
Isn't that great, folks?
I don't think you should have
wrecked their wedding.
Oh, I forgot. I don't want ginger.
Waiter.
It's all right.
You don't like ginger?
I'll have it. My favourite.
Here you are.
What's your name?
Zen.
Zen, like the shopping mall?
Like Japanese Buddhism.
I know.
It's so strange.
-I think we've met before.
-When?
I have ordered Nam-Neaung.
Right, one moment.
We can't break up.
We are bound together by destiny.
I don't think we are.
Give me back the 5,000 you borrowed.
Excuse me.
Do you know where the blood lab is?
I'm not a nurse.
Can't you tell?
I think it must have been you.
It's so strange that I can remember.
Look, and here we are.
Nonsense.
The first time I was in high school.
How could you remember me?
You listened to my story and made it up.
By the way, if you're going to woo me,
you need a better story.
I don't know about wooing,
but the way we've met is not normal.
What is it then? Destiny?
What if it really is?
I put up with my three ex-boyfriends
because of 'destiny'.
I don't want to hear it anymore.
It makes me sick.
You may not believe in it...
but I do.
Very well. We'll split up here,
and don't try to reconnect.
Don't try to find me.
If it's as you said,
we'll surely meet again.
All right.
Are you serious about this?
See you soon, Fah.
Bye now.
What does that mean?
Fah has been gone the whole night.
I can't reach her.
And she's not home yet.
Should I be worried?
Everything is about Fah.
Why aren't you with her
instead of me?
Hey, be sensible.
If your friend disappeared,
what would you feel, Pai?
Let it be.
Friend, not lover.
I'll call you back.
Bas must have called you.
So you're here.
If you were gone half an hour longer,
I'd call the police.
You turned off the phone.
I didn't, it ran out of battery.
So what time was your flight back?
Hope it wasn't delayed
and you made it to dinner with Pai.
We did.
That's good.
Keep her happy.
You don't see each other much.
Let me go get changed.
Gotta go to work.
Thank you for caring.
Fah, where will we go on holiday?
What holiday?
Those two haven't told you?
We've talked about it.
I forgot...
Our group plans
to have a long holiday abroad!
Pueng told me already.
She said we're stressed out.
We work in an airport
but haven't been anywhere.
Still taking some pictures?
Everybody is here.
Better hurry if you want to go.
I'm almost there, hold on.
Hey,
the meeting about the holiday, is it here?
Well, well. Whose brother is here?
Oh, are you here for me?
Sit here.
Easy, Bas. This is my brother, Pao.
Hello everyone.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Come here.
You're always late.
Attention seeker.
Well, since everyone is here.
Let's vote that we are going to...
Korea!
Whoa!
No.
We are going to India... Taj Mahal.
Is that right, Beer?
Right, Bas?
No, sis.
I have changed my mind.
Me too.
We're going to Japan!
What?
Why are you 'single' on FB?
Because I am.
Because of Fah?
Nope.
Bye-bye.
What are your routes next month?
Only to Japan.
Someone has to
be responsible for Tae's sorrow.
Why?
I want to enjoy onsen!
It's once in a lifetime.
Taj Mahal, the monument of love.
Now it's myself and Mek. Two votes.
Who else? Raise your hand.
Who told you I'd go to India?
-What?
-Uh, oh!
I don't like roti.
How about Australia?
Don't be so fancy.
Chooose somewhere cheaper.
I have two votes,
plus one from my nephew makes three.
So I win.
Everybody must go to Japan with me!
Japan.
Australia.
Korea.
I thought you're going to Bali.
Damn!
Right, let's make it fair.
I have an idea!
Put a magnet at the 'India' slot.
When the ball is spun, it will fall there.
-Five hundred.
-I'll do three hundred.
Any country the ball falls into, that's
a public opinion. Our destination. Okay?
Let me throw it.
INDIA
JAPAN
Japan!
-See? Japan.
-I forgot to mention,
the first one is a rehearsal. Bet again!
JAPAN INDIA
KOREA BALI AUSTRALIA
INDIA
JAPAN
Japan!
Oh, sakura!
I'll give you 500 to
make it fall into Japan.
Repeat, Japan!
Hello?
Where are you guys?
I got here a while ago.
I don't see anyone.
Hello?
Beer?
Is it fun for you?
Breaking up relationships?
What are you talking about?
You are the reason Pai dumped Tae!
Bas, can you settle with her?
I don't get it.
You're the one I should
settle things with!
You did this to Tae.
Don't you feel responsible?
What are you talking about?
I haven't done anything!
Your fault!
It's not!
Don't tell me that you also
blame me for the breakup?
If it's not you, who else?
Because of me?
You're bad!
Why do you look so calm?
I have something funny.
If it's not, I'll slap you, Pueng.
The hotel we booked
is in Kansai,
not Sendai.
Your humor is too far.
Just give me a room key. I'm cold.
Sendai and Kansai... sound similar.
You booked the hotel in the wrong city!
You let me book when I was drunk.
Odds were I'd get it wrong.
Book it yourself next time then!
Why haven't you checked in?
Thank goodness!
Tae, you're here in time.
Find us a hotel, will you?
It's high season, so many tourists
are in Sendai.
You can hardly find rooms.
Did you tell Bas and Beer
to come to Japan?
No, I thought they wanted me
to go on holiday,
so they arranged
the trip according to my schedule.
They could have told me they want you here
so I didn't have to pay 300
to the waitress.
Three hundred?
Nothing. Let's just find the hotel.
Welcome!
Yeah, we just ended up at your restaurant.
If we can't find a hotel tonight,
I think we should stay in a temple.
Temples here don't allow overnight stay.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
That Japanese
sounds like Southern Thai dialect?
I'm not Japanese.
I'm Thai.
Whoa.
Sith.
My friend is also Thai.
Hello.
I'm so happy to meet Thai people here.
They have different dialects.
Welcome!
Having a good time, huh?
I'm busting my ass finding a hotel.
I don't think those guys can find a hotel.
Oh well. Tonight...
let's try to get laid with these two.
Then we'll have a place to stay.
At their home.
What do you think?
Try something exotic,
and you'll get hooked.
I'll bring you back to Thailand.
That's very funny.
They're Thai?
Can you just pretend
that you don't understand?
I understand damn well.
Hey, coffee!
Four cups, please. The signature ones.
How about this ladyboy?
Can he handle hot stuff?
He seems to have a bad mouth.
I heard that you're looking for a hotel?
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you know anywhere
with four rooms available?
Have some drinks.
They are preparing your rooms.
Who found this place?
I have two friends.
We got scholarships at Sendai.
They work in Ryokan.
The old man passed away.
His Thai wife is taking care
of the business.
She's kind.
I'm sure she can help you.
Students that work at
Gelato speak Northern and Southern.
They speak Isaan here.
Don't be confused.
They got scholarships
from four regions of Thailand:
North, Northeast, South, and Central.
Lucky for you, the clients didn't show up.
We have three rooms available.
Plus my son's. He'll give up one room.
-So you have enough.
-Where is your son?
Let me show him my deepest gratitude.
He is arranging the room for you.
Don't worry, his room is not so messy.
He only stays when
he has a night shift here.
Mrs. Ang's son loves reading.
You can read them,
just put them back when you finish.
This drawer is private.
He asked not to touch it.
Why did you choose this room?
I want to sleep in the same room
as the owner's son.
A good-hearted man must be good-looking.
If anything is gone, he'll blame us.
Let me see what's valuable.
Don't mess with it.
I know what he looks like.
Disappointed? He must be ugly, right?
On the contrary...
Look.
Hey, he looks familiar.
Like someone I know.
Don't you even try.
I call dibs.
This can't be.
It can't be that coincidental.
You guys only fail difficult subjects.
Me? I can't even pass easy subjects.
Difficult or easy, we still failed.
If we don't graduate,
we have to pay everything back.
Do you know how much to pay back?
Three times the grant.
It's the consequence
of not focusing on studying
and bringing shame to our country.
We spend more time earning
extra money, and what now?
If I go back home, my dad will kill me.
Oh... can we rely on black magic?
Black magic?
In Japan?
Hey, Zen.
Is that the girl from the wedding?
I don't think so.
This one seems fine.
Because the one we met
was a drunken thief.
I hope you chose my room.
I saw your photo in the room,
and I wished it wasn't you.
But it is you, flesh and blood.
That means you had a peek in my drawer?
What did you steal this time?
You must have planned all of this
so I'd end up staying here, right?
I should be the one asking.
What made you end up at my hotel?
I think, maybe...
destiny has started working now.
I know what you're thinking,
but stop that thought.
How could you stop my thought?
Last night when I saw you come in,
I was a bit shocked.
About what? It's just a coincidence.
A coincidence that
you were drunk and I was there.
That you were arrested at the checkpoint.
That we had rice soup together.
That you came here
and couldn't find a hotel.
Coincidence that someone brought you here.
That we have spare rooms.
And coincidence that I'm the owner.
So many coincidences.
It's called 'destiny'.
Enough. So corny.
Stop talking nonsense.
And don't tell my friends about this,
or I'll hate you.
Fah, where should we eat?
Destiny has brought us together
Who is that guy?
I have no idea.
We are here... just for
Fah and Tae to get together, right?
But we ran into the destiny nutcase.
If Zen is bound by destiny to Fah,
there is nothing we can do.
Are you saying that
you'll let this happen by destiny?
That's right.
Are you taking his side?
No, I just don't want to get between them.
But really... whether Fah likes Tae
is totally up to her.
It's like we're butting in, Bas?
If you say so.
You know well that
Tae has always liked Fah.
He tried to move on, but he can't.
So Pai left him.
Tae is a good man.
But with Zen, it's destiny.
Pueng, you want to be my enemy?
Why do we complicate things?
Let destiny do its job.
Fine, let's bet then.
If Tae wins,
you both do whatever we want.
But if Zen wins,
you can tell us to do whatever.
I'll do what you told me.
I'll surely win this game!
I'm out. I don't want to bet on it.
You can't.
Teamwork, get it?
What the hell?
What are you up to?
Here, I found it eventually.
I want to change my hairstyle
so it looks nice
when I take pictures with Sakura.
Don't worry about your look.
The food is here. Let's have breakfast.
Have you eaten?
Look, Pueng...
about Tae and Fah...
are they dating?
-Who said that?
-Fah.
Thank you very much for finding us rooms,
and you also took time to show us around.
You're welcome.
I'm glad to be of service.
Before we go to see Sakura,
I will take you to upper Sendai,
to the top of Shiogama Shrine.
Why did you tell Zen that we're dating?
I'm afraid he'll be flirty with me.
He seems untrustworthy.
Hope you don't mind.
Of course not.
Sakura here blooms in two seasons.
In spring...
Excuse me. Excuse me. Sorry.
Come on, Beer.
Let me finish telling the story first.
-Just a second, I'm in a hurry.
-Come on.
You're in a hurry, let me help.
I'm all broken.
You're a guide, how could you do this?
Moron! What an asshole!
You had it coming.
Look! Destiny is working.
You want everyone to know about our dare?
What's wrong with that?
Seems like you are afraid of them knowing.
Or you are afraid
that Tae would be jealous?
Right, I don't want him to know
about the silly game
that can never be true.
But the silly game happens to be true.
That's why you're embarrassed
that we met here.
So stop acting like we met before.
What if I don't?
I will make you hate the word "destiny"
like I do right now.
I'm not sure
if you are a photographer or a pervert.
Peeking under the skirt, aren't you?
To get good candid shots,
it's like a tiger stalking its prey.
Like soldiers waiting to ambush
without letting the target know.
When it's the right time, shoot!
You think the psychic can really help?
Maybe she can tell us something.
When you were in grade two,
you ate a piece of chalk
because you wanted to
write on the board like a teacher.
You had to get your stomach pumped
at the hospital.
You did that shit?
That's a secret.
I've never told anyone.
You...
had an operation
for a hemorrhoid.
So many other things to see,
why a hemorrhoid?
And this one...
you were an ox in a previous life.
Can I know about this life?
As a kid
you helped your family raise cattle.
As if she could see.
Last life you were an ox,
this life you raised them,
and you love eating beef?
Why do you like eating your own kind?
Yeah.
Your name is Mc.
Not Mac, the computer.
But Mc Jeans.
I think she'd better dig up something deep
so it's more convincing.
Go away, if you don't believe.
Sorry.
All of you
want to graduate, right?
Yes, we do.
Luckily, I know the way.
Easy to fix.
Please tell us,
we will follow your advice.
If you want to graduate,
one of you
has to sleep
with a blonde.
With a westerner...
Let me do it, okay?
This person will come in ten...
Ten days?
Nine
Eight
Seven
Six
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Shit!
God damn it!
How can we tell Tae?
So he can try harder
and get ahead of Zen.
If Pueng knows, we'll be disqualified.
She won't know.
Make sure Tae doesn't tell anyone.
I think if what the psychic said was true,
we should just fail the exams.
I can't. If I fail,
my dad will kill me.
What's with Pueng and shopping?
Why does Zen take good care of her?
Pueng told me that
she'll make a move on Zen.
She'll get a chance while shopping.
Bit by bit.
Actually,
those two seem good for each other.
One is mental, the other has dot disease.
What is dot disease?
"Don't tell anyone" disease.
Everything is dot dot dot.
They're holding hands now.
How embarassing.
Letting a man hold her hands.
It brings a bad name to Thai girls.
Zen is Thai, not Japanese.
Pop, you want her to lose her
virginity or what?
It's just a joke. Why are you mad?
Yeah, why?
Do you have a crush on Zen?
What are you talking about?
No, I don't.
You shouldn't have to
prepare food for us, Ang.
Actually, this is not my idea.
Zen wants to cater to you.
He said all of you are nice.
Especially you, Fah.
He speaks fondly of you.
Uh-oh, what did he say?
I'd love to hear.
You'd better not hear it.
Just go take a shower
and get ready for the party.
The boys should be done by now.
What?
Are you kidding?
Not only us,
Pop and Pueng also heard it.
I think we made it here to Sendai
to stand here shivering.
It must be Zen's plan.
We are here in Sendai,
because you guys chose this place?
Yeah, I forgot.
But don't underestimate him.
If Fah buys the idea of Zen's destiny,
your game will be over.
Game over? Is it, Beer?
I knew that bearded man...
couldn't keep his mouth shut.
He can't keep a simple secret.
Zen didn't spill it.
These two overheard you talking to Zen.
I didn't mean to intrude.
But once I knew,
I couldn't hold it back.
Fah, what do you think about this?
I'll...
make him tired
of someone destiny sent to him.
I'll start at the party tonight.
Awesome, Fah.
This is a great plan to scare off a rat.
The crazy one up there should be you.
How did you let him take the spotlight?
I didn't.
He drinks faster than me.
Zen, take your brother away.
This has become his welcome party.
Okay, Mom.
-Top...
-What?
Enough.
You'll wake up late tomorrow.
Not enough,
I sure can wake up.
He has an attitude.
Will this be dangerous?
I apologize about Top.
Top, let's go home.
I'll give you a ride.
No, I'm not going back.
I have something to tell everyone.
Listen carefully.
My dream is not to be a hotel staff!
He is getting intense.
And what is it that you want to do?
My dream is...
to be a wrestler.
Top, enough. This is embarrassing.
Don't stop him,
just let him do what he wants.
I want to know what he wants to do.
That's not good.
So exciting.
-Zen, stay out of this.
-Top, enough.
Surprise!
I can't be here any longer.
I have to go practice, goodbye!
I hope he stays warm in those clothes.
I'll follow him to be sure.
Never mind.
He's just going home.
It's always like this when he's drunk.
People here are used to it.
Hey!
You assholes go to bed!
I want to drink with Zen privately.
We have some matter to discuss! Whoo!
Fah, you are mocking Top so well.
My mom has a good sense of humor.
Keep dancing. More.
I never knew you're so funny.
No wonder Zen likes you,
because you're like this.
Good night.
I'm not funny like this at home.
Top might not be able
to take you around tomorrow,
so I'll take you myself.
That's great.
Zen, you don't have to.
I have studied the route.
I know the way.
We can go on our own tomorrow.
Yeah, we can.
We can find toilets and restaurants.
No, we'll get lost.
We had a guide today,
but these two ladyboys
still got their asses kicked.
There might be a ladyboy hater here.
Is there a problem?
-Hey, Bas.
-Yeah, with your mother.
All right then.
I hope you have a great time tomorrow.
If you have a problem or get lost,
you can call me or the hotel.
Good night, everyone.
Come on!
Pueng, go to your room. It's late.
Or your pretty face will
get wrinkles.
Bitch!
Your friends are not up yet?
They must have stayed up late last night.
What's this?
Ginger tea.
Did you forget that I don't like ginger?
I forgot that anything healthy...
isn't your favorite.
I'll get coffee for you then.
No thanks.
Just leave me alone.
In real life and in photos,
It's totally different.
Where did you learn photography?
From Google.
If Google can teach you this much,
you don't have to go to school.
Why do we have to study?
To know technical theories.
That's not true.
Why do we have to study then?
One, for your information.
Two, for your consideration.
Lame.
Where is everybody?
Off for shopping.
Shopping?
So we're not going inside?
We are. But they went shopping
before the products run out.
Can I run my errands then?
So we can go in together.
You can just go do your thing,
and I can go inside by myself.
This is the God of Love.
Young people who are in love
tie a ribbon and make a wish
for a happy love life.
You might be curious why he looks angry
even though he is the God of Love.
That's because
this is his face when he feels ecstatic.
No! Nonsense.
He said so.
Or you can use a translation program.
I'm not a psycho stalker.
So why are you here?
And you came when I'm all alone.
Coincidental much?
My Dutch clients
want to make a wish here.
So I took them here.
And I met someone
who happens to need an interpreter.
I don't buy it.
Think as you please.
I also don't buy that
you and Tae are together.
Why?
Because the hotel staff
have never seen you show affection.
Why are you with him?
I have something to settle with him.
Just send me the GPS location.
Okay, will do.
What do you want to eat?
Ramen?
Too boring.
Onigiri?
Too many carbs.
-Tonkatsu?
-Deep fried food hurts my throat.
Takoyaki?
Not filling.
Sushi?
I want something more famous.
Yakiniku?
Too smoky. I don't want to wash my hair.
Just tell me what you want to eat.
I told you, something easy.
Chicken and basil with fried egg.
Chicken and basil with fried egg
in Japan?
Let's take this place. My call.
Come on, follow me.
Where has Fah gone?
With Zen.
-Ridiculous.
-Zen took Fah out for a meal.
Look at Tae.
He's so stressed out.
I think it's not fair
that you're judging me based on
your three ex-boyfriends.
And is it fair for me?
I'm in the same old situation
even though I'm tired of it?
Why don't we make it fair to both of us?
I'm not asking you
to believe in the same thing.
I just want a chance to prove it
in a way that's fair for us.
Can you repeat it again?
I want to know if you understand it.
From tomorrow on,
you'll go to places
in Sendai without telling me.
And If I can meet you
by accident like today,
that means we're bound by heart.
And that is destiny.
How many times have we accidentally met?
Ten.
But I think that's too many.
How about two?
Two and ten are not close.
I'll reduce it...
to seven.
If we meet less than that,
I'll take it that we are not soulmates.
You don't have to prove anything.
It doesn't matter.
Since seven times is not possible.
I'll make him stop obsessing over destiny.
What if we swap...
if it was Tae, would you do like this?
No way, you'll never hit on me.
You have to sacrifice.
Go and force yourself on Bas
and get it over with.
Why does it have to be me?
We have an agreement
Bas has to be consensual...
and choose one of us.
If I had a nice body like Pop,
I wouldn't have to do anything pathetic.
That's pathetic, not sexy.
Too pathetic.
Philips, why don't you try it?
Hey, that's equally disturbing.
So the plan to trick Bas at Onsen
failed then?
You're making a travel plan?
You keep looking at the map.
Don't let her know where you are going.
She's like a snake.
She will tell on you.
Don't you know
Tae is letting us get around on our own?
No, nobody told me.
But wherever you go, I'll tag along.
I'll find a quiet temple
to practice meditation.
A temple?
Not my thing.
I'll go with the others.
Zen, you haven't told me
why you chose to come here.
I want to see the ocean.
Although Fah is sure that
Zen can't be at the same place,
I won't be careless.
I think so too.
Because how they met here
is not just a coincidence.
Playing hide and seek?
Will this be a foul play?
I just want to see how you're doing.
Why didn't you say hello?
I don't know what to do.
Haven't you ever had a girlfriend?
It may be because
nobody makes me feel
like when my dad met my mom.
How?
My dad is Japanese.
He met my mom in Thailand.
He said the first time he saw her...
there was something
that made him feel like
she is the one.
Can I ask you something?
You must be honest. Don't lie.
Did you send someone
to spy on where I'm going?
Nobody has that much time.
To have the hotel staff watch you
is already more than their duty.
Can I prove it one more time?
All right?
Hi Fah, you want ice-cream?
Don't tell Zen or your friends at Ryokan
that I'm here.
You came here unnoticed,
like God sent you to represent us.
Represent what?
Our message to Bas.
What do you want to tell him?
Good evening.
You're glad to see me, I guess.
Looking for souvenirs?
Yes. We'll go back soon.
I still can't find souvenirs for the kids.
I saw Fah walking somewhere here.
I wanted to say hello, but she's gone.
Pop told you, right?
He did.
All right, I admit you are good.
But it's not that difficult, is it?
Everybody comes here in the morning.
Try another place.
So I take it that
we met at the last place?
What time do you want me
to find you again?
Okay.
See you.
Anything I can help?
What do you mean?
Fah told me where she is going today.
I can tell you,
but you have to keep secret
that it's from me.
If you do that,
it's a foul play
and it won't be destiny.
If you don't talk, I won't.
Who'd know?
Many couples only realize
that they are not soulmates
after they have children.
So I think destiny doesn't matter
in our lives.
By the afternoon, Fah must be at...
I don't need you to tell me.
If Fah and I meet seven times,
you will admit that
Fah and I are made for each other.
And you won't come between us again.
Can you do it?
If that's what Fah wants,
I'll respect that.
But on the contrary,
if you don't make it
to the same places as Fah,
will you stop?
I always follow the rules.
Only three more places.
And the sun will set late today.
I'll see you again. I'm dead sure.
Fine.
If we meet again,
I'll buy you a meal.
CHANKO HOTPOT
Welcome!
Welcome and come inside please.
Hey, you.
I almost went to the wrong place,
but I recognized you told me that
you'd buy me a meal. So I came here
and found you.
All right, eat up.
Two glasses of beer.
Welcome. May I take your order?
-Draft beer.
-Two draft beers? Okay.
-Is that all? Okay.
-Thank you.
And don't get drunk
like when we first met.
Of course, I can't be drunk.
I have a mission tomorrow.
I have to go to the most mysterious place
before I can return as a winner.
We'll see.
Let me know if you want to throw up.
No.
It's a waste.
I swallowed it.
You're so stingy even with puke.
Tough people don't throw up.
Are you out to meet Zen?
I thought this was over.
I saw you celebrate last night.
No, two more places.
But he won't find me this time.
Only a half day left.
You want Zen to go to the wrong places?
Come back before the train, okay?
OKAZAKI RYOKAN
Are there more inside?
Bring them here.
Are you okay?
Destiny is just a made-up thing.
I've been played again.
THREE MONTHS LATER
King Shah Jahan might have
a too high level of Oxytocin.
That's why he built the
Taj Mahal in 16 years.
And Oxytocin is...?
A hormone that makes you feel attached to
someone you live with for a long time.
Ugh.
What is it?
I want to go.
Go then.
It's just the two of us?
With a tour group of over forty people.
Why?
You're afraid
that people will misunderstand?
Something like that.
I tried to invite your friends,
but nobody is interested.
Of course,
we've just come back from Japan.
Who would want to spend more money?
How about holidays in Thailand?
I'm sure all your friends will come.
Where is it?
There is someone I helped before.
He wanted to take his family
to a birthday party
in a luxurious hotel in Rayong,
but his wife got sick
so he had to cancel everything.
But the accommodation
and meals are still there.
Shall we?
About this trip to Rayong...
Tae has paid for everything
so he can ask Fah to marry him.
He wants us to be the witnesses.
We'll move at eight o'clock.
After that, there will be some problems
and we can't go.
So we'll let Fah go first.
Actually, we leave at six o'clock.
Whoa, I can't get up that early.
Come on, you crybaby.
I saw you carry the luggage in the airport
You can manage even at 3:00 or 4:00 a.m.
And we have to do that for...?
For Fah to meet Tae,
who's waiting for her.
And they'll have time to be alone.
When it's the right time,
Tae will propose.
And when Fah says yes,
we'll storm in to congratulate them.
We'll spread the rose petals
all over the place
and get drunk from dusk till dawn.
Do you understand?
I almost get it.
But what excuse
are we going to give to her?
Why do we follow her later?
I'll tell her that
you hurried to work a morning shift,
but you dropped some luggage on your foot.
And we'll take care of you, so we're late.
Why me?
I'm not a careless person.
But you have a careless look.
That's it.
Tae has invested so much.
Don't be fussy.
Beautiful.
Yes. All of them.
When will you take a photo
of the one you have a crush on?
Then I can read her personality,
and see if you can bluntly
tell her how you feel?
I can't.
It might ruin our friendship.
Even easier as friends.
Really?
You find the right moment,
look into her eyes, and say...
"I like you."
Let's try.
I like you.
Yeah, that's it.
-Next time you see her, say it like that.
-Hey, Pao.
I like you.
In the past three months
that I told you about...
Hey, I think this beer tastes strange.
Let me buy a new one.
Pao.
I like girls. Okay?
Why did you get my hopes up?
What hope?
I gave you nothing.
You are my friend, Mek.
But you took it the wrong way.
We should be apart for a while.
No ginger, please.
Yes.
You don't like ginger?
I can eat it. I like it.
What is this?
Ginger tea.
Did you forget that I don't like ginger?
Next time when we meet,
I'll call you Ginger Man.
I'm sorry, this one has no ginger.
What's up, Mek?
Will you drink with me, Fah?
I'm heartbroken.
Heartbroken?
When did you have a girlfriend?
Are you fooling yourself and
getting heartbroken?
What?
You like men?
Since when are you gay, Mek?
Our parents will have a heart attack
when they find out.
Did you just wake up?
What took you so long?
Yeah, there was a little accident.
The luggage fell on Pop's foot,
so we have to stay and take care of him.
You go ahead, don't wait for us.
We'll be there around midday.
Why should I go there first?
Did you just wake up, or are you drunk?
I'm a bit drunk.
I'm drinking with Mek.
Hey, he will go to Rayong too.
Huh?
Mek won't go.
Tell him no. There's not enough room.
He said he can sleep on the beach.
Right?
I can't reach them.
What are they doing?
Where are we?
We'll be in town in about half an hour.
What time is it now?
Why does it still look early?
Where I come from, it's called evening.
It's almost 5:00 p.m. now.
Are we not there yet?
Driver, where are we going?
-We're going to Ranong.
-What?
Ranong!
The driver said Pueng told him "Ranong".
Even the hotel name is Ranong.
Rayong, I said Rayong. Damned driver!
You got me into trouble.
If you didn't turn off your phone,
this wouldn't have happened.
Mek told me to.
He said it would disturb his sleep.
You stay at Ranong tonight,
and come back tomorrow.
I'll call to book a hotel for you.
Thank you, Tae.
Then I won't roam around to find a room.
Since I'm here, I'll look around a bit
so Mek can feel better.
Have a great time in Rayong, guys.
Bye.
Come on, nobody blames you.
I am not good with young people's lingo.
Once I was asked to drive to Chiang Rai,
and I heard Chiang Khan.
To Nokhon Chai Sri,
I heard Nakhon Sri Thammarat.
That's why my life is a mess.
But he shouldn't make me
think he likes me.
It was that obvious, and he said no.
My gaydar is always correct.
He lied to me.
He didn't.
My ears are bad.
Don't blame the customers.
May I show you the bill?
I haven't asked for it.
Just for your information.
Sixty-four thousand!
A fine? Two thousand baht fine!
What fine?
Our restaurant is at a public park,
where drinking alcohol is not allowed.
But those two...
Don't panic.
We have this problem very often,
so we have a special
service to reduce the bill.
What service?
If Fah realizes that it's you guys' plan,
you'll be in trouble.
Just don't tell her.
Play pranks on people sometimes.
Life is fun.
Here's the bill for the food and the fine.
Thank you.
They eat a lot, don't they?
-Here.
-Yes.
Tell that girl that she dances really well
so the restaurant doesn't charge her.
You know how to prank people.
Don't you want to say hello to her?
Yeah, meeting like this
is not a coincidence.
Mek,
come on.
Now. Get up. Get up.
Go.
I'm about to go to the morning market.
Mek? He's not up yet.
Let him rot in the hotel.
Sure, if I see something interesting,
I'll call you.
Yes. Bye-bye.
Stop!
This dancing creature...
is it a human or a spirit?
This is not in the game plan.
How do you end up here?
I'm looking into Ranong mineral water.
Cooperation between me and Sendai Mining.
How about you?
You're here for holidays with Mek?
How do you know I'm with Mek?
Random guess.
Who are you with?
With the four boys.
Ae is from here,
so he volunteers as a guide.
The three of them
are here for their holidays.
They went to thank Bas
for helping them graduate.
Bas?
How?
Well, now tell me
why you want me.
-Or...
-we want to graduate.
What?
The psychic told us
that one of us had to sleep with you
so we will graduate.
Now we are here, so just choose one.
Just get it over with.
Fine.
You want to graduate?
I choose all of you.
Don't be shy,
you're ready, right?
Bend over slowly.
Now.
Bow a little more.
Perfect position.
Take that! Take that!
If sleeping with me
makes people pass exams,
I would have a PhD by now.
You want to pass the exam?
Yes.
Bring your books.
If you read but don't remember,
I'll hit you.
Damn kids.
This hot spring is natural.
This largest one is the main one.
Why did you bring eggs?
To make soft-boiled eggs.
Even his eggs can be cooked,
so why wouldn't our balls be?
The hot bath and
the hot spring are different.
Do we have boat tickets to
Koh Payam for everyone?
What? Only two?
We have booked in advance!
We only have two tickets to Koh Payam.
You and Fah should go ahead.
It's easy to get around on the island.
The boat is arriving soon.
Hurry up.
When it snows in Sendai, it's very cold.
Unlike here.
If I faint, don't be mad.
How could it not be hot,
your clothing doesn't match the weather.
The world is getting hotter.
Or is Thailand always this hot?
When I was a kid,
it was still cold this month.
Let's find a drink.
How is it?
Is it cooler now, Japanese boy?
What are you doing? Fine.
Wait. I'll get wet.
Hey, I'll get wet.
I'll get wet. No. No.
You have to.
What are you doing?
From Bangkok, huh?
This is inappropriate.
Do you know where the water is from?
From the tap?
No.
From there,
the reservoir that the king gave us.
People here know the value of water.
It's very difficult during the dry season.
What now?
You always think about bullying others.
Yeah, you saint!
You never bullied anyone in your life?
Not that I remember.
Only teasing at most.
From now on,
you can bully me. I allow you.
Why bully?
Well, your life will be more colorful,
not so bland like it is now.
Look at this.
A heart-shaped rock.
Like in Sendai.
What heart? I can't see.
Here. Look at this.
Here, do my hands look like it?
Ding!
Heartbeats.
Beep. Beep.
Beep. Beep. Double. Beep beep.
An upside down heart.
For one with a change of heart?
On the day that we bet,
I went to the heart-shaped rock.
Where did you go?
I went to the fox park.
I thought a fox like you
would go visit your friends.
So you lost.
If we guess what's in each other's minds,
you'd score more points.
Because we're staying
at the same hotel, right?
Correct.
I'll go to my room now.
Are you all right?
Fah!
You met Zen here,
and I'm starting to believe in destiny.
Do you have any idea
why I invited you to Rayong?
Is there a hidden agenda?
I was gonna propose to you.
Will it really be okay for us?
To be together?
If we were in Rayong,
I can really say yes.
But I am not sure now.
Can I have another chance, Tae?
If the answer is still you,
I will then be confident
about us... please?
Excuse me.
Can you call room 341?
I'm sorry. The client has checked out.
-Checked out?
-Yes, he left in the early morning.
THREE MONTHS LATER
Hello.
Yes, I booked a table for ten.
Inside, please. The second table.
There are your parents, and the rest?
Why did you book for so many?
Only relatives and my mom's friend.
They want to see the in-laws.
Is this Sompong's?
No, I'm Tuk's son.
What name did you book the table under?
Sompong booked it, so I go by that name.
For the rotating saving group,
we go by the one who booked the table.
Rotating saving group?
Let me call my mom.
Can you help me
create a photo album on Line?
These photos.
Yes.
Oops, you went to Sendai?
Have you been there?
-I have.
-You know, I almost became disabled.
I fell over there.
Luckily someone caught me,
and it was a Thai man.
I was told the exact location.
So embarrassing.
Tae, wait here a moment.
I have something to ask that lady.
What is it?
I've just realized that
the day I bet with Zen,
he went to the heart-shaped rock as well.
You fell at the heart-shaped rock?
Are you OK?
It hurts.
Are you Thai?
After he helped me, he hurried back.
Said he had an appointment
with someone at noon.
I didn't know what was wrong.
When he is excited
or uses too much strength, he faints.
The staff took him to the hospital.
Seriously, are there photos or anything
to prove that it's Zen?
And if it was really him,
Why did he lie
to you that he didn't go there?
He must have wanted to reject you
so he took that chance.
What are you talking about?
There is no beer on the table.
Pueng, get some beer. I'm thirsty.
Here's yours.
I was about to close the shop
and Tae turned up like a ghost.
He said he found it in Japan
and realized that you want it.
He bought you sweets.
So romantic.
I asked him to.
It's my mom's birthday present.
He might have forgotten.
But I got them from someone else already.
Your mom likes sweets?
She collects them.
How strange.
Hey.
I remember now.
On the day that you were drunk
and wrecked the wedding,
I called Tae to come to help,
and he told me to say
that the gift was for Mom.
Then he went in.
It was to trick you to go home,
but he lost it.
This is not mine.
I've been looking for the owner.
But Tae was looking for you.
He lost the present,
and couldn't find you,
and Pai dumped him
because he didn't turn up for the date.
But he has a reason for not telling you.
How do you know?
At Ranong,
Zen told me.
On the day we bet,
I went to the same place as Fah.
I went to the heart-shaped rock.
Why are you telling me this?
Me telling you this...
doesn't mean that I am asking
for her back.
But I want you to know I lost that game
because I had to.
Why?
I have a problem that is wrecking my life.
If she chose me,
her life would be full of sadness.
She would never find happiness,
and I don't want her to be like that.
I believe there will be no one
who takes better care of her than you.
Idiots.
You both are idiots.
I'm selfish.
I didn't want to tell you.
I didn't want to lose you to him.
SENEN RIFU HOSPITAL
His condition is getting worse.
He's been unconscious for five days now.
There will be a chance
that he'll wake up again, right?
I hope for a miracle.
Like in the last minute,
we could find a stem cell donor for him.
We have been looking for years,
and still haven't found anyone.
Zen, you have to be patient.
There must be a match for you.
We are soulmates. We get to be together.
I didn't think anyone
could make me believe in destiny.
But you can.
So you have to wake up
and take responsibility for what you did.
Did you know
you made me believe in love again?
You made me fall in love again, Zen.
So please... can you wake up?
Please, Zen.
He recorded this
and told me that when
you come back to Sendai,
I should give it to you.
When I sit here drinking ginger tea,
I always think of a woman
who declared herself an enemy of ginger
but a friend of beer.
Actually,
I think she is not good at drinking.
Just sniffing it, she can get drunk.
So today,
I want to invite that woman
who doesn't eat ginger
to listen to the benefits of ginger
right now.
If you feel bloated or gassy,
drinking ginger tea
or eating fresh ginger
makes you feel better.
Furthermore, it cures car sickness
and nausea.
I'm sorry, Fah.
I don't talk sweet,
but I really care about you.
Goodbye.
THREE MONTHS LATER
Here it is.
-Thank you.
-Please come again.
Have a nice flight.
She works so hard
that she became
the best employee three months in a row.
Have you heard of
''putting on a brave face''?
Yes.
Let me know if you need help.
Where do I pay?
I hope for a miracle.
Like in the last minute,
we could find a stem cell donor for him.
Hello, Mek. What's up?
I'm in Japan.
Mom cleaned up the house and she
found a letter from the Red Cross to you.
I thought it could be
important, so I opened it.
Is it what I hope it is?
The letter said something like...
your are a match with a patient.
What is the result
of my parents' health check-up?
Your family history has high
potential for diabetes and hypertension.
I don't want my children to risk it.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Excuse me.
Have we met before?
Of course. We are...
Zen is conscious.
But he still can't remember anything.
The doctor said it will take a while.
Zen,
this is Fah.
The Fah you said destiny sent to you.
I'm sorry.
I really can't remember you.
We met at the wedding.
I was so drunk,
and I was arrested for drunk driving.
And you helped me.
Then we had rice soup.
You like ginger but I don't.
Then I...
Maybe we have really met,
but I've just recovered from
a medical condition.
I don't want to think too much.
Can you please proceed with the payment?
I'm in a hurry.
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey. Isn't that Zen?
He doesn't remember me.
Why? I haven't proven anything so far?
What else do I have to do?
Have you finished work?
Do you want rice soup?
What?
I saw that there is
a rice soup restaurant in the airport.
I want to invite you to join me.
I want to know if it is as good as...
the place you took me to.
You remember me now?
A rare woman like you,
I won't forget so easily.
But I just talked to your mom.
She told me you can't remember
anything in the past year.
"You just need to give him
some time, Fah."
My mom said that, right?
I wrote a script for her.
Whoa, sneaky!
-My mom?
-You are, moron!
Why did you do this?
You have fun while another is suffering.
Wasn't it you who asked me
if I have ever bullied anyone in my life?
Here, this life...
once.
Just this one time.
So do you want rice soup?
No.
But the toppings are really good
at this place.
Okay.
They said the ginger is good here too.
Dad.
This is the girl I told you about
so often.
She saved my life.
Tell your dad about our destiny too.
Anytime I visit him,
I only talk about it.
Tell him again. He won't be bored.
So I'll start here then.
I went to this wedding,
and saw a drunk woman wrecking the party.
Hey, not this one.
Fast forward. Change the subject.
Change the subject.
Fine.
About a woman who was a thief
and took what was mine.
There are many other good stories.
Tell good stories.
-Good stories?
-Yeah.
All right.
This is a story about destiny.
Yeah, this one is good.
Destiny brought me to a woman
at the breathalyzer checkpoint.
Oh man.
It's true.
Say whatever you want. Suit yourself.
Really?
And I had to bail her out.
But luckily, she wired
the money back to me.
Hey.
You still want to be my friend?
A good friend like you...
it would be a shame to lose.
I'm sorry.
I'm taking a photo of the bird.
-This bird?
-No
The bird in the tree.
I'm sorry.
No problem.
Destiny.
Yes. Destiny decides who your soulmate is.
No matter how far they are apart.
It's already pre-destined
that you will finally meet
and fall in love.
Destiny?
Did she tell you?
She totally believes you.
She told me
that destiny will send her a soulmate.
Do you want me to tell her
that she was conceived because her parents
made love the first time
they met without condom?
Don't be loud, she would hear it.
Hello.
Are you the person in this photo.
No, no, no. But this one looks familiar.
As if I've just seen her around.
Definitely not us.
But the girl in the photo...
looks exactly like her.
Let's settle this at the police station.
-Excuse me.
-"Chotto" means "hold up"!