TAWEETANSAMAI
At 8 p.m. last Tuesday,
Pol. Sub-Lt. Chidchob Kobkarnklai
led his men
to raid a house on Sukhumvit 38,
which was owned by Boonchu Kiatkrai.
After searching the premises,
the police found
a stash of illegal Buddha heads
and other religious artifacts
hidden inside the house.
The housekeeper, Somjai Niantae,
stated during the interrogation
that the tenant,
Mr. Samuel Victor,
a 54-year-old American expat,
has an extensive criminal record
in trading illegal antiques around Asia.
Police are still looking
for Mr. Victor,
who has fled the scene
and is believed
to be hiding
somewhere
in northeastern Thailand.
14 HOURS AGO
Three are actually more useful than two.
Yes.
That's a lot of stuff.
What are you celebrating today?
Yes.
Hello, Kwan.
Will you go to Lin's engagement party?
No. My car broke down.
You can ride with me.
It will be a big party.
You should show your support.
You're dating Ann.
Bring her along and show her off.
No way.
So the rumor that she dumped you is true.
Where did you get that?
I was the one who dumped her.
Look who's talking.
If a girl like Ann dumps you,
you're beyond help.
You'll have to find somebody
who has too much of something, like you.
Asshole.
A CHILD WITH THREE ARMS WAS FOUND,
VILLAGERS ARE WORSHIPING HIM
Everybody has something
they don't want to see in the mirror.
For some people,
a tiny pimple
can look like a huge stone.
Crow's feet, too.
Or baldness.
Or a big belly.
I completely understand those people.
Sometimes,
they can look away
and pretend not to see their defects.
But those people can never understand me.
No matter how hard I try to ignore it,
this extra arm
sticks out as if it's mocking me.
TAWEETANSAMAI
Lin has stolen my heart
since we were in high school.
To tell you the truth,
I was quite popular back then.
I was the star
of the school's volleyball team.
My third arm came in handy
every time we wanted to fake a move.
THE TENTH PROVINCIAL
YOUTH VOLLEYBALL COMPETITION
Everybody wanted me to be on their team.
Lin was the star of her class.
Don't move.
Your arms are amazing.
However, my athletic life
existed only in the school's playground.
When it came to real matches
against other schools,
I couldn't participate.
They said I was breaking the rules.
My arm was an unfair advantage.
Where is it?
How did you know?
Let's go again.
One, two...
Whenever I'm with you,
I never know which hand to hold.
Does it matter?
It's still one of my arms.
It's hard for me
when everybody stares at your arms.
I used to think that
I'd get used to it one day.
But it's just impossible.
Do you think my arm is disgusting?
No.
I mean, we were younger back then.
Don't think too much.
Just tell me
who this guy is.
Don't be mad at him.
I just get along better with him.
Who else
can satisfy you
the same way my arms can?
But he has a device from Italy.
A DEVICE?
FROM ITALY?
My job isn't exactly cool.
Who wouldn't want to be cool?
Ann, take this to the supervisor.
I don't have any talents.
I'm just an ordinary guy with three arms.
So I ended up sorting mail
at the post office.
It's perfect.
I work in the back.
I don't need to see anybody.
These World Cup cards keep pouring in.
Yet, it's strange.
When the piles of mail
in front of me get so big,
I can't help but feel
that having four arms
would be even better.
EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH
TRAITHEP BOONSET
I GUESS EVERYBODY KNOWS
Today's my birthday.
Here's your birthday present.
You bought this for my birthday?
I saw this on the street for just 59 baht.
Are you putting a price on my goodwill?
It's not the price.
I'm upset because you didn't even try
to get me a decent gift.
Of course, I tried.
I bought it
because I think it fits your lifestyle.
My lifestyle?
A rubber lizard?
I know you're not in love with me.
You're with me
because you don't think I'm pretty,
because you don't think
I'll dump you, right?
Who said that I don't love you?
I do love you, Ann.
Liar. You don't love me.
You just couldn't bear to be alone
after Lin ditched you.
Were you that desperate
to pick an ugly duckling like me?
Ann.
You think my arm is disgusting, don't you?
Don't change the subject.
What I can't stand
is the fact that you don't love me.
Everyone warned me about it,
but I didn't believe them.
If you really love me, prove it.
-How?
-I don't know. Just prove it.
I knew it. Jerk! You're a freak.
You're a jerk with three arms.
Kwan.
Yesterday, I dropped by Tawee's shop.
He said your new shirt
for Lin's engagement party
is ready.
He asked you to come and pick it up.
Are you really going?
The whole town is speculating about it.
I don't think you should go.
I placed a bet.
I bet you wouldn't dare show your face.
Mister. Why did you have to tell everyone?
I never said I would...
go.
Your shoulders...
Perfect.
Your arm.
One at a time.
Perfect.
Thank you, Tawee.
Remember,
a man must look for things that suit him.
Do you understand?
That's right. The clothes sold at shops
are for normal people.
But you,
you need something special.
What does "special" mean?
It means you're special.
But what is "special"?
Something extraordinary.
Well...
It's like when you order
a special kind of pad thai.
I see.
Look.
Your new shirt
is ready.
Luckily, you found him
before he got bloated.
Tough luck, Kwan.
No more new shirts for you!
NO MORE NEW SHIRTS
I'm screwed.
Kwan, didn't you go
to Tawee's funeral yesterday?
I didn't have any shirts to wear.
That boy has a sense of humor.
TELEPHONE
Is this Dr. Somboon?
I'm Kwan.
Do you remember me?
You don't?
I...
I was on Life Finds The Way two years ago.
I'm the guy...
with three arms.
A few years back,
-this stupid TV show
-You remember now?
aired my story.
They turned me into a pathetic loser
who was living in total misery.
At first glance,
you'd think this boy's life
is no different from anyone else's.
But if you look closely,
you'll see something sticking out.
His extra left arm.
This is Traithep or Kwan,
a boy with three arms.
LIFE FINDS THE WAY
THREE-ARMED BOY
Here we are in the province of Lampang.
The extra limb we'd never see
on a normal human being
has made his life totally miserable.
He lives in a small house
by the railroad track,
where there used to be
a pad thai restaurant.
When his mother died,
Kwan didn't keep the business running.
His dream is to be able to wear
two-sleeved shirts like everyone else.
However,
Kwan's life will have to go on.
Because it's his life.
And because
life finds the way.
As soon as the show went on air,
this damn doctor called me.
This arm has blood vessels
directly connected to the heart.
To remove it, it will require
a risky
and expensive operation.
He'll need expert care.
Our center
is willing to perform the amputation
free of charge.
Chop your own balls off first!
Yes, I'll have the operation.
How soon can you do it?
It's too bad
you're leaving so suddenly.
I don't want you to quit.
World Cup cards are all over the place.
All right.
I wish you luck.
By the way,
can you recommend someone
who has your qualifications?
Hey.
HANDLE WITH CARE
-I already gave you a discount.
-Make it 40, please.
NIYOM PAD THAI ON CHAN ROAD
Damn it.
It broke down again.
Twenty thousand?
Your car is too old.
Even if I fix it,
it will just break down again.
I'll only make money by selling its parts.
But this was my mother's car.
Fine.
Twenty thousand, it is.
I'll go get the money.
Here.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Are you sure you're not
rushing into the arm thing?
I have no choice.
Tawee is dead.
I don't have shirts to wear.
What a stupid excuse.
Anyway, is the rumor true?
That Ann dumped you?
Where did you hear that from?
Do you think a guy like me
wanted to get serious
with a girl like Ann?
RICH MAN TRANSPORT
Oh, my...
Hello.
Hello, Piak. Hello, Kwan.
Why did you honk?
-Hey.
-Are you deaf or what?
What?
-What are you looking for?
-Your deaf ass.
Are you making money off Kwan's car again?
-Shut up, you jerk.
-Don't.
What's that? Superman with a snub nose?
Hey.
You don't know anything.
This is my get-rich-quick talisman.
The guardian of Northern bus drivers.
Do you see his hands?
He's grabbing a wad of cash
and bringing it to me.
Wow.
I bet it doesn't work.
-Why not?
-You have a lot of gambling debts.
You still haven't paid me back.
I haven't forgotten.
-Let's change the subject.
-Hey.
Kwan, do you want to sell your car?
Yes.
He's going to Bangkok
-to have his arm chopped off.
-What?
Really? That's big news!
Stop messing with me, will you?
If you're going to Bangkok,
I can give you a ride.
But I'm not leaving until later tonight.
Free of charge, just for you.
I have to return the bus
to Bangkok, anyway.
Boss wants me to drive it back.
It'll be the two of us.
I will drive. You can relax.
We can talk. We'll be there in a flash.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Kwan, come on up.
A superhero
always comes when you need him the most.
I thought you'd come at sunrise.
Come on, it's a free ride.
Don't complain.
Be careful with the turn.
Relax, I'm a professional.
Easy.
I really envy you.
-Stop it.
-Why?
Listen.
If I had three arms like you,
I'd grab a porn magazine with two hands
and I'd still have my third hand free
to give myself a hand party!
Or when I sleep with my wife,
I'd have a hand for each tit
and one more to get creative with.
Lorlee, your balls are working harder
than your brain.
Let's stop here.
I have to take a whiz.
What's that?
MEN
Let me go!
Are you crazy?
Don't.
-Damn it.
-No.
Where are you going?
Let me go. Leave me alone.
Let me go.
Don't play hard to get!
She's my wife. Mind your own business.
Since when was I your wife, pervert?
What's your problem?
A third arm. What are you?
He's down.
Damn you.
Take this.
What are you doing, Lorlee?
So he can't come after us.
Okay.
All right.
Look.
That's quite bushy!
It's disgusting.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Let's see what he's got.
What are you looking at?
No, what are you looking at?
Where are you going?
To see my husband in Bangkok.
My husband works there.
A man from the village gave me a ride.
Who would have guessed
that he'd pull over and try to rape me?
I would.
Your tits are like watermelons.
You can come with us.
We're going to Bangkok.
My name's Na.
Look!
-Oh, shit.
SGT. MAJ. PORNCHAI PONGPO
Why do you want to chop it off?
-Can't you just keep your mouth shut?
-Hey.
With those arms,
you'll get plenty of work in my village.
What sort of work?
Sorting green tea leaves.
Thai people drink green tea
more than water now.
Those Japanese firms
have put in a lot of money.
I'm not bragging,
but my village is getting rich
because of it.
Lorlee, wake me up when we get there.
Okay.
-Lorlee.
-Yes.
Why don't you get on the main highway?
Kwan.
We just beat up a cop.
If we get on the highway,
we'll get busted.
Just make sure I get there in time
for the appointment.
Relax, Kwan.
Thailand is a small country.
We'll get there in a flash.
Kwan, just a moment, please.
Wait for me. I've got something to do.
You guys can look for
something to eat first.
I'll stay here. You go ahead.
I don't want to go.
Come with me.
I don't know this place.
I don't want to go alone.
No, I'm sleepy. I'll get some sleep.
Pad thai sounds nice.
PAD THAI
No, I'm sick of it.
Let's have some steak.
STEAK
Here's your order.
-Miss.
-Thank you.
Is this a steak?
It's nothing like the one in the photo.
Yes, it's northeastern style.
Are we in the northeast?
Damn you, Lorlee.
Just eat your food.
Damn it.
Aren't you hot?
What about you?
You've been holding on to your phone
since we were on the bus.
Are you waiting for a call
from your husband?
Listen, I have an awesome ringtone.
Try calling me.
I don't have a phone.
I have nobody to call.
It's Lorlee.
Miss, check, please.
Where is he running off to?
Where are you going? Stop.
-Shit.
-Hey.
Wait.
Hey.
Oh, no.
-Hey.
Pay me 70 baht for the steaks.
-Stop the bus. I got the wrong girl.
-Wait.
-Stop the bus.
-Hurry.
-Wait for me.
Wait for me.
I said, stop!
They're gone. Let's follow them.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
Go!
Her arm was way too fat
to be mistaken for mine.
Who are they, Lorlee?
The thugs from the casino.
I lost to them and owed them money
so they came after me.
What kind of casino opens in the morning?
Are you kidding?
Gambling dens never close.
Damn it, they're here.
I shouldn't have come with you!
Hurry. Don't let them get away. Hurry.
Don't let them get away. Follow them.
-Hey.
-Stop.
Kwan, we are safe.
Kwan, what should we do?
How would I know?
Oh, no.
Just go through them.
I can't.
Don't!
-Oh, no.
-What?
The engine died!
Restart it.
How much do you owe them?
Forty-five thousand.
Forty-five thousand?
-Yes.
-You were there for five seconds.
Yes.
Hey.
Come down here, you bastards.
All of you.
Why were you with them?
Ask them.
Search them.
Hey.
A three-armed man.
Put him on show at a temple fair
and then you can pay off your debts.
-Hey.
-What's your problem?
Stop moving or I'll chop off your arm.
That's good.
You don't need to go to Bangkok for it.
Watch your mouth.
Wow.
With boobs like that,
you can sell her for a lot of money.
You watch too many soap operas.
This is all they've got.
-Is this all?
-That's my money.
-What's your problem?
-Hey.
Stop resisting or I'll...
Give me my 70 baht.
-Why?
-They haven't paid me yet.
-Your 70 baht?
-Yes.
All right. Take it. How annoying.
How hard was that?
Lorlee.
What are you going to do?
This hardly covers what you owe me.
And we haven't even started with
what you did to my car.
That's your problem.
What do you expect me to do?
It's 45,000 baht.
Shit, the police are here!
Let's go.
Come on.
-Police!
-Help.
-Help us.
-Hey.
Kwan, the police are here.
I said, stop.
Stop right there.
-Hey.
-Stop.
I feel sorry for you.
Why?
You're crippled for life.
If I saw you in the dark,
I'd run for my life.
-What's up, sir?
-Kid, excuse me.
Can I take a picture with you?
-I'll show my wife.
-Good.
-She likes weird things.
-Sure. Go ahead.
-All right.
-Do you know how?
-Yes. Are you ready?
-Do you want one?
-Okay. Two fingers, please.
-No.
How can you put up two fingers?
He's got three hands,
put up three fingers.
You're right.
Three fingers, then.
-Three fingers.
-Three fingers, okay.
-Smile. Click.
-One, two...
One more, please.
-Please.
-One more.
-Okay. One more.
-He's a rare species.
Not bad, sir. That's good.
Smile.
Click.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Save one for me, will you?
-I'll show my friends.
-Thank you so much.
Good luck.
Are you a human or an octopus?
You've got a lot of arms.
Sir.
Let them go.
If he didn't let us go,
I would have blackmailed him
with this photo,
I would've even sent this to his wife.
Look.
Oh, my god.
Mom, it's all torn up.
Okay, ask for money from your dad
when he returns.
Hello, Yod.
Thank you for letting us
stay here tonight.
Make yourself at home. It's no problem.
Thank you.
Hey.
Let's eat. I won a lot today.
I'm waiting for tonight's match.
So which team do you like?
Any team that wins.
What a joke.
Come on. Which one?
Well, Germany.
I like England.
Do you like Beckham?
-He looks like me.
-Germany...
Come again?
It's getting cold. Let's go.
It's lonely out here.
It's okay. We can shower together.
Oh, no.
Oh, my god.
Kwan.
-What?
-I think it's payback time.
Hey.
Let's take a peek.
No, I don't want trouble.
Oh, my... You like her, right?
I can tell, Kwan.
But she's already got a husband.
Lorlee.
Shut up.
I'm broke and we're stranded here
because of you.
Go fix your bus.
Yes, sir.
Three arms?
Yes.
Our family has been jinxed.
Will he bring us bad luck?
We are screwed.
Lorlee brought us bad luck.
I'm betting on Germany tonight too.
Why don't you kick him out?
Calm down.
Tonight's match,
if Germany wins,
-So?
-it means he's a good luck charm.
But what if they lose?
You've got a point.
Will this thing ever run again, Lorlee?
This is a piece of cake.
It will be done soon.
You can sleep first.
I'll wake you up when it's fixed.
If you can't fix it,
I'll take the bus tomorrow.
Aren't you afraid
that people will look at your arms?
You're looking at them again.
Come on, Germany.
I'd be a better player than you.
Run faster, idiots!
Quick!
Do better, please.
They're stupid. I knew it.
He is a jinx.
Asshole!
Kwan.
-Wake up.
-What?
What is it? I want to sleep.
Well, you can't.
-Oh, no.
-What?
Oh, no.
Shit.
Lorlee!
-Lorlee!
-I'm sorry, Kwan. I need to borrow it.
Please forgive me.
Lorlee, give me my mother's ashes.
-Lorlee!
-Oh, shit. I thought it was cocaine.
Damn it. I almost snorted his mom.
Mom.
Sir, can you give us a ride?
Come.
Hey.
What's wrong with him?
What the hell...
Mister, can you give us a ride?
Of course. Get in.
Thank you. Let's go.
Come on.
Mom.
I was robbed.
I don't know.
How should I know?
I don't even have enough to eat.
Why are you complaining? I don't know.
I don't know where I am.
What's your problem now?
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
You're closed on Sundays.
So I'll have to wait until Monday?
Okay.
Hey.
Why didn't you tell me you needed a phone?
You could have borrowed mine.
I didn't want to bother you.
See?
Now you've only got five baht left.
Five or twelve, it makes no difference.
Can you call me?
My ringtone is really nice.
Why should I? You're right here.
I want to hear my ringtone, please.
Don't be stupid.
Call me, please.
Please.
No one has called me
for over a year.
Why don't you just cancel your number?
Then my husband won't be able to reach me.
What's your number?
I've been waiting for somebody
To wander my way
To have a conversation with
To see his face
To say hello
To...
Wasn't it beautiful?
Why did you answer it?
I'm right here.
The last five baht.
I forgot.
Hold on!
Then,
let's just talk until the money runs out.
Now you can talk to me through the phone.
What do you want to talk about?
Say something before the credits run out.
I can't think of anything.
Say whatever you want.
Just talk to me.
Let's go.
Eat it. Don't think too much.
I can't. We bought it with dirty money.
What's so dirty about donation money?
You stole it.
They donated the money to charity.
We used the money
because we're broke and starving.
The donors are still doing good deeds.
And we didn't take it all,
we just took enough to buy a meal.
Eat it. We don't know
when we'll get to eat again.
A guy like me doesn't need
to eat something bought with stolen money.
Here.
Isn't this considered stealing too?
Somebody owns these trees.
It's not the same.
The owner neglected them.
Catch it.
Throw it properly!
It's perfectly ripe.
-Hey.
-Hey!
I'm sorry.
Throw it one at a time.
It looks kind of weird. Can we eat it?
It doesn't look weird.
You don't know anything.
This tastes great.
What are you doing there? Come here.
Come this way.
-Let's go this way.
-Let's go that way.
We can't go that way.
Trust me, it's this way.
The train's coming. Come here.
Na.
Do you know
the legend surrounding this tree?
What legend?
You see,
it has golden leaves.
In the olden days,
the leaves weren't gold.
They were green like every other tree.
But this tree didn't want
to be like other trees.
So it asked a god
to turn it gold.
Why?
I guess it wanted to be cool.
After the god turned it gold,
the tree got bored after a few days.
It wanted to be green again.
But the god
had ascended the Seventh Heaven
and couldn't come back.
That's why the leaves
remain gold to this day.
Did you make that up?
No.
And do you see that tree?
It used to be a very small tree,
much smaller than all the others.
So it then asked a god for help.
Hey,
stay away from my god.
How did you know?
Well, your god had ascended
to the Seventh Heaven, right?
So the tree asked an angel instead.
The angel was nice enough to let it grow.
However,
it became so tall
that the other trees
didn't want to stay near it.
It got stressed out.
So I begged the angel for help again.
The angel was kind
so she let it stay with this golden tree.
And even though
they're the last two trees on earth,
they're happy together.
Wait here, I'll hitch a ride.
No.
Let me do it. I got one this morning.
Come on. Let's take turns. I'll go first.
Don't forget to vote...
Let me try another one.
If you didn't have those boobs,
nobody would've picked us up.
But me?
I always have to cover my third arm.
Otherwise, they might run me over.
What's the point of hiding it
when it's a part of you, anyway?
Well, it won't be soon.
You'll miss it then.
Why would I? It's useless.
Unlike your breasts.
You can get a ride with them.
Okay, you're right.
People only look at my tits.
They ignore the rest of me.
Of course. They stick out like signposts.
You know people look at them,
so why wear such clothes?
Are you jealous?
No, you're crazy.
I wear these clothes
because if there's a guy
who doesn't look at my breasts,
it means he's an okay guy.
What do you mean "an okay guy"?
It means he's a nice guy.
You're dumb.
Men don't think that "sex"
and "personality" are the same things.
They think of them as different things.
Even the nicest guy
will look at your boobs
if he sees you in those clothes.
Sure, I'm dumb.
I have big tits and I'm dumb as a rock.
Happy?
I was joking.
I don't always look at your boobs.
Are you saying you're an okay guy?
Sure, I'm so useless.
What's the matter?
You don't have to get upset
because he didn't stop.
Do you only have three arms
or are you bald too?
I'll do it.
Please stop.
Will you please give me a ride?
Thank you.
Come on.
Hey, come up.
Please stop.
Come up.
You should go.
It's easier for us this way.
What if he tries to rape me too?
What?
Hello.
TOILET
Is that you, babe?
I'm about to stop. I need to poop.
I know. I'm not stopping anywhere else.
Yes.
All right. I'm almost in town.
My stomach hurts,
so I have to stop at a gas station.
Okay. Do you want anything?
Okay. I'll buy it for you.
Sir, please stop.
Please stop.
Who are you?
When did you get in my truck?
Where are you going?
Hey.
It looks kind of weird. Can we eat it?
It doesn't look weird.
You don't know anything.
This tastes great.
HOW COULD I DIE HERE?
IT WOULD BE THE MOST SHAMEFUL DEATH
A glowing light
and a voice,
they're calling for me.
Faces of angels appear before me.
They beckoned me to come to them.
If I had let them take me,
I wouldn't be sitting here now.
But it's strange.
The face I saw wasn't my mother's.
Aren't you going to say anything?
What's your name?
I am Thai.
What did you say?
There are more cops
than buffaloes around here.
Excuse me, may I see your license?
Where are you headed?
Get out of the truck.
We have to search it.
What's in the box?
They're all fish.
Search it.
They're fish.
I guess the fish aren't dead yet.
Bring them down.
Hey.
Come on. Hurry.
Get up.
Now, get up.
-I'm Thai.
-Where are you from?
Yes, I know.
Is that all you can say?
-I'm Thai.
Sure, you are.
Sing me the national anthem.
-I'm Thai.
Thailand embraces all people of Thai blood
Every part of the land
Belongs to Thai people
We've maintained our sovereignty
Because Thais are
United...
What the...
What more do you want?
I said I am Thai.
Why don't you believe me, Squad Leader?
I'm a sergeant, not a squad leader.
Whatever.
I have sung the anthem.
Immigrants can't speak Thai this well.
But you don't have an ID.
I told you, it got stolen.
Why don't you believe me, Squad Leader?
It's "Sergeant"!
But there's something
suspicious about you.
I'll have to run a check.
What is it? Just say it.
Cut off his dick! You son of a bitch!
You're a useless shithead. Bastard!
Everyone seriously tries to nail you.
Hey.
Don't be mad at me.
Please,
stop being mad.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
-Oh, my god.
-Hey.
Men are all bastards.
They all leave me on my own.
My husband is the worst.
He wanted to become a magician,
so he ran away with the troop
that came to perform.
He's been gone for a year
and never sent a word.
If someone hadn't found him
at a club in Bangkok,
I would've grown old waiting for him.
What if he doesn't want to come home?
What will you do?
My mom said
I can find myself a new husband.
I'm...
I'm glad I ran into you again.
Here.
Let's go.
Hold my hand
And together we can face the world
With me, you'll never walk alone
Hold my hand
I'm glad too.
No one will feel alone
And no one
Will walk alone
Watch your steps.
We have to find a place to sleep.
But we don't have any money.
It's like a school trip.
Keep it down.
It's a bit creepy.
If you were born back in the day,
men would want to jump you every day.
you wouldn't have a jacket
to hide your third arm.
Don't look.
CAN I TOUCH YOUR BOOBS?
What did you say?
-Pervert.
-What?
DID I SAY IT OUT LOUD?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Again?
My boobs again?
Does nobody care about my other parts?
What if I don't let you touch me...
What if we just kiss...
Do you want to?
Are you crazy?
I'm not going to touch or kiss you.
It was an accident.
I'm sorry.
Why not?
I said it was an accident.
I didn't mean to.
Look.
I...
I really won't mind if you kiss me.
What?
Can you not be so easy?
You have a husband.
All right.
Fine.
Who's there?
Hey!
Don't wake up late
or the morning shift guy
will take it out on me.
And just sleep, no messing around.
Respect the building.
Girl, your face is so pale.
-Did you lose something?
-What...
What do you mean?
Will I find it?
Accept it.
What's been lost is no longer yours.
Are you making things up?
Read mine.
This is a tough one.
Which one is your real palm?
All of them.
Just pick one for me.
They look totally different,
but they both speak of sadness.
You don't see
anything good in our lives.
I just told you what I saw.
I don't want to be sad.
I want to be happy.
It's up to how much you can spare.
I can use the money
to dispel your bad luck.
Do we need money?
We don't have any.
Then get ready
for what's coming.
Come here. Quick.
Don't do it.
Come on. We need to eat.
Don't do it, please.
Listen.
You can do your arm trick
at the temple lawn to earn some money.
I'm not a clown.
But we're hungry, aren't we?
Now we'll bless the congregation.
Two glasses of Coke.
Do you want some?
Tee!
-Tee!
Are you hurt? Thank you so much.
-Thank you so much.
Are you all right?
I told you to watch him.
Why didn't you?
Are you all right?
Thank you.
We can't accept it.
Take it.
I'll drive you
to the bus terminal tomorrow.
You can take the morning bus.
Take it.
Thank you so much. Sorry for the bother.
It's okay.
Kwan saved Tee's life.
This is the least I can do.
Stop playing, Tee. Dinner is here.
Come eat first.
Tee, wash your hands.
But, Mommy,
I just washed them.
Wash them again.
Wash your hands now.
-This is your favorite.
-Let me help.
Wow.
It's really delicious.
-Tee.
-No, Tee.
You can't eat that.
He's a cursed, three-armed freak.
You didn't listen to me.
I'm a disease.
Everybody has always been disgusted by me.
When I was born,
my father was shocked.
He was repulsed
by my three arms.
He ran away from us,
leaving my mother to raise me by herself.
A few years ago,
my mother heard that
he had moved
to Bangkok.
She insisted that I take her to see him.
But I never did...
until...
she passed away.
But who would want to see him?
What if he still found me...
disgusting?
I don't even dare to
leave the village.
Are my three arms really that hideous?
No.
You're okay.
Am I?
DON'T WAKE UP YET
DON'T...
Attention, please.
Passengers waiting for bus 21-1
headed to Bangkok,
please board platform 12.
Please make your way to the platform.
Right now...
HOURS: MONDAY TO FRIDAY
8 A.M. TO 5 P.M.
SATURDAY AND SUNDAY ARE HOLIDAYS
Do you still want to cut it off?
POR KUNGPAO CLUB
Oh, my... It's so scary
Will I... Will I die?
I guess we have to try
In order to find out
All right. Next,
we'll play our last song for tonight.
Then the magician will take center stage.
I don't want to watch anymore.
You didn't tell me that you don't love me
You let me assume things
I thought we were friends
But if I leave,
then what will be the point
of fighting my way here?
You didn't tell me
You tricked me into dreaming
You made me confused
You tricked me into daydreaming
You let me be obsessed with you every day
What a twist! This is huge
Where are you going?
I need to pee.
This twist
Is making me lose control
Who will I get it back from?
Why didn't you ask for her number?
Her tits are the size of my head.
Damn.
I really want to nail her.
It looks like she wants it too.
You should go for it.
She's perfect for 69-ing.
Do you like 69-ing?
Can you handle it?
-Damn. Let's do it.
-Let's not do a 69.
Let's go for a sandwich.
The three of us will make a Big Mac!
How tasty.
We'll chew her up.
We'll chew her up really well.
-Are you blind?
-I'm sorry.
-Watch where you're going.
-I didn't mean to.
Do you think you're a hotshot?
-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
-Do you want trouble?
What the hell is wrong with you?
-What?
-I didn't mean to.
-Do you want trouble?
-Don't look at me.
-I'm sorry.
-What?
I really didn't mean to.
-I'm sorry.
-You have three arms,
so show them you're better than them.
If your friends hit you again,
just hit them right back.
You have more fists than they do, anyway.
So what now?
-What?
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
-Are you pissing me off?
-Do you think three arms are better?
Don't act so cool.
You're a hotshot?
Here. Take it.
So? Are you cool?
Take this.
-Take this.
-There.
Mom, I don't want to be special anymore.
I want to be normal.
You didn't tell me the truth.
That being "special"
also means being a monster.
I'm going home.
Don't chop your arm off.
We're both losers.
Which arm are you going to cut off?
Don't be angry with me.
Are you Kwan?
Mister.
Hello, Doctor.
Are you ready?
SHIT... IS IT ALREADY GONE?
DON'T CRY
Today's episode of Life Finds The Way
has the great honor
of witnessing a major medical achievement.
Doctor, how do you feel
after this successful operation?
And here's the man
who once had three arms.
He's now left with just two.
How do you feel now?
I...
I feel light.
It feels like something is missing.
Of course, your arm's gone.
Doctor.
After this operation,
do you have any other exciting operations
lined up?
Now, we have another patient.
-He's a man.
-I see.
However, somehow,
he's with child.
You can't take it back.
We need your arm
for genetic transplant research.
Yours is a major case study,
and your severed limb
will contribute to the future of humanity.
HUMANITY?
A special portion with eggs, please.
NIYOM PAD THAI ON CHAN ROAD
-He fell down.
-Where are you going?
Get up. Go.
-Catch him.
-Hey.
Stop right there.
A MIRACLE
Kwan, is that really you?
I thought it was someone else.
Who?
I don't know. Just someone else.
You don't have three arms anymore.
I thought you were someone else.
When did you cut it off?
You look funny with two arms,
it's so unlike you.
I just realized
that it's not about the arm.
It's the fact that
I don't have anyone like my mother
or Tawee in my life anymore.
TAWEE CHANHORM
BORN 1952, DIED 2006
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't go
to your engagement party.
I only have two arms now.
It was good that you didn't show up.
I would have been uncomfortable otherwise.
Excuse us, then.
We didn't send him an invitation, right?
No, we didn't.
Did I only lose my arm?
Or did I lose something else too?
EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH
Ann, are you busy?
Give Kwan a hand.
At this rate,
we'll miss the afternoon truck.
What a waste.
Hello.
Yes.
I can't talk. I'm working.
What's the point of having two arms now?
This is Kwan,
the three-armed man I told you about.
He's only got two arms now. Kwan.
You look so cool with two arms.
I was a fool, Mom.
I don't want to be normal.
I want to be special.
I want to be special to someone.
TRAITHEP BOONSET
Hello, Kwan.
How are you?
You never called me.
Are you still playing hard to get?
Look at me.
I'm a woman, but I wrote to you first.
Listen.
I have something to confess.
I didn't see the TV show that you were on.
I was very busy that day.
I was sorting tea leaves all day.
I shouldn't have missed it.
I wanted to see what you look like
with two arms.
I happened to see this photo
in the newspaper.
I was shocked!
Did you help the police catch a bad guy?
You're still playing the hero.
Kwan.
Don't worry.
You look even cooler with two arms.
When are you going to call me?
I've changed my ringtone.
I want to hear it.
I miss you.
It's...
It's probably an experiment
It's probably a test
For everyone
How much
Love have we got?
How much faith do we have?
Is it enough?
You live your life alone
And I live my life alone
We are walking in the emptiness
We're taking care of our lives alone
We're fighting just to make it each day
And one day
I will need somebody
Hold my hand
And together, we can face the world
With me, you'll never walk alone
Hold my hand
No one will feel alone
And no one
Will walk alone
You can rest
On these shoulders
I will have everything
That you want
This hand
Will wipe your tears
Even though things won't return
To how they were before
You live your life alone
And I live my life alone
We are walking in the emptiness
We're taking care of our lives alone
We're fighting just to make it each day
And one day, I will need somebody
Hold my hand
And together we can face the world
With me, you'll never walk alone
Hold my hand
No one will feel alone
And no one
Will walk alone
Hold my hand
And together we can face the world
And no one will walk alone
Hold my hand
And together, we can face the world
And no one will walk alone
It's...
It's probably an experiment
It's probably a test
For everyone
Subtitle translation by Kong Rithdee