THIS FILM IS INSPIRED BY A TRUE STORY
CHARACTERS, LOCALES
AND INCIDENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
AND HAVE BEEN CREATED FOR
THE SOLE PURPOSE OF ENTERTAINMENT
LORD BUDDHA ONCE SAID
TO MAUDGALYAYANA,
"THERE ARE TWO KINDS OF MIRACLES.
ANUSASANI, MIRACLES OF TEACHING,
AND ITHIRIDDHI,
MIRACLES OF MAGIC AND SUPERPOWERS."
BUDDHA ENDORSED THE FORMER,
BUT DIDN'T REJECT THE EXISTENCE
OF THE LATTER.
In 1945, World War II was about to end.
The country was bruised and battered.
Desperate people took up arms
and became bandits.
They robbed and killed the rich,
giving some back to the poor.
They were called the Blackshirt Bandits.
That year, I was sent to head
the Chai Nat Police Department.
NONG MAMONG, CHAI NAT PROVINCE
Sir, these Chinese hoodlums
must be from Suphan.
Members of Jek Ma's gang.
They must have stepped on the toes
of Bandit Fai,
and fled here to cause more trouble.
I heard this Jek Ma practices black magic.
He can make himself invisible.
Radio the district chiefs.
Chief!
Khun Pan has ordered an attack.
He thinks he's the boss?
Eat first.
Sir!
Sit tight.
Get down!
-I'm out of here.
-Get down!
Shoot!
Stop!
Kill him!
Go get him.
Don't let him get away.
Follow him. Kill him!
There!
Get him!
Protect me through the power
of Namo Buddhaya.
Susing susang arahang bhagava.
Chief!
-All dead?
-Except the women and children.
Good. Let's go.
Sons of crooks will grow up to be crooks.
We can't let them live.
Look, we're rich!
I'll take you alive
if you turn yourself in.
I don't think so, sir.
You know how the war has made us all poor.
Government servants like us
can't make ends meet.
What we impound from the thieves
goes to state coffers.
We risk our lives
and get nothing in return.
Am I right?
We...
pledge our loyalty to the nation
and to the people.
Being law enforcement officers
means you have to follow the rules
of law and justice.
You have to be ready to wage war
on all kinds of crimes,
and uphold the dignity
of the Royal Thai Police.
Sorcery is all about arming your mind.
To learn this art,
you must first free your mind.
Find samadhi,
and concentrate on your faith.
Remember,
what you believe
defines what you see and hear.
A great rock
is made of tiny grains of sand.
Its strength is transient
and it will soon return to nature.
Birth and death are parts of a cycle,
and what remains is energy.
To control this energy
is to define what you hear and see.
Namo tassa bhagavato arahato...
The magic formula.
Focus your mind on your enemy.
See the bullet coming at you.
Buddhang. Protect the skin.
Dhammang. The flesh. Sanghang. The bones.
Ohm. I'm indestructible.
Buddhang. Protect the skin.
Dhammang. The flesh.
Sanghang. The bones.
Ohm. I'm indestructible.
Use this power to protect others.
You know, Khun Pan
actually wanted us on that mission.
Luckily, we were off duty,
or we could've been in those coffins.
Khun Pan is invincible,
but his men aren't.
He always returns safely
while everyone else is dead.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Your husband was a brave policeman.
You should be proud of him.
He had such faith in you.
He told me that if you ordered him to die,
he would go and die.
Maybe you should be proud of that.
Excuse me.
I'm from
the Office of the Inspector General.
You're under investigation.
Pol. Maj. Gen. Khun Pan,
chief of the Chai Nat Police Department,
has committed excessive
and intemperate acts,
resulting in several deaths
of the officers under his command.
The extrajudicial killing of Chief Yun
was above his authority.
The Royal Thai Police rules that
Khun Pan is guilty of serious misconduct.
Therefore, the punishment is
his dismissal from the force.
However, since he has a record
of commendable service,
he will be suspended from duty
for an indefinite period.
Effective immediately.
SUSPENDED
PROVINCIAL POLICE REGION 1
Newspapers! The war is almost over!
-Who is he?
-That's the bad guy.
-He looks like a bandit.
-Your coffee.
Your coffee, sir. There you go.
HAPPY RETIREMENT, SERGEANT LAEM
Hey, will you go anywhere tonight?
-Come to the fair tonight.
-Yes, sir.
Bike safely.
-It's been a long time, hey
-Hey
-It's been a long time
-It'd be good if I could fuck you
Hey, Inn?
Give me those.
Right. Come. Your target.
Sir,
does the invisibility spell really exist?
Can you teach me?
I want to hide money from my wife.
Must be useful on payday.
Sergeant Laem,
have you ever misplaced a key?
Do you think the key is really lost,
or you just can't see it?
The invisibility spell works like that.
News of the hour.
The Blackshirt Bandits have robbed
opium dens in the central plains,
causing huge losses
to the concessionaires.
Now they've gone into hiding.
The police still have no clue
where to find them.
These bandits
think of themselves as tigers.
Have you ever heard these names?
Tiger Yom, Tiger Fai,
Tiger Mahesuan, Tiger Bai.
They're skilled in fighting
with black magic and tattoos.
They know which palms to grease.
Policemen like us can't do a thing.
Hello there!
What's that noise?
Firecrackers?
Hi, handsome.
Help! Run!
Yod. Hey!
-Yod.
-Move!
No.
The murders of our police officers
are an outrageous insult to the law.
I promise I'll do everything
within legal bounds
to bring the murderers to justice.
Eyewitnesses said the gunmen wore black
and covered their faces.
-Are they Bandit Fai's Blackshirt gang?
-Stop right there!
We couldn't make any arrest
without more evidence.
-Don't ask me that again.
-Deputy, sir!
Go ahead.
It's humiliating for the police
to be ambushed on their own turf.
Will that undermine
people's confidence in the force?
I'm a policeman.
I don't care about that.
My job is to put bad guys in jail.
-Deputy Padet, do you have...
-That'll be all.
-Deputy.
What's your plan
-for catching evil bandits?
-Will you be able to catch them?
Is it true that Bandit Fai is behind this?
It's strange
that they only targeted these guys.
What do you mean?
I found the victims' photos
on the guys you killed.
EVIDENCE NO.1
PHOTO OF SERGEANT LAEM
And they
were just low-level police clerks.
More like accountants.
Why did the Blackshirts have to take out
these unimportant men?
How well do you know these bandits?
Very well.
I was a doctor in Suphan before.
Bandit Fai
asked me to treat his men a few times.
There are two powerful men in Suphan.
One is a commissioner.
Governor Thammarong is one.
The other is Bandit Fai,
or General Fai.
All the top thugs
in the central plains are with him.
But among them,
Bandit Fai trusts Bandit Bai the most.
When a criminal wants to join the gang,
he has to put his name in a record book
which will be approved by Bandit Bai
and Bandit Fai.
Bai is the leader
of a local anti-Japanese movement.
They rob the Japanese and merchants
who cheat the villagers.
They steal from the rich
and give to the poor.
That's why the villagers cover for them.
In short,
people have no faith in the police,
and instead look up to the bandits.
PROVINCIAL POLICE REGION 1
Those police clerks
took bribes from the bandits.
Perhaps...
they asked for more,
or broke the deal with them.
So, the gang sent hit men to whack them.
They were a disgrace
to the police force.
Deputy Padet,
do you think Bandit Fai's Blackshirts
are behind this?
Anyone can wear a black shirt.
Fai may or may not be involved.
Anyway,
I'm glad to see your concern.
Don't worry,
I'll wage an all-out war
against these criminals.
You have been suspended...
so I don't think I can ask you to help.
The train carrying weapons and supplies
for the Japanese
will go to Kanchanaburi by way
of Bang Pla Ma at 4:00 p.m.,
every couple days.
But the next train will be the last one.
Last week, I was told to clear the tracks
all the way through.
Because this train won't make any stops
along the way.
Make sure it's all right.
-It's OK.
-Yes, sir.
ALY 2420
-Make sure it's all right.
-Yes, sir.
We've been robbed! Go find it! Go!
-Hey!
-Bia!
We're fucked, man.
Prepare to fire!
What the fuck are you doing?
Stop it.
-Son of a bitch.
-Sir, all stolen weapons are here.
Good.
-Assholes!
-Let me go!
-Assholes! I've told you.
-Scumbags! Assholes!
-Let me go!
Namo Buddhaya.
-Don't do it, Jap!
-Namo Buddhaya Yadha Budmona.
Don't do it, Jap! Don't do it!
Yadha Budmona
Namo Buddhaya Yadha Budmona.
Yadha Budmona...
Careful!
-Drop your weapons!
-Don't move.
No, it's nothing.
Kill them all.
-What are you doing!
-It's not me! I can't control myself!
My arms just move.
They move by themselves!
-No!
-I didn't do it.
Namo Buddhaya.
Bai!
Boss.
-Boss Fai.
-Bring their bodies back for a funeral.
Yes, boss.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Let's go.
Kamma, where's Mahesuan?
He can't make it. But he told us
-to follow your orders from now on.
-Fai.
Suphan is your territory.
Now you've got Bai and Mahesuan under you.
That means Suphan, Sing Buri and Ang Thong
are all yours.
Bro. I think...
you're becoming too big for your own good.
The more powerful you are,
the more attention you'll attract.
Your Chai Nat gang
has quite a large headcount.
If you join us, we'll become untouchable.
The authorities won't dare mess with us.
Trust me,
we should stick together.
Cheers.
Boss Fai,
the Chai Nat gang may have lots of tigers,
but their guns are all rusty,
Yom, I'll let you use mine.
You wanna test me?
To see if my gun's all rusty?
I just want to know
if it's true that Tiger Yom
is the fastest draw in Chai Nat.
Enough! If you don't want to join me,
I won't force you.
Just stick to our own turf then.
But if I ever hear
that you've stepped on my toes
here in Suphan,
we're not going to be drinking buddies
like this again.
Let's go.
-Drink up.
-Have some.
Thanks, Bai.
I'm Captain Asawin Petchsiri
from the
Department of Special Investigation.
I studied special warfare
and territory defense in the US.
I fought with the Free Thai Movement
during the war, sir.
Tell me.
They say the bandits have magic.
How do you plan to catch them?
I was trained to believe in science,
psychology,
military strategy and political warfare.
I do not believe in fairy tales, sir.
Good. I'll promote you
as the new police chief of Suphan.
Do not disappoint me.
Sir!
SUPHAN BURI PROVINCE
Could you tell me...
where the temple is
that's hosting a merit-making ceremony?
Go this way. Cross the canal.
You'll see the temple
with lots of policemen.
Life and death
Are like a theater
Have to die, inescapably
Like the end of a drama
Life is like a drama...
Well, well...
You came to apologize to me at a ceremony?
Where the hell is he?
Suramerayamajja Pama,
can you say a prayer?
You all go and pray
at the shrine by the river.
I'll see you there.
Bai.
See you again, love bandit.
You never change...
My friend, the war is over.
The Japanese were kicked out.
The Free Thai Movement
has come into the open.
Those who still love this country
should now turn to politics.
I'd like to ask you
to join my party.
Are you in?
You and I...
have different ideologies.
We've chosen different paths.
Which is right and which is wrong,
we'll soon know.
-Tigers!
-Attack!
We mean no harm.
Don't try to fight.
Who's in there?
Open it! Open!
Sadhu.
May you have a long life. Sadhu.
Suramerayamajja pamadatthana
veramani sikkhapadam samadiyami.
Lock him down.
Found it?
Bai. Found it!
TITLE DEEDS
Return these title deeds to the villagers.
-Hey! Police!
-Retreat!
Follow them!
Stay here.
Who's it?
Bai, use the magic bullet.
I can't until I've seen him.
Damn!
Dead. He's dead.
Thought you could mess with us!
Tigers, retreat.
Retreat!
Suramerayamajja pamadatthana
veramani sikkhapadam samadiyami.
Help! The bandits are raiding
the governor's house!
-Go!
-Let's go!
Doctor,
I have a question.
You told me Bandit Fai
used to ask you to treat his men.
How did you contact them?
There are two ways.
The first is to go through Bandit Bai.
Go to the temple by the river
in Bang Pla Ma.
He goes there every full moon night
to sell stolen Japanese weapons.
Japanese rifles. Cheap and good!
-Come take a look!
-Show me the Japanese stuff.
Here.
If you want to fight Tiger Fai,
these are for you.
Bang! He got down, he got up.
You fire again! Bang!
His flesh is impenetrable,
but his insides will be bruised to death.
Feels just right.
I'll take it.
Everything you have.
How much?
Five rifles and a crate of ammo.
Twenty-thousand baht.
I was just joking!
-Twenty-thousand?
-No, 30,000.
-Inflation.
-Asshole.
Second,
Bandit Fai will make contact
if he wants to see you.
He'll go through the woman called...
Busara.
She runs Suphan's famous tavern,
The Golden Flower.
She's the one who knows all the secrets.
If you see him pass by
On horseback, on the fly
Don't look into his eyes
If you see him pass by
His clothes as black as night
His eyes as furious as fire
If you steal something or if you lie
Be careful, he'll come and say hi
Because you know only his name
Don't even know what he rides to come
Go try to report and you will realize
Not tiger but a cat...
That man is a thorn in my side.
Take him out.
Just name your price.
I'll pay you double, Busara.
If your intel is useful.
Triple.
This intel is really useful to you.
Tell me.
Boss Lhong is sending someone
to whack you.
Let me be frank.
What brings you to Suphan?
I'll hazard a guess...
You don't look like a salesman.
You're neither a civil servant
nor a criminal.
The Golden Flower
is famed for our booze
our girls,
and our trove of information.
I bet you're looking for the latter.
Good evening, officers.
How could you tell?
Our regulars don't have a taste
for such shiny leather shoes.
More drinks? On the house.
Have a good evening then.
I've seen you before.
Have you been following me?
Hey!
Come here!
This is my table!
Get these two puppies out!
Who are you?
Why have you followed me?
Hey! You don't know who I am?
Ouch! It hurts!
Good shot.
Now tell me,
who you are.
I'm the person who saved you
from the Japs at the ruins.
My name's Butr.
I was on the run to Kanchanaburi.
The cops accused me
of being a bandit.
They killed my wife.
So, I killed them at the police station
and ran here.
My plan is to find myself a good gun
and offer my service to Tiger Fai
and Tiger Bai.
The more the merrier.
Are you Bai?
I heard you're a hotshot.
My name's Asawin, the new police chief.
May I interrupt?
Mr. New Police Chief,
As you may know,
here at The Golden Flower,
the good, the bad,
the ugly, and the police
have equal rights to enjoy themselves.
If you're going to make an arrest,
show me your warrant.
If you don't have one,
then talk to my lawyer.
I'm not arresting anyone today.
But don't play me for a fool.
One mistake...
and I'll throw you all in jail.
A police chief? Looks like a puppy to me.
Hey.
My dear customers...To make up
for the slight disturbance tonight,
your next drinks are on the house.
Let's have fun.
Yay. Woo-hoo!
Bring more whiskey!
Butr, right?
You know the golden rule of banditry?
Trust no one.
And if someone you happen to trust
betrays you...
You know how it'll end, right?
Tubtim! You're drunk!
Boss Meng, excuse us.
Enough. Come with me.
-Enough. Let's go.
-Bai!
-See you around. Go.
-Bye.
Watch your step.
-I don't want to...
-Sleep now.
-No.
-Go to sleep.
Thanks, Tubtim.
This is the only place...
I can sleep in peace.
Bai.
Kill them all.
I can't control myself! My arms just move.
-A ghost!
-I didn't do it!
Everyone calls me Tiger Fai.
You want to be a tiger too?
Yes, sir.
If Bai hadn't vouched for you,
I wouldn't have taken you in.
Ayutthaya perforated amulet...
Impressive stuff you've got there.
-The Blackshirts are coming!
-Go.
Let's hide!
Hide! The Blackshirts are on the way!
Good morning, folks!
The Blackshirts are here!
Take your valuable belongings out.
Hurry up!
THE BLACKSHIRTS WREAK HAVOC
ACROSS THE CENTRAL PLAINS
SING BURI
Is it true that the police are intimidated
by the bandits in the central plains?
What kind of police are scared of robbers?
Tigers, attack!
Tigers or monkeys,
they're all worthless to me.
I'll put them all behind bars.
BANDIT FAI AND GANG WANTED DEAD
Please help the poor!
-Please.
-Go buy some food.
God bless.
You're so cheap! Robbing poor villagers!
Their clothes are ridiculous.
Change them.
Yes, sir.
Nice.
TOP COP ASAWIN
DECLARES WAR ON THE BLACKSHIRTS
Let the sacred water be the witness.
Now we're sworn brothers.
We share money.
We share gold.
We share happiness.
In joy and in danger,
we'll have each other's back.
Maybe more?
I have a small child.
-Get it done.
-Don't worry.
Anyone who's drunk this oath water
and later betrays his brothers,
may he die by the sword.
May bullets and storms take his life.
Even in his death,
may he burn in hell and never be reborn.
We pledge our loyalty to the nation
to the people
and to our duty.
BUTR PHANTHARAK
You've put your blood stamp in the book.
From now on, you're Tiger Butr.
And these men...
are your blood brothers.
Tiger Bai, Tiger Fai, Tiger Butr,
brothers forever!
Forever!
We grow our own rice.
We give away the surplus to the villagers
or the monks.
All of Fai's gang live here?
No.
It's the village
where Bai and myself grew up.
The police know nothing about it,
so Fai likes to come here.
Repeat after me.
-They sell...
-Louder. They sell...
-Silk...
-Let's go.
-New pots and pans...
So, where is Fai's base?
You ask many questions!
Well, there's no base,
no stronghold.
What?
-Really?
-Why would I lie?
We live anywhere we want.
With villagers usually.
There's many tigers in Fai's gang
that he has to have a record book.
He's smart.
He let the villagers spread the rumor
that he uses black magic to hide his base.
When the police hear this story,
they get chicken-shit.
That's why the cops
are always one step behind him.
-Hey, Bai.
-Give me that.
Thieving, huh.
These children are orphans.
Their fathers are criminals, like us.
Some are locked up. Some were shot dead.
Fai has taken care of them all.
I send them to school.
Because if they can't read, the
authorities will take advantage of them.
If they grow up to become bandits,
they'll end up with Fai.
Like Bia and myself.
Hi, kid.
THAI LIFE INSURANCE
Gather round, folks!
This is a new Thai company.
We'll take care of your lives.
Governor Thammarong
doesn't give a damn about poor people.
He buys votes
and calls himself a representative.
He is more like a crook to me.
Right. But if you run for election,
I'm sure the people will vote for you.
Everyone!
We're a Thai company.
We're ready to take care of you.
The country is going through a hard time.
Only Thai people
can take care of other Thais.
Life insurance will give you security.
What's certain in life is uncertainty.
-Life insurance is a safety net...
-Don't!
Buddhang Pacchagami.
Sambaddhicami.
Will he make it?
You know nothing
about Governor Thammarong.
Enlighten me.
He used to be
an influential district chief.
He's Fai's friend.
They rely on each other.
They link up the state
and the criminal world.
That's why no policemen
has dared to touch Bandit Fai.
Now that Thammarong tried to take him out,
it means the order came from
someone above him.
The central plains tigers
are playing above their weight.
How do I pay you for the intel?
Just don't die.
There's not many men like you around.
Half of Suphan
is mine, and the other half is his.
All villagers will become nothing
but his servants
if we let him take our part.
When that day comes,
Suphan will legally belong
to that corrupt politician!
Taking on the governor
is a tough job.
In three days,
Governor Thammarong will host
a reception for the merchants
and wealthy bureaucrats
he wants to recruit into his party.
I've been asked to bring the girls
to entertain them.
The guests will bring cash
to contribute to the vote-buying fund.
We'll take the money
and kill them all.
Governor Thammarong is a fine man
Now give him a hand
Vote for him! He's a good man.
-Thank you.
-Go to the poll.
Thank you!
-Hi, everyone.
-I'm Thammarong. Vote No.1!
-Good business?
-It's good.
Today the boss wants to have fun
Come here, father, mother and son
If you want a man who gets things done
Please vote for No.1
Governor Thammarong is a good man
Vote for him in the poll
We'd like to contribute
to the governor's campaign.
Thank you so much! Whoa! That's a lot!
I won't let you down.
-Hide.
-Shoot if you dare, baby-face!
Fai!
Hide.
-Hey!
-Go!
No.
-Fai, the police!
-Hey.
-Go, I'll hold them.
-I want them all dead.
Go.
Vadho No-a Mama Vava. Hey!
Take care of this.
I'll go help the captain.
-Go.
-Yes.
-Hey. Fai's here!
-He's back!
Stop.
Ming!
-Take the money.
-Sir.
-Bia.
-Duen. Dao.
Dao, Duen! My darlings!
It's going to be a very noisy night,
sorry about that!
-Damn Bia.
-OK.
I'll make you mine!
-Let's go inside.
-Go for it.
Hey, everybody.
Besides money,
I have something else for you guys:
Letters! Your wife wrote...
-The baby can call your name now.
-Thank you, Bai.
Bad news...
Your husband said:
"Come pick me up from prison
in two months."
Yay!
Daddy will come soon.
Bai...
Had your shot hit me instead of him,
would you have been sad?
Of course.
In my life...
I made a big mistake once.
I won't let it happen again.
My life belongs to you.
Take it.
Sometimes a big change
has to come from the roots.
We must plant new seeds.
-What do you want to do when you grow up?
-I want to be a policeman.
A district chief.
A merchant.
And you?
A soldier.
All right. Go to bed now.
Why do you want to see me?
I wonder who tipped off the police
to raid Thammarong's rally.
Find the mole.
Time for bed.
Tubtim seems so deep in love with Bai.
Tiger Bai avenged
the death of her parents.
It was all because of
a pack of sticky rice.
Tubtim was sold to a brothel.
Her very first client was Bai.
She had not a dime on her,
just a pack of sticky rice.
Next morning,
Tiger Bai went and killed the men
who murdered her parents.
They've found
that precious thing in each other.
They've found...
love.
You sound scared tonight.
We're on a tiger's back.
It's dangerous.
But I'm not scared.
Not right now.
You're telling me
you've disobeyed the suspension order
and embedded yourself
in Bandit Fai's gang?
I suspect
that the murders of the police clerks
must have something to do with Fai's gang.
Right now...
I know his hiding place.
I'll tell you.
But promise me
that you won't use excessive force.
In my career as a policeman,
I've killed plenty of bad men.
But their number
never seems to have declined.
One day I realized that...
giving them a chance
could reduce the number of criminals.
These people are just misled.
All they need is a second chance.
On your feet, please.
Pol. Maj. Gen. Khun Pan,
I hereby reinstate your official rank.
I assign you to the operation
to suppress the central plains bandits.
Effective immediately.
Thank you, Deputy.
You're lucky that the bullet
went through your cheek.
It didn't hit your brain.
But the extensive burns on your body...
I'm afraid there's nothing I can do
about it.
You're drunk again.
I shouldn't have run away with you.
Right, Lamduan,
you shouldn't have married me, either.
I miss you, Bai.
Can I sit with you?
Go ahead.
Here.
Let me ask you something.
Why did you become a bandit?
Why not?
It's a good life.
Lots of money.
Well, I give it away
to anyone who's in trouble.
What I have left I send back to my wife.
I don't want to stay with my wife
because I can't stand her!
She's an old bat. Always complaining.
"You're drunk again," blah, blah.
And you know,
you can't trust
the law.
Guns are justice,
the rest is bullshit.
Damn!
Let me go!
-Don't touch me.
-Lamduan!
Lamduan...
Lamduan!
Run!
No, Lamduan!
Lamduan!
Lamduan?
Have you ever thought
of giving yourself up?
Lamduan,
let me be free...
Dumb card again, Officer Isra.
Your ambition
is getting the better of you.
If you hadn't agreed,
Governor Thammarong would never
have had the nerve to hit me.
I know that eventually
you'll be the winner in this game.
It's time you came out of the dark, Fai.
Enter politics and stop sneaking around
like petty thieves.
You need to decide.
The government has issued death warrants
on the Blackshirt Bandits.
Think about it.
Hey!
Someone asked me to deliver this.
Tubtim!
-Don't come near me! Explosives!
-Tubtim!
Tubtim!
-Bai!
-Butr!
Hello. You two are fast.
Who the fuck are you?
Show yourself, coward!
What do you want?
Bandit Bai, you should thank me.
I've arranged this confessional meeting
for you.
What the hell are you talking about?
Khun Pan, feel like talking?
Tell him who you are.
Will you tell him or not?
Tubtim!
One...
Two...
I'm a policeman.
-Tubtim.
-Bai!
-Tubtim. Go!
-Don't come in.
Don't!
Tubtim!
-Get out of here. Bai.
-Tubtim!
-Tubtim. Go!
-No!
No!
Had the bullet hit me,
would you have been sad?
Of course.
In my life...
I made a big mistake once...
Tubtim! Please don't die!
Tubtim!
We'll settle this after her funeral.
If you're enough of a man.
I know you'll be the winner
in this game eventually.
It's time you came out of the dark, Fai.
What do I have to lose?
You will be arrested.
If you die, your ideology dies with you.
But if you still want to fix this country,
this is the price you have to pay.
You and I both know this.
Now what you have to do... is help me
shut down all the central plains gangs.
Including yours.
Then I'll testify that you've been
working as our informer.
Deal?
Cheers.
Vandhidava.
Achariyang.
Gruba-dhang.
MISS TUBTIM MONGKOLSAP
The magic bullet can go right through
your protective spell.
Only when you can see me.
-Bai!
-Bia!
The cops! They know all our names.
The Blackshirts have been killed
one after another.
Sir, there's a gunfight.
Fai, you've betrayed us!
I'm sorry, Bai. I have no choice.
Mister...
Slowly.
Get him down.
Lock him.
TO STEAL SOMEONE'S BLACK MAGIC
REMOVE HIS TATTOOED SKIN
AND STITCH IT ON YOURS
HOW TO DESTROY SOMEONE'S SPELL
LET HIM TOUCH MENSTRUAL BLOOD
COVER HIS HEAD WITH A WOMAN'S SKIRT
Why did you help me?
Conscience.
This time, too?
I'll take you in alive
if you give yourself up
and testify in your favor to the police.
I can't promise...
I'll turn myself in.
But if you want me to talk,
I'm ready.
What do you know?
Deputy Padet...
is the mastermind
behind the Blackshirt racket.
Tiger Fai is his key player.
They ordered us to steal all the opium
from the government's warehouses
and resell it to the market
at twice the price.
He bribed a group of police clerks
to cook the books.
One day, an innocent clerk...
DOCUMENTS TO DESTROY
...found out about the scheme.
Roj.
The amount of the confiscation is unequal
to the one being destroyed.
-Let me take a look.
-Here.
Nothing to worry about.
This is an outdated file.
So, the deputy ordered Fai
to send hit men to kill them.
But the men he sent were drunk.
Instead of taking out a few clerks,
they massacred the whole precinct.
Deputy Padet was pressured
to end the Blackshirt gambit.
I should've guessed it.
When Fai sent us to kill
Governor Thammarong,
it was only for his own
political aspirations.
Where's the opium now?
Busara!
I'm here to pick up a package.
Where are you?
You're in the house of pleasure.
Enjoy yourself first.
You go first.
I'll wait here.
Come,
handsome...
Go.
So, this is who you are.
Officer.
Now you know me,
but I still don't know anything about you.
I'm one of the Blackshirts,
the criminals you're pursuing.
My name is in that book.
It's only that the role I've been given
is different from those tigers.
Why did you become a criminal?
Survival, I guess.
I could run to the end of the world.
But as long as our names are in that book,
Deputy Padet will come after me
and everyone you're seeing here.
This opium is the only evidence
you can use to incriminate him.
I'm sure he's sending his men to steal it
and to kill us all.
We will help you guard this evidence
if you promise
to treat us as witnesses in the trial,
and let us go back to live a normal life.
-Look out!
-Hey.
Joi!
Joi! What happened?
-How're you doing?
-My leg, boss.
Why are you here?
-What the hell are you doing!
-Ouch.
What the hell?
-Joi, hurry up!
-Joi, shoot him!
-Shoot him!
-Quickly!
-Joi!
-Come help.
-Hurry up!
Get down!
Asawin!
Stop that.
Let the sacred water be our witness.
We share gold.
Anyone who's drunk this oath water
and later betrays his brothers...
May he die
by the sword.
May bullets
and storms take his life.
Even in his death,
may he burn in hell and never be reborn.
Relinquish the black magic,
so you can die without suffering.
Namo Buddhaya. Have them out.
Tiger Bai, Tiger Fai, Tiger Butr.
-Brothers forever!
-Forever!
Allow me.
By the power of great masters.
I am wearing these talismans on my skin.
The 84,000 verses of the scriptures
are now a part of me.
Think you're so clever?
Paying bandits to get rid of bandits.
You think the Blackshirts
will kill one another?
Search!
Where's the opium?
Khun Pan... I want him dead.
Where the hell is he?
Vadho No-a Mama Vava. Hey!
Girls, hide first.
-Come here.
-Now!
-Go!
-Run!
Busara, go! Everyone! Go!
Shall we arrest them?
Arrest your ass! Haven't you seen?
You want to get killed, too?
Let's run!
Let's go!
Bai, you're under arrest.
Go.
Papers.
Captain, they're all Blackshirts.
There are many things that can't be
beaten with supernatural power.
After arresting Tiger Bai,
I gathered all the evidence
-to bring Deputy Padet to justice.
-You ordered Fai to rob the opium
then you doctored the books.
You know it belongs to me.
How did you dare touch it?
Because I'm a police officer.
Anyway,
thanks for delivering the evidence.
This will back up the report
I've sent to Headquarters
that Isra is the mastermind.
-The deputy dumped it all on Isra.
-Sir!
His signature in the accounts
sealed his fate.
-Deputy Padet walked free.
-What's this!
Let me go! Sir! You can't do this!
-Padet, you asshole.
-Try harder next time.
Power always gives you more options.
But the consequences
-depend on which one you'll choose.
-I know that eventually
you'll be the winner in this game.
Some choose the path
where they'll become somebody.
Hey, Bai. Are you dead or what?
Others choose the path
-where they'll disappear forever.
-Shit!
Tiger Bai has escaped! Find him!
He's escaped!
In this country,
you can pay your way through everything.
You can even avoid jail
if you have enough money.
It's a fact,
I can't convince anyone otherwise.
I just hope that sometimes,
luck will be on the right side.
You've cleared his name,
he died an innocent man.
That's more than he could ever ask for.
I did my best.
He told me to bury
all his belongings in his grave.
PROVINCIAL POLICE REGION 1
Excuse me, sir.
And I just hope that one day,
I'll find the answer
that validates my belief
and what I'm fighting for.
THE ONLY TRUE FAITH
IS OUR FAITH IN VIRTUE
THE MOTIVATION TO MAKE THIS FILM
"I WAS INSPIRED BY
THE IMAGE OF KHUN PAN LIGHTING
A CANDLE, FROM KING RAMA IX.
IT LOOKED LIKE HE WAS RECEIVING
A ROYAL BLESSING,
AND AN INSPIRATION
TO DO GOOD FOR THE COUNTRY.
THAI PEOPLE
MUST KEEP THAT CANDLE BURNING."
KONGKIAT KOMESIRI.