B.C. 1904
[ducks quacking]
Do we have any other petitions?
Yes, sir.
About what?
I would like to propose
the extension
of the slaves' retirement age,
sir.
Why extend it, Luang Sorachak?
It's already long enough.
Khun Bun Lue, please be sympathetic.
It's those slaves who deserve sympathy.
-Khun Bun Lue!
-All right. Enough now.
I agree with Khun Bun Lue on this matter.
Let's call it a day.
I'll have to meet the French ambassador
in the afternoon.
[sighing]
-Khun Bun Lue, please follow me.
-Yes, sir.
Siam must sign the treaty, giving up
lands on the left bank of the Mekong,
opposite Louangphrabang,
and to the south of them.
They are still not happy.
They are pushing us harder.
What do these French people want?
Give them an inch,
and they'll take a mile.
How indignant.
We'll have to negotiate with them
to lose as few territories as possible.
Oh, right, Khun Bun Lue.
Since I'll be busy all of next month
meeting the French,
I would like you
to run an errand for me in Chiang Rai.
You are familiar with the place, right?
-[chuckles softly] You go there regularly.
-Not regularly.
[chuckles softly] I know you do.
[panting]
-Sin, stop.
-Yes, sir.
[tram's bells chiming]
-I'll be back shortly.
-Yes, sir.
Ouch!
My calves are all swollen.
Your betel nut is here.
Thank you, Sonklin.
Oh!
-Spittoon.
-Yes, ma'am.
Keep making that face,
and I will spit it in your face.
Give me a massage.
Ek, what are you holding?
A package sent from Chiang Rai
for Master Khun.
[clanging]
Mod, what's wrong with you?
Suddenly lost your strength?
How careless!
I'm sorry.
You've ruined my stuff.
Ek, take it away.
Let Bun Lue open it himself.
Come back, you idiot.
Clumsy fool!
Breaking everything you touch.
You should be taught a lesson by caning.
You're crossing the line.
Yes, ma'am. She's crossing the line.
I mean you.
-Massage me!
-Yes, ma'am.
Just you wait.
Ow, ow!
Are you trying to break my joint?
Isn't it beautiful?
Mmm.
Soybean, rice steamed in banana leaf.
Sin, let's go.
You have a car, why not use it?
I prefer a rickshaw.
Don't you at least feel for me?
-How exhausting can it be?
-Why don't you try?
[panting]
See?
I'm not even exhausted.
[laughing]
I'm so lucky.
What an idiot!
Why? What are you looking at?
Looking for a fight with me?
Just you wait.
Want to fight with me?
Do I look like your master?
[dog whimpering]
What the hell are you doing, Mod?
He stole the food in the kitchen.
He was hungry.
Don't you eat when you're hungry?
Of course I do.
But you are spoiling your dog.
You don't listen to me.
I cannot say anything.
You only take the dog's side.
What's wrong with her?
Is it menopause?
Guess she has too much time
to fight with a dog.
Damn!
Daddy is here, Silver. Come here.
Wow. A photo taken with Khun Thepmala.
He sent this from Chiang Rai.
Who's this lady standing next to you?
She looks beautiful. Is she...
Right?
Of course, she is.
Are you shy because I hit a sore spot?
Women in Chiang Rai are so beautiful.
-Don't you agree, Mod?
-Yeah.
What's going on with her?
[chuckles softly]
Bun Lue is shy. Isn't that cute?
Yes, ma'am.
[chuckles softly]
-Sin.
-Yes?
Come here.
What can I do for you?
Come closer.
Did you stick your head in a bush?
You've got leaves in your hair.
Next time...
be more careful.
Yes, ma'am.
Do you...
like him?
Of course, you do!
Don't be shy!
I really hit your sore spot.
Are you shy now?
I'm sure she likes him.
-[dog barking]
-Come here. Eat your food.
This way. Eat. Come on.
Hurry up and feed him.
-Yes, sir.
-Come, come, Silver.
-My baby.
-Silver.
-Eat your meal now.
Aren't you hungry?
Come on, Silver. Eat!
You eat it, then.
I was joking.
-Yes, sir.
-You're funny.
Come here.
Eat now.
Yes, eat.
Don't be mad at Mod.
She just has a foul mouth.
-Give him more.
-Yes, sir.
-You want to eat it yourself?
-No, sir.
Where the hell is Mod?
Has she fed Goldie yet?
I think so, sir.
Go check it out. Leave this here.
Here you are.
Instead of doing my chores,
I have to take care of you.
Here. Come on.
One is not enough.
Eat a lot to satisfy your daddy.
Four pieces.
Are you full? Here. Eat another one.
How boring!
She's more well-fed than I am.
Juicy chicken breast.
I only got the feet.
What's wrong with that woman?
She's been moody all day.
This is why her husband got tired of her.
Who would want a wife like that?
If no one wants her, can I have her?
Take care of Silver and Goldie
while I am away.
Yes, sir. Where will you go?
Chiang Rai, Mother.
How long will you stay there?
Probably many days.
That's great. On the way back,
don't forget to buy me some durians.
I'm going to Chiang Rai,
not Rayong or Chanthaburi.
[giggles]
Just kidding.
They say people in Rayong
are more well-endowed.
Please eat your food, Mother.
But I think people in Chanthaburi
should be more well-endowed.
Whatever.
But I heard that people from Trad
are the biggest.
Whatever you like.
You look tense.
[playing upbeat music]
You guys are having fun. Plarn!
Yes, sir?
-Where is your mother?
-At home, sir.
Master, Plarn composed a new song.
You should listen.
[playing slow instrumental music]
♪ Yo yo ♪
♪ The nobles call me Plarn
A servant of Khun Bun Lue ♪
♪ Who treats me like a dog ♪
-[beatboxing]
-♪ Just like what people said of him ♪
♪ Have you ever known how tired I am? ♪
♪ I look shabby because I'm overworked ♪
♪ You call me moron all day all night ♪
♪ I have to stay or I'll be doomed ♪
♪ Sleep at dusk
Work at dawn ♪
♪ He won't let me eat
if I don't do my job perfectly ♪
♪ I'm so tired of this
Plarn is ready to leave ♪
♪ Khun Bun Lue is ruining my life ♪
♪ He yells when he doesn't get
what he wants ♪
♪ I'd rather die than continue
living this way ♪
Sing it to your father.
-There's one more song.
-That's enough.
What an absurd song.
Doesn't make any sense. What a waste!
♪ A teenage girl with a sexy body ♪
♪ I am still young ♪
♪ I have been through 19 winters ♪
♪ But yet still no lover ♪
♪ As pretty as I am ♪
♪ Still no one wants me ♪
I do.
Come home now.
You get drunk everyday.
Can you work tomorrow?
Seriously, are you my husband
or my father?
I am your husband, of course!
You are lucky to have
a husband that you can bully.
[laughing]
I don't even have a chance.
Of course, you don't.
-Who is this flat-faced man?
-[Duangjai] It's Khun Bun Lue.
You're totally wasted.
Duangjai, take your wife home.
Yes, sir.
-See you tomorrow.
-[Mod] Hey, don't leave yet.
Wanna fight?
-[Duangjai] Stop looking for trouble.
-Stop dragging me.
[Duangjai] You wouldn't
want to get flogged.
Because of your debauchery,
your husband got tired of you
and ran away.
He didn't just run away, sir.
-He has a mistress.
-No way.
Yes, in Chiang Rai.
You don't know anything.
Who told you that?
Khun Theng and Khun Nong.
Mother.
That's enough, Mother.
Time to sleep now.
Mother, let's go.
-[grunting]
-Please forgive her.
-What are you doing?
-Let's go, Mother.
Khun Theng and Khun Nong
are loose-tongued.
[playing merry music]
What is this?
[sighing]
Sia.
-Sia!
-Yes?
Come here.
I can't sleep.
Oh, I can help.
Go ahead.
[singing]
♪ A koel laid an egg for a crow to hatch ♪
♪ A crow sings ♪
♪ Caw caw ♪
♪ If you don't sleep ♪
♪ A lizard and a cat will bite your neck ♪
[lizard squeaking]
[cat growling]
Mission accomplished.
A son and a daughter.
What are their names?
The older one is called Thara.
The younger one, Tharin.
Both are good-looking like me.
[all laughing]
You have a brass neck.
Anyway,
please take care of them.
Luang Anuphak,
we're like family.
I'm always glad to help.
What a relief to hear that.
[both laughing]
How long will you stay
in Europe this time?
I suppose seven or eight months.
-For what purpose?
-I would like to buy a horse.
Last time I went to Arabia.
The Arabian horses won't cut it for me.
Since I'm going to Europe this time,
I would love to buy a Haflinger.
I see.
It will make me a lot of profit.
Right.
How many pieces can you breed?
It's an animal.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Do they make you hallucinate
and become alert?
Alert? Yes, if there're too many.
[both laughing]
-Euphoric?
-Yes.
You mean the horse keeper?
No, this Haflinger breed
has a strong consciousness.
Unlike Thai horses
that hallucinate easily.
They're hard to raise
and generate little profit.
When I come back,
I will invite you to my place.
So I can teach you how to raise a horse.
Oh, it's okay.
I'll leave you to it.
Iang, Mod.
Why don't you bring some snacks
for the guests?
This is Mod. This is Iang.
If you want something, just let them know.
-[Luang Anuphak] Yes.
-[Tharin] Yes, sir.
Off you go.
Six.
-Five now.
-Six
[all cheering]
-Take the money.
-Take it.
Finally, I won.
-[shouting]
-You're rich.
[woman] What?
-Can you lend me some?
-Will you pay me back?
Otherwise I will tell your mom.
Yes!
Four.
-High!
-Hey.
What's the first rule of this house,
Duangjai?
-No gambling.
-Yet you are doing it.
Stop now!
I lost my money.
-Let me try again one more time.
-Fine.
Go all in.
High!
-Six. High.
-Here you go.
Whatever you have left, go all in.
Sin, open it. Not yet!
I'll bet three ones. One low.
I will take this one. Sin, open it.
Three. Three.
One.
Three, three, one. I won.
Thought he was a good guy,
but he's pretty savage.
He took all the money in one try.
-I'm broke.
-I told you, Sin.
If you don't pay me back, I'll tell Mod.
Last time we met, you weren't
a grown man yet, Keerati.
Yes.
How long ago did you graduate
from medical school?
Two years ago, sir.
I see.
How's your father?
He's suffering from hemorrhoids.
-And your mother?
-She scalded her head,
but she's better now.
Ten years, 20 years, time flies.
I remember you running around
the house, naked.
[sighing]
I guess I'm old now.
Hmm.
-Why don't you just eat her up?
-Yes.
I wish I could.
Go, go.
You're so good at flirting, aren't you?
Keerati, Keerati.
-Keerati!
-Yes?
-Are you going to diagnose me?
-Yes, I can.
Let's go.
-Watch the tray.
-Yes.
[clanking]
I told you!
I'm not picking it up.
Why are you so happy today?
I'm proud to have poor taste.
Are you?
-Iang.
-Yes?
Be careful. Don't break anything.
They are expensive.
Once you finish those, come help me here.
-All right.
-Hey.
-Plarn, you're here.
-Yes?
Move the bottle to the left.
And don't break anything.
Mom.
Who's my father?
Your father is a man.
But he doesn't love his family.
Now I'm getting cranky.
[sighs]
I'm tongue-tied.
Perhaps Sin is my dad?
What?
Plarn, you're foul-mouthed!
Our father cannot be that ugly.
Oh, come on.
What's wrong with me?
You have a fungal infection
on the groin.
It's called tinea cruris.
Or simply jock itch.
What is jock itch?
Groin rash.
I see.
I will leave the antifungal cream
with Sin.
Thank you so much, Keerati.
I'll take my leave now.
This disease is not easy to get.
You must be exceptionally dirty.
How disgusting.
-Let's get wasted tonight after work.
-Sure, Luang.
How is it?
Wow.
This is awesome, Bun Lue.
It's nothing special.
I just want the slaves to have
additional income.
So one day they can pay off
their debt bondage.
Oh, my.
You're so generous.
I guess I will have to use
some of your ideas.
Go ahead.
I will need your help.
This is superb.
Buy two get one free.
Step right up, folks.
Newly fermented, a new recipe
from Khun Bun Lue.
What glowing skin!
This drink is for ladies, too.
Once you drink this,
your adrenaline will pimp like a piston.
"Pump" not pimp.
[laughing gently]
What is it, anyway?
It's called Stomping Tiger.
What about this one?
This one is called
Dog Stomping Cat.
And this one?
This one is "I will stomp you."
Stop asking!
But you can ask me anything.
[chuckles softly]
Actually, I know all the rest.
And you are...
-You are...
-I'm Tharin.
What a beautiful name.
♪ My name is Plarn
Where is she from? ♪
♪ She sets my soul on fire ♪
♪ Her style and her face
make my heart flutter ♪
♪ Do I have any chance
to be her love slave? ♪
♪ Because a mixed race girl
is so stunning ♪
♪ Be with me and I will never
make you frown ♪
♪ Buy two get one free ♪
♪ Let me know if you need some loving ♪
That's a beautiful song.
Shit. Bun Lue is here.
[chuckles nervously]
[chuckles] Plarn is such a player,
just like his father.
Like father like son.
[laughing]
I told you not to sing that kind of song.
Don't let me hear it again.
Come on, Bun Lue.
They probably just want to have fun.
Let's go.
Oh, my.
Your face is as long as my foot.
-What's your name?
-Bunleng, sir.
Are you related to Bun Lue?
I'm his servant.
Yeah.
You look the part.
If I saw you through the window,
I'd definitely think
it was someone's foot.
One, two, three.
That's it.
May I?
Oh...
Sure, the toilet is over there.
[sighs]
No, I mean the photograph.
I see.
Let's take a photo together.
Then who will press the shutter?
Just kidding.
Please.
Let me arrange your shirt.
If only someone cared about me this much
and helped arrange my shirt
like this everyday,
that would be great.
Soi.
I have to take a photo now.
[Bun Lue] This place
also has many customers.
[laughing]
Not bad.
It's one of the most popular shops
in town.
Yeah.
I believe it.
[chuckles softly]
[Bun Lue] This is Mod who is in charge
of this shop.
She looks decent.
I'm sure she was pretty
when she was young.
Indeed. She was the prettiest.
But heavy drinking led to weight gain.
Hey. You'd better take good care
of your body.
Or else your husband will find a mistress.
It's too late, sir.
Oh.
That bastard.
Son of a bitch.
Men like this shouldn't have been born.
And though they have been,
I'm sure they are ugly.
Asshole.
[music playing softly]
♪ Is it true, Khun Bun Lue? ♪
♪ All the servants are saying ♪
♪ That you have jock itch ♪
♪ And a scald headed ♪
♪ What are the conditions now? ♪
♪ Any better or ♪
♪ No improvement at all? ♪
Gosh, you're dirty.
Get it treated.
I mean, you already look dirty.
-Cheers.
-Is it contagious?
Not the jock itch.
[laughing]
-Sin.
-Yes, sir?
Go get more side dishes.
Yes, sir.
What is this song?
Actually,
Sin has a pretty good voice.
He sings well, but I hate the lyrics.
But the jock itch
doesn't get any better.
[both laugh]
Cheers, cheers.
Cheers. And after cheers?
We drink.
[laughing]
Here it is.
Took you long enough.
It smells nice.
Wow, this is not bad.
It melts in your mouth.
Come on, let's drink.
[Luang Anuphak imitating dog barking]
[Bun Lue] What the hell is wrong with you?
-[banging]
-[Luang Anuphak wailing]
Sin!
-Sin!
-Yes, sir.
What is this?
Didn't you tell me to hide this picture?
That's not what I meant.
I meant to put it somewhere
no one would notice it,
where no one can see it.
Well, no one can see the picture now.
I flipped it around.
Are you an idiot?
Nothing but pure stupidity.
[yells]
[laughing]
[Bun Lue] Aren't you
supposed to be working?
Such a good dream.
[rooster crowing]
You're drunk.
Of course, we drink to get drunk.
You're drinking all day.
Well, it's socializing.
-I have to socialize with my friends.
-Oh, yeah?
What's so good about alcohol?
Well, it's delicious.
Otherwise, we wouldn't drink it.
You're always as drunk as a skunk.
Hmm...
How could you compare me to a skunk?
Do skunks get drunk like us?
You're totally wasted.
You don't even work.
Look at the other households.
Why?
We have been sexless for months.
Oh.
I guess it doesn't work anymore.
No more erection, just like these monks.
It's not that bad, child.
Amen.
Go.
Please.
Be prepared to receive the precepts.
Long life, beauty, happiness...
-Strength.
-Amen.
[yawning]
[chuckles softly]
Didn't you sleep last night, Grandma?
I did.
But I dreamt that I had insomnia.
So I woke up feeling restless.
[yawning]
-Sin.
-Yes?
Help me go inside.
Yes, ma'am.
Feel like I'm about to faint.
Feel like you're trying
to get his attention.
That must be it.
Clean up the table. Stop being nosy.
Now!
This wench is so harsh.
Always so satirical.
-Ouch.
-Quick!
Perhaps her brain no longer functions.
There's nothing serious, Auntie Bua.
Just a lack of sleep.
Rest a lot and you will be fine.
Yes.
Get well soon, ma'am.
I need you here with me.
[coughing]
Something stuck in your throat, Sonklin?
Perhaps the doctor can remove it?
I cannot. She'd better just swallow it.
[gulps]
[meows]
[meowing]
[imitating cat growling]
[Bun Lue yawning]
Why is Thara so obsessed
about taking photos?
It's been all day.
I don't think it's photography
that he's obsessed with.
Probably something else.
Anyway, Uncle,
I would like your permission
for me to teach the slaves
-how to read.
-That's great.
So they can finally read.
Good. That's a very good idea.
-I'll see you later, then.
-Yes.
See you.
Hand me the account book
in a few days.
Yes, sir.
Since we're done with the numbers,
we'll move on
to English letters.
Be careful, Grandma.
Yes.
You're quite excited that you're
going to Chiang Rai.
You look ecstatic.
Chiang Rai must have impressed you a lot.
Be careful of the disease.
What are you talking about?
Tharin, Thara, please look after Grandma.
-Yes.
-Definitely.
See you, Mother.
-Good luck, Bun Lue.
-Thank you.
Everyone is here,
but no one cares to help me.
What a bunch of useless servants.
Let's go.
[engine sputtering]
Try again.
Release the clutch pedal first.
[engine sputtering]
What are you looking at?
Come push it forward.
-Push.
-Will he make it there?
-Yes.
-Will he make it to Chiang Rai?
She's doing fine.
She just wants Sin's attention.
Your condition has improved a lot.
There's nothing to worry about now.
I'll take my leave now.
Thank you, Dr. Keerati.
You're welcome.
Yes.
Why are you still here? Get out.
See? I knew it!
They want to be alone together.
You're so cute.
-I want to squeeze your cheek.
-Come on.
Goodbye, Doctor.
Goodbye.
Shit!
-[screaming]
-[yelling]
[bicycle crashes]
I'm so sorry! Are you okay?
I'm fine. Ouch!
Looks like you've sprained your leg.
It's nothing.
Iang.
Why are you so clumsy?
I'm sorry, Doctor.
I'm the one who was clumsy.
Mother... Mother.
Let me check her.
It's okay. She'll be fine.
Why weren't you careful?
You're lucky it's not serious.
Be more careful next time.
How clumsy.
Iang.
I wish she could stay forever.
You almost break your leg.
Stop flirting!
He's a doctor.
-You want a private diagnosis?
-Come on, Mother.
[mooing]
Iang, what happened? Are you in pain?
I'm fine, sir.
Why are you still working
in this condition?
I'm okay, sir.
Please smile.
Very beautiful.
One, two, three.
Today we are going to learn
how to speak English
with an American accent.
Here we go.
[all in English] I am fine.
It means I'm fine.
Very good, Plarn.
[in English] I like it.
[all] I like it.
I like it.
Very good, Plarn.
Let's continue, shall we?
[in English] I miss you.
[all in English] I miss you.
It means I miss you.
Very good, Plarn. Last one.
[in English] I love you.
[all in English] I love you.
I love you.
Why don't you just have
a one-on-one session with her?
From the look of her eyes,
it seems that she only wants to teach you.
This is not for us. Let's go, folks.
Once we're gone, you'd better get a futon
so you won't hurt your back.
What...
was Sonklin trying to say?
You're about to find out.
[in English] Yes.
[Keerati] You're lucky
you didn't break the bone.
I wasn't being careful enough.
I only look at your eyes.
You might as well look at mine.
They are turning red now.
Why don't you just glue them?
A glue is not eye drops.
What if I cannot open my eyes?
Hmm...
[sighing]
He totally lost his mind.
Head over heels in love.
Plarn, just do it.
-What?
-Yes.
Yes?
Thank you, Sin.
You know how to hit the right spot.
Would you like to try a yoni massage?
What is that? Yoni massage?
It's an erotic massage
for women.
Really? Never heard of it.
Is it relaxing?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, go ahead.
-Sure, ma'am.
-[lively music playing]
Oh, so good.
Nok.
No need. I'm not going home.
I'm not taking you home.
I just want to join.
Have a seat, honey.
-Yes.
-Honey.
[kissing]
[Duangjai] I like that.
That's why they say
having a good husband is like
having a father. They are not horndogs.
[both laughing]
Mod, let me tell you something.
Your husband should be here with you.
No, he shouldn't.
He's probably eating sausage
with chili dips
and having fun with someone else.
-Someone else?
-Yes, someone else.
-Doing what?
-I'll show you.
♪ Fun fun fun ♪
Oh, so delicious, baby.
Oh, yes.
Now I want to kick him in the face.
Come on, Mod.
He's not that kind of man.
Can I kick you instead of him?
-I saw everything.
-Discipline your husband.
[Bun Lue] You ordered my urgent return.
Anything you'd like me to do?
Was your Chiang Rai trip fun?
Yes, it was.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you.
I hope you finished the errands
that I asked you.
And about your personal affair,
please settle it quickly.
Don't keep it pending for long.
[chuckles] You're something, aren't you?
You look like a dog,
yet you're a womanizer.
-May I leave now?
-[chuckles]
Spit it out.
I said spit it out!
Spit the chicken out!
Why do you always steal food?
Sneaking out and stealing stuff...
just like your father.
-Spit the chicken out!
-What did Goldie do, Mod?
What?
He stole my chicken.
What's done is done.
But I raised that chicken.
Can't you just talk to him nicely?
Talk nicely?
Will he understand it?
He's a monitor lizard.
What's got into her? First a fight
with Silver, and now it's Goldie.
How are you, son?
You have gained weight lately.
-Here, take my bag.
-Yes, sir.
And where is Silver? He always greets me.
He's probably with a female dog somewhere.
Taking after his master.
Keep your smart mouth to yourself.
Tea, sir.
-Sin.
-Yes?
-Has Silver come back yet?
-Not yet, sir.
Where could he be?
Do you think someone ate him?
There are no dog eaters here.
But we do have the son of a bitch,
the cur, the motherfucker.
[Sin laughing]
[Bua] No.
Enough.
Oh, Sin.
Oh, you're killing me.
Sin.
-[breath trembling]
-[screaming]
Sin!
What's wrong with my mother?
-[rooster crowing]
-[amusing instrumental music playing]
[groans]
Hey, the monks are here!
Cheers, brother.
[laughing]
-The monks left.
-Please.
-What the heck!
-It's me, Sonklin.
Where's your hair?
-You look like a monk.
-I was in a rush.
Here they are.
Please.
Long life, beauty, happiness, strength.
Amen.
Oh, which temple are you from?
Now he's asking for trouble.
[giggles]
Bua, let's go home.
Yeah?
[giggles]
How insolent. You'll burn in hell.
Please.
[grunting]
[in English] You must tell
the workers to work faster.
-Yes.
-They're behind.
[in English] Yeah, I will hit them.
Tharin, Thara, are you having fun?
Yes, sir.
Yes, despite the hot weather,
I'm happy to see how you work.
All right.
-Nok.
-Yes?
Take my grandchildren to rest inside.
-Yes, sir.
-Go.
Let's go, sister.
-[in English] Do they speak English?
-Yes, maybe, we must ask them.
Let's ask him.
[in English] Excuse me, sir.
Do you know where the nearest hospital is?
Oh, shit.
-Duangjai.
-Please.
Don't look at me like that.
[in English] Uh, far from here...
[in English] 15 to 20 Kilometers.
[in English] That's very far.
[in English] Do you think you could
maybe take us there?
[in English] Yes, of course.
[in English] Uh, this way.
Let's follow him.
Plarn!
What did you say?
I don't understand at all.
They asked me to take them
to the hospital.
-Yeah?
-Yes, sir.
You said something about 15 and 20.
Is that a hospital?
Fifteen kilometers, sir.
Fifteen to 20 kilometers away.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
What does "how are you" mean?
You have no idea, you fool.
Poor me.
[sighs]
Who is this for?
That's Khun Bun Lue.
When did he come back
from Chiang Rai?
Let's hurry up and go home.
Just shut up.
-Why?
-Hide.
Do as I say.
This one is nice.
This one is also nice.
I can't decide.
It's okay.
We can keep looking,
and you can decide later.
Yes.
We're late because of you.
Let's get home.
As slippery as an eel,
as fast as a monkey.
That lady, the way she dresses up
is different from the locals here.
She's a northerner.
I guess Khun Bun Lue has a thing
for northern girls.
Where did they go?
[man] That's your grandfather.
Next is your great-grandfather.
And your great-great-grandfather.
Your great-great-grandfather...
Everyone was so handsome.
But how come...
-you are so ugly?
-He's just kidding.
Of course.
What about you, Bua?
Do you like Caucasians?
Oh,
I prefer Asians.
Caucasians are...
too big for me.
You'll get used to it.
[all laughing]
By the way, Khun Sriwichai,
when do you plan to go back
to the South?
I'll go home tomorrow.
Hmm?
-Let's duel tonight.
-What?
I didn't know you knew the Nora dance.
No, I meant booze.
Sure, what kind of boost do you need?
I meant a drinking duel.
♪ Booze means alcohol
Drinking it makes you stagger ♪
♪ And throw a page boy into the sea ♪
We're going to have fun tonight.
Sin, Sin.
-Yes?
-Come here.
Look.
Go get us some delicious hors d'oeuvres.
There's nothing left in the kitchen.
Then you go find it.
Yes, sir.
-Do you know--
-Not yet.
I'm just practicing.
Practicing drunk talk.
-Now, if you will excuse me.
-Yes, see you later.
Cheers.
Here come the amazing hors d'oeuvres.
He's really good at preparing
hors d'oeuvres.
-He's a true master, this one.
-Thank you.
This smells so nice.
Go on, Khun Sriwichai.
-Who are you?
-No, who are you?
Who the hell are you?
[speaking Southern dialect]
You think you're the boss?
[laughing maniacally]
[growling]
Holy shit!
[speaking Southern dialect]
Lue!
[wailing]
[speaking Southern dialect]
My Lord.
Since you plan to install
electricity posts all over Phra Nakhon,
Why don't we cover the Thon Buri District
simultaneously?
We cannot, Luang Sorachak.
It will exceed our budget
and complicate things regarding
logistics and construction.
Since we don't have a crossing bridge
like in the West.
Well,
you're right, Khun Bun Lue.
We'd better start
with the Pha Nakhon District.
Once we have the bridge,
we shall discuss this again.
[giggling]
What's so funny, Sin?
It's just funny.
-Take these.
-Yes, sir.
-Has Goldie come inside yet?
-Not yet, sir.
Or someone ate him up already?
Who on earth would eat such a foul thing?
Perhaps a foul person could do that.
[giggling]
Silver, why are you still in heat?
That bitch must be something.
Where is he?
Goldie! Goldie!
Goldie!
[sighs]
Iang.
Just pick one already, bitch.
I want to keep them both.
My, my.
It's beautiful.
Oh!
Oops!
Gosh!
Thank you.
[sighs grimly]
Why didn't you tell me, Mod?
Because I wasn't certain about it.
But now I am 100% sure.
Since she's staying
in a house that he bought.
Dresses elegantly,
speaking the Northern dialect.
She must be from Chiang Rai.
Right, Mod?
Yes.
Then why does Bun Lue has to hide her?
It's in the DNA, ma'am, to be so sneaky.
I suppose it's more fun.
[giggles]
[groaning]
Fun? DNA?
What are you looking at?
Never seen anyone get kicked
in the face?
My nose is still intact.
Good thing her foot didn't stick
to my face,
otherwise people might call me
foot-face.
You want more?
No, ma'am.
Keep it for the next time.
Do you want to see me,
Luang Sorachak?
Khun Bun Lue,
let's talk man to man.
What about?
About the power plant in Thon Buri.
If you convince the lord,
then we are all set.
Tell me how much you want.
This kind of business
is not for me. It's dirty.
Keep the money
and share it amongst you, gentlemen.
If there's nothing else,
I'd like to bid you farewell.
[cigarette burning]
You... You... Put it away now!
[grunting]
Idiot!
[both] Are you going to
Loy Krathong with anyone this year?
I don't know yet.
[both] Come with me!
We can go if I finish work on time.
Otherwise we cannot.
This Loy Krathong Festival,
what time does it start?
4:30 in the morning.
[laughs shrilly]
You think I'm stupid?
That Khun Bun Lue, we can't let him
get away with this.
What are you going to do?
Get rid of him!
Yes, sir.
Why are you smiling?
It's my style.
[firecrackers crackling]
-[lively music playing]
-[indistinct conversations]
[fireworks whistling]
Tharin, Thara, you can float
your Krathong over there.
-Yes, sir.
Let's go, sister.
-Be careful.
-Yes.
That's the lord.
Excuse me, Mother.
Sure, Bun Lue.
-Look after my mother, Sonklin.
-Yes, sir.
Don't bite her neck.
If I see you and a cobra,
I will hit you first.
Bitch.
-My Lord.
-Hey.
-My Lady.
-[giggles]
You came as well?
We can't miss this festival, right?
Any progress on what he asked you to do?
Everything is going smoothly, My Lady.
Really? And where is he now?
Probably somewhere around here.
I'll take care of it.
-Thank you, Khun Bun Lue.
-My pleasure.
-I'll see you later, then.
-Sure.
He looks pale.
Must have been exhausted post-coital.
-Oh, Sin.
-Yes, sir.
Why are you here just now?
I thought I was not going to come.
-What happened to your forehead?
-I got stung by a wasp.
-Stung by a wasp?
-Yes, sir.
-What kind of wasp?
-A bee, sir.
-So what stung you?
-A wasp.
-What kind?
-The bee kind.
So was it a wasp or a bee?
A wasp.
-What kind of wasp?
-The bee kind.
Stop being ridiculous.
Was it a wasp or a bee?
A wasp, sir.
-Get out of my sight.
-Yes, sir.
So was it a wasp or a bee?
He didn't make any sense.
What the heck? A bee kind of wasp?
Hold it carefully, Sonklin.
Where is he?
Where is Sin?
Sin.
Where have you been?
Here. Take this.
And take her after this.
Ouch.
Let's fill the river with Krathongs.
Sin.
Why are you looking so serious?
It's Khun Bun Lue.
Look here.
I told him I got stung by a wasp,
but he kept asking if it was a bee.
I think he has gone nuts.
Don't take it to heart.
You know he's in love now.
Let's float our Krathong.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Come.
Ganga goddess,
please send me a decent man.
That decent man is here.
Probably not decent enough.
-Go.
-Further.
-Closer, closer.
-Closer.
-May all the pain and misery,
illness and harm...
Misfortune, curse, and evil go away.
[in English] Wow, monkey.
[speaking Thai with Chinese accent]
He's peeing!
How rude of you.
Go away, you stupid westerners.
Now, now.
Are you stupid or what?
He's peeing not pooping.
It's been a while since I last
gave someone a good beating.
What are you wishing for?
Am I a part of it?
I won't tell you.
I'd better get going now.
Please tell me a little bit.
[romantic music playing]
What are you wishing for?
To be loved and adored.
Sin, is that Bun Lue?
Yes, ma'am.
And who is that lady?
Could be the woman from Chiang Rai
that Sonklin talked about.
Are you gonna float it or not, Mod?
No, I'm not.
Twenty yards.
No wind.
One.
Two.
Three.
Shoot!
We missed. Let's go!
You're holding the wrong side, Plarn.
Let me show you.
Hit the ball.
-I see.
-Yeah, just like that.
Hit it.
Do you know how to play, slave?
This is called croquet.
Someone like you only knows
how to hit a cockroach.
Give it to me.
Stay behind me, Plarn.
Give it back now.
Didn't you see he was playing?
I did. So what?
Oh, I see.
A heroine saving a damsel in distress.
Look at you. Beauty and the Beast.
Beast?
-Hey!
-Don't come any closer!
Tharin!
Plarn!
Take Tharin home.
Yes, sir.
You two listen to me.
This is my house and there're rules.
Whoever breaks those rules
must be whipped.
Even a daughter of my friend
is no exception.
-Sin.
-Yes, sir.
Bring me a cane.
Rak is holding it.
Wouldn't it be easier
for him to just hand it to you
since he's holding it now?
This jerk... He asked you!
I know, but you can just hand it to him.
Come take it from me. He asked you.
I'm just holding it.
Have you no kindness?
-He asked you to do it.
-I know.
He asked you.
Take this and give it to him.
He asked you!
You could have just handed it to him.
You take it to him.
-Have you no kindness, Rak?
-He asked you.
I know.
You just hand it to him.
What the hell are you fighting about?
You have a short uvula,
yet you can't stop talking.
"He asked you, he asked you."
What the heck?
I'm sorry, sir.
May this be your lesson.
Sir.
It's not her fault at all.
I'll let you go this time.
Don't ever do that again!
It's okay now.
You!
Piece of shit!
You, too!
Such an easy task, and yet you failed.
Then, what else can you do for a living?
I can sell coconut milk custard.
-Come back quickly.
-Fasten it tightly.
Last time you forgot gecko skin
and Du Zhong leaves.
[sighs]
[screaming]
Khun Kaeo?
[muffled screaming]
Hey!
[grunting]
Mod, take Kaeokanda away.
-Hurry up!
-Yes, yes!
[grunting]
[thuds]
Hey, Silver, Goldie.
Where have you been?
Why are you hiding here?
Your daddy has been looking for you.
Come quickly, Goldie.
[whimpering]
Where have you been, Goldie?
Is that your girlfriend?
Go home and wait for me.
Sin.
Come here.
Go.
Where have you been?
Something happened.
How many times have you shagged him?
Who?
Of course you know who.
[speaking incoherently]
This is her.
Khun Bun Lue's girlfriend.
The one Mod stalked.
She looks so plain.
This is the one?
Why did you two have to date secretly?
[man] What's going on here?
Why so noisy?
[chuckles] Oh, Lady Bua.
What brings you here?
My Lord,
I came to see Bun Lue's girlfriend.
Bun Lue's girlfriend?
That's absurd, Lady Bua.
She's not who you think.
She's not Bun Lue's girlfriend.
Her name is Kaeokanda.
She's from Chiang Rai,
my daughter in law.
She's my wife, Lady Bua.
These scandalmongers!
And you are credulous.
Why did you believe them?
All of you, go home immediately!
You, too.
Go.
Kaeokanda, are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
Luang Phiphat, please accept my apology.
Of course.
Please forgive my people, my Lord.
No worries.
Very well,
I'll take my leave now.
Go, Sin.
This way, you fool.
Your big mouth...
always spewing nonsense,
causing great misunderstandings.
You brought shame upon me.
You will be whipped 30 times today.
So you won't do it again. Duangjai.
-Yes, sir?
-Get the cane from Bunleng.
Wouldn't it be easier
if he just handed it to you?
I don't want to walk over there.
I just want the cane, not your face.
You're looking more and more
like a big toe every day.
Get some surgery!
Perhaps you'll look more human.
Remember this.
-[cane cracks]
-[Mod whimpers]
Sir,
instead of whipping my mother 30 times,
can you whip me and my sister
ten times each?
So there would only be ten times left
for my mother.
Sure, if that's what you want.
Anyone else want to help?
Maybe five times each?
Step back.
-[cane cracking]
-[Mod whimpering]
-[cane cracks]
-One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Ten times.
Now it's Iang's turn.
Iang, your turn.
[shuddering]
Plarn, you bastard!
You didn't even ask me first.
[whimpering]
Go.
What a lovely family.
-Sin.
-Yes, sir.
Take the cane away.
Where did you get that ring?
It belongs to my mother.
When did he become a thief?
You commit petty theft now?
You ungrateful slave.
Tell me!
Apart from this ring,
what else did you steal from my mother?
-You won't talk?
-[cane cracking]
Bun Lue, please stop.
-I gave him the ring.
-Why?
Are you and him...
Yes.
That's right.
How ungrateful you are!
-How's my mother in bed?
-Amazing.
-Amazing?
-[cane cracks]
Mother, you shouldn't have.
At this age, why are you still
seeking worldly pleasure?
Be gentle.
Does it hurt, Plarn?
Of course, it does.
Anyone can tell
by seeing these nasty gashes.
Use your brain.
Why are you making fun of me?
I was just kidding.
No matter how many times I got whipped,
as long as I have you by my side,
I feel no pain at all.
Well...
I'd better get going now.
If Uncle Bun Lue see us,
I will be in trouble.
[sniffing]
Damn.
She smells so nice.
This will hurt a little.
My body hurts,
but my heart hurts more.
It's like nursing a viper
in my bosom.
Yes, exactly.
So the old saying is true.
We can't all be masters...
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Ouch.
Now it hurts more.
♪ Alas ♪
♪ Why didn't you think before you acted? ♪
♪ Now you are consumed by guilt ♪
♪ Why didn't you think it through? ♪
♪ How pitiful ♪
♪ The mother and her children ♪
♪ Who were whipped ♪
♪ And caned ♪
-Go sing somewhere else.
-Yes, sir.
It's not the time for singing, you moron!
Just tell them, Khun Bun Lue.
Why do you keep dragging it on?
Lady Bua wouldn't mind it
since she's your mother.
-Let's talk next time.
-Yes, sir.
Have a seat, Luang.
Yes, My Lord.
What you're thinking,
what you're doing,
I'm asking you to stop.
Because if you don't stop,
I will stop you.
Yes, sir.
[Bun Lue] I would like to thank you all
for serving me for your whole lives.
But as of now,
you are no longer slaves.
You are all free men.
And this is your dividends
from our businesses.
You will need it in the future.
Use it wisely.
All my harsh words,
don't take them to heart.
I just wanted you to be disciplined
and follow the rules.
I have a sharp tongue.
But I love you all.
Be good. Don't let people think
that I've never disciplined you.
Thank you all once again,
and good luck.
-Tharin.
-Yes?
Give them these documents.
-Okay.
-Thara.
-Give them the money.
-Yes.
Congratulations.
[Sonklin crying]
What are you waiting for?
Where should we go?
You are free now. Go wherever you want.
If we can do that,
then we will stay here, sir.
Okay, if that's what you want.
But you are no longer slaves.
You are my employees.
Employees?
Sir,
I would like to keep selling liquor.
You can leave your jock itch issue
to me, sir.
[all cheering]
[Bun Lue] Where are you going?
Since the master of the house
dislikes us, why should we stay?
Who said I don't like you?
It's all in your head.
You've never listened to me.
The reason why I kept it a secret
is because I didn't want my mother
to find out
that my wife was a slave.
But today,
since my mother is hooking up with Sin,
I have to come clean now.
You're not embarrassed anymore?
No, because I love you.
Here, I've been keeping this for years...
for you and your daughter.
I just haven't had a chance.
See? I told you it's not Sin.
Don't be so gullible.
Don't listen to what people say.
Especially Khun Theng and Khun Nong.
They are not stable.
Don't you love me anymore?
Aren't you just like them?
It's never occurred to me to do so.
It was just a rumor in Chiang Rai.
I've never had a mistress.
You were obsessed with her
for a while, weren't you?
Groundless gossip.
You don't love me anymore?
But I love you.
Even if you die like Mae Nak,
I'll be waiting.
Waiting until you reincarnate.
-Touching, isn't it?
-Yes, it is.
Here. First night of the wedding.
Wishing you a lifetime of happiness.
[chuckles] May your firstborn be a girl,
the second a boy, the third a girl,
the fifth a boy, and the sixth a girl.
[chuckles] May you lay eggs like a frog.
Yes. Since we have come this far,
from now on,
you'd better schedule your days carefully.
If you're with both of them
on the same date,
one will be on the bottom
and the other one will be on top.
May you be happy.
Learn to forgive each other.
Iang, my child.
You can do it. Doctor...
You've been giving people injections.
You can use your special needle
to impress Iang tonight.
May your love forever grow
and be filled with lasting joy.
Congratulations.
Have fun tonight.
What kind of wish is that?
[all laughing]
Please stay for a drink
after the ceremony.
Sure.
Since we haven't seen each other
for a while.
Bun Lue!
Today is your last day.
Thank you so much, My Lord,
for coming to my place today.
With pleasure, Khun Bun Lue.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you, Sin.
Call me Daddy.
You've gone too far.
45 yards.
A bit windy. Move your aim
a little to the left.
I'll do it myself.
-[groans]
-Khun Bun Lue.
[woman screaming]
[man] Khun Bun Lue got shot!
-What?
-Father!
Bun Lue!
-Shit!
-[man] Help!
-Khun Bun Lue got shot!
-[Plarn] Father!
[Mod] Bun Lue!
Bun Lue, stay with me!
You'll be all right.
Where is it, Father?
-It hurts.
-Where?
-Here.
-Oh, I'm sorry!
How are you?
Are you okay?
They missed the target.
-You didn't get shot?
-No.
[Sin in strained voice] Yes.
I got shot.
-What?
-Sin.
Bun Lue, please help Sin!
Keerati! Keerati!
[Bua] Sin!
Sin was shot.
[wailing]
Wait until I get out of this.
It's so tight, you'll never be able
to escape.
If you can't say something nice,
don't say anything at all.
I told you. I warned you to stop.
Why don't you listen to me?
When did you warn me, sir?
I wasn't talking to you!
Should I beat you up now?
Send them to prison.
[Sorachak] Just you wait!
Forget it...
Rather than sending me to the hospital,
they wanted me to be the photographer.
[groaning]
All right.
Smile, everyone.
One.
Two.
-Three. [groans loudly]
-[all yelling]
Who wrote this?
-Whose letter is this?
-I have no idea.
It's from Chiang Rai.
How could you not know?
Does it hurt, sir?
Why don't you try it yourself?
Call me Daddy.
[Mod] Answer me! Now, this is fun.
I like it.
-Hi, son.
-Son my ass!
Mother, aren't you going to help me?
Why should I? No bad deed goes unpunished.
Most importantly,
you must respect your father, Bun Lue.
You can ask me.
Your mother does everything I say.
You are all the same.
Just like Khun Theng and Khun Nong.
Why don't you answer my question?
Is it fun?
[Mod] You sneaky bastard!
You pervert carpet muncher!
Subtitle translation by:
Ratiporn Chaipiyaporn