Welcome to Street Racing Circuit.
Please state your name.
Are you sure this is the place?
That’s what I’ve gathered from the source.
What source?
You don’t need to know.
Sky.
My ex.
But now that you’ve
seen it, let’s go home.
No.
Wait here.
I don’t wanna cause you problem.
I’ll be gone for a sec.
Rain! Rain!
What a troublemaker.
These people aren’t assholes like my ex.
Right?
- Ready?
- We’re all set, Mr. Payu.
Hey. It’s rare to see you go all out today.
Higher-up’s order.
But you like it too, right?
Your babies are such beauties.
Of course, I like them.
They’re P’ Pakin’s babies.
I don’t dare to mess with that guy.
Nice bike, by the way.
Catch that man!
Which daredevil’s causing a ruckus?
But the real devil’s right here.
Hey! Stop!
Stop!
I’m leaving early today.
You can punish me
later if you’re unhappy.
- I’ll have Saifha replace me.
- Hey!
You’re disobeying P’ Pakin?
This is an important event.
But there's something more important.
Let go of me! Let go!
He’s my boy.
Let’s talk, shall we?
Don’t you know it’s bad to sneak in?
Are you a friend of that boy?
How stubborn.
It’s fine if you don’t wanna answer.
But do you know outsiders
aren’t allowed to enter the venue?
Which means an intruder
like you isn’t allowed to leave.
What do you want?
It depends on what you can offer me.
But if I can choose…
So do you know now what you
need to give to get out of here?
You’d better hurry up.
Looks like the next race’s about to start.
Tick tock.
Just take what you want.
Not Just Wind, but a Typhoon
Where’s a condom?
Under the pillow.
Say something.
Do you realize what you did?
I…
Do you know what would
happen if I wasn’t there?
I’m sorry.
I’m asking if you know.
I don’t want your apology.
Wanna throw your future down the drain?
No matter how stupid you are,
if only you used your brain…
Then you would’ve realized how powerful
illegal street racing’s organizers are.
Making a stupid brat disappear
is a piece of cake for them.
I…
I thought you were mature.
Don’t think that crying out for your
parents’ help can solve everything.
Some matters...
Can’t be solved with just apologies.
Grow up.
Don’t be a crybaby.
I didn’t mean to get anyone in trouble.
I just wanted to get back at you.
That’s all.
Stupid.
Go home.
Stupid. Stupid. Stupid.
That’s all you’ve been saying.
You keep calling me stupid!
Fine, I’m stupid for being reckless.
I’m brainless just like you said.
Just you wait.
I’ll make you so head over heels with me
that you won’t call me stupid ever again.
Then I’ll be waiting.
You’d better keep your word.
What the hell have I done?
Wanna make me fall for you?
I wasn’t gonna show you my bad side.
You wanna make me love you.
But do you know what kind of a man I am?
The night has just begun.
Bring it on.
They’re all assholes.
You’re also an asshole.
You’re leaving?
I don’t have to stay.
So cold.
You were so cute earlier.
At least leave me your number.
At least tell me your name.
What a cold boy.
Have you gone crazy
from being pent up, P’ Pai?
Your big brother? Pent up?
Don’t take your frustration out on me.
Aren’t there any good men left around here?
He’s right here.
Rich and handsome.
A total package.
I want someone wild, not rich.
How do you know I’m not wild?
Please stop, it’s cringey.
Let’s go, we’re gonna
be late for family dinner.
I don’t wanna go.
Mom’s gonna preach
at me for sleeping around.
She won’t stop until
the three of us settle down.
Not gonna happen.
Single life’s the best.
I can sleep with whoever I want.
You’re right.
Freedom is the best.
Let’s go.
Shitty things always happen to me.
Now’s the part you’ve been
waiting for, ‘Chitchat of the Day.’
Today’s topic is...
‘How to forget the one you want to forget.’
Let’s hear some answers from our listeners.
Khun Focus says, ‘Try to live well
every day and we’ll soon forget them.’
I guess Khun Focus is focused
on living her life to the fullest.
Continue.
Let’s check out Khun Pompam’s advice.
She says, ‘Working is the way to forget.’
‘Work to forget. Work to death.
Soon you’ll get over a heartbreak.’
Oops, this method’s a bit
too hard on your body.
This one’s interesting.
Khun Oum says, ‘Why must we forget?’
‘The more you want to forget,
the more you remember.’
‘Let them occupy your thoughts
until they leave on their own.’
What about you? How do you
forget the one you want to forget?
Share your tips with us.
Three Months Later
I’d like to ask about class shirts.
Oh right, we’ve agreed to
use this design for the shirts.
I came up with it.
I think it’s the best one.
Hold on, P’ Som.
What’s this old-fashioned design?
Who uses red and black nowadays?
- It’s so cheesy.
- What’s bad about it?
I’ll show you.
This abstract design strongly
represents architecture.
- It’s got three-dimensional structure.
- It looks confusing.
Do you know how to make your design better?
- I'll show you how to make it better.
- Sig!
- Just turn it upside down!
- Give it back!
- See? It looks so much better now.
- Sig, give it back.
- Or better yet, flip it like this.
- I thought the design out.
I think we should stop for today.
Why?
I’ve got something to figure out.
Sorry.
I’ll make it up to you next time.
And when is that?
I’ll call you when I’m free.
But today I want you to go home.
Please understand me.
It must be changed.
The design you came up with totally sucks.
But we’ve decided on…
Change it.
That’s enough, guys.
Please stop.
Why are you arguing?
Sig, you should accept
the seniors' decision.
- Stop arguing with him.
- I can’t, I’m the sophomore rep.
And I’m just voicing my opinion.
What’s wrong with that?
Just voicing your opinion?
We’ve reached the decision
on the freshmen orientation.
You can’t just ask us to change our plan.
Have some respect to your seniors!
You always bring up seniority
when you can’t argue back.
Cool down.
I’m the coolest I’ve ever been.
If I get any cooler,
I’ll become an ice cube.
Give me some time.
Calm down.
I’m sorry, Sky.
P’ Som’s been moody lately.
He’s been in charge of
orientation activities from the start.
He won’t hand it over even
though he’s in the 5th year.
It’s okay, I understand.
So how have you been lately?
Let me know if you need any help.
I know you’re very busy
with the student club’s works.
It’s a piece of cake.
I can handle them.
And I’m especially free
during the summer break.
But I prefer to do only paperwork.
'Cause I can't lead orientation activities.
You’re so capable.
You’re good at studying
and student club’s works.
‘Cause I’ve volunteered to help.
Unlike Rain, that annoying guy.
He said he’d help but
I haven’t seen him at all.
I’d better go find P’ Som.
Don’t know if he’s calmed down yet.
Just let me know if you need any help.
Better do my work to occupy my thoughts.
Are you okay?
Do you need a hand?
- Sig, deliver these documents for me.
Okay.
Good grief.
- What’s your time?
- Don’t know. Wasn’t paying attention.
As far as I know, your
attention is usually on bikes or…
What does it mean when you
can’t get something out of your head?
It’s either you love it very much
or hate it very much.
Or interested in it very much.
Who is it?
Nice weather today.
Nice my ass.
It’s fucking hot as hell.
What does it have to do with the weather?
Beautiful sky and nice weather
are perfect for making a decision.
And I’ve made up my mind.
About what?
Since he won’t get out of my head...
I won’t let him go.
Wish me luck.
I really feel sorry for his prey.
Has sky watching become
popular among people around me?
Tanjiro’s super cool.
Huh?
I finished it.
Next volume.
Nine. Six.
Huh?
Where’s the next volume?
I remember I bought the complete set.
11 o’ clock.
I stayed up all night again.
So hungry.
And sleepy too.
Wash up, eat, sleep.
I’ll decide what to do after waking up.
He fought with his boyfriend
and wants to complain again.
Hmm?
Sawasdee krub.
Hello?
How come I spoke the lines from this novel?
This is weird.
Hello.
Hello, can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
Who’s calling, please?
And who’s asking?
I don’t know who you are.
But if you’re trying to
annoy me, I’m hanging up.
Hot-headed, aren’t you?
I wonder if you’re hot and bothered too.
Do you want me to help cool you down?
In case you didn’t know,
humans are warm blooded.
And I’m a human.
It’s normal for my body to be hot.
You don’t have to help me.
‘Cause I don’t associate
with cold-blooded animals.
Farewell.
Asshole.
If you’ve got a lot of time to
spare, I suggest seeing a shrink.
No need for that.
I know the nature of my illness.
And it must be treated from the cause.
Prepare yourself, I’m gonna pursue you.
Who are you?
A hot wind god.
Brace yourself, ‘cause I’m serious.
Hey! Wait!
Don’t hang up!
What the hell?
Wind?
Nah.
Impossible.
Someone like him won’t be attracted to me.
What now?
I just wanna tell you that it doesn’t
hurt when you call me an asshole.
I’m used to it.
What now!
Are you angry with me?
No, I’m about to eat.
Then I won’t bother you.
Enjoy your lunch.
I’ve lost my appetite!
I’ve never met anyone
who’s so cute at being rude.
Be careful or this asshole
will be your boyfriend.
Weather forecast for this
morning until tomorrow morning.
Blustery with a chance of typhoon.
Sky!
- Yes, P’ Joy?
- Are you going to class?
Yes.
First day of semester.
Do your best!
Yes, thank you.
Right, have you heard
about the tenant in room 204?
No.
She broke up with her boyfriend.
The whole floor heard
them fighting last night.
I heard it loud and clear.
Looks like the guy was two-timing.
Have you heard?
- Do you know anything about it?
- Not at all.
Then I’ll continue.
The girl was all screaming and shouting.
And…
- P’ Joy.
- Yes?
I need to hurry or I’ll be late.
- Please excuse me.
- Sorry, I got carried away. Run along.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Do your best!
- Yes.
Bye bye. Do your best!
Alright, today we’ll be
talking about formal structure…
See you later.
Chicken white butt.
It will be grilled.
Grilled to the left.
Grilled to the…
Okay.
Everyone now knows the song.
Now, try dancing while
you’re sitting. Okay?
Do you know the dance moves?
Can you dance like a grilled chicken?
Grilled to the left.
Grilled to the right.
Dance while you’re sitting.
Remember, the best dancers
won’t have to sleep in the tent.
Ready? Drums. Go!
Chicken white butt.
It will be grilled.
Grilled to the left.
Grilled to the right.
Very hot. Very hot. Very hot.
Stop.
We’ve found a pheasant.
- What’s your name?
- Ray.
Come up here, Ray.
P’ Som.
You’re already a 5th year.
Can you dance as good as her?
How can a senior lose to a freshman?
Please dance as energetically like her.
Okay, ready, go!
Chicken white butt.
It will be grilled.
Grilled to the left.
Grilled to the right.
- Very hot. Very hot. Very hot.
- One more time!
Good night, good night, good night.
Get home safe, everyone.
Good night, good night.
Good night. Bye bye.
Get home safe.
Shit, how did he get here?
Oh! P’ Pai, Sawasdee krub.
Was it hard to get here?
Nope.
Hey, hold on!
Come here, come here, come here.
You’ve met P’ Pai, right?
He said he got you out of the racing venue.
It’s okay, I’ll introduce you again.
This is P’ Prapai, P’ Payu’s
best friend from the race.
- Oh, and this is my friend…
- Sky.
You already told me.
Wind.
Prapai.
Well?
Am I as hot as I promoted myself?
Umm…
P’ Pai, you’ve got
something for P’ Payu, right?
Where is it?
Oh.
Just a sec.
Here.
It’s very important.
Don’t let anyone but Payu see it.
- Got it?
- Got it.
- I’m leaving now.
- Wait, I’ll give you a ride.
It’s okay, you’ve got a date with P’ Payu.
I can go back on my own.
Hey, that's a lot of stuff.
How will you go back?
Surely not by a bike taxi.
I’ll give you a ride.
I can give you a ride.
Rain doesn’t know about us, right?
I’ll go back with P’ Pai.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay, then I’ll be going first.
- Yeah.
- Bye bye. See you.
Bye bye.
Safe travels, P’ Pai.
See you later.
Bye, Sky.
Let’s go.
This way, please.
Thank you.
You should find someone else to play with.
I wouldn’t have been here
if I wanted someone else.
Look, I don’t wanna play with you.
If you never try, you’ll never know.
It’s because I already
tried that I don’t want to.
Come on, I couldn’t get you hooked at all?
- No.
- Not even a bit?
- Just feel it a bit.
Look, no matter how hard you try
to persuade me, the answer’s still no.
This is so unfair.
Am I the only one who
can’t get enough of you?
How is it unfair?
I didn’t ask for it.
Okay, I give up on this matter.
Good, now move.
That was then, this is now.
Let’s start over.
My name is Prapai.
See? I told you I’m the hot wind god.
A wind god?
I thought you were a Cyclops.
I admit I'm a giant with a
huge, dark one-eyed monster.
Pai Jr., someone says
you’re as huge as a giant.
- Are you done?
- No.
You haven’t told me your full
name, birthday, blood type...
Your favorite food.
Favorite movies.
Most importantly...
Do you have a boyfriend?
You wanna know?
I'll tell you in your next life.
Are you clear, P' Black Giant?
And are you clear, Nong Sky?
That I’m determined to pursue you.
Can’t believe how shameless that guy is!
Pursue me my ass!
No way. Never.
Rain, you’ll be dead meat tomorrow.
A guy like him only wants sex.
Get it together, Sky.
Why would I want you to be my boyfriend?
What an adorable boy.
What’s up, dude?
You went to my boyfriend’s
university just to give a coffee receipt?
It’s important though.
Yeah right, asshole.
Now I consider being called
an asshole a compliment.
Believe me when I say that
the receipt’s very important.
If there’s nothing else, I’m hanging up.
If I hadn’t had an excuse, I wouldn’t
have met the steeled-heart boy.
I’ll give in to you this time.
I’m sorry.
You know why I’m angry?
Well…
I gave P’ Pai your phone number.
Yeah.
Next time, tell me before
you give anyone my number.
But he said he knows you.
Forgive me, I really regret it.
Sure, I forgive you.
- But you must take these.
- What are they?
Student club’s papers.
You must fill out these documents,
ask the seniors to check them.
Then ask the teachers to sign them
and deliver them to the student council.
Got it?
But I haven’t finished a single homework.
And do you think I finished them?
Sky.
Yeah?
I’m sorry.
Can...
Can I get up now?
No, stay like that until you repent.
But I am repenting.
From now on, I’ll guard
your number with my life.
I’ll never give it to anyone again.
Please allow me to get up.
My knee hurts.
Good to hear, but no.
Let me get up.
Can I get up now?
No.
Please.
Can’t you just kneel?
- For how long?
- 30 minutes.
- 30 minutes?
- Your hands too.
- Sky.
- Hmm?
- Please let me get up.
- No.
Don’t you pity your friend?
No.
Scandals happen at my dorm every day.
Which one do you wanna hear?
That’s right.
Hey, I’ll call you back.
Sky, darling. Sky.
Yes?
- You finished your class?
- Yes.
Right, someone asked me to give you this.
What is it?
Here you are.
Take it.
A hot guy driving a luxury car asked
me to give you this sunflower bouquet.
He’s tall and dark.
I wanted to ask his name
but he left in a hurry.
Do you know who he is?
Umm, I think you’ve got the wrong person.
No way, I’ve absolutely
got the right person.
‘Cause you’re the only Sky in my dorm.
So who is he?
Beautiful flowers.
Meanie, why can’t I get you out of my head?
Psycho
Do you like the flowers?
Can you take them back?
No, I don’t have time.
I’ve been very busy these days.
I worked my butt off just to
find time to deliver the flowers.
But I don’t want them.
Do you know why I gave you sunflowers?
- I don’t care…
- ‘Cause sunflowers face the sky.
I can’t be the sun for you.
But whenever you see sunflowers...
Remember that this wind’s
watching over the sky.
Oh, I have a meeting.
Gotta go. Bye bye.
How did he come up with that?
So cheesy.
He's cheesy.
And utterly shameless.
I’m sorry, because of your owner...
You’ve got to end up in the trashcan.
What flowers do teenagers like these days?
Where do you want them delivered?
If the flowers are in stock, the recipient
will get them in two hours at the earliest.
I’m just asking for your opinion.
You usually order roses.
That’s out of courtesy,
but this is different.
Why don't you choose from
the recipient’s personality?
Sometimes sexy.
Occasionally sad.
Mysterious at times.
But I want flowers
that give off lively vibes.
So that he’ll give me a bright smile.
Sunflowers.
Okay, and the delivery address?
No need.
I’ll choose them myself.
I wanna deliver them
to the recipient's hands.
Help me clear my schedule for two hours.
He’ll deliver them himself?
English Subtitle by Saowalak K.
I did a bachelor's and master's degrees in the UK.
-I don't wanna know.
-But I wanna tell you.
Don't you like Prapai?
He's kind, funny and handsome.
I wanna tell you that...
I won't give up.