Rain, wake up.
- What time is it now?
- 8.15.
No matter how hard you cry,
I won't accept your work.
Why am I here?
P' Payu.
Dry your hair properly.
Don't get sick.
I don't wanna take care of you.
How’s your boy?
Better.
Get someone to buy dinner for Rain.
He hasn’t eaten since yesterday.
Okay, leave it to me.
Payu.
P’ Pakin called just now.
Next month’s race schedule is out.
He said that you mustn’t
let another mistake happen.
Yeah, I understand.
I'll call him.
And he said that if the boy’s
naughty, just bring him along.
Not now.
Hey, what do you mean?
Payu! Payu!
- What are you looking at?
- The person who’s eating.
I know I’m eating, but I’m gonna
lose my appetite with your stare.
But you almost finish the food.
It’s because I’m hungry.
Seriously.
You're eating like a baby.
There's food on your mouth.
Just so you know,
I don’t date underage people.
I’m already 19.
Which means I can kiss you.
You already kissed me.
Does it count?
All I tasted was blood.
Then...
Kiss me again.
Rain.
Yes?
You shouldn’t come here anymore.
What do you mean?
Don’t joke like that.
You’re annoyed with me, right?
I know I’m annoying.
I’m sorry, I won’t bother you again.
I... I won’t sneak into
that racetrack again.
I won’t mess with you again.
But please don’t forbid
me from coming here.
Listen to me, Rain.
I’m not annoyed with you.
But…
Didn’t I tell you that I wanted
you to balance your time?
You’re only on your first year,
but what’s it gonna be after this?
Before you design a house,
you need to design your life first.
And if you’re really
serious about pursuing me…
You need to understand that I don’t
want a spur-of-the-moment relationship.
If you can’t be responsible
for your own life...
How can I expect
a more serious relationship?
This is how I am.
If you can’t accept it,
then don’t come here again.
What if I can prove that
I can be responsible?
Can I come here again?
Not until you prove it to me.
But now, finish your dinner
and sleep over tonight.
I’ll send you home tomorrow.
Warm Me with Your Heart
The window’s position isn’t right.
It shouldn’t be here.
- Can’t I put it here?
- No.
See? It’s the wrong direction.
It's blocked.
It should be here.
P’ Som, you’re so eager
when it comes to your sister.
Of course, she’s my favorite little sister.
That's for sure.
What’s up, Rain?
What’s the matter?
You look pretty down.
It should be here.
Okay, I’ll redo it.
As you wish.
Cheer up.
I was recently scolded that a
kindergartener's more creative than me.
And look at me.
I’m still fine.
Alright, alright.
Think of it as an advice from a senior.
Set four alarm clocks and
place them in four corners.
Let’s see if that can’t wake you up.
But you still go back to sleep anyway.
Nonsense.
That’s not true.
Come on.
I’ll buy you lunch.
Okay?
Are you okay?
I’m not hungry.
You go ahead.
Suit yourself.
Whatever floats your boat.
Rain, let’s have lunch together.
It’s not every day P’ Som
offers to spring for a meal.
Let’s go.
I’ve already eaten.
You should go with P’ Som.
Okay.
What about you?
I’ll be with you shortly.
Okay, suit yourself.
- Then we’ll be going first.
- Okay.
Okay, I’ll see you later.
Let’s go.
You don’t like Ple anymore, do you?
I still do.
They guy you’re trying to
win over is P’ Payu, right?
You’re not feeling down
from the teacher’s reproach.
You usually recover fast.
You’re like this because
of a different problem, right?
Rain, be honest with me.
Do you like P’ Payu?
I don’t.
Before you answered me...
Did you look into your heart?
Don’t worry.
You can take your time to think.
And tell me later when
you’re sure about it.
Because no one knows
your heart better than yourself.
Got it?
Goosebumps.
I’d never said something like this to you.
I’m leaving.
Hang in there.
I don’t know.
I just don’t wanna let you down.
- What’s wrong with you, Sig?
- Aren't you gonna work?
- Move your ass!
- Please go ahead.
See here?
I think there’s no need for a rooftop here.
Too easy.
Piece of cake.
- What’s your suggestion then?
- Your work’s finished?
- Easy.
- Finish your work first.
Easy?
You finished your work?
You’ll be short-lived if you sigh often.
Even so, I’ll still live
much longer than you.
So what’s the deal?
Lovers’ quarrel?
We’re not yet a couple.
So my guess was right.
It’s really a love problem.
No wonder you’ve been gloomy all day.
So who’s this person?
Younger? Older?
Well…
Younger. A freshman.
You’re so bad.
So what’s the problem?
The problem is...
They're an architecture student.
I get it now.
Let me guess.
Too busy to answer texts, go on
dates, and have meals together.
Let’s just break up.
Personal experience?
Yeah.
First one broke up with me on 2nd year.
Second one ditched me on 4th year
after we dated for only three months.
Before she left, she lectured me
about having no time for a relationship.
And that I was selfish,
focused only on my works.
Forget it, let’s talk about you.
You broke up with them
or the other way around?
It’s not like that.
By the way, what’s the progress
of Sathorn's house renovation?
Wow, what a sudden change of subject.
Those guys are sleeping like corpses.
Let’s wake them up in an hour.
Sky.
What?
Remember what we talked about last time?
I said that...
I wasn’t sure if I liked P’ Payu.
I still don’t know if I like him.
All I know is...
I don’t wanna give up.
Rain, you know what?
Every time I say you’re annoying...
I never mean it.
Because you never give up easily.
And I like this side of you.
I wanna prove it to him.
Then what are you waiting for?
You’re right.
I’m the kind who acts fast.
Yeah.
He’ll never see my effort if I do nothing.
That’s right.
I’m gonna prove to him that I can do it.
Way to go, buddy.
Thank you.
Don’t mention it.
No biggie.
Just buy me ice cream.
P’ Payu.
Sawasdee krub, everyone.
Sawasdee ka, Nong Rain.
Haven’t seen you in days.
You’ve been busy?
Sort of.
May I sit in the office?
You do it.
Me?
I’m sorry, Mr. Rain.
Boss doesn’t allow you to enter.
Then may I borrow a chair?
Sure.
- Here.
- Thank you.
It’s hot today.
You'll really let him sit outdoor?
It’s not that I don’t pity him.
But who’d dare go against Boss’ order?
If that person’s not you,
then it’s definitely not me.
Let’s get back to work.
Didn't I tell you not to come here?
I just wanted a change of scenery.
Then go to a café or the faculty.
I promise I’ll sit quietly
and not disturb anyone.
But it’s an eyesore.
I wanted to see your face
just for a moment.
How many assignments
do you need to submit?
What about your
project for the finals?
I’m doing it now.
Then go do it at a café or the faculty.
You told me to be responsible.
That’s what I’m doing right now.
Instead of getting distracted elsewhere,
isn’t it better if I stay focused here?
I only need a small space for myself.
I’m not disturbing anyone.
Only this much.
See?
- Mr. Rain.
- Yes, P’ Aon?
Mr. Saifha tells you to go inside.
But P’ Payu told me not to.
Between you and me, someone’s
using his twin as a cover.
Let’s go.
Weather changes can make you sick.
Young men these days are so mean.
Come on, I’ll give you a hand.
Thank you, P’ Payu.
You’re so handsome and kind.
Do you wanna get scolded?
Let’s go.
Oh, a meanie.
Don’t piss me off.
I’m not.
I’ll be straight with you, Big Bro.
It’s okay to worry that the boy
will lose focus because of you.
But don’t be too mean
to him or he’ll run away.
If I thought he’d run away,
I wouldn’t have been this invested.
Don’t tell me.
Yes, I’m confident that
Rain won’t disappoint me.
That’s true.
Everyone you pull tricks on
always runs away.
A fighter like him really suits you.
He’s more than just a fighter.
Who’s smitten with who exactly?
The lovestruck one’s not
the boy but you, Big Bro.
What are you guys doing in my dorm?
- Because it’s the closest place.
- Yeah.
Sky, lend me your underwear.
I’ve been wearing
the same one for three days.
Ew, three-way technique?
- Yeah. Back, front, and inside out.
- Gross. Eww.
Just bear with us.
It’ll be living hell again at 8.30.
Who’s gonna wake us up if we’re alone?
We’re gonna pull an all-nighter here.
Yeah.
Isn't it what you’ve been doing these days?
Hey, what about you?
You usually go home when it’s not urgent.
‘Cause your dorm’s close.
I’d rather spend my time
working than driving.
And I can stop by the garage
with the remaining time.
Huh? What garage?
Your car’s broken, Cloud Jizz?
- Shut up, Home Sig.
Shut up, Home Sig.
- You’re mocking me?
- Okay, that’s enough.
You won’t finish it
if you stop working.
- He’s getting on my nerves.
- Shut up, Home Sig.
Shut up...
Stop.
And you’re still provoking him.
And you, Give me the seaweed
and I’ll let you stay.
Give it to me.
- Here.
- Gimme, I wanna eat too.
- Well, you’re sure enjoying it.
- It’s tasty. I want more.
Here, take it.
- Want some, Sky?
- My dorm belongs to everyone now.
Finally submitted all the works.
I’m so sleepy.
You okay, Rain?
Wanna go sleep in my dorm?
Thanks, but I'm wide awake.
But you haven’t slept.
You’ll still go?
Yeah.
Wow.
Fine, suit yourself.
Later.
Bye bye.
Rain, did you submit the works?
Wanna have lunch together?
Great job, smart boy.
Are you seducing me?
You’re really not gonna wake up?
Ouch!
Why did you hit me?
You seduced me with your bare belly.
I didn't seduce you.
Sleep assaulter.
Sleep assaulter?
How do you know that?
Weren’t you sleeping?
When did you wake up?
When you touched my cheek.
So you were still sleeping before that.
Do you wanna know what I said
while you were sleeping?
Why would I wanna know?
‘Cause I wanna tell you.
I said…
You said…
Looks like I’m interrupting.
Don’t mind me.
I’ll close the door and leave.
In 3, 2, 1 and continue!
Let’s continue.
Dummy, back off.
Oh, I forgot.
You got a call,
but I told them you’d call back.
Anyway, don’t forget to lock the door.
What I wanna say is…
Great job, smart boy.
Go back to sleep.
I’ll let you rest.
Fighting!
Great job.
It’s done!
Model, check.
Presentation boards, check.
I finished two days before the deadline.
This is a miracle!
Wait, Rain.
Let's think over.
How many assignments do I have left?
Two.
Read textbooks and...
I’m all done!
My bed.
Seriously, Rain.
Shouldn’t you use this time to sleep?
Oh, Rainy Boy.
- P’ Saifha, Sawasdee Krub.
- Here to see Payu?
Since you’re here,
I’ll take you to a good place.
We’ve been busy with the
next month’s race preparation.
There, especially that guy.
I run the garage in public while
he takes charge behind the scenes.
But he won’t quit his full-time job
no matter how tired he is.
He’s a stubborn guy.
When he was a student...
He wouldn’t give up his car modification
hobby even if he was very busy.
Have you finished your work?
Jeez, just be honest
and say that you’re happy.
Have you finished your work?
A boss like me can
order people to do the job.
I’m gonna teach Rain how
to ride a superbike today.
Can you ride a motorcycle?
Then I’ll teach you.
Call me Ajarn Saifha.
Okay?
Go get your work done.
As for him, leave it to me.
Okay?
Such a dog in the manger.
- I finished my works.
- Did you get any sleep?
Yes.
I don’t have time to teach you today.
Can we do it another day?
It’s okay, you should get back to work.
It’s my fault I came unannounced.
Since you’re busy,
I should go home.
Bye.
Stay.
Can you wait until I finish my work?
I’ll speed things up.
And I’ll take you to dinner.
I can wait. I’m not in a hurry.
Get back to work now.
You gave up sleep to come to me.
So why can’t I rush through
work to spend my time with you?
I didn’t give up sleep.
Thank you.
I’ll have someone make a bed
for you, so you can take a nap.
I’ll wake you up after my work’s done.
Sawasdee Krub, Ajarn.
This is my end-of-year project.
As you can see, this house is...
Thank you.
My project is inspired by…
Umm…
Great job.
Thank you.
The inspiration for this
house design comes from…
And that’s the end of my presentation.
It appears that you've
gained a better understanding.
Thank you.
Payu, there’s a problem with
roof structure at the riverside site.
It must be fixed today.
I have a meeting.
Can you go there for me now?
- Okay.
- I’ll leave it to you.
So cold.
Rain, what are you doing here?
You’re back.
I have something to tell you.
Why are you out in the rain?
Do you wanna catch a cold?
Didn’t I tell you not
to make yourself sick?
Listen to me, P’ Payu.
You told me to prove
that I could be responsible.
I didn’t know how to do it,
but I did my best.
And today, the teachers praised me.
So I wanted you to be
the first person to know.
Have I done good enough?
Can I stand by your side now?
Naughty boy.
You constantly stir my heart.
Didn’t you wanna take a bath?
Let me go.
That's what we're doing right now.
Because someone’s
body is cold from the rain.
I was waiting for you.
Get out, I’m gonna wash up.
I’m all wet too.
I’ll get sick as well if
I don’t wash up immediately.
Then go to another bathroom.
Stay still.
Rain.
I’m sorry my phone’s battery ran out.
I’m sorry I was late.
I’m sorry I let you sit
in the rain for hours.
I’m sorry.
I forgive you.
I didn’t come here for this.
I came to tell you about
the teachers praising me.
Didn't you ask me...
If you could be by my side?
This is my answer.
Please don’t stop me.
I won’t hold back anymore.
Will you?
But...
I’ve never…
I’ll teach you.
‘Rain belongs to P' Payu now.'
Let me hear it.
Rain belongs to P’ Payu now.
You sneaked in here to sleep again.
Your lips aren't covered.
How careless of you.
I’ll wait until you’re ready.
Do your best.
I’m waiting.
English Subtitle by Saowalak K.
I won’t let you escape.
You lost your chance.
Don’t you understand my feelings?
I wanna talk to you after the finals.
Spring may be coming for you.
Can I have your number?
A place where you can bet everything.
From fame, wealth, to lovers.
That’s the street circuit for you.