My name is Lin.
I grew up outside of the city.
I like studying, reading manga,
and I have a dream.
I want a boyfriend
just like the girls in the comic.
Someone sweet and romantic...
Happy Valentine's Day!
Someone manly wouldn't be bad, either.
Lin, are you okay?
I'm okay.
There are just three of us in our family.
NGOR POCHANA
My brother-in-law, Kieng.
He makes amazing Raad Na
and owns his own restaurant.
He's very kind but very blunt.
Kieng! One Pad See Ew, please.
Do you know what
my secret ingredients are?
-What?
-First, an ass.
What?
-Second, wine.
-Seriously?
Ass and wine. A swine.
So it's pork.
I won't eat just because of that joke.
The second member is someone
who always troubles me.
His name is Due, Kieng's son.
He's technically my nephew.
His dream is to become
a runner on the national team,
but what I don't understand is
why he always finds a way
to interrupt my love life.
Hey!
Due!
Who is that?
When I asked him why,
he told me
to consider him my bodyguard.
Look at that. Nice skin. Very pretty.
Shit!
Who did that?
He not only has a problem with me,
but also his dad.
Why do you run so much?
Shouldn't you be studying?
Listen. If you can't get
into engineering or medicine,
-I will stop paying for your schooling.
-Really, Dad? Medicine?
My GPA is only 1.4.
Then I have a plan for you.
You take over my restaurant.
I'll give you my recipes, everything.
-That's the plan.
-No, it's not.
Due!
Come on, arguing again?
I'm not arguing with him.
I'm teaching him a lesson.
Come on. You've got
a packed restaurant waiting. Let's go now.
How did you get this one?
I tripped during the race.
You tripped and still won a gold medal.
You are pretty good.
Hell, yeah.
Funny though...
Dad never said that.
What's so funny?
You're the only one
with an accent around here.
Is it ever going to go away? Country boy.
Because of his stubbornness,
he decided to run away from home.
He got a sports scholarship
and went to college in Bangkok,
without having to ask
his dad to support him.
4 YEARS LATER
I got into nursing school,
and now work as
a physical therapist in Bangkok as well.
All right, we have a try-out today.
Today's highlight, my honored guests,
is Due, our reigning champion,
also known as Mr. Due, the Speed.
Ready.
Another rising star to watch out for
is a newbie, Mr. Game.
We shouldn't underestimate him.
Because if we did,
we probably wouldn't see him.
-Smart and strong.
-Set.
Is Game going
to beat our reigning champion?
Here we go, everyone!
Look at them go.
Due is in the lead. He's in first place.
Game's right on his heels.
Now he's passing Due!
Due is now in fourth place.
Still in fourth.
He's fifth now.
Still in fifth.
What the hell?
Son of a bitch, he lost!
Shit! I bet a lot of money on him.
LOVE AND RUN
There.
Did your mother-in-law cook like this?
I follow every detail of her recipe.
I even learned how
she would breathe while cooking.
How did she breathe?
She inhaled, then exhaled.
-Sounds familiar.
-Sure.
Is this what you made Due do?
Do everything the same as you.
Now he's run away,
and we have no idea where he's gone.
Hello, customers!
Today, we have
a special promotional offer for you.
Palm oil is normally 25 baht per bottle.
Today, it's 100 when you buy four.
One hundred!
Not only that,
we also have a wide variety
of quality items for you to select from.
-Buy tilapia...
-Get free grouper.
-Buy basil...
-Get free sweet basil.
-Buy collard...
-Free coriander!
-Buy curry paste...
-Free MSG!
-Quality pork...
-Super fresh!
-Pineapple...
-Super sweet!
So take out your wallets...
Come on in.
This offer is for today only!
You two have been working
part-time here for almost four years.
Don't you want to go back to school
and get a college degree?
You can work here full-time
and earn more money.
The reason I dropped out
was to get back on my feet.
-Yeah.
-Nonsense.
I wouldn't have hired you if you weren't
related to my wife. You know?
-I'm here because of a family connection?
-Not me, right?
You both are just the same.
You ate all of this?
Shit!
Well, you're late.
What the hell is wrong with you?
It's delicious.
What's up?
Stay still.
Damn, she's so pretty!
So many places to eat here.
I've never been here before.
Should have come here long ago.
What the hell is wrong with you?
That's my aunt.
Seriously?
Seriously.
-Why don't you go say hi?
-That's crazy!
If she sees me, she will tell my dad.
He will drag me home.
Let's go.
I'm gonna get something
before we head out.
Sure.
Lin!
Do you still read these mangas?
Why not? It's fun.
Look, this one's Silly Girl's Last Love.
It's my favorite book
since its last issue.
I especially love the last scene
when she had no one left,
standing alone
in a field of purple flowers.
Then the guy came out of nowhere
and embraced her.
He said, "You are not alone."
I believe I will meet
a guy like this one day.
How can you still daydream?
Don't good guys only exist in novels?
There might not be many,
but I believe they do exist.
PHYSICAL THERAPY BUILDING TWO
Hi, Mr. Man, back again?
What brings you here today?
You know, musician's life.
I play at Ratchada at 9:00,
Ratchavipa at 10:00, 11:00 at Ratchayo.
Then after midnight at Bucalo.
I actually had to go to Bangklo
this morning, but my body said no.
Why do I need to know this?
Patient information. For your benefit.
Not really, sir.
Please get your blood pressure checked.
My shoulder hurts,
so I'd like some physical therapy.
The same nurse, please.
Lin.
Lin is working
with another patient right now.
I happen to be free. I can do it.
For someone like me, you can't.
-When will Lin be free?
-I'm not sure.
I feel like you're not really
cooperating with me.
You do?
-Nurse.
-Yes?
It's sucking me in!
It got tighter!
-Nurse!
-What are we gonna do?
Nurse! Help! Nurse!
-Who are you calling?
-Nurse!
-Who the hell are you then?
-Shit, that's me.
Calm down. Please stay still.
What is this thing?
It's to check your blood pressure.
Mr. Man...
THERAPIST: MEEN PROMMONTREE
Are you done here?
Can you do me now?
I'm sorry, but I'm leaving now.
Perfect.
Can I give you a ride like last time?
What about your shoulder?
It still hurts,
but I don't care about my shoulder...
I care more about my heart.
Does he know what he looks like?
Please wait for me here.
I'm gonna get my stuff.
Lin, what the hell is this?
Why are you letting
this silly-faced guy follow you around?
Don't you know how to say no?
I already said no,
but he keeps persisting.
But you let him go out with you anyway.
It's not like we go out together.
He just follows me around.
What? How about this?
Instead of saying no, say yes.
You want a boyfriend, right?
Shouldn't we at least have standards?
Ready?
You don't have something else to do?
I have you.
Maybe today you don't have to
because I have to buy stuff
at many places.
No problem. I'll carry stuff for you then.
Good Luck, Lin.
I'm gonna go change.
Let me take care of that.
Can I ask you something?
Do you have a type?
I've never really thought about it.
If you had to think about it?
Do we have to?
Let me do the thinking for you.
Firstly, he should be a sharp businessman.
Secondly, a manly athlete.
Thirdly,
an eccentric musician.
I think I'd like
someone manly like an athlete.
So you like sweaty guys?
I said, "manly like an athlete."
Not sweaty.
-Someone active and nice.
-I see.
This might be the last time
I get to walk you home.
I don't think I can from now on.
Really?
-That's really okay.
-Because...
I'm moving into
the same apartment building.
What?
Damn! That's creepy.
Are you happy?
-I think I'm shocked.
-Why?
I'm only moving
into the room opposite yours.
Opposite room?
Lin.
Trust me,
he's moving so he can be
in the same apartment as her.
He'll get her within two months,
or two weeks at the earliest.
If he uses the pill, then two days.
Could even be tomorrow night with force.
He's coming to get your auntie!
Son of a bitch! Stop aggravating me!
-Hello.
-Why a mixed-gender apartment?
-What?
-There are many only-women apartments
that auntie can stay in.
It's dangerous here.
Bangkok is much more dangerous
than you think.
-Wait!
-What if something happened to her?
-Due!
-Think about it, Dad.
What the hell?
Shit, what's going on here?
Are you surprised?
Please don't tell me this is because...
No, I didn't just change
to match your type.
This is a side of me
that no one has seen before.
It's open for you to see.
Well...
Here!
This is a Garmin watch,
the latest model to monitor your heart.
I don't know why, every time I listen,
I only hear, "Lin, Lin, Lin..."
Well,
the weather is getting hot.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm spraying mineral water.
Don't you think this is too much?
The more the better.
So you can look into my heart.
You tattooed my name?
No, I just wrote it.
Did I hurt you?
No, I was pretending. Was it good?
Why are you doing this?
I just wanted
another glimpse of your face.
But for real,
why are you knocking on my door?
I just moved in, so I'd like to borrow
some plates, utensils...
And I'd like to eat inside too, please.
I can lend you the plates and cutlery,
but you coming in...
I live alone.
I don't think that's appropriate.
-But I don't mind.
-I do. I'm sorry.
Shit. What is it this time?
Due!
Where have you been all this time?
Don't you know
your dad is worried about you?
Where are you staying?
What have you been up to?
-What?
-Did you graduate?
One question at a time, please.
I don't know how to answer.
Just answer. Any of the questions.
Fine.
I work with a Japanese company
in the IT department.
I live with a friend.
I stay away because I don't want
to answer all these questions.
You asked if I graduated. No, I didn't.
I dropped out.
Why? You should at least get a degree.
Well, I'll tell you later. Later.
Not like this. Come on.
Hello, auntie.
My name is Men. I'm his friend at work.
All this time,
I've been taking good care of him.
More importantly,
I'm still single--
Probably will be forever, right?
My number is 09--
Eleven, 12, 1150. Whatever!
How do you know where I live?
You are so out of date.
Just take a quick look
at Google these days.
That's crazy.
Shit.
Oi!
Have you been living alone all this time?
Of course.
-That's good.
-What do you mean?
It's good that you live alone.
Your dad is calling!
Don't pick up!
-Hello?
-Too late.
Lin?
Why did you do that?
Don't tell him I'm here.
-I don't want to lie.
-Lin?
Just talk.
Can you hear me?
What's up?
So Due called me...
What did he say?
He was scolding me for letting you
live in a mixed-gender apartment.
Where did you see him?
See him? Where?
What is up with you, Lin?
Can you hear me?
Lin?
It's upside down!
Hello?
I can't read!
What is going on with you?
I think he must have gotten
the wrong person.
Got the wrong person?
How is that possible?
Well, that's true. How is that possible?
Are you drunk, or am I just confused?
Well...
Did you see him or not? Tell me.
Well, I have to go now.
If something comes up, call me.
Something's come up now.
That's why I called.
That's true.
That's it then.
"That's it" what?
Still don't know anything.
Kieng, I need to talk to you.
-What about? I'm busy.
-What?
What a prick.
Wait.
Let me ask you one more thing.
-What?
-Why did you move here?
I'll tell you when it's time.
So, when was the last time
someone hit on you?
Yesterday afternoon.
Who was it?
I'm not sure who he is.
Could be a musician or an athlete.
Is there anyone else besides that guy?
What's up? Why do you ask?
Why not? Do you have someone or not?
Wait, why? Having someone
is supposed to be a good thing.
Do you want a boyfriend that much?
What is wrong with wanting a boyfriend?
Nothing wrong,
but maybe you don't need to hurry.
I'm a grown woman.
You don't need to follow me around
and dictate my life.
Come on, being alone
isn't that bad in this day and age.
Hi, what's up?
I sent you a new song. Play it now.
Yes, ma' am.
-Auntie!
-What?
-Where's the towel?
-It's in there.
Found it.
So sexy.
You wanna see more?
If you dare.
I thought so.
How is it, living with your pretty auntie?
What is it like?
Nothing.
Why?
Let me tell you something.
What more can you do
to keep people from flirting with her?
You can't be with her all the time.
I admire his dedication.
Following you around all the time.
He got here so early today.
You have to see him.
I don't know what else to do.
I'm going to clean your skin
with alcohol. May I?
You don't need to ask me
because, as far as you're concerned,
you can do anything with my body.
It's a little cold.
Refreshingly so.
Other side.
If you're going to touch me this much,
maybe we should go shower together.
I'm gonna attach the device.
Mood ruined.
May I?
Devices attached.
Lin, I'm gonna head out.
What is this thing? It's everywhere.
It's an electric
muscle stimulation device.
Is there a way to treat this
with your hands on my body?
You're fine. We don't have to.
Too bad.
I shouldn't just carry my guitar.
I should carry the whole drum set.
Lie down, please.
If it hurts, please let me know
because our skins are quite different.
If you have sensitive skin,
the electricity can be too strong...
It could have some side effects.
The word sensitive doesn't apply to me.
I can take anything.
Well then, I'll just turn it up a notch.
Bring it on.
I set the timer for about 15 minutes.
I'll come back when the alarm rings.
But if you can't take it,
press the button here.
Keep that away from me.
I just want you close to me.
That's enough.
Okay, then I'll put it right here.
Excuse me.
Will you sit with me for 15 minutes?
I don't feel like being alone.
Well, I'm gonna excuse myself.
I need to answer a text.
You can answer here.
-It's okay.
It's really okay.
So who is okay and who is not okay?
I'm so confused.
I mean, it's okay
if you answer your text here...
But it's not okay for me
if you go outside.
Well, she's out.
What are you up to?
You know, you just saved my life.
Why? What happened?
Nothing. Just a weird patient.
I got out of it to answer your text.
Shouldn't have bragged so much.
Ann...
I'm taking a week off
to make offerings at the temples,
nine temples to be exact.
Follow your heart.
Temples aren't my thing.
A host bar is more like it.
By the way,
the maintenance guy said
the A2 stimulator is not broken.
The broken one is number A1.
Where is A1 now?
Jum.
I smell something burning.
-I think...
-Oh, my God.
Jum! The patient!
This is the A1 that we're looking for!
Who sent them the A2?
Me, me!
How can it be you? It's gotta be a nurse!
Me dying!
Oh, my God!
What should we do?
-I can't turn it off.
-What then?
The circuit breaker!
-Okay.
-Quick!
Shit!
Now power for the whole building is out!
What do we do now?
Turn it on!
Wait--
Now off!
Off now.
Shit, turn it on!
Jum, why didn't you pull the plug?
-Okay, okay.
-Shit!
He's still alive.
Since you are okay now,
you can change and then go home.
Wait.
Where is Lin?
She's on her break.
When is she coming back?
She's not. She has to tend to other cases.
Still asking for the girl. Unbelievable.
We should be glad he didn't die.
If he had, his spirit would be here,
following you.
I heard about a new student coming
to do research. They said he's cute.
Can't be as cute as my doctor, Dr. Eak.
Here he comes.
-Hello, Doctor.
-Hello.
Why are you here? Get back to work.
I'm almost done.
Slut.
So we were wondering...
Why are you here so often?
Actually, I want to be here every day.
Oh, my.
Excuse me. I have to go back to work.
I'll try to come by every day.
Yes, Doctor.
Don't work too hard.
It's the right room.
Who's there?
Oh, it's Man.
Lin.
Who is this guy?
This is my nephew.
Oh, nephew!
My name is Man. I live right across.
Call me Uncle Man.
Give me a hug.
No need to push. I don't mind at all.
-Lin and I are--
-Stop.
-No need to be shy.
-Is there something you need?
Yes, there is.
I'm a guy who cares about health,
and I got some healthy stuff for you.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Since you don't live alone anymore,
can I come in?
And we can have a meal together.
I'd like to get to know
your nephew better, too.
Coming.
How do you know this guy?
He's a patient at the hospital.
Here we go.
Wait. Where is the water?
Uncle Man.
Your armpit hair is so close,
it's merging with my nose hair.
I didn't think you'd mind. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
That is a detox drink for your health.
It cleanses your small intestines
to your large intestines.
Health comes from within.
I must tell you. It's very good.
And this is all organic.
It makes your skin glow and look radiant.
Fills your body with healthy antioxidants,
delays aging, and helps you stay young.
Just the way I like, forever.
Would you like some, dear nephew?
Try this.
I have quite a lot.
It's in the veggies now.
It's not in.
It's so in!
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm eating this one then.
You're going to eat that?
Of course, my armpit hair is also organic.
Very safe to eat.
When are you leaving, Uncle?
Leaving? We need to finish eating.
So you'll leave when we finish?
All right. Okay.
Are you okay?
What do you think?
Are you free tomorrow?
I wanted to ask you
to bring some stuff to the hospital.
Lots of stuff. Is that okay?
Where are you going?
Getting some grilled pork.
I need some meat.
I heard you're getting grilled pork.
I'd like to go, too.
Nope.
Where?
Right inside.
Hi, Doctor. You're here so early.
I'm here for a patient. Are you alone?
Where do I put these?
On the table.
The others are coming.
Have you eaten anything?
-Would you like some coffee?
-Which side of the table?
Any side.
Left or right?
Any side. Just put it down.
I'll leave you
to take care of your things.
I'm going to work.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
My nephew lacks etiquette.
I asked him to help, and now it's a mess.
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
That's okay. I just got here too.
Besides borrowing your papers today,
I'd like to shoot
a physical therapy video.
Sure.
What are you doing here?
Are you...
I remember you.
You lost your title to me
during my freshman year.
You!
What are you doing here?
He's my relative. My nephew.
You are Lin's nephew?
Yeah.
You look older than her.
You want to bring it on?
Such a small world.
I'm doing my research here,
and Lin is helping.
Who cares?
So I haven't seen you
since my second year.
I work, okay? I have to work,
so I dropped out. Get it?
Is that so?
I didn't see you for your graduation.
When are you coming back?
Don't you have
something else to talk about?
Okay, we're going to shoot a video, right?
Wait for me in room two, okay?
Okay.
What video?
He just told us. It's for his research.
I'm gonna start now. First position.
This is for someone who has
muscle paralysis in the facial area.
We'll start from the forehead.
Raise your eyebrows like this.
And for someone who has this condition,
they won't have any wrinkles here,
and we would do this...
in order to relax the muscle.
Next, we ask the patient to smile,
grin like they're super happy.
Is that your grin? Okay.
Then we would massage, like this.
Next, pucker your lips like this.
This is how we stimulate.
All done.
We support them with our hands, like this.
From what I gather,
you seem to have a very healthy body.
You're truly an athlete.
Well, I'm not that healthy.
Did you know that this research
has taken me to many places,
but this place is the most impressive one.
Because of you.
Because of me?
You're very good and very pretty.
Thank you.
Are you free tomorrow?
I have an assignment from the university.
They want me
to shoot a video to teach people
how to practice physical therapy.
Tomorrow?
Please, Lin. Please.
It's at the park nearby.
I'll buy you lunch.
I think I can go.
And you don't have to buy me lunch.
The freshman kid that we lost to?
-The world is really small.
-Yeah.
This sucks.
Does he like your aunt too?
How would I know?
Why are you taking it out on me?
-Very good.
-Cute, right?
What are you watching?
Look at this.
She's making videos
to sell vitamins online.
Who can take these vitamins?
Everyone can.
Only one month,
and your skin will be radiant.
You can say goodbye to your ugly face.
Bitch. How do you make a sale
with that mouth?
Did you know the hospital
is offering scholarships to employees?
You can apply
for a scholarship to England.
You only need to submit a form,
and if you're suitable,
it's two years of free education.
No need to take an exam?
No. I wouldn't apply
if it required an exam.
I would eat so many foreign sausages
if I got to go.
What do you say, Lin?
It's too far. I don't want to go.
There is no place like home.
Suit yourself.
Stay here and enjoy your hometown.
Nothing is that hard.
Listen to the the guru.
You don't have to do it by yourself.
How's that?
Haven't you heard?
In order to defeat your enemies,
you need to befriend them first.
Thank you!
All right.
We need to interrupt this performance.
The restaurant has asked us to promote
only good things for our customers.
Our hot promotion for today!
Order one Fameson, get one Dorson free!
Dorson is a whiskey
that helps the gentlemen.
With 69 exclusive ingredients.
You don't need Viagra anymore.
This will turn a boy in to a man...
down there.
Turn a needlefish into an anaconda!
You just enjoy yourself
and let the drink do the work.
It will be hard to control at first,
but once you get the hang of it...
A wild horse to a unicorn!
We can control it as we want!
Give me that.
What brings you here, dear nephew?
I need to ask you for some advice.
You've come to the right place.
Well, I think this might upset you.
What is it?
-Someone is hitting on my aunt.
-What? Are you serious?
I'm serious!
And he doesn't deserve her!
That's right!
You mean I deserve her, right?
I mean, you need to do something.
Are you okay?
It's the rage.
So, everyone, the first position
we're gonna do is this.
It helps strengthen your back.
You can do it at home.
And your family could help you.
Hello, Uncle Man.
Where are you?
I'm in the bathroom.
I'm not ready.
What's wrong?
Yesterday, I drank Dorson.
What about it?
I'll show you on the camera.
Shit!
Okay, let's get started.
Draw your knees up like this.
Okay. And lift your back.
That's it. Support here.
So close again.
Game and my aunt are getting close again.
Go down. Go down.
Do it like this
and hold for ten seconds. Do four sets.
This is quite a bold position.
A little.
I wouldn't do this
with anyone except my husband.
Actually, you can. We are not a couple.
It'd be nice if you were.
You look cute together.
Please, don't tease.
She's gonna be mad at me.
If you don't get her, let me know.
I have many nieces.
These grannies are encouraging them.
You need to get here, now.
It won't go down.
Go down. Go down.
Are you tired?
It's quite hot.
You really don't have a boyfriend?
Why do you ask?
Do you want to be my boyfriend?
Not only are you good at what you do,
you are also good at guessing.
Lin!
Why are you here?
I'm claiming my love back.
You little kid.
Do you know who I am?
Everyone, this is my girlfriend-to-be.
And this little kid
is someone who is taking her away.
Lin, is that true?
He's just a patient.
Just a patient.
Man.
I think you misunderstood something.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Oh, no!
Man, you're creeping me out.
I think you should go.
Don't talk to me like that!
Here's my rage!
Man,
please go.
I'm asking you.
Well, if you ask,
I must go.
Does she even know you were behind it?
I didn't tell her.
-Don't.
-Don't do it again?
Don't ever admit it.
Someone wants to buy your building?
If Kieng agrees to sell his place too,
they're gonna buy it
for five million each.
-Five million!
-Yes.
Is that true?
They're really gonna buy it
for five million?
Yeah, is that true?
It's so old. I wonder
if they'll really pay five million for it.
If you agree to sell,
I'll call them right away.
Excuse me. I think I forgot
my tote bag here the other day.
It's white,
and it has a prince and princess decal
on it.
Let's go!
Has anybody found it or seen it?
I don't think so.
You can contact our officer via Line.
It's our official account
for lost and found services.
Thank you.
Is this your aunt?
What do we do?
Hello, I'm Mr. Chat from Super D.
I'm an officer at lost and found.
I will use this account to contact you.
Okay.
Do you have a picture of the item?
It's a tote bag.
I'm gonna send you the photo.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Asking for details.
It's quite old.
Yes, mine is so much better.
True. Can't beat yours.
If you talk on the second floor,
everyone on the third floor can hear.
Well, it's an echo.
It's not. It's a broken ceiling.
What are you laughing at?
Why is there a garbage room
on the third floor?
That's his bedroom.
Why are you telling him?
You could have spared me.
Are they your ancestors?
Yes, I will tell you their stories.
I know it so well.
The guy is his father-in-law.
He owned this building.
The woman is his wife.
The Raad Na recipe was hers.
And this one is Kieng's wife,
his better half.
What about these two kids?
These two? The boy is Kieng's son.
And the girl
is the grandmother's daughter.
She is his aunt, and he is her nephew.
So they are relatives. Makes sense?
Not really.
But there's more to the story.
-There's more?
-There's more. Let me tell you.
It occurred 23 years ago.
They were on their way
to get ingredients for Raad Na.
When they were crossing the street,
a sedan came straight at them...
-Bam!
-No, it went past them.
The three of them hurried into the car.
He started the engine.
Drove to the intersection,
and just then...
-A truck!
-No truck.
-A trailer!
-No trailer.
-What then?
-Appendix.
His appendix burst.
It hurt so bad,
he stepped on the accelerator.
The car hit a bicycle, and they all died.
I should have gone somewhere else today.
This is Mr. Chat again from Super D.
We're trying our best
to find your missing item.
I see. It's okay if you don't find it.
No, it's not. I'll try to find it.
Thank you.
I need more information.
What was in the bag?
A manga.
So is it still five million?
If you decide to sell this year.
What about next year?
Next year, the price will go down.
It'll probably be worth four million.
Just one year,
and a price-drop of one million.
-What about two years?
-Then it might be three.
-Only three million?
-Three hundred thousand.
That's a major price drop.
Three years and 4.7 million gone.
Well, hey.
Hurry up and make a decision.
Excuse me.
Which manga?
It's a girly manga.
Silly Girl's Last Love.
I've read that too.
So strange.
I've never met a guy who's read it.
I like it, especially the ending.
When the guy says, "You are not alone."
My friend keeps mocking me about it.
I have that sticker.
I like cats.
Really? Are you also a cat person?
I used to have one growing up,
and then it died.
Now, it's hard for me to keep one.
Same for me.
What a coincidence.
It's quite old.
Is it still five million?
If you decide to sell this year.
Hurry up and make a decision.
Who are you talking to, Lin?
A guy for sure.
I knew it.
What?
You're hitting on your own aunt.
I'm not.
You son of a bitch. Ungrateful nephew.
Our manager can see those texts, remember?
I did see it.
Are you hitting on your own aunt?
No, I'm not. I'm not.
What kind of nephew are you?
Having feelings for your own aunt?
I don't have any feelings.
I'm doing all this--
Don't tell me the whole story yet.
I'm having fun.
Where is your badge, by the way?
You'll get fined if you don't have it on.
Shit!
What's up with him?
Where are you?
I'm heading back to the apartment.
My friend is stopping by.
What's up?
Nothing.
Is that a guy?
It's my nephew.
Let me go first. Quick! Over there!
Could you be more gentle?
He could have popped my boobs.
Is there an elevator here, Lin?
Just walk.
I told you so many times. I'm low-class.
I don't like going up so high.
Walk.
Is it on the third floor or 300th floor?
Come on. We're almost there.
Can't get it in?
-Yeah.
-Hurry up.
I'm home now. Why did you text me?
What's wrong?
You know, stretching.
A little exercise. Nothing to do.
Lin, is this your nephew?
Stretching? Let me help.
All done.
Lin, your nephew looks super yummy.
Wanna adopt him?
You can't take that back.
You know I'm serious.
Anyway,
don't you think this Mr. Chat is weird?
Is he supposed to text you like that?
Have you met him?
No, it's an official account.
Is he flirting with you?
No.
Let me see.
"What are your likes and dislikes?"
"I don't like being alone."
Ugh!
"I totally understand.
I'm from another province too,
and now live alone."
"Same here."
"You've been alone all this time?"
"Yes."
Yes, my ass.
Aren't you living with your nephew?
Well, he just moved in.
-So flirty.
-I didn't flirt.
Can a company's admin
talk to a customer like this?
Well, he said the company
wants him to be friendly.
And you believed him?
Don't you think he's a creep?
Don't say that.
At least I know where he works.
Let me see more.
"What about the things you like?"
"I like many things, especially...
food."
Enough.
What are you doing?
Reading your lover's texts?
Oh, my God. How did you know?
Look at this.
She hasn't even met him.
So what? It's my business.
Lin, I have to go now. Damn.
If I didn't have work,
I would have stayed longer.
All right. You can come anytime.
You said it.
Excuse me.
I'm going now.
Can I have a kiss?
Next time then.
See you.
Take care.
Dear nephew.
You can't just walk past me like that.
Uncle Man, I didn't see you there.
What can I do for you?
You don't need to do anything.
I'm in the process of not being
in love with Lin. Permanently.
What process?
Yesterday, I wanted to delete her
from my Facebook friends list.
Just when I was about to do so,
I saw one of her friends.
She's super cute.
I would like to get to know her.
Look, she sells things online.
So go ahead.
You can buy the stuff she sells.
You don't need to tell me that.
I already did.
Bought these contact lens.
You are so fast.
I'm going to order 20 bottles of vitamins.
And she will deliver them in person.
Here?
It can't be here. What if Lin sees her?
She will be heartbroken.
They're friends!
Very thoughtful.
Am I a bad person?
How could that be?
All you did was follow your heart.
-That's cool.
-You mean it?
-Mr. Man?
-Yes.
This is your order.
Twenty bottles of vitamin C.
Where is Ya?
I'm Ya.
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm not. I'm Ya.
Shit.
How come you don't look like your picture?
It's the natural look today.
-Can I get my money back?
-What the hell?
Due!
Go check on the seafood sales for me.
Men came up with a weird promotion.
Buy clams and get free mothballs?
What was he thinking?
Stinky clams. Who is going to buy that?
Go on. Check on the bakery sales too.
I'm not returning the money.
If you don't, I'll tell everyone.
Shouldn't have bought your stuff.
Look at this.
I'm wearing this for you!
Even though it burns!
-Why is your face like that?
-What is wrong with my face?
-It's not like your picture!
-So what?
You, too, act super rich in your profile.
Look at the real you.
Is that really human hair?
Shut up, scammer!
What is going on over here?
It's getting quite loud.
This guy is a scammer!
-Bitch, stop talking like that.
-What's going on, Ya?
-Lin!
-Man?
Auntie Lin!
Men?
What are you doing?
Working.
I know you are Mr. Chat.
I think you should come down.
It's quite a mess.
Auntie.
Auntie, calm down.
Why are you doing this?
Well...
I told him.
I don't know why he's doing this.
You don't get it.
-There is more to this story.
-How so?
It's obvious he's hitting on his aunt.
He's not.
He just doesn't want her
to have a boyfriend.
For him, if she can like
someone she's never met,
that's better than someone else.
At least the chat guy is not real.
Let's just say
he can't make a move on his aunt,
so he's doing everything he can
to get in the way. That's it.
Thank you, Lin.
You helped me a lot with my research.
Lin.
Is something bothering you?
Why? It's that obvious?
You're quite distant.
But you're still cute.
Excuse me.
Is that all?
That's all. We ordered four dishes.
I mean you.
Besides the food, do you also want me?
Just like that?
-So cheesy. Right?
-Yes.
Did you invite him, too?
No.
How did you find me?
I went to the hospital.
They told me you were here.
Why are you here?
You're really going to be with him?
Why are you asking me these things?
-Well, I'm--
-Quiet.
Don't be with him.
How do you know if he's a good guy?
I am a good guy.
What about someone
who lied to his own family?
Is that a good guy?
-Calm down.
-Shut up!
Just don't be with him.
I don't think he's a good guy.
What?
Who are you to judge him?
Would you be okay
if someone messed with your life?
You shouldn't mess with anyone's life.
You know, you always upset people.
What do you want me to do?
Instead of following me
and getting up to nonsense,
you should go back to school.
At least, that will help your dad.
Until you do that,
I'm not gonna see you anymore.
Lin, take a seat.
How are you?
I met Due.
He hasn't finished college,
and he's too afraid to tell you.
He's working part-time at a supermarket.
One more thing.
Someone wants to buy this building.
Really? Are you gonna sell it?
That's okay with me.
Because I don't think Due is gonna
come back and do something here.
I'd like your opinion.
Why?
This is yours. It's for you to decide.
Professor.
We'd like to come back to college.
Well, it's about time
you came to your senses.
And...
is there a try-out for college?
-Yes. You want in?
-Yes.
It's full.
Only one left. Hurdles.
Okay.
Sign here.
Is Game in, too?
Are you scared of him or something?
Auntie.
If I'm gonna sell this place,
I need to tell the kids the truth.
What should I do?
What would you do?
It's you!
Here we are again.
We'll see.
I'm not gonna lose to you forever.
I won't make it easy for you.
I'm on A team.
You need to pass from B team
to compete with me.
I'll wait for you.
We're back again at the college try-out.
Ready.
Five of them are all set.
A TEAM
Keep your eyes on them.
Don't take your eyes off Game.
B TEAM
Believe it or not,
we have Mr. Due, the Speed.
Always brings bad luck
and keeps disappointing a fan like me.
He's in B team, that means
he needs to be in the top three.
Waiting for the signal.
Set.
A TEAM
Here we go!
It's so fast, I can't catch up.
Look at their legs go. Here we go.
B TEAM
All right, it has begun.
Very beautiful start.
Don't look anywhere.
Game already jumped two hurdles.
He's moving up from fourth to second.
Here he comes.
His legs are working super hard.
There he goes.
Game won first place for A team.
Can Due make it to the top three?
Can he do it?
Oh, my! He made it into the top three.
An announcement
for the buffalo racing event in Chonburi.
It takes place every year
on October 18th at Ban Bung.
My honored guests,
before we begin another race,
let me thank all our sponsors.
Suriyan Coffin, everyone.
"Your suffering is our joy. Buy one
for the parent, get one free for the kid.
If you're sick and in the hospital,
kindly prepare yourself."
They also provide
decorative lighting and a joss-stick pot.
The next shop is Porn's Kites.
They've got all kinds of kites,
BDSM, bondage...
Quality kites that fulfill
all your desires.
You have to win.
Due.
Someone's here to see you.
Dad.
Do you have a minute to talk?
I have you something.
Your mom and I
were just grandma's employees.
What?
Lin is their daughter.
We were just their employees.
But she loved us so much.
After she passed,
I made a promise to myself.
I would take care of Lin as family.
Just like they took care of us.
I've been keeping
this secret for a long time.
Why are you telling me now?
Because you're not
coming back to live there.
I'm gonna sell the building.
Part of the money will be Lin's.
I don't have a plan B for you anymore.
You need to take care of yourself.
You mean...
Lin and I are not related?
Ready.
All right.
We're back with another hurdle race.
Let's see if Due
can make an awesome comeback.
Set.
They're very close now, everyone!
Game's cleared the first hurdle.
Second.
Due is close. Game is ahead.
Third one.
Can he catch up? Can he?
He's back. Due!
Where the hell is he going?
Where are you going?
Leave me alone.
I have to tell you something.
-I don't wanna hear it.
-You must know this.
I don't wanna hear it!
We're not related!
What?
Look...
My mom and dad...
were just your parents' employees.
Is that true?
Are you teasing me again?
There's nothing to tease about.
My dad just told me.
Lin.
We are not related.
What the hell?
Lin.
I'm sorry.
All this time...
You can be stubborn, terrible...
You can tease me however you want.
I don't mind.
But now you're telling me this.
That we're not related?
That means I have
no one else left in this world.
At least I had you as a nephew...
I had him as my brother-in-law.
I had a family.
And now you're saying...
we're not family.
How is that supposed to make me happy?
-Lin...
-You're so cruel.
Do you even know?
Sometimes I feel lonely, but at least...
I know
I have a family waiting at home.
But now...
you're telling me
that I never had a family at all.
Lin...
Is this what you were afraid of?
The scholarship in England,
is it still available?
It's very close to the deadline now.
There was one space left last week,
but I'm not sure
if they've finished the selection.
Do you want to go?
Yes, is it still possible?
I'll see to it.
They only accept people
younger than 30. Do you know that?
Yes, I do.
I'm not over 30.
Lin, that's right!
You're two days away
from turning 25. I remember.
Wait. You're younger than your nephew?
Ann!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll leave it to you then, Doctor.
All right.
I'm going to see patients, then.
Where have you been for so many days?
I went to Khon Kaen for merit-making.
I see.
If you're interested,
Jum can take you to do that in Isan.
She's invited us so many times,
but we just can't.
Her itinerary is so packed.
Do you know where she took us?
We went to pay our respects
to Lady Mo in Korat.
The relics at Nakhon Phanom.
Praya Tao Ngoi at Sakon Nakhon.
Then we circled around.
Kham Chanot at Udon Thani.
Then we paid our respects at Phra See.
Phra Sai!
Phor Phra Sai at Nong Khai.
If that were not enough, we also went
to see the sand chedi at Roi Et.
I don't even know why you're a nurse.
You could just work
for the Thai Tourism Department!
Why are they smiling?
Don't tell me that you and Jum...
Is it gonna work?
Of course.
Quick, your aunt is here.
Due, try to look nice.
She's here.
What the hell? Light the candles.
Are you waiting for them
to light themselves?
Can you look better?
When she gets here, just go in.
She's coming. Ready.
It's hot today.
Hot?
Is it going to rain?
-Yeah?
-Shit!
Fire!
Help me!
The doll!
You dumbass, come help me first!
Water!
Shit!
I've got water!
Water's here!
Son of a bitch.
The fire was out already.
Happy Birthday. I wish you the best and--
Okay. You take care.
Lin. I'm sorry.
It's okay, brother.
Safe travels.
Call me sometimes.
Ya, Lin is leaving soon.
We're going to miss her so bad.
Sure.
What are they looking at?
Oh, my God!
I didn't know you come here.
Not dressed like a rocker today?
You scammer!
You and your ugly face!
So what? Got my feet stuck in your mouth?
You want some of this?
Ya! Be quiet!
Man, I'm asking you--
I think you should mind your own business.
Why is he dancing over here?
Shut up. You don't even know how to dance.
This is only for real dancers.
Move.
Do you want a dance-off?
Bring it on.
Nice butt.
Man, are you okay?
Bitch! You kicked me.
How do you know that?
Ya!
LIN, I VALUE YOU THE MOST
FOR ALWAYS BEING BY MY SIDE.
I MISSED YOU THE MOST.
NEVER MEANT TO ANGER YOU.
I'm sorry. Do you really
need to memorize this?
I'm sorry. Do you need to memorize this?
Shouldn't it come from the heart?
Stop talking. This comes from my heart.
But it's a lot. I can't remember all,
so I have to memorize.
Hi, Dad.
Due, did you know Lin is leaving?
What? And no one told me?
Which flight? Which airport?
Due!
-This one.
-Which one? This one?
You're the only one
with an accent around here.
Is it ever going to go away? Country boy.
Well, then you're a country girl.
What are you doing?
Lin!
Why didn't you tell me you were leaving?
Can we talk?
Lin.
You know,
I value you the most.
For 18 years, from then to now.
When I was away for seven years...
I missed you the most.
I never meant to anger you.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Can you forgive me?
-Let's go back.
-What's the matter with you?
We're good now.
We should go home.
How can I go home? Are you crazy?
Did you really think you'd say sorry
and things would be the way you want?
What am I to you?
I said sorry.
Why are you still mad?
I'm doing everything I can.
Can't you understand that?
I'm not the one who decides
if we are relatives or not.
You're not doing anything wrong.
We just feel different things.
I'm sad...
but you're happy.
How can you be happy?
Because I like you!
I've always liked you.
Isn't that disgusting?
Because I felt this way...
I was disgusted with myself.
How can I have feelings
for someone who is family?
Why does...
being with you make me so happy?
I never wanted to acknowledge it
because I knew it was impossible.
But it's not now.
Now I can like you.
I don't have to feel
like I'm weird anymore.
I don't have to be confused anymore.
I just hope that maybe...
you feel like that too.
After all this,
and all you can think about is yourself.
Okay, Lin.
Okay.
We don't have to go that way.
How do you want us to be? Tell me.
We can be siblings, friends, anything.
Or you want to be
aunt and nephew like before.
We can be like that too.
From now on,
you can be with whoever you want.
I will not bother you.
I will fully support you.
Okay?
I'm asking you for just one thing.
Please don't leave.
Please.
That's the last time I talked to him.
I decided to leave.
I really had to be alone this time.
At least, being alone
gives us time to review
the things that happened.
In reality, meeting someone is not as easy
as the manga makes it out to be.
Sometimes, the person we like
doesn't feel the same.
Sometimes, the person who likes us,
and we think he's cute, too,
we still have to part ways
because of something else.
Sometimes, no matter
how hard someone tries,
we could never like him back,
even though he would go
as far as changing himself.
Ann told me that having someone,
maybe we don't have
to think about that at all.
Just let life happen.
For me, right now,
I know that having someone
is not as important.
It's family that matters.
I think Due might feel the same.
Thank you.
NGOR POCHANA
MENU
Can I order Raad Na, please?
Just like he said,
you're not alone.
Without Kieng and you over there,
I was super lonely.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too.
I didn't know you could act your age.
I'm going now.
Okay.
Can I ask you something?
Yes?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why don't you ask me?
No need to text.
Have you found someone you like?
Subtitle translation by Sirin Sinthupong