[lighthearted music]
[upbeat music]
[Nam] This edition's questions: Love,
H2O Volume 24.
[ping]
[woman] I have a crush
on my colleague. Should I tell him?
If you do, you might lose a colleague
but gain a boyfriend.
Nice girls finish last, remember?
[man] I'm dating two girls at once.
I can't break up with one of them.
What should I do?
[Nam] Not being
the chosen one is bad enough,
and you still want to fool them?
Don't be selfish.
[woman 2] He ditched me. I'm so mad.
What should I do?
[Nam] If you can let go, you'll win this.
Let go of what's not right
and rather look for the right one.
[woman 3] Is your resort nearly finished?
I wish you and O the best.
[Nam] It'll be in two more months,
thank you.
[phone ringing]
-[receptionist] Hello.
-Hello.
O, have you sent in the manuscript?
[O] Nam.
Yes?
Let's break up.
[O takes deep breath]
I'm sorry.
[melancholic music]
[bright music]
[Dog] Hey, wait up.
TWO WEEKS LATER
[Nam] Where is the freshy group?
[Dog] I'm not sure.
Nobody is handsome around here.
What is it with you?
Are you here for the popularity check?
-[female student] Let's ask for photos.
-What is with you?
Is it really you, Dog?
Yes, I'm Dog.
I watch every episode of your show.
I watch every clip;
3,000 views are just from me.
You have very good taste.
Thank you. Take a selfie with us?
-Sure.
-[giggling]
[lighthearted music]
[male student] Hurry.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
[male student] Hi, bro.
Nam! Hurry up.
Come on.
[female student] Dog! Dog!
Get up, get up. Hurry.
Tuk tuk, and three... four!
[all singing]
♪ Tuk tuk carries charcoal ♪
♪ Going up the bridge, down the bridge ♪
♪ It goes left, it goes right ♪
♪ And shake, shake, shake, shake ♪
♪ Tuk tuk carries charcoal ♪
♪ Going up the bridge, down the bridge ♪
♪ It goes left, it goes right ♪
♪ And shake, shake, shake, shake ♪
[cheering]
Are you sure about doing performing arts?
[groans]
Why do you say that?
The study material is hard.
And hard work lies ahead.
[female student]
And if it doesn't feel right,
what should I do?
[Dog] Don't force yourself into it.
If it doesn't feel right, change it.
And find something you really like.
If it's not right, then it's not.
If you happen to find
something you like...
it will be with you
for the rest of your life.
Whoa.
Are you advising me to choose
my major or my boyfriend?
-[laughing]
-[Dog] What do you think?
[female students sigh]
Hey, just do your best.
And be happy with your choice.
Do you understand?
[sentimental music]
[Dog sighs]
Nam.
I just met Taek.
Taek who?
The architect, O's junior friend.
Oh, that Taek.
Yeah.
Uh...
I don't know...
O doesn’t talk about him much.
I only talk to him about the resort
these days.
Where did he ask you to go hang out?
No, I only ran into him.
Why?
Nothing.
What is wrong?
Pay attention to me, you come with me.
What's wrong with you?
You become more like a dog.
And who is it that makes me
become more like one?
It's because of you. You have a good nose.
Hey, how ungrateful.
Who helped you
at the freshman reception, remember?
If I didn't help you sniff the alcohol
that the seniors put random things in,
like socks and stuff...
And you cried
because you didn't want to drink.
When I sniffed it,
I found out that it was only tea.
And I told you,
"It's just tea, you can drink it."
Do you remember? Do you?
And ever since then,
you've called me "Dog."
And now, everybody calls me "Dog."
Even my dad calls me "Dog."
Did you know that my dad
calls me "Dog" too?
[Dog groans]
[Dog] Nam?
Huh?
Are you free at the end of July?
Let's go to Lijiang.
Lijiang?
You just went there. Why again?
I want to shoot a TV program.
The first one will be aired
on national TV.
I'm not sure if you want to go.
I'm just asking.
If you happen to agree, it'll be free.
Free food, free accommodation.
-We can take some photos.
-Sure,
I decided to go
when I heard the word "free."
That's my girl.
[lighthearted music]
Hey...
Thanks for inviting me.
And also for the China trip.
Don't worry, I know you like free stuff.
Dog.
Are you free on August 13?
Well...
I want to ask you--
I know.
You want to celebrate
the belated Mother's Day?
No, not that.
Is it not?
Sure, wherever.
If it's for you, I would go anywhere.
Thank you very much.
Just go get some rest.
[sentimental music]
TAEK
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
THE BRIDE IS NOT NAM?
[sentimental music]
EDITOR
About the resort for O's column,
he sent the resort in Pai to me.
He told me to feature it.
It's okay.
We discussed it last week.
The resort is not quite ready.
Let's do that later.
I have to go.
Wait, we haven't talked about the sponsor.
-Yeah.
-[message notification]
[Dog] "Will you come see me
at the office tomorrow?
I need help."
Hey, I need to do something.
-I have to go.
-Okay, bye-bye.
Hey?
[newscaster] Hello, everybody.
And now, I'm here at the press conference
of the concert
for the famous boy band, A.CIAN.
You want to know now?
Listen up. This Ohm guy...
is the one who imports concerts
from abroad.
An A-list celebrity like him
is very difficult to reach.
But...
But?
Nam already interviewed him.
It's going to be easy.
Is that right, Nam?
You've  interviewed him before.
-You have.
-Haven't you?
-You have, you really have.
-Is that right, Nam?
Yes, I have.
Hey, Chef, that was one to one.
But he's rumored
to be with a lot of girls.
Your hair looks great today.
And when you dumped your bride
at the wedding,
what was really going on?
Are you sure that it was me?
It could be someone else.
But he never goes on anybody's show.
How will you approach him? Enlighten me.
Do you think that you are a playboy?
What is the definition of a playboy?
How?
Silence?
[upbeat music]
[woman] "How do I hit on a playboy?
I met a guy; his profile is like A+++.
If I get someone like that,
I'll rest in peace.
I want him. How can I get him?"
"Aiming high, you'll get your back stabbed
and your heart broken.
If you think you're pretty enough,
go get him."
[man] "Can I see your photo first?
Then I'll give you the answer."
"Dress up and be focused,
and don't be too easy."
[man] "If you want a cub,
you have to raid the tiger's cave.
Good luck."
[Ohm] Day three...
Ohm, will you give me an interview
on my show?
Mr. Peter, please.
Ms. Lina, please.
[upbeat music]
I have an urgent matter.
Contact my secretary.
-Ohm!
-[commotion]
Ohm, wait!
Ms. Nam, please.
Ms. Susie, hello.
-Should I come in?
-[woman] Please.
Hey you, wait!
-I've waited for so long.
-Miss, please.
Ohm has limited the meetings for today.
How come?
I've been waiting for a long time.
[upbeat music concludes]
PERVERT
[woman] Miss Nam?
Yes.
Mr. Ohm has to cancel the interview.
You don't need to come. I apologize.
But... What?
Hello?
[Nam] Bastard,
you think you are so handsome?
I asked for an interview,
and you did this...
[groans]
I'm so unlucky.
You got dumped too, didn't you?
Such an asshole.
[uptempo rock music]
That's okay!
[gasps]
What the hell?
[midtempo rock music]
I didn't do it.
I really didn't do it.
I... I...
I... didn't do it.
Seriously.
Please believe me.
[car engine starts]
[tires screeching]
[Nam] Dog, how long were you in China?
Ten days.
There is a cold stream
that flows through the town.
The best thing is the hotel itself.
It's so romantic. I want you to go.
Here, here. It's still hot. [groans]
Be careful.
[groans]
What are you laughing at? It's hot.
It smells good, Dog.
Hey, Let me smell it.
No, you made it for me, didn't you?
Yeah, let me sniff it.
It's mine.
[sentimental music]
[phone ringing]
What's up, Woon?
[Woon] Nam, I have already checked.
Mr. Ohm is going to
the K-pop conference tomorrow.
You won't miss him there.
[pop music playing]
I'm sorry, you can't go inside.
Why is that?
It's very crowded in there.
It's limited to the cover dance crew.
I have an appointment with Ohm.
I'm sorry, you really can't go in.
Please contact the person
you dealt with for further assistance.
Of course, and I did it already.
-It's okay, I'll talk to--
-I'm so sorry.
-You really can't.
-[scoffs]
Hey, hey!
-Is Tong here?
-Not yet.
-We can't perform without her.
-What should we do?
What now?
Why isn't she here?
Where has she gone?
[pop music playing]
Why is she so late?
She should have been here by now.
Hey, hey. We have a problem.
Tong called me.
She can't come.
She has a broken leg, car accident.
-What should we do?
-Broken leg?
Yes, she can't come.
-What should we do?
-Every team wants me in theirs.
Champion of Bangkapi district,
three years in a row.
What now?
Are you sure?
-The four of us...
-We have to find a substitute.
Sure, whatever.
-[crowd cheering]
-[uptempo pop music playing]
[announcer] That's Leopard, thank you.
-And now another band, this one...
-Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Are you leaving us like this? You can't.
-We are up next.
-The Knock Out!
-Hurry up, this way. Get up.
-[cheering]
[pop music playing]
And the champion is...
Pre-addict.
[cheering]
I should have gone to school, not here.
[announcer] And lastly,
thank you, A.CIAN.
Thank you.
Thank you to all the fans.
[Ohm] Gamsahabnida. Thank you.
[in English] Gamsahabnida. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Excellent show. Gamsahabnida.
[in Thai] What do we do now? It's over.
Ohm!
I beg you.
Please come on my show. Please?
I'm impressed by your efforts.
[Ohm laughs]
Mr. Ohm!
[man 1] Look at her moves.
[man 2] Did she get splashed
with water?
[laughing]
She can't blend in with the others.
It looks like a long rehearsal.
[man 1] You big mouth.
[man 2] Here she comes.
Ready!
[grunting]
Hey!
That's enough. Get out.
-Are you ashamed?
-Get out. Get out now.
That's embarrassing.
That was brutal.
What were you doing, Nam?
[laughing]
Turn it off, Chef.
-What?
-Turn it off.
[sighs]
Where is Dog, Chef?
His dad is not well.
He took him to the hospital.
Nam, you did all that.
Can you get the deal with him?
[woman] Can you?
Can you?
Oh.
And what did you do that for?
[scoffs]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[woman] Hi, Miss Nam,
this is Mr. Ohm's secretary.
Yes.
You can see him tonight.
[pop music playing]
She pretended.
Is it real or an act?
-It was random.
-Hello!
I'll talk to you later.
-Hello.
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
[Ohm chuckles]
Can you believe it?
I laugh every time I watch this.
So what is it that you would
like to talk to me about?
Our company, Fish and Dog,
we create shows about food.
So what?
I would like to invite you to China
to shoot the TV program You Are--
Why do I have to go?
What would I gain from it?
I will ask Chef Pla to promote
your Korean band's concert in the show.
Something... In the episode...
The leftovers from the fridge.
Well, what if...
I preferred something else?
Will you give it to me?
You...
want me to play badminton with you, right?
Let's play. Here's the racket.
Let's play badminton.
Wait. Hey, hey, hey. How about...
if you win one game...
I will go with you.
[lighthearted music]
One zero. Pick up the shuttlecock.
Hey.
I wasn't ready.
That's got nothing to do with me.
Come on, throw the shuttlecock here.
Two zero.
[groans]
Hey! Are you messing with me?
Fifteen zero. Game over.
Wait.
What?
Ohm.
Can I have another chance?
Please! Please, Ohm?
[Dog sighs]
Nam.
-Nam.
-Huh?
What?
Nothing.
Just checking?
Hey.
[Dog] I will find someone else
instead of him if it's too much.
You are getting old, you know.
[groans]
Dog!
You have a foul mouth just like dogs.
Thanks for your compliment.
Okay...
[sighs]
Are you ready?
Whenever you are ready.
Well?
Why are you staring at each other?
If you are ready, let the game begin.
Are you sure?
Serve then.
[midtempo upbeat music]
I won't give up.
-Hey!
-In the court accidentally.
Your knee hurts?
-Oh?
-Yes! Nine four!
Red took a chance, coming up at 9-4.
Okay, I won't let you win.
Yes!
Fifteen four.
Game over. Blue wins.
Hey.
You were much better than last time.
I lost anyway.
What?
I said I lost anyway.
Come on.
I'll give you another chance.
[in English] Oh shit!
[in Thai] I forgot to tell you, I can't.
I will be in Korea
the day you go to China.
Then why did you trick me in coming here?
I just wanted a badminton partner.
[sighs, clicks tongue]
You are an asshole.
Just like all the girls you dumped said.
Do you know why?
Because you are selfish.
Your life isn't the only one that matters.
Fine.
As you wish.
But dumping girls and all, it's my shit.
You haven't been dumped, huh?
Fine.
I hope you get dumped.
Then you will know
what it's like to be dumped.
Damn you!
[melancholic music]
Very good, Nam.
Chef!
What is it?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Why?
This is brilliant, you know?
What?
What's brilliant?
Didn't they tell you
that Ohm already accepted?
This is your huge success.
What?
And he left an apology for you.
He is better than we think.
He's also paying for the flight himself.
-Chef?
-What?
-Ohm...
-Yeah.
-...accepted?
-Yes.
[midtempo upbeat music]
[sighs]
About the script and camera,
I'll let them be in charge.
And you are responsible
for coordinating with the crew.
How is your dad doing?
He is waiting for the operation,
then the result.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of this.
Too bad we won't get to travel together.
We can go somewhere else when I get back.
Sure, we'll go on a trip.
Please take care of the crew...
and Ohm, will you?
PERVERT
[Ohm] "I agreed to go to China.
Take it as my apology."
[Nam] "If you really want to apologize,
are you free on August 13?"
[sentimental music]
I'LL FIND A NEW GUY,
BETTER AND MORE AWESOME.
Hello. I'm Chef Pla.
I'll show you around in Kunming.
You Are What You Feed in Kunming.
And here, we have arrived...
-[in English] Sorry.
-[in Chinese] Go ahead.
You first.
[in English] You first.
It's okay, I can wait.
[midtempo upbeat music]
In a moment, we will try real Yunnan food.
[man] Wait, wait, wait...
Wait, wait, this is my bag.
[speaking Chinese]
It's my bag.
What? My bag! My bag!
Nam, help.
Hey!
[Chef] Nam, help.
You listen to me!
Put that down, stop shooting.
Help me first.
It's mine.
[in English] Chef!
No, no no, it's not yours!
[guard speaking Chinese]
[in English] This is mine! It's mine.
[Chef] It's really mine.
What do you mean about water?
Thirsty? Go buy water!
[midtempo upbeat music]
Can anyone say sorry? Assholes.
I'm sorry.
You think you can just say sorry
and it'll be okay?
-Is this yours?
-Yes.
Yes.
Thank you.
[speaking Chinese]
It's just a misunderstanding.
It's fine now.
-You think it's nothing?
-Thank you.
He almost killed me.
Come on, Pla.
This is Liu and this is Lian.
They are the coordinators.
-Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Let's go to Lijiang.
Let's go.
[Joe] We are gonna stop
right here real quick.
-[Joe] We're close to Lijiang.
-[Chef] My bum is so sore.
It's beautiful.
Keep taking photos of the mountains.
Keep taking.
Take some of me, come on.
Nah, Chef.
-Come on.
-[grunts]
[groans]
-How's that?
-Look at your face.
-Like a rock star.
-I better take some of the scenery.
One more, hurry up.
Chef, how is the scenery?
It's okay, but when it's me in it...
Ruined.
So, Dog couldn't make it?
His dad is not very well.
He couldn't come.
That's why she has to be here
on his behalf.
If you're going to talk like this,
then get lost.
Get lost?
-Go!
Fine, I'll go.
Joe.
I'm sorry about the airport.
Don't worry.
It feels good to have an argument
with Thai people once in a while.
How long have you lived in China?
Around ten years.
I'm responsible for taking care
of Thai people around here
or special guests from Thailand.
So, where will our special guest meet us?
In Kunming.
Let's see if he is really coming.
Don't be sarcastic, Chef.
He already bought the ticket.
"So what time will you get here?"
"Please reply."
[in Korean]
They're in the conference room now.
[in Thai] Okay.
Your special guest
seems to be quite something.
More than quite something, actually.
He is very difficult.
I texted him, but he hasn't replied.
I don’t know why he even has a cellphone.
Don't you think?
[music box plays]
DETERMINED HEART
Yeah, don't worry. I can handle it.
I'll break them up into two crews.
I'll take care of the restaurant
and the stocks.
Prite will go too,
but he wants to check with Pla first.
We're short-staffed.
Right now, I don't know what to do.
How is your dad?
My dad? Right here.
Let me talk to your dad.
How is it going, Dad? He is strong.
He's about to go for a jog.
Ni hao, Dad.
[Nam] How are you?
I'm in Lijiang at the moment.
I miss you. I'll take you
on a trip when I get back.
Okay, bye, Dad. Zaijian.
Bye, Dog.
See you later, take care.
You go to bed very late.
A little. I've just finished
discussing work.
I think you should go to bed.
Ni hao. [speaking Chinese]
Hello.
[speaking Chinese]
-[in Chinese] Thank you.
[in Thai]
The shop owner will allow us to shoot.
That's great.
Yum.
[in Chinese] Delicious. [laugh]
[in English] Very good.
[downtempo music]
It's so clear!
[Joe] Water is the heart of Lijiang.
It comes from the snowy mountain up there.
That's why it's cold all year round.
-Cold?
-Yes.
Yes, it is.
Cold as ice.
Now I really believe
that it's from the melted snow.
What did you say earlier?
Water is the heart?
No.
I mean, what you said to the chef
at the food place
after ni hao.
[laugh]
"Ni hao." [speaking Chinese]
It means nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
[midtempo upbeat music]
[sentimental music]
[Nam] It's a very beautiful city.
It looks classic. I like it.
Joe?
Are you okay?
[speaking indistinctly]
The car is broken.
We have to wait for the driver here.
Okay.
Oh!
Jade Dragon Snow Mountain
is very beautiful from here.
Have you ever been up there?
Joe?
Uh...
Someone told me...
the snow up there...
will be all melted one day...
but I have never seen it melted.
So I have to go there to see for myself.
[driver speaking Chinese]
[speaking Chinese]
Um... it looks like he can't fix the car.
He said there's a village nearby.
We can get some rest there,
and he will stay with the car.
[sentimental music]
Here is some hot tea.
Thank you.
I can't catch my breath, Joe.
There's less oxygen here.
And you are not used to it here.
I told Chef Pla
that we are staying overnight here.
The car should be fixed by tomorrow.
All right.
[speaking Chinese]
[in Chinese] Thank you.
-Thank you.
-[in Chinese] Thank you.
[in Thai] Grandma asked us
to join the dance party tonight.
Dance party?
[people singing]
[speaking Chinese]
[both speaking Chinese]
[people singing]
How do you do it? How?
[all singing]
Here.
You won't be cold.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So warm.
Why don't you go back to Thailand?
I feel attached to this place, I guess.
[music box playing]
Fei Fei...
was the first Chinese person I met.
[downtempo sentimental music]
[Joe] She taught me everything.
Language.
How to live in China.
Until I got used to living here.
[sentimental music continues]
But what I can never get used to...
is living here without her.
Whatever has been in our lives,
even though it has gone...
it will come back to be a part
of our lives.
I'm sorry.
Can you tell me about yourself?
[sentimental music]
[upbeat music]
We are lucky that the people
in the village helped us.
-I was so worried about you here...
-[Nam] Chef!
-What?
-Ohm sent confirmation
that he will arrive tomorrow.
Is he really coming?
-Here is the ticket.
-Shit.
Hey!
[Chef] Everybody, let's celebrate.
[Nam] Yay! Cheers!
Yeah!
[throat clearing]
Take a seat.
Please let me introduce View.
She will replace me starting tomorrow.
Welcome, View!
Cheers.
Here is the best question.
Are you sure?
Has anyone... slept with a ladyboy?
[in Chinese] Who?
What a shitty question.
-Is there anyone?
-Yes.
Yes.
Sure?
-Who?
-Tong?
Chef!
Gross!
What's wrong?
I have one life.
Got to live it to the fullest.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
I don't see anything wrong with that.
Exactly.
Yeen, you jerk.
-Both of you?
-Bob, you stay with me tonight.
You stay with me, okay?
And the next question.
Has anyone been heartbroken?
Drink!
I hate this question.
Drink up.
Drink. Drink.
Drink it all. Drink the bottle too.
Nam, why don't you drink?
Give her a drink.
Can you pee for me?
Drink up.
-Drink.
-I did.
Next question.
[downtempo music]
Joe.
Yes?
Are you free on August 13?
Just in case...
the snow is melted that day...
and you wanna go home.
[downtempo music]
-This way.
-Thank you.
Joe.
How do you pronounce the hotel name?
Haojiu Bujian.
It's the name of a song.
It means "long time no see."
It talks about...
a man who keeps waiting.
He won't stop loving.
How about these photos?
They're probably photos
of the guests here.
There are a lot of them.
[in Chinese] Thank you.
[in Thai] Nam.
Nam.
-Nam.
-Yes?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go then.
[downtempo music]
NAM, I'M THE DOG THAT WAITS
FOR YOU FOREVER.
See you later.
Yes.
See you on August 13.
Hurry up. Come on.
Hurry up.
-Hurry up.
-Come on, Pla.
Where are you going now?
[Joe] I'm going to greet some guests
at Xishuangbanna.
[sentimental music]
[Dog] Haojiu Bujian.
A man who keeps waiting.
He won't stop loving.
[sentimental music]
-[gasps]
-[laughs]
It's me.
Well.
So you don't like my gift?
I'll wear it myself then.
Mr. Ohm!
-Is that you?
-Yes.
Hello. Welcome to Kunming.
How was your trip?
It was okay.
Hey, Nam.
Go, hurry up!
What?
Suitcase!
It's his.
Yeah, but you take it.
Sure.
My staff are so keen.
Is that so?
-Can't you do it?
-Hurry!
[upbeat music]
Then what?
Turn around.
Is it too tight?
[upbeat music continues]
[Chef] Cut!
Great!
Great, great, great.
Okay?
[in Chinese] Thank you, thank you.
Yes!
[in Thai] Thank you.
-Chef.
-Huh?
-It's okay? All good?
-Great.
I like it when you swing the dough.
-It's very difficult.
-It's skillful.
Should I return the uniform?
Sure.
When you stretched the dough into noodles,
it was next to perfect.
Hey, keep that too.
[upbeat music]
[in Chinese] Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Good stuff.
Is it the noodles we made earlier?
Yes.
You should take it home.
Let's go.
Where to?
[sighs]
What?
What are you doing?
I'm just stretching.
[Nam] Hey, where are you going?
Wait for me.
Hurry up.
[traditional Chinese music playing]
[in English] Excuse me.
How do you write "water"?
Water?
Yes, "water."
Okay.
[in Chinese] Thank you.
Thank you.
-[in Thai] You!
-[in Thai] What's up?
What are you doing?
Ninja Turtle.
Hey!
Be serious. This is their culture.
They don't have turtles here?
Hey!
Okay, okay. I'm taking it seriously now.
I'm serious.
For real.
I'm focused.
What are you drawing now?
Look.
I wrote "Nam."
Your name.
Wait a second.
-What?
-What are you doing?
I'm throwing it away.
Why? It took time to write it.
I can write another one.
The new one and this one,
they don't feel the same.
By the way, it's my name.
I won't let you throw it away.
Give it to me.
Here.
[text notification]
[Joe] "Nam, is everything okay with work?"
Who are you chatting with?
Must be a guy.
Leave me alone.
You are fierce.
[Nam] "Everything is okay, Joe."
Hey.
What?
-Where are the noodles?
-What noodles?
The noodle basket.
What noodles?
The basket!
Oh, that... Where is it?
Or did I leave it in the taxi?
No, no, it can't be.
Or when I went to the toilet?
When I pooped, maybe?
Come on, be serious.
Where is it?
Or I left it at the brush shop?
Yes, it must be there.
Never mind. If you really want it,
I'll buy you another one.
Aren't we going back tomorrow?
You are a jerk.
You never think
of other people's feelings.
They made an effort to make it for you.
[Nam] Uncle!
Uncle!
Okay?
[in Chinese] Thanks, thanks.
[in Thai] Hey! What are you doing?
-Don't ask me.
-Wait, wait. Stop.
-What?
-Can you ride a bicycle?
-Do you need to be in such a hurry?
-Yeah.
Get down, let me ride.
Hurry up.
You are so bossy.
Faster.
Yeah, I'm speeding up.
What is this?
Why didn't you ask him for directions?
Ask what? Will we understand each other?
-We speak different languages.
-Hurry!
Do you think I know Mandarin?
Do you usually dump everything so easily?
Now what?
About everything you left.
It's so selfish.
Fine, you are an angel.
You've never done
anything for yourself?
I'm not like you.
Not like me?
We might have more in common
than you think.
-No way.
-We'll fall.
Just keep speeding up.
-What now, to the right?
-Keep going straight.
You told me right before.
Right, right, right.
-Hurry up, right.
-Right.
[Nam] If we get lost, I blame you.
[Ohm] I never get lost, trust me.
-Go straight then?
-Straight.
Wait, let me have a look.
Instead of whining,
why don't you ride it yourself?
-Will you go faster?
-Nagging all the time.
[Nam] Will you stop complaining?
Hurry up.
-I'm going across.
-Let me help.
Just go ahead.
Shit.
What the hell? [sniffs, coughs]
[Ohm speaks in English] Sorry.
-I have the noodles.
-[Ohm] I don't understand.
Will you come help me?
Come here.
Went to get the noodles.
[both speak in English] Yes, noodles.
-Noodle, noodle.
-Let me find the dictionary.
You have a dictionary? Give it to me.
-I didn't bring it.
-Damn it!
[speaking Chinese]
Run!
[Chef] When I got the call, I was shocked.
[Ohm] Actually, I appreciate your help.
But I think I can handle it.
Is that right?
Let me go thank her.
When you were scolded
by the Chinese guard,
it was funny.
-Funny?
-Yes.
You should be locked up.
If I'm in jail, who will take care of me?
That's easy. You just...
die in jail.
Tough, huh?
When he scolded you,
you didn't look different.
I was going to ask.
The August 13-14 thing,
what do you want me to do?
What?
I can remember.
August 13, yes.
What is on August 13?
-I didn't invite you--
-Wait.
Don't pretend that you don't remember.
Let's check it out.
Let's see who texted me.
You sent me the message.
I was not being serious.
You don't need to go.
I don't care. I will go.
You don't have to.
I have nothing for you.
Nam.
This time, I might not want
anything from you.
[sentimental music]
[Chef] Nam, I'm cold. Come on.
Hurry up.
TO NAM - H2O VOLUME 25
[woman] "I tricked three guys
into ridiculing my ex.
I feel guilty. What should I do?"
"You want others to hurt like you.
Selfish."
"Go tell them."
"Why don't you say sorry?"
[upbeat music]
[cheering]
[cheering, whooping]
Did you see how he danced?
-Such a disaster.
-Did you see his tummy?
Just imagine, his tummy.
Nam.
What's wrong with you?
I have to go.
Hey, hey!
Hold on a minute. You look drunk.
I think you should rest.
No, I can make my way back.
Nam.
[downtempo music]
♪ To someone I once loved ♪
[O] Nam.
Yes?
Let's break up.
I'm sorry.
♪ You made me lost ♪
♪ And fall apart ♪
♪ You made me laugh ♪
♪ You made me cry ♪
♪ You gave meaning to my life ♪
O, will you try this shirt on?
You always wear worn-out T-shirts.
♪ Am I too stupid? ♪
O, where are you? Come out now.
Why didn't you tell me before?
Can we just talk?
No!
We're over!
♪ I've gone crazy because of you ♪
♪ I still remember ♪
♪ And think of you ♪
♪ You made me laugh ♪
♪ You made me cry ♪
♪ You are the last one that ♪
♪ I'll let this happen to me ♪
Nam.
Are you okay? You never answer my calls.
I want us to watch
the first episode together.
And I'd like to hear
about your China trip.
All right. Take care.
Dog, will Nam come to join us?
You are smiling like a dog
waiting for bones.
[grunts]
The station called
to postpone the China episode
to August 13. Is that all right?
No, I have an appointment.
Really?
But I said okay anyway.
I also booked the billboard
at the Rajaprasong intersection.
How could you do that, Pla?
I can't postpone my appointment.
It's important.
How could you do this without asking me?
I'm asking you now.
But it's too late.
I don't know, you decided it yourself.
Go settle this with them.
I'll leave it to you.
If Ohm is here, take him to the sound lab.
-Sound lab?
-So we don't waste his time.
Okay, okay.
Okay, go. Quickly.
As if you're my boss.
[upbeat music]
Nam.
Are you free on August 13?
-I want you to watch--
-No.
-Hey!
Where is Dog?
You've only asked for him
since you arrived.
He is standing by at Sound Lab 1.
Ohm has some sound editing to do.
-And on--
-Ohm?
-...the 13th--
-Is he here?
-Yes.
-Already?
-No--
-He is with Dog?
For how long? What are they doing?
Nam. Nam! Nam!
He is behind you.
[music ends]
Will you let go of me? Good.
-Mr. Ohm, hello.
-Hello, Chef.
-I haven't seen you since the China trip.
-Yes.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
Sorry for bothering you
with sound editing.
No problem.
Actually, our crew is great.
Except for this one.
I have to keep my eyes on her.
Oh, are you free on August 13?
So we can watch
the first episode together.
The 13th, is it?
Yes.
-Actually, I have--
-Chef! Dog wants you!
There, he went into the room already.
Really, he said he needs you right away.
-Where?
-Go now, hurry.
-Wait.
-Chef, on the 13th--
They are going to discuss work.
Just about work.
You've just arrived, take some rest.
[Chef] Dog, what do you want from me?
[Dog] What? Who called you?
What the hell?
Let's go to this room. Have a rest.
Isn't this... the studio?
-Wait here?
-Right here.
-But they are working...
-I'll be back.
-Don't go anywhere.
-I've arrived.
Joe, are you free on August 13?
We will watch the pilot episode together.
I'm not available. I have an appointment.
Joe.
Nam?
Joe?
Joe, can I borrow your phone?
Mom? Wait, wait.
Joe, take a seat here.
Okay, Mom, everything is okay.
I'll be back.
Hey!
-Where are you going?
-I'm thirsty.
Let me?
Here... take this money.
-One hundred then.
-All right.
Ohm.
Here's some water.
Thank you.
[phone ringing]
You look strange.
Even a phone call makes you jump.
Hello, Nam?
I'm on my way there. No need to call.
Nam.
Where is Ohm?
[upbeat music]
Talk.
He is in the bathroom.
He said he has a funny stomach,
don't bother him.
Shit.
Chef, just calm down.
And Joe, where is he now?
Nam.
Hey!
How's it going?
Where is Ohm?
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Dog.
Nam?
-Nam?
-It's hot, let's get in the room.
Nam, what...?
Dog.
Nam... Nam...
Prite is staring at us.
Dog!
You wait here. I'll be back to talk.
Just wait here. Don't go anywhere.
[upbeat music]
-Joe.
-Nam?
Where are you going?
The gate was locked.
It's hot.
I just want to go to the bathroom.
Here is the bathroom.
Excuse me.
[upbeat music]
Ohm.
Ohm, fortunately...
[upbeat music]
What the hell is that?
You better go back now. Let's go.
Wait, do we have to hurry?
Yes, let's go.
Who locked the bathroom door, Joe?
I don't know.
-That's weird.
-Come this way.
Don’t need sound editing...
This is my brother, Joe.
He helped us in China.
And this is Mr. Ohm, our special guest.
Hello.
It’s you.
What a pity we didn't get to meet
in China.
Are you ready?
I heard you have an upset stomach.
Hello.
-Mr. Ohm?
-Yes.
I'm Dog. Nice to meet you.
I'm Pla's partner.
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
What's up, Dog?
-Joe!
-How are you?
-I'm good.
-Good? Good?
We are all here. Should we go up?
-Wait, wait.
-Let's go.
Since we are all here,
let me announce it again.
The first episode
is postponed to August 13.
Please kindly accept our invitation
because I have booked a big billboard
at Rajaprasong.
-I'm sorry.
-Yes.
Why?
-Pla, you bastard.
-Why?
I told you to postpone it.
I'm not available, don't you get it?
[Chef] Yes, so I checked with the others.
[Dog] No, you have to
stick to my schedule.
It's really important, I beg you.
Pla, I am also not available on the 13th.
Yes, Chef, I can't go that day either.
There, nobody is available.
Wait, what the hell is going on?
Nobody is available?
I have an appointment with Nam.
Bitch.
Why, Nam? What the hell is on the 13th?
[Chef] Huh?
O's wedding.
It's your wedding, bitch!
How could you do this?
You invited everyone but me.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you getting married?
She won't be marrying O.
[Chef] Shit.
And why three of us... on the same day?
Here, this is just like
what you cursed me.
[Ohm laughs]
We might be the same kind of people.
Goodbye.
Ohm.
Damn.
Joe?
What is wrong with you?
Joe!
Dog!
You know,
I really feel sorry for you.
I know how strong you are
for not saying that you are heartbroken.
So I waited.
For the day you could get over it.
For the day you are ready.
So I could tell you
that I'll take care of you instead of O.
But I'm stupid.
I let you do this to me.
You don't understand.
I don’t want to hurt anyone.
I'm hurt too.
You think you're the only
heartbroken one in the world?
If I knew that you were like this...
I wouldn't have waited this long.
Dog! Dog!
[melancholic music]
Woon.
Nam.
Man.
Sis.
You stayed overnight at the office?
Yes, we were finalizing volume 26.
It wasn't quite right.
Give it to me. You both should go home.
I'll take it from here.
Go get some rest. Don't worry.
Oh, Woon.
The column, Love, is it finished?
Yes.
Let me double-check it just in case.
It's okay, Nam.
We can wait until you feel better.
What he means is...
You guys know?
Yes.
O told us.
Nam.
We love you and O...
as much as we love this magazine.
But we understand
if you want to stop making it.
You don't have to act strong.
I want you to just cry.
I love you.
We love you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Nam.
I will be all right. Don't worry.
QUESTION OF LOVE
MY BOYFRIEND CHEATED ON ME,
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
KEEPING MANY OPTIONS, IS IT WRONG?
HOW TO KEEP LONG LASTING LOVE?
[Nam] "Dog, I'm..."
[sentimental music]
"Joe, I'm sorry."
"Ohm, how are you?"
[Nam] L: Love, Volume 26.
In this issue,
we're not replying to questions
because this will be
the last issue of H2O.
I used to make myself...
a glass full of water.
I thought that
I clearly knew what love was.
But no.
I never knew what love was.
But there is someone
who made me realize...
"Even though love has ended,
the happiness of loving
will never melt away."
[midtempo sentimental music]
Here it is.
Okay.
[Chef] You are what you feed.
Some food is suitable for some people
but also not suitable for others.
So if it's not for you, don't eat it.
[Nam] And when there is someone
who knows how to love...
[Nam] They will never hurt love
even though they will never own it.
To hurt others...
doesn't mean you don't feel pain.
[bride] Ohm.
[bride] Ohm, where are you?
Ohm?
[Ohm] "I'm sorry."
[sentimental music]
[Nam] Now I have a glass half full.
And I don't dare resolve anyone's love.
Actually, I don't know anymore...
what love is.
AUGUST 13
[Nam] Uncle.
[Nam] Can you give me a ride?
[midtempo music]
[Nam] Are you sure
that's the groom's outfit?
I am glad that you came here.
Aren't you worried
that I'll ruin the wedding?
If you do, I have to accept it.
I'm sorry, Nam.
All along...
you did everything for me.
You tried to dream of the same things.
But look at this.
This...
This is your real dream.
And now...
I know that the most selfish person...
is me.
I'm sorry, O.
I'm so sorry.
And from now on...
We are really broken up.
I...
am breaking up with you.
[sentimental music]
O.
Mom is here.
I'm sorry.
[Nam] Congratulations.
I really mean it.
[sobbing]
[Ohm] "Choose! Throw up or cry?"
What are you looking for?
Oh, look at you.
Oh... you look like shit.
How about Dog and Joe? Are they not here?
Just want to be sarcastic?
Is that why you're here?
You invited me.
And I didn't say that I wouldn't come.
[upbeat music]
I did that to you...
Are you not mad at me?
[retching]
[Nam] Hey!
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Wait.
Just wipe your mouth.
Wait, wait, wait, let me do it.
Wait, wait.
What's so funny?
You don't look any different from me.
And...
Aren't you mad at me?
Forget it.
You are just screwed up,
and you screwed things up.
I don’t mind.
I think I don't know much about love,
and neither do you.
[midtempo music]
Don't you remember what I told you?
Both of us might be the same.
Thank you.
I really thank you.
♪ And this too shall pass ♪
♪ And you will change your mind ♪
♪ And one day it will be all gone ♪
♪ Even though you'll still miss him now ♪
♪ In every breath you take ♪
[Chef] Let's gather around.
[woman] "Someone
waiting for you to punish."
♪ Bite your lips and hold on ♪
[woman] "Dog, come in here,
or they'll make me go stay with you."
♪ There is no love left in him anymore ♪
♪ Just let it go ♪
[Chef] Our next target is...
to get the highest rating!
♪ And this too shall pass ♪
♪ And you will change your mind ♪
♪ And one day it will be all gone ♪
[woman] Mr. Ohm,
can you give me an interview?
[light up-tempo music playing]
[downtempo sentimental music]