I really want a chopping knife.
What do you want it for?
To cut off this post.
It interferes with our love.
Do you know
what will kill you?
What is it?
Your sweet addiction.
I'm a sweet guy.
Hello, Dad Johnny.
I'm not your dad.
I bought you grilled chicken.
Mam.
Get on.
It runs out of gas.
And a spark plug failed.
Pol…
I love you so much.
I love you more, Mam.
Go get her.
Are you serious?
I will.
What a dirty trick.
Mam!
Kick him hard.
Knee him!
And now freestyle.
You have a good hip, huh?
What's the problem?
What the hell?
Piss off, you lame fighter.
And you just nurture your chicken.
He's flirting with your niece.
What? They're just sparring.
Sparring my ass.
Mam, get in the house.
Why are you still looking at my daughter?
Get out!
I really love her.
Dad Johnny.
Don't call me dad, I'm not your father.
Daddy my ass.
A poor guy like you
can never take care of my daughter.
You always call me a poor.
Yes, I know I am.
How rich do I have to be to be her man?
Impossibly rich!
All right.
I'll prove to you
that I'm not just a loser
or a lame fighter.
My love is worth more than money.
Mam.
What now?
Wait for me.
SIX MONTHS LATER
Come on, everyone.
Let's make merit at Koak E-Gerng village.
Coming up next,
Luang Por Yhong
will light the Talai skyrocket.
A symbol of blessing to our Koak E-Gerng.
Talai exploded!
Run for your life!
Run!
Run, folks. Run! Get outta here!
Hey, Suer.
Luang Por!
I can't feel my legs!
It's huge.
Talai is launched, folks.
Long live Koak E-Gerng!
How come is Mam like that?
She looks miserable.
Yeah.
Yes?
How are you, son? Will you come home?
Mom, I don't think I can.
I'm overwhelmed with work.
Mom, I gotta hang up. My hands are in use.
Talk to you later. Yes.
Your turn, call him.
Yes, Dad.
Pol.
What are you doing?
Why do you call again?
Are you not with Mom?
She's with me every night.
She usually pokes me, wants more babies.
Stop fooling around.
I'll have you castrated.
Busy with work is good.
Save up more money.
You can come home during Songkran.
No need to hurry back, all right?
Yes, Dad.
What now, Uncle Waeng?
Hello, my beloved nephew.
You have a free talk plan or what?
No, I only have a free love plan.
Love you, darling.
Hey, that's your nephew.
I'm just joking.
Is that right?
-Will you come?
-No.
Oh, busy?
All right then.
Let me talk to my friend.
Dude.
I miss you.
You don't need to come during Songkran.
I'll visit you during Buddhist lent.
Show me some nice Bangkok girls.
Bangkok girls my ass.
Your wife is here.
I'll whoop your ass.
I gotta go.
Okay.
Yes.
Sarakam to Koak E-Gerng! Want a ride?
Come on, hop on.
Sarakam to Koak E-Gerng!
Johnny.
Are you drunk? Sober yet?
I am.
We're here.
Stop.
I'm in a hurry.
Auntie, you dropped something.
Don't you want it?
Thanks, young man.
I almost lost my dinner.
Let's go!
This is a sandalwood glass
This is a Murraya exotica bowl
May you live happily
After you get married
May your essence in the orchard rush back
May your essence in the paddies rush back
May your essence
In the abdomen slowly come up
Today is the wedding day
Of a farang couple
The first Isaan-born
Farang couple in the country
Love you, Koak E-Gerng
May your essence…
Oh, your essence comes back.
WEDDING CEREMONY
MAM - MARK
May your essence come back!
Mam!
Pol?
Oh, my gosh! This is so not good.
How did you get here?
What are you doing here?
Are you gonna wreck my daughter's wedding?
No, Dad Johnny.
How many times
have I told you I'm not your dad?
My daughter is getting married today.
Stay away from her.
-Go!
-I won't go.
Not until I talk to Mam.
She can't marry another man.
Leave by yourself or I'll make you.
Wait up, Dad Johnny.
I just want to…
Hey.
He has a gun!
Get him.
I don't have a gun.
I'm not here to wreck your wedding.
I came back for you.
Don't hurt him.
Stop!
Let me go!
Stop fighting, we're homies!
E-La, you stay here, sis. I'll find Pong.
Pol is alone, you beat him like an animal.
Looks like I have to disrobe this time.
Enough!
Pong! Why don't you pick up?
Pong, pick up the phone.
Stay out of it.
It's all ruined, don't you see?
Tell them to stop. I feel sorry for him.
Why do you care about him?
He has wrecked your wedding.
He didn't start the fight.
It was you, Dad!
Mam!
Pol.
Pong, where are you?
Pong. Why don't you answer?
-Thip.
-Pong!
What's wrong, Thip?
Pong? Why didn't you pick up, Pong?
That's why the basket is vibrating.
Answer it now!
All right.
What's going on, Thip?
It's Pol.
Pol is back and he's getting beaten up.
Thip called me and said Pol was beaten up.
Pol was beaten!
Pol.
Why are you back?
I thought you were working in Bangkok.
You thought I wouldn't be back
so you're getting married
without telling me?
It's not like that.
I wanted to tell you
when the time was right.
When that day comes…
the gift I have saved up to buy
to show you what's in my mind
won't mean anything.
What is in your mind?
I intended to come back and tell you…
that I don't want
to be your friend anymore.
Can I be your boyfriend?
Pol.
Hey!
That's my daughter's dowry.
No, I bought it.
Don't you lie to me.
Get him out of here.
No! Don't!
Don't hurt him.
-No, Dad.
-Beat him.
No! Don't hurt him.
Calm down.
Don't hurt him!
Dad! Don't hurt him!
Pol, go.
Calm down.
Mam.
-Dad, don't!
-Mam!
-Pol!
Pol!
Pol.
Johnny, you beat my son severely.
I'll beat the shit out of you.
No!
Calm down.
Stop!
I'll knock your teeth out, you farang.
Oh, my God!
My rice paddy.
500 baht. Each plant cost me 500 baht.
Dad.
Look around here!
My daughter's wedding is ruined.
You have to be responsible for this!
Responsible with my feet!
You hurt my son
and you ask for my responsibility?
You shitty farang,
you only sell your daughter.
I'm not selling her.
I'm not that greedy.
Any father would do the same.
We all want our daughters
to live comfortably.
We hope they don't have to be a performer
or stay with a poor man like your son.
Just wait
for the day when E-La gets married.
I'll call you out as well!
Dad.
With this shitty mouth,
you can't live at Koak E-Gerng!
I'll kill you!
Stop!
Stop.
What is this?
Enough with this nonsense.
Today is a good day,
an auspicious day.
A merit day for our village.
Can't I ask for one good thing
for Koak E-Gerng?
Pol!
Have you seen Pol?
Have you? Have you seen him?
Pol.
Pol!
Where are you?
-Pol!
-Dude!
Where are you?
Dad Johnny.
I love Mam.
And I'm willing
to sacrifice anything for her.
Dad.
I love Pol.
I love Pol!
Enough.
So you've planned
to run away after the wedding?
Dad.
Well, I…
Mam.
You can't lie.
Your dad found the bag you hid.
I don't love Mark.
And I'm not ready to get married.
You don't want to be married
but you're running away with Pol?
It has nothing to do with Pol.
I just can't let you
-force me any longer.
-Mam.
Ungrateful bitch.
Calm down. Calm down.
That's your daughter.
She's still your daughter no matter what.
Mam.
Martin and I are childhood friends.
We grew up together in England.
I think about
your happiness and well-being
so I want you to be with someone I trust.
Is it my happiness
or yours?
Dad.
Just leave me alone!
Pol!
Come down here now!
Scared of even an old man?
Oi!
Pol is not home. Just go back.
Kiddo, don't lie to me.
Come down now, Pol!
You crazy farang.
Don't you understand? Pol isn't here.
Fine.
I'll find him myself.
And when I find him, he'll die at my feet.
Crazy farang.
Pao!
Mam is gone.
What did you say?
Mam ran away, Dad.
Mam.
Where are you?
Come back to talk to me.
Quickly. Go find her.
Mam.
Come back now.
Come on, girl.
Come back to talk.
Let's sit and talk.
-Mam.
-Stop.
Mark.
Have you seen Mam?
I saw her go that way.
Come on. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Mam!
Mam. Where are you, Mam?
Come back to talk.
Thanks, Mark.
Mam.
Let me help you.
I've prepared this motorbike for us.
-Let's go.
-But…
If your dad sees us,
we'll be in a big trouble.
Are you coming?
Let's go.
Have a seat.
KHAO TOM PHRA NAKORN
Khao Tom Phra Nakorn.
Is that it?
I'm looking for Auntie Thim.
She left. She's gone to Pattaya.
What does she do there?
How would I know?
And you own this place?
Yes, it's mine.
But Auntie Thim said
she's the owner's wife.
What are you talking about?
Look at this photo.
What?
Thim.
You did it again, bastard!
-How much did you give her?
-Let's leave.
The staff ran away because of you.
-Calm down, honey.
-I can't calm down, bastard.
What now, Mam?
Do you want to find Auntie Thim
in Pattaya?
I'll take you there.
Mam.
Please let this friend take care of you
when you have no one left.
Okay?
Hello, Mr. Tou.
How is it going?
I heard the news and I'm worried.
If he had been come to me,
his daughter wouldn't have run away.
Thank you, sir.
And about the debt…
Don't worry about your debt.
Just watch over Johnny.
Don't let him drink too much.
Loser farang, drinks like a fish.
Go.
Mam. Your phone.
Should I really turn it off?
Yeah.
Sorry, Dad.
Don't worry.
Wait for the dust to settle
and everything will be all right.
Leave other people's world.
It's not ours anymore.
We're tired from traveling.
Let's get some rest.
Don't you worry.
We're not gonna sleep together.
You sleep here, I sleep next to the wall.
Pol!
I just want to say
that I toss and turn while I'm sleeping.
I also want to tell you
that I shudder while I'm sleeping.
Ouch!
Mam.
Are you not worry it's broken?
You don't know
how to take care of your things.
You had it coming.
It's all you think about.
Nobody gets to sleep tonight.
Are you tired?
No, sir.
But I'm tired.
Will you fight?
Yes, sir!
Uncle Pao.
What?
They said Johnny's motorbike
crashed over there.
That way.
-That way?
-Yes, that way.
Let's go.
Is he all right?
Hurry up.
Come on. Let's go.
Johnny.
Johnny! Wake up!
Wake up!
Mam ran away from me.
She's gone.
She finally left her dad.
Mam.
Don't leave me.
Come back home.
Mam.
Who said Johnny was dead?
Make way.
We're relatives.
Let's see if it's really him.
Let me see his face.
Guys.
Is that Johnny?
Johnny is really dead?
I can't believe my eyes.
Johnny is really dead.
It's Johnny laying there.
Poor Johnny.
Why did you die here in Koak E-Gerng?
How will I tell your relatives?
He had just visited me this morning.
Johnny, when did you get here?
Martin.
Can you promise me
that if anything happens to me,
you'll bring Mam back to England?
Don't talk like that.
Mam is like my niece.
Of course I'll take care of her.
Come, have some breakfast.
Hey, wait!
What is it, Dad?
Have you washed your hands before eating?
Come on, Pun.
Everyone in Koak E-Gerng is clean.
Really, Sa-Waeng?
-Yeah, look at these flies.
-Why?
When they land on something,
they wipe their little hands.
You look like a fly.
Can I have some booze?
Kaewta.
Get him some booze.
All right.
You're so kind.
Here.
Let go of my wife's hand.
I said let go.
Let go of her hand.
Thanks.
Go. Get lost.
What's wrong, Kaewta?
Suer.
Johnny's hand was as cold as ice.
I have goosebumps.
Really?
He came to us this morning.
He asked for booze, didn't he?
Yes.
I've just asked the officers.
He died last night.
Last night?
If that's so, what we saw…
Johnny, Isaan ghost.
This is going to be a legend.
Attention!
At ease!
Your belly, what's that for?
Huh?
Can you chase after the bad guys?
Can you?
And sleeping on duty as well.
Don't let me see it again!
Just yawning will get you fired.
Sir!
Are you mocking your superior?
No, sir.
How was it, Pao? Can you reach Mam?
No.
Can you reach Pol?
Poor Johnny.
It's like what they said in the old days
about people that died and wouldn't leave.
He has worries,
so he haunts us all over the village.
Sister-in-law, don't talk nonsense.
The reason he's still around here
is because he's vengeful.
Oh, you foul-mouthed…
Luang Por is here.
Greet them.
Why are you heading back?
Dying and departing are kind of forlorn.
Why do those monks hide behind you?
They are newly ordained.
This is their first time.
They are not used to it yet.
Don't know the right manners.
Stand back.
And line up.
Fall in line.
Mhom.
Two days ordained
and you would be an abbot?
Wrong place.
You ignorant…
Johnny Anderson.
How old was he?
Fifty-nine.
He was not that old.
-Whoa, what was that?
-A cat.
I'm startled.
Get a hold of yourself.
We'll start chanting.
Johnny!
Who's that?
I'm terrified.
Oh, no!
Pun.
The door!
The window is open!
It's quiet now.
He's gone.
Luang Por, can we stay with you tonight?
All right then.
Take cover under the blanket.
Who farted?
Luang Por?
I didn't.
I only yawned.
And that was just a yawn.
Don't you see, Pun?
When Johnny was still alive,
you always fought with him.
He must be coming to you now.
Not only me, you too.
You always want a farang husband.
Johnny, come take Pong.
I broke up with her.
The lucky lotus.
Like… I have seen it somewhere.
Thank you.
It's mine.
Why didn't you die back in your country?
Instead of dying in Koak E-Gerng.
Johnny Isaan Ghost.
The first farang ghost of Isaan.
So terrifying.
I knew it. What the hell?
Get inside.
Luang Por.
Why is the window open?
It's the wind. The window isn't latched.
Luang Por!
Chant something, Luang Por.
Get out, please.
Luang Por, he keeps accelerating.
Have you heard of a monk
who jumps out of the window?
No, only a monk who jumps off the wall.
I'll show you.
The first-ever jumping-out monk.
A jumping-out monk!
And Johnny Ghost.
This bastard won't go away.
Stubborn ghost.
I'm going.
Drink to cheer ourselves up.
-Another shot?
-Sure.
Who would buy booze for ghosts?
-Sieng, I've got a craving.
-What?
A craving?
Sa-Waeng! You said just a sip.
Save some for me. I crave it too.
Give me some booze.
Johnny Ghost!
You crave it too?
All right, come and get it.
-Wait.
-What?
Sieng.
I have an idea.
Run.
I'm running.
Run faster!
Hurry up.
I think we lost him.
Johnny, I'm done playing your game.
That's it, run!
Where are you going?
Running away from Johnny.
How about you?
We're doing the same.
-Which way is he coming from?
-That way.
He's gone!
He's back!
I wanna shit my pants
to scare the ghost away.
Why doesn't he sleep at this hour?
Gotcha! Johnny.
Help us, guys!
Who hit my head?
You all raise your hand for what?
Run!
You surprised me.
How did you get here?
The mall is about to close.
Why are you here?
I can't stay by myself at night.
So… I came to see you.
I'm glad to see your smile.
But if your superior knew,
wouldn't you be fired?
Mam.
Who would dare fire the owner's son?
Don't be silly.
If I was fired,
I could find a new job.
You must have applied at many places.
Aren't you into Bangkok girls
and don't want to go back to Koak E-Gerng?
I have no one.
All I want is to make big money
to prove to Dad Johnny
that although I'm not a boxer,
I can take care of you.
Pol.
Mam. I'll show you something.
-Show me what?
-Follow me.
This way.
What is it?
You'll see.
A wedding gown.
A wedding suit.
Here they are. My dream.
The gold necklace I bought you
is proof that I didn't boast about it.
I really love you.
And I'd like to know what you think.
Pol.
I…
Mam.
You don't have to tell me now.
I'm afraid I'd be disappointed.
For now,
just let me rehearse our wedding.
Just in case you turn me down,
so I don't keep my hopes up.
All right?
Thank you everyone
for joining our wedding ceremony.
I promise that I will love
and take care of my bride
for the rest of my life.
Now the emcee can take it from here.
Where's your emcee?
Right here.
And now, the groom may kiss the bride.
The bride…
may kiss the groom now.
Pol.
Mam.
Does anyone object to our marriage?
I object!
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
You didn't hear that?
No. What is it? Where?
What are you looking for?
What was that noise?
Come this way.
I shouldn't have.
Pol.
Oh, I'm in deep shit.
What's wrong?
Who are you looking for?
I think I saw…
I saw someone walking here.
-What…
-Who was it?
An illusion?
Mam, run.
Pol, stop.
Pol!
Mam, come on.
Run.
You broke those things
and brought an outsider to the property.
Stop, Pol. Pol!
You're fired!
You're also wearing boxing shorts.
Looks like tonight
there'll be a Koak E-Gerng fight!
What a thought!
You just got fired.
How can you still be playful?
Don't worry.
I can find a job anywhere.
If I can't get one here,
I'll go somewhere else.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have
dragged you into this mess.
I'd do anything for you, Mam.
I want to see you happy,
and your sweet smile.
Smile for me.
Tonight, is the red corner ready?
The red corner is ready,
the blue corner is ready…
and in peak fighting shape!
Now we start the foreplay.
How?
Here, Mam.
Foreplay now.
The bell hasn't rung.
You jump start?
Aren't you afraid of a head kick?
If you gave me a head kick,
I'd hold your legs,
plowing for four or five rounds.
And if I punched you below the belt?
I'd hold you down
and knee you
until you begged me to stop.
Now that you've heard this,
do you still dare to fight me?
Since both boxers are ready,
let's get in the ring.
The referee inspects the gloves.
Gloves, check!
Now the groin guard.
Red's jockstrap is good.
Why don't we check yours?
Be my guest.
You think I wouldn't?
You lost on a foul.
You bring a bamboo tube to the ring.
Want to hit my head with it?
Soon you'll know…
the reason I brought it.
Does the first round begin?
Hold on.
Is that your phone?
No.
I turned it off.
Is it yours?
I turned mine off too.
Dad Johnny.
Dad.
What is it?
It was just on.
How is it off now?
Turn it back on.
Uncle Pao.
Mam. Where are you?
I couldn't reach you.
Just hurry back home.
Listen…
Listen carefully, Mam.
Your dad…
He died.
What did you say, Pao?
Just now, my dad called me.
That's impossible.
Your dad's been dead for days.
How could he call you?
What?
Dad…
Dad died.
My dad died.
-Mam.
-Dad.
-Dad!
-Mam!
Mam!
Dad.
My dad died.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me, Dad Johnny.
It's my fault.
It's not your fault.
It's because of me…
running away.
Don't blame yourselves.
Johnny died because of booze.
Can't only blame booze.
Johnny had a heart condition for years.
He wanted her to marry
a promising young man.
Not someone with no future like Pol.
That's why he's so vengeful.
Stop talking shit, Sa-Waeng.
Speak of the devil.
Johnny's spirit won't spare you.
We've all seen him.
Oh, no.
Seriously, Pol,
we have been wickedly haunted.
Nobody wants to go out after dark.
Why did the drum fall just now?
Because we're talking about Johnny.
That's why it happened, Pun.
Do you see?
Since you came back, he got way scarier.
That's right.
You should leave Koak E-Gerng
if you don't want Johnny
to break your neck.
Honey, where do you want Pol to go?
I don't know.
Johnny can follow him everywhere.
I have an idea.
Pol has to break up with Mam.
Great idea, Sa-Waeng.
No!
I love Mam.
Nobody can stop me.
Keep it in your mind.
Don't say it out loud.
You know I've been in love
with her since childhood.
And I'll love her until I grow old.
Pol, I know you share my qualities.
But you shouldn't speak
about your love too loudly.
Well…
Johnny's spirit is fierce.
No, Dad. Absolutely not.
Love is love.
I can't hold it back.
It might kill me
sooner than Dad Johnny's spirit.
Don't you get it?
What?
Back off!
Move back!
What's wrong?
Don't come close!
My friend, I'll help you.
Hey!
Why are we still here? Run!
Pol, run!
Go!
Johnny's spirit is so vengeful.
Nobody gets any sleep.
We're all troubled, Luang Por.
I want you to cast a spell on the chains.
On the chains?
I can cast a spell
with holy water or yarn.
I've never done it with chains.
Can't do this, can't do that.
Why did you become a monk at all?
Sa-Waeng.
You think I'm your playmate or something?
Cast whatever you want.
If you want me to, all right.
But actually,
you should just ask for his forgiveness.
We'll just do this for now.
What's wrong, Luang Por?
It's sacred.
Buddha's grace.
Amen!
Mam, light the incense.
Let Pol ask for his forgiveness.
Explain nicely. He should understand you.
He hasn't even started yet.
Give my son a chance.
Johnny, I beg you.
Dad Johnny,
me and my family have come
to ask for your forgiveness.
We want to make things right…
and tell you the truth.
When Mam and I were away in Bangkok,
I didn't offend her in any way.
All we did was hold hands,
a kiss on the cheeks,
a little kiss on the lips.
But…
there was no tongue involved.
He's at it!
I don't believe what Pol said.
They were alone together.
She isn't pregnant already, you think?
Your filthy mouth.
All right. Don't be afraid.
I already cast a spell on the chains.
Bring it on.
Come on.
I've cast those chains.
Locked it myself.
He can't escape.
Are you challenging me, Johnny?
Don't be afraid.
It's the end of the chains.
Hey, Johnny.
To the main road, how much?
It's no time for jokes.
Luang Por.
Our family…
Stay united!
And run for your life!
Go!
Pol.
Why are you standing still? Go!
Good luck, everyone.
No. Let me go, Mom.
I love Mam.
Dead or alive,
I'll love her until I grow old.
I'll never stop loving her.
Dad!
It's me.
Pol!
From now on, stop being my friend
and be my boyfriend.
I love him.
I love her too.
Dad, stop being angry at him.
He really loves me.
And I love him back.
Your daughter here…
can't live alone
without him by her side.
Where has he gone?
-He's gone.
-Behind a tree?
Get off.
Go.
Hey!
What did you do?
I used to be a boxer.
Pao.
Go one on one…
Get up.
Three million Baht in debt!
So much.
Since your mom passed away,
your dad became a drunkard.
Ignored his boxing gym.
He got an illegal loan.
I warned him but he didn't listen.
It was just 500,000.
But its interest has compounded
to three million.
Hang in there, Mam.
You know that's cheating.
Johnny only owed you 500,000.
You added one more zero
to make it five million,
then "discounted" it to three million.
Nobody can come up with
that kind of money.
You have a problem, huh?
How could you do it?
Stop!
This is a temple, not a boxing ring.
You fight like dogs.
Yes, you can't keep arguing.
The problem is still there.
If you want me to judge this case,
then sit down.
Sit down!
Negotiate with new rules.
If anyone argues,
I'll cast black magic on them.
What the heck.
Well, Luang Por.
We want to help Mam.
We sold our assets,
and mortgaged our land.
We've got one million.
So we've made a decision
to bet our one million Baht
on a fight with your best boxer.
If you win, you take the million
and lands, homes, boxing camp,
whatever you want to cover the debt.
But if we win,
all the debts must be cancelled.
Are you in?
And who's your fighter?
Don't tell me it's Mam.
If it's Mam, I'll only mingle with her.
It's me! I will fight you!
You're not on my level.
You will fight with Saen Phu Kwai.
Oh, Johnny
May your spirit come help us
Damn, Waeng. Just ask him.
Tell him directly.
Pol will fight on the ring.
Please help him win. Help him.
If you don't,
Mafia Tou will confiscate
the land from all villagers
and your daughter, Johnny.
We hope you understand, Johnny.
Oh, so annoying, you drama queen.
For Koak E-Gerng villagers,
for all the debts.
And most importantly, for your woman.
You think I'm gonna win?
You'll meet with your favorite boxers.
In the red corner,
the handsome boxer Tossapol Koak E-Gerng!
Pol! Pol! Pol!
And the fighter in the blue corner,
Saen Phu Kwai!
With that body, he isn't Phu Kwai.
More like a monster Phu Kwai.
Tou, you were born to cheat us.
Why don't you blame yourself
for being poor?
Fight him, Pol. Beat him up.
Round one. Begin!
Box!
Wait, go to the corner.
Oh, I'm gonna faint.
Whoa, so close.
End of round one.
Sister-in-law.
I'm gonna faint, can I have some balm?
Here you go.
You'll get him this round, Pol.
Full on, Pol.
Nobody can take you now. Trust me.
Second round!
Punch him!
Yeah!
What are they doing up there?
What are you doing?
The referee hasn't counted yet.
Get out of the ring.
Why the hell did they go up there?
Get down.
Go to the corner.
One. Two.
Three. Four.
Five. Six. Seven.
Eight. Nine.
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you punch him?
I did.
Pol. Keep it up!
I'm here, nephew.
He can't see anything this time. Fight!
Get up. Come here.
Here is round three!
Box!
Yes!
Kick!
What?
-Kick!
Now he's disoriented.
Hit him hard.
Why are you running around?
Box!
He got punched and disoriented.
What's wrong with you?
He's not human.
Not human, my ass!
He's standing right there.
Are you throwing the fight?
I said he's not human.
Go!
Come on.
Pol! Fight him!
Box!
Pol! Keep it up!
You must fight him. Don't give up.
You are the hope of Koak E-Gerng.
Fight him, Pol.
Fight him, my son-in-law.
Fight him, my son-in-law!
Son-in-law?
To the corner.
One.
-Pol.
-Two.
Son-in-law?
Pol!
Come on, fight!
Four.
Fight him!
Five.
Son-in-law?
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Fight!
Kill him!
Box!
This hook is for Mam!
You must fight him.
Fight him, my son-in-law.
This hook is for Dad Johnny!
Don't give up.
You are the hope of Koak E-Gerng.
This elbow is for Koak E-Gerng!
To the corner.
Wait.
Wait. Don't go up yet.
Didn't you learn something?
-What?
-Let the referee count first.
That's right.
I forgot.
One.
Saen Phu Kwai!
Two.
Get up!
Three. Four.
-Get up! Quick!
-Five.
Six. Seven.
Eight. Nine.
Ten!
Check in at Koak E-Gerng
Always have a good time here
No more struggling
No more fighting in the big city
No matter what, we still have our home
Beat down by a tough life?
Pain and discouragement is normal
We are poor at Koak E-Gerng
But have fun all year
What?
Mam, come here.
-Come on.
-What?
Come on. Don't speak up.
Come here.
We won the grand prize!
What?
Don't be loud.
We won the grand prize!
We won the grand prize
in the lottery, Mam.
-How much?
-20 baht.
Damn it!
Two basil chicken, please.
I knew it!
Mam.
Give me your phone.
It's green.
Really?
Yes, don't be so loud.
We won the grand prize!
How much?
Twelve million.
Don't be loud.
-Twelve million!
Beloved ones, come back home
Send your location to remind them
The old route home.
Let's dance to get rid of loneliness
Come on, beloved ones, come back home
Beloved ones, come back home
Thank you so much
for making me this happy.
I take it as a wonderful gift
that is invaluable to my life.
And I take it that
Dad Johnny gave you to me as
the most valuable gift in my life as well.
Don't worry about people
Criticize our poverty
Koak E-Gerng people don't mind
Martin, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
About your son, Mark.
He wants your blessing.
To be ordained?
Or to have a new wife?
No. What a stupid man.
Mark!
He won't come out by that name.
You're supposed to call him… Markie!
Hello, Daddy.
I want your blessing to be a ladyboy.
So happy he fainted.
Daddy.
Bring your heart back
Wealth can always be found
If we are still alive
Bring the broken heart back to our home
You like hot and steamy liver?
I guess it's gonna be
hot and steamy all night.
Kidding.