May I have your attention.
Parents of new elementary students,
please submit your documents
at the assembly hall
no later than 11 a.m.
Move, everyone.
Let me through.
This way, son.
Oh, my god.
Come here.
Isares Arunvilai is number one
on the waiting list.
He's got 97 out of 100.
How much did the accepted students score?
Between 98 to 100.
-May I see their names?
-No, you may not.
Thank you.
So he's giving up his seat?
No. I'm going to speak to the director.
To hold his seat, you have to register
and pay the administration fee.
But you said he's on the waiting list.
Four students
who scored 96.5 are also waiting.
All right. How much?
A total of 9,800 baht.
Ohm.
If we have 25,000 baht
and we pay 600 for the registration fee,
how much do we have left?
It's 24,400 baht.
And if we pay an extra 9,800 baht fee
to hold a place on the waiting list,
how much do we have left?
We'll only have 14,600 baht.
Also we need new uniforms,
new shoes, and a new school bag.
Mom.
I can't believe
you only got on the waiting list.
Just one more point,
why couldn't you do it for me?
Try harder next time, okay?
I will, Mom.
Ohm, come with me.
Just one game, then study hard.
Don't let me down.
8 YEARS LATER
FEBRUARY 8
OHM'S SCHOLARSHIP EXAM
"Today, students spend an average
of five hours a day in their classroom."
"Statistics also show that they spend
4.1 hours a day looking at their phones."
"The number is likely to go up."
"They prefer looking at their phones
to playing sports."
"So I'd like to propose a project called
'School…'"
No, scratch that. "Phone-Free Classroom."
"We must now realize
that mobile phones are a major threat."
Hello?
Ms. Ben? My son won't need
your tutoring services this month.
His friend took an online class
and got good grades.
So my son wants to give it a try.
That's okay. Bye.
TUTORING INCOME -4,000 BAHT
ELECTRICITY BILL -3,000 BAHT
INTERNET BILL -1,000 BAHT
CREDIT CARD BILL -3,000 BAHT
WATER BILL -400 BAHT
Your friend SonicFighter is back again.
Hello, everyone.
Triple Kill, I got you! That's it, boy!
Here it is, attack now!
Nice one!
Tank? Take this!
Arum, go! Go now!
Easy, I'll go round.
Yorn with low mobility! It's over!
Shit!
Why didn't you open the door?
Sorry, Mom.
I'm writing a speech.
What speech?
My speech for Mother's Day.
I was selected to read it on stage.
What's with the earphones?
Well, when I need to focus,
I always listen to music.
Well.
New computer set?
Yes, Mom.
It was Palm's.
I sold my old PC
and used the money
to buy this one from him.
Don't worry. It's a cheap outdated model.
And this?
What is it?
It's a letter
asking for your permission to let me
enter a game tournament.
Where will you find time for that?
You have to focus on your studies.
I have some free time
when I'm not studying.
Look, I'm always on track, right?
It's just an online game.
Please sign it.
Have I ever let you down?
NEXT MORNING
INVITATION TO JOIN
MOTHER'S DAY ACTIVITIES
PERMISSION TO PARTICIPATE
IN ROV TOURNAMENT
Director, we must realize that
mobile phones are a major threat.
The Wi-Fi here is very strong.
That means if our school's Wi-Fi
is this strong,
mobile phones must be
unequivocally banned in class.
Sir, she's right.
Schools in France have already
implemented this rule.
I will push it through.
Our school should've been stricter
in this regard a long time ago.
I'll send the two of you to other schools
to study how they restrict
mobile phone usage.
That way,
you can adapt it to our classrooms.
From now on, our Ratpanyavittayakom School
will become a model of excellence!
All right, the Burmese attacked us
from three separate fronts.
From the North,
in the town of Chiang Saen.
From the West, here.
Through the Three Pagodas Pass.
And from the South, at Ratchaburi.
King…
Hold on.
Right.
King Bodawpaya split his last troops
into nine armies
and marched them toward Bangkok.
King Rama I sent his three armies
to halt the Burmese.
But in a war, numbers aren't everything.
What you need is a strategy!
Holy crap! Just like playing RoV!
Class, what's the name
of the Burmese general?
Another great battle is here.
We're entering a new war!
The Army of Valor
marching into the jungle battlefield.
The troop is split into three fronts.
The five heroes must work together
and marshal their forces into the fray.
Their mission
is to reach the enemy's Core.
They have to rely on a combination
of skills and talents
to fight their opponents
in this breathless battle.
But in war, there must be sacrifices.
But that doesn't mean defeat.
The only way to win is
to destroy the towers!
For the glory of…
RoV.
Come and get me!
See? Who's the boss now?
I just saved you.
All of you!
March your asses to the Discipline Office!
-Yes, sir.
STUDENTS ON DISCIPLINARY PROBATION
ACADEMIC YEAR 2019
DISCIPLINE OFFICE
Kobsak,
I haven't tallied your latest offense.
But this is already your ninth.
One more time and you'll be kicked out.
How many times have I told you
to behave yourself?
Why can't you be like other students?
All you do is cause trouble
and play stupid games.
You will have no future!
All you do is cause…
KOBSAK WONGVIJITSUK
Kobsak!
Where are you going?
Haven't you listened to anything
I've said?
That's a game-addicted teen for you.
Aggressive.
MOTHER'S DAY
PADUNGKIAT PATTANA SCHOOL
ISARES ARUNVILAI
STUDENT OF THE YEAR
Did you watch Ohm's gamecast
the other day?
RoV?
Yes, I did.
He was on a roll
when his mom suddenly walked in.
He lied to her without skipping a beat.
Son of the year.
His channel is "SonicFighter," right?
It was fucking hilarious.
Totally.
Yes, nice one!
You rock, Champ.
Super awesome.
Shit!
Mom.
Why are you doing this?
Did your game addiction
make you lie to me?
I never taught you to be a liar.
From now on, I'll limit your phone use.
-Mom.
-Not another word.
Quit playing
and resign from Higher.
Next, Isares Arunvilai,
Student of the Year 2019,
will represent the class
by giving a speech.
MOTHER'S DAY
Isares, please come up on stage.
Isares, please come up now.
Ohm!
Come down, Ohm.
Ohm.
Mom, is Ohm there with you?
Nothing.
Hi, my name's Best.
I'm the one who called you.
Ohm.
Come home with me.
You're not competing.
He could go home.
But if you want him to quit the team,
you're obliged by contract
to pay compensation.
The equivalent of his 12 months' pay
plus allowance.
What allowances?
Do you really think giving your kid
100 baht a day is enough?
Ohm earns several thousand
a month by himself.
You really have no idea?
The compensation will be 675,000 baht.
Wait a minute.
What for? Why do I have to pay for it?
Because you signed the contract.
I didn't sign any contract.
To terminate the contract,
you must pay for the damages.
My team has a sponsor.
You can't ruin my team
and get away with it.
What is this, Ohm?
Come home with me now.
Yes, go home and talk it over.
But while Ohm is still under contract,
he must come and train with the team.
We will compete in the national league
to represent Thailand
in a world tournament in Korea.
On February 8.
I ask for your understanding.
Don't ruin the hard work
all of us have put in.
FEBRUARY 8: OHM'S SCHOLARSHIP EXAM
Ohm.
How long have you been playing?
It doesn't affect my grades, does it?
Answer me, how long have you been playing?
Why do you care more
about money than about your future?
How much can you make by playing games?
More than you. I don't even have to
rely on you for money now.
See? Games make you aggressive.
You can make your own money, huh?
Student of the Year?
You forged my signature.
I did ask you to sign it.
But you kept saying
whatever you wanted to say.
Really, have you ever listened to me?
FEBRUARY 8: OHM'S SCHOLARSHIP EXAM
I'LL TALK TO YOU
ONLY AFTER THE TOURNAMENT
Ohm, have your breakfast.
Ohm.
I'LL TALK TO YOU
ONLY AFTER THE TOURNAMENT
But if you want him to quit the team,
you're obliged to pay 675,000 baht
for the damages.
I've got all the documents
for the refinance of your home.
Your property is in a prime location.
You've had it for three years.
The value must have risen.
Don't worry.
I'll speed up the process
and get back to you.
We will compete in the national league
to represent Thailand
in a world tournament in Korea.
We will compete in the national league
to represent Thailand
in a world tournament in Korea.
If they lose, then they won't get to go.
OHM, WILL TAKE HIGHER
EVEN HIGHER THAN BEFORE
WON THE CHAMPIONSHIP
FOR THE SECOND TIME
KOBSAK, MAPRANG, GUIDE
GOT KICKED OUT
Kobsak.
What's up, ma'am?
You know Higher Ground Thailand, right?
You were on this team before.
Why do you ask?
I'm starting an E-Sports club.
Sorry, ma'am,
what have you been smoking?
This Higher… Are they really that good?
Their new gen is not bad.
But the original members
were a whole lot better.
Then start a team and beat them.
I'll be your manager.
-Ma'am.
-Yes?
Are you kidding me?
I already struggle in school as it is.
I don't have time for anything else.
If you win the national tournament,
I'll help you graduate.
How about this?
You know the RoV website, right?
There's an application form
for the tournament there.
I'll send you all the members' IDs.
But one more thing,
I get to choose the players myself.
But I have to know
their backgrounds, okay?
I heard you had a fight
with one of your teammates.
No!
Ms. Ben, chill.
I'm not a thug.
Now we are with Gold Cobra.
They are our new champions!
How do you feel?
What's up, Kob?
Guide, do you want to join my team?
Hell yes!
"Hell yes!" That's how a champion feels!
SO WHAT SHOULD WE CALL OUR TEAM?
I'LL TALK TO YOU
ONLY AFTER THE TOURNAMENT
FEBRUARY 8: OHM'S SCHOLARSHIP EXAM
First, I play the jungler.
My position is vital to the team
because it decides victory or defeat.
Without me, the first-gen Higher
wouldn't have made it.
Even now, people still call me
"The Living Legend."
This is my buddy, Guide.
He's so versatile
that he can play any role.
But when he's the marksman,
prepare to beg for your life.
Once, he was so off his game
that Best kicked him out.
But now I'm ready to announce
that he's back in top form.
This is Bank.
A famous gamecaster
with a million subscribers.
His family is loaded.
He's our team's sponsor.
Not a pro player,
but he's a brilliant mid laner.
He can save your ass anywhere in the game.
This is Maprang,
the former girl idol of Higher.
Although Best used to
keep her as a bench-warmer,
don't underestimate her baby-doll looks.
She's quick and sharp.
A perfect roaming hero
who keeps an eye on what happens
to cause trouble for the enemies
and to support the team all at once.
That's our team.
Why only four?
Meet Max.
Get the fuck off.
Get off, you dickhead.
Sure, dickbag.
This little shit is Max.
He's my neighbor.
He may not look like it,
but he's actually around my age.
Max plays the solo fighter.
Crafty and fierce.
The only shortcoming is his potty mouth.
Motherfucker.
I'll smack your head right here.
Bitch.
I'm Ms. Ben, your team manager.
A sub.
The rule doesn't require a team manager.
Besides the main players,
one sub is allowed,
but he or she must meet
a minimum skill level.
A rookie like you won't cut it.
Just give me your ID,
I'll handle the rest.
The Core must be destroyed
in three minutes!
Hi guys, Winsy Mavin's here to welcome you
to Road to Arena of Valor 2019.
The match
I'm doing a commentary on is between
Ohmgaga and Beta Blue.
Our main talking point is that Ohmgaga
has three players
who used to play for Higher.
They are Maprang, Kobsak,
and Guide, a veteran marksman
who's making a comeback.
Let's see if this match will really
be settled in three minutes.
I'm looking forward to
an exciting game ahead!
Breach their defense
with Five Sisters Matrix.
This complex maneuver by Ohmgaga
relies on a tight interplay
between Kobsak and Guide.
They've unleashed non-stop kills
from the first five seconds.
-Awesome!
Sweet dreams.
What now, daddy?
Next, we'll go for Tier-1 Tower.
Let's do Looking for Trouble, okay?
-Who will do it?
-Not me, I'm pretty.
I'm ready to sacrifice
for the public good.
For freedom.
I'll return happiness to the people!
-Fuck-a-doodle-doo!
"Looking for Trouble" is a plan
in which Bank sacrifices himself as bait
to clear the path for his friends
to destroy the first tower.
How generous!
Without sacrifices,
there will be no victory.
No pain, no gain, right?
Tier-2 Tower, Girls Just Want to Have Fun.
This plan relies on a gang of "girls."
Kobsak plays the seducer.
His role is to lure the enemies in
so the other "girls" waiting in the back,
Maprang, Guide, and Max,
can sneak an attack on them.
Amazing!
Smooth and swift!
That's it!
Let's end this!
Or they'll hit our towers.
When they're born, we'll kill them.
What a savage little guy!
-Always going for a kill.
-Yes!
-Come on! Let's kill them all!
-Come on.
Three minutes are almost over.
Ohmgaga is raiding the Core
with a huge advantage.
They're also ruthless and sadistic!
They're waiting to kill newborns
in the tower!
Man, what a bunch of cutthroats!
-That's it!
-Let's do it!
Beta Blue's Core has been destroyed!
It has now been reduced to ruins!
Ohmgaga is through to the next round.
I've never witnessed a game
as exciting as this in my life!
See, my plan always works.
Awesome!
Are you that hungry?
Seriously?
Look at him.
Hungry online and offline.
ORIGINAL MEMBERS RISE AGAIN AS OHMGAGA
FOUR STRAIGHT WINS
AMONG THE LAST 128 TEAMS
OHMGAGA DECLARES WAR ON HIGHER
You guys were phenomenal
in the last four matches,
what's your secret?
I've studied the game's meta thoroughly.
The secret is to pick the right heroes.
Let me tell you,
Ohmgaga is ready to take on anyone.
PHONE-FREE CLASSROOM PROJECT
A one-on-one match with Higher
is coming up.
Do you have any message for your rival?
Go to hell, assholes.
Do you want to fight one-on-one with me?
What was that?
With Kob and I on the team,
we'll never lose.
-Listen, Maprang.
-Yes?
Thanks for joining my team.
I did it because you sounded desperate.
If we win and go to Korea,
will you still go to study in England?
Let's wait until we get into
the round of last 16 teams first.
-I have something to show you.
-What?
My dad just gave it to me.
Congratulations!
Now you're a biker like you always wanted.
I'm still missing a biker babe…
Stop.
Why?
Thanks for the ride.
ROUND OF 128 TEAMS
Ms. Ben, are you free?
What happened?
Shit happens!
Guide has dumped us!
-How come?
-Higher has bought him back.
Because we can't pay him a salary.
Goddamnit, he quit just before a match!
Call him now!
He won't come back.
You're our sub.
You have to play.
I can't.
You have to.
Game starts in 15 minutes!
MAP INFO: STANDARD MODE
Ms. Ben, you have to play the marksman.
Choose a marksman character, any of them.
And please don't die!
The marksman is squishy.
Now tell me what to do.
Dumbass.
You're Yorn. Go to Dragon Lane.
Who's the teacher here, stupid?
Watch your language, kid!
Don't follow me.
Go to Maprang. Go!
Get behind the tower.
Hide!
Just hit the right button.
Don't let anyone get near the tower.
Who's in there?
I need to pee.
Are you on drugs or what?
She's playing like a frigging kid.
Who's in there?
I need to shit.
Don't just stand there.
Move around.
Please check if there's anyone missing.
We've been knocking but there's no answer.
Maybe there's been an accident.
Ms. Ben…
MS. TOOM IS CALLING
No answer.
Can we just win it now?
What's the hurry?
Do you need to shit or what?
Please stop at a gas station.
It's an emergency.
Yes, we won! We won!
Without Guide, we should just quit.
We won't be this lucky in the next match.
I'm out.
Come on.
Relax.
We've made it this far.
We're going to be in deep shit.
You guys just have to quit,
but my reputation will be ruined.
We played like rookies,
it was embarrassing.
Ms. Ben, do you really think
you can fill in for Guide?
Bank.
She's a rookie.
Don't pressure her.
Sorry, ma'am.
I have to speak honestly.
You must try not to be a deadweight.
What do you want me to do?
From now until the finals,
you have to play the game
at least 1,000 times.
Impossible, I won't have time for that.
Just play 30 times a day.
We'll play with you.
What about the one-on-one challenge
with Higher?
There's nothing to fear
when I'm right here!
Listen up!
Starting tomorrow,
we all sleep here
so we can teach the teacher.
People keep asking me
what the best strategy for a marksman is.
The first thing you have to remember is
who plays the tank on your team.
Who is Tank? Is it a water tank?
Or maybe "tank you"?
No.
Tank is the hero with the highest HP.
The toughest, strongest guy
who can protect you,
because your body is squishy.
Without cover you're dead.
So you have to follow
the tank of your team.
YOU SHOULD EAT HEALTHY FOOD, OHM.
You have to keep in mind
who your Tank is.
Or you're finished.
Don't go at it alone,
because you're squishy.
Again, the marksman
always follows the tank.
Never let him out of your sight.
What are you doing?
First, you have to develop your skill
Because the enemy will go for a kill
If you're too thick to know the drill
And so clumsy
You'll be trapped and killed
Boom!
Pack it up and roll down the hill
See, you don't know how to kite.
You have to move when you're under attack.
The marksman must support the tank.
Follow him and watch his steps.
Got it?
Take him.
Omen, a crafty warrior.
Omen's first skill is hooking the enemies.
The second skill is deflecting the damage.
The third skill is imprisoning enemies,
with a 40-second cooldown.
Valhein is a marksman.
Got it?
You even know how to hit it?
You keep missing!
Having fun?
HI, MS. BEN. YOUR LOAN IS APPROVED.
PLEASE COME IN AND SIGN THE AGREEMENT
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
CAN I HAVE A LITTLE MORE TIME
TO THINK ABOUT THIS?
Now you attack. I'll show you how to kite.
Okay.
No! That's not it!
That's fencing! It's not kiting!
Take that! This is kiting!
Kob!
Take it easy.
Does it hurt?
Careful.
-You're all bruised up.
-Not so hard.
Yes.
-Kob should've held back.
-That's right.
I told him so.
Ms. Ben,
I told you, no pain, no game.
Brush your teeth, Max.
Hey, you.
When was the last time you brushed?
Fuck off.
Do you want to fight me?
Sure. Can you reach my face?
-What?
-Oh, my!
Four in the mid lane! Attack Dark Slayer!
All of you, come here!
I'm dead!
Ohm!
I'm coming.
I'm dead.
We can still get it!
I'm dead too, Ohm.
Their jungler is dead.
I'm dead too.
Ohm, get Dark Slayer!
I'm dead.
Ohm, why didn't you come help us?
I can end this myself.
-Why didn't you come when we called?
-I will show you.
-You're the only one left!
-Ohm, what are you doing?
Don't fucking say "yes."
Do you think you're the star player?
If Violet wasn't so lame,
you would've been crushed.
Why did you hide in the bush?
Why didn't you come out
and help them get Dark Slayer?
Had you come out sooner,
no one would've gotten killed. Got it?
We could've won more clinically.
You think you're a hotshot?
But…
But what?
I just won.
But you did not win
like a Higher member is supposed to.
Since Guide left, we've played like shit.
We're a joke.
Our subscribers have left in droves.
Maprang, you have to help us now.
Do I have to do it?
Come on,
just like when you were with Higher.
You did this before.
Hi, today…
Best forced me to do it then.
Please, I'm begging you.
Doll yourself up like
you're in a girl group.
It will boost our team's rating.
Hi, today is a holiday…
No way. Don't you think I look
more like a boy?
I'm sure you can do it.
We have no other options.
I'm desperate.
Please help me.
Or should I ask her instead?
Need my help?
-No way.
-Go.
-Go!
Maprang, come play with us.
-Nice and smooth.
Maprang.
One down!
Did you do your makeup without a mirror?
Wow,
cute.
Thanks.
So cute…
because you put duct tape on your brows!
Good one, man!
I'm proud of you.
Our ratings will go through the roof.
I mean it.
You're cute.
Cute, my ass.
Best,
I think I'm a better player
when I play in my own style.
Only a good plan can make you win.
Your relentless attacking
has made you famous,
but it's not enough to ensure our victory
in a one-on-one with Kobsak.
What will happen if we're over-confident
and don't follow the plan?
Ask Guide about it.
If you indulge yourself too much,
you'll end up like this team.
This is an example
of a dreadful, ad-lib play.
This is Ohmgaga.
What a shame they have
our old members among them.
Kobsak may be sharp,
but he can't carry the whole team
on his shoulders.
This is Max,
a clusterfuck in the making.
The player True_Heroes
still has a lot to learn.
Maprang keeps running around
fixing others' problems.
But seriously,
she's not useful to anybody except Kob.
This is how you play with zero planning.
Can you see how disorganized they are?
They failed as a team.
Their marksman is a disaster.
Hey, Guide.
And who's this BenJay?
A teacher at Kob's school.
Her real name's Benjamas.
Hello and welcome to
Garena Special Match 1-1.
Kobsak from Ohmgaga
up against Ohm from Higher.
Both of them have to play Raz
in this head-to-head battle.
Will the upstart outsmart the pro?
See you in the game!
And who's this BenJay?
A teacher at Kob's school.
Her real name's Benjamas.
Mom, you're playing for Ohmgaga?
And the winner is Ohm from Higher!
Ohm's plan was to let Kobsak
come straight at him…
Mom, when I grow up,
I will take you to a mountain
where there's lots of snow.
What will we do on the snowy mountain?
We'll go skiing.
I'LL TALK TO YOU
ONLY AFTER THE TOURNAMENT
Kob,
I want to talk to you about your grades.
Do we have to discuss this now?
Wait, it won't take more than a minute.
-No more than a minute?
-Yes.
-One minute, right?
Fine.
Is that really necessary?
Yes, I'm timing it.
Go!
You got a C in social studies
and a C+ in Thai language.
D in math, D in science,
and D in Buddhism.
D+ in Thai music, D+ in computer studies,
D in English,
B in health education, A in PE.
Bottom line is,
you won't graduate high school.
You have to do better
in subjects with high credits.
At least a C.
For subjects with lower credits,
try to get an A,
like health education
or PE which is your favorite.
Put them all together,
your GPA will go up
around 0.3 to 0.5 points,
which means you'll pass.
But for math,
I want you to get at least a C.
With free electives,
you can fail as many as you like,
and you'll still graduate!
Just 36 seconds.
Badass!
I have an idea.
You will study hard?
No, I have a better idea.
Ready?
Nakroth, 24 seconds.
Tel'Annas, 35 seconds.
Maloch, 40 seconds.
Raz, 20 seconds.
Nakroth Ult.
Maloch Ult.
Tel Ult.
Raz Ult.
Nakroth, 10. Raz, 15. Tel, 27. Maloch, 29.
-Badass!
Not bad?
ROUND OF 64 TEAMS
Fight! We'll get to
the offline round soon.
-Of course.
All in the mid lane, go invade Red.
Tel is alone, attack it.
No, I don't want to ruin my nails.
-Awesome!
Maprang, cover Ms. Ben.
Relax. Stay in the tower for now, Ms. Ben.
Fourteen.
Thirteen.
And this one?
Ten seconds left. Go for it.
Kob, that one's got Ultimate, careful.
Got you!
Max, now!
Got it. Take that!
Nice!
Their timing is perfect.
Like they can read our minds.
The screen doesn't show a counter, right?
So how do they know how long
until we can use our ultimate skills?
-Kob, you've got five seconds.
-Now!
Maprang, you've got seven seconds.
They will use Ultimate soon, go now!
We're almost there.
Yes!
You're awesome.
So precise like clockwork!
You know the exact moments
to attack or retreat.
Sure. I trained her myself.
If there's anything you want,
just let me know.
In that case, can I ask you something?
Sure, go ahead.
Now that our ratings have gone up,
can Maprang stop wearing
this cutie-kitten outfit?
Please.
If that's what you want,
of course!
Thank you.
Just be yourself.
All right.
-Hey!
-Wait!
Don't just take your t-shirt off.
Take everything off!
You guys!
Hey, Max!
In your dreams!
Let's eat.
Actually, I like it all.
How it was before or how it is now.
This pork, I like it however it's cooked.
Thought you were talking about me.
I was talking about you.
This one's for you.
Couple of the year.
How come I never knew?
Why should I tell you?
Peek-a-boo!
Attention, today we will launch
a new program.
"Phone-Free Classroom" starts now.
We request all students
to leave your phone here
and retrieve it during lunch break.
Leave your phone here
Stop!
and retrieve it during lunch break.
Leave your phone here
Leave your phone…
Cellphones are great, but we often
ignore their negative effects.
Statistics show
that 75 percent of Thai youths
use mobile phones without limits.
A total of 42.2 percent
use their phones only to play games.
That's why they suffer from
a short attention span.
Research shows that 85 percent
perform poorly
in English and mathematics.
Thai students spend
an average of five hours a day in class.
But they spend 4.1 hours a day
on their phones.
And the numbers are going up.
They don't play sports,
all they do is look at their phones.
So I'd like to propose
the "Phone-Free Classroom" program.
We must come to the conclusion…
that mobile phones
are a clear and present threat!
Error Identification Exam guidelines…
ROUND OF 32 TEAMS
"Environ…" what?
What "environment"?
This is too hard for me.
Get lost.
I don't want to.
Kob!
What?
I'll smack your head.
Go on.
But let me touch your brows.
This is fun!
Stop smiling.
Sneaky punk.
Sir,
I was using it to review a lesson.
Not for chatting or playing games.
Ms. Ben sent me the review materials.
Look.
Stop lying, Kobsak.
Ms. Benjamas will never allow
her students to use their phones.
What do you know?
She runs the school's E-Sports team.
She's not a dinosaur like you.
Look, Kobsak.
I'll never buy your lame excuse.
You know why?
Because the Phone-Free Classroom
is Ms. Benjamas' project.
Not so fast.
Come and get it after school.
I can't reach Kob.
What do we do?
I knew this team would never work!
No, don't say that.
You and Max wait here.
We won't give up easily.
The match starts at six.
Six o'clock sharp!
Hi, Ms. Ben.
Mr. Tos caught Kob with his phone.
The brat even used your name as an excuse.
Hello, Guide.
What's up, Maprang?
Is Kob with you?
No.
Ask Ohm's mom.
She teaches at Kob's school.
What are you talking about?
Oh, so you didn't know?
-Your presentation was amazing.
-Thank you.
Let me take you to dinner.
That's very kind, sir.
But I've got something urgent to do.
-Go on then.
-Thanks!
Ms. Ben, where's Kob?
He's in detention.
Damn it.
Okay. You find a way to get him out.
I'll find a room with Wi-Fi.
You've become a very aggressive boy.
LIBRARY
Look at your penalty points.
One more slip and you're finished.
And you've got the nerve
to use Ms. Ben's name.
When I report this to the director,
I wonder if you could still be so cocky.
Hey, did you pay any attention
to what I said?
I feel sorry for your parents.
They work hard to pay for your tuition.
But instead of studying,
you create trouble.
DIRECTOR WISET'S OFFICE
AVAILABLE NETWORKS: DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
Why didn't the janitor lower the flag?
How could he abandon his duty?
Hey, Kobsak! Where are you going?
Stop right there!
Ms. Ben, I've got Wi-Fi.
Come to the director's office.
Kobsak!
What a trouble maker!
Hey, Kobsak! Wait for me.
Gosh, it burns.
Kobsak!
Oh, shit.
Password? I'm fucked!
Shit.
"Greg Norman"?
No. That's not it!
Maybe Norman Greg?
Wrong again.
Norman111.
Goddamnit!
Do you know the password?
WisetNorman.
Got it.
I'm in.
Bank's in.
Max's in.
-Where's Kob?
-Kob.
Where the hell are you?
Kob's in!
Help me in my lane, Ms. Ben.
Coming. Don't rush in, Bank.
I'm dead!
I'll cover you.
Shit, my battery!
Find a charger.
It's in here.
There it is.
I'll cover you.
Keep playing.
Hey, I'm still in the toilet.
I'm still here!
-Oh, my god!
-A blackout, seriously?
I was in the toilet,
why did you turn off the light?
Who the hell are you?
I'm the school director.
Help me, Maprang.
Give me a second.
"Director Wiset Kasiwara."
It's really you. I'm sorry.
I did not recognize you
without your cowboy hat.
I'm really sorry, Director.
My hat?
Right, I must have left it in my office.
Could you turn on the light for a minute?
-Oh, my!
-Oh, gosh!
It's back on.
Go!
-Get Dark Slayer first.
-Okay.
You shoot, I'll tank it.
I got it.
Go!
Yes!
Good job, everyone.
We won.
Cool.
Ms. Ben?
What's going on here?
Just playing games, sir.
Kob! Maprang!
Are you guys okay?
Are you hiding something from us?
This Phone-Free Classroom project
is your brainchild, right?
Yes.
And Ohm?
Is he your son?
Yes.
Ohm's your son?
What are you trying to do?
Why did you lie to us?
Say it.
I want my son to quit playing games.
So you're using us?
Ohmgaga, right?
I quit.
Kob.
HI, ORN. I ACCEPT THE LOAN AGREEMENT.
Hi.
Hi, Best.
I agree to pay the compensation.
Have you eaten, son?
Ohm?
Have you ever asked me
what I want to do with my life?
Have you ever asked me…
STUDENTS ON DISCIPLINARY PROBATION
KOBSAK WONGVIJITSUK
Max!
Who are you?
Max's not home.
-I'm a teacher, my name's Ben.
-A teacher?
Is Max in trouble?
No! He's not in trouble.
What are you doing here?
What did you do, Max?
Pain in the ass.
Do you know where Kob lives?
Follow me.
No worries, he's not in trouble.
Where is it?
We're almost there.
There he is.
Why can't you leave me alone?
Get lost now.
I apologize.
But please don't quit.
Don't quit what?
School or games?
I suck at everything anyway.
So what's the point?
I'll quit every goddamn thing.
You lied to me.
You lied to your own son.
You lied to all of us.
Yes, I lied to everyone.
I'm selfish.
I'm a bad teacher and a worse mother.
But I never lied about one thing.
I was so happy when I played games
with you guys.
I think my son must feel the same.
I've made up my mind.
I want to play with you again.
I will set up an E-Sports club.
Mom, when I grow up,
I'll take you to a mountain
where there's lots of snow.
What will we do on the snowy mountain?
We'll go skiing.
Welcome to the Round of 16…
-of Road to Arena of Valor 2019.
-Of Road to Arena of Valor 2019.
From a thousand teams
from all over Thailand,
we are down to the last 16.
Only one of them
will get to represent Thailand
in the world championship in South Korea.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to cancel the agreement
to pay the compensation.
You have my permission to let Ohm compete.
I'm a man of my word, ma'am.
I removed Ohm after you called me.
And now I trust my first-team squad.
But Ohm is your best player.
I agree with you on that,
but Higher is Higher
because we believe in teamwork.
And now I believe in my team.
Please leave now.
Don't make things worse.
Go back to your team.
My guys need to concentrate.
SCHEDULE
Let's start with Ohmgaga.
They've been amazing, don't you think?
Ohmgaga is impressive on every front.
At the start, they ran into
some trouble in the bottom lane.
But with Nakroth's Split-Push,
they turned the situation around
and won the game.
Kobsak was brilliant.
His AutoQ11 has done a great job.
The first team to go through
to the next round is…
Ohmgaga!
Higher is the tournament's favorite.
But the team missed Ohm SonicFighter
in the first round,
and things didn't run smoothly.
They won but it was a narrow win.
Let's see if they'll bounce back
in the next round.
In the quarter-finals,
Ohmgaga played
with such astonishing teamwork.
Especially Ms. BenJay.
A real ass-kicker for someone her age.
Such incredible skills.
That's why Ohmgaga
is the dark horse of the season.
-It's good!
-Kill it!
Can Higher go any higher?
Their coach comes prepared
with a masterly playbook.
They're doing much better
than we expected.
All in the mid lane.
Maprang, go.
Got it.
-That's it!
-Now, Ms. Ben.
Go!
Unbelievable!
Ohmgaga has made it to the finals!
They've played with such flair
and team spirit.
Ohmgaga is playing in the final round!
-BenJay!
-Stop.
SCHEDULE
Destroy the tower!
That's it! Now we have the two finalists!
Ohmgaga vs. Higher.
It could also be Mother vs. Son!
BenJay up against SonicFighter.
Let's see who'll come out on top.
This is the final game you can't miss!
Get the marksman first.
Locked, three, two, one!
Ohmgaga is going full throttle.
They move smoothly as one, up and down.
BenJay, their marksman,
is improving every second.
Her skills are still limited,
but her attacking moves are so clinical.
And watch Maprang.
Her timing is perfect.
She was a substitute
when she was with Higher.
How is that? She's better than
their first-team players!
-I agree.
-That's it.
Go in and attack.
Yes.
-That was easy.
-The all-time favorite Higher
has lost the first game to Ohmgaga.
This is going to be epic!
Higher will have to come back stronger
in the next game.
Higher seems a little tense.
They aren't at their best.
Perhaps it's pressure
from having lost the first game.
Or it's because they don't have their
talisman, Ohm, known as SonicFighter.
Lock it for me.
BenJay's items are full to the tilt!
They're ready to close the book on Higher!
Go!
That's nice, keep going!
There's a fight here.
Watch BenJay closely.
Her Valhein has crushed
007x so forcefully.
Look at that!
Another one bites the dust.
THE BLUE TEAM'S CORE IS DESTROYED!
Kobsak's Murad surged past everyone
to get to the Core.
It's done! Ohmgaga is up 2-0.
Yes!
Ohmgaga is up 2-0.
Will Higher find a way to come back?
See you after the break.
We're screwed.
You have to let Ohm play.
Ohmgaga knows all our moves.
We can turn things around.
You have to believe in Higher's system.
We've come this far and we will beat them.
They play purely by instinct.
No fucking qualification at all.
They've been lucky since the first match.
They will slip.
Slip?
How?
They play like they can read
each other's minds.
We're a total failure.
We play like shit.
You have to admit that
Ohm is our key player.
Our plans aren't working
because he's not here.
Do you still think he's dispensable?
Go get him then.
This is our re-match, Ohm.
Our victory would mean something
only if we beat Ohm.
Ohm, you wet fart, prepare to die!
You'll cry like a baby
when we beat the shit out of you.
Fucking loser.
Get your hands off me.
Now, this is exciting!
Ohm SonicFighter is taking his seat.
Let's see if Ohmgaga will take it home
or if Higher will live
to fight another round.
I'm here, go on!
This isn't good.
Go back!
Take out Dragon.
Dragon!
My HP is low.
Stall it.
Wait for me.
Go back!
All in the mid lane.
All in.
An eye for an eye!
Thanks. Go.
Protect the Core.
Destroyed!
That's it!
Higher has outclassed Ohmgaga.
Ohm SonicFighter has turned
the game around.
He was superb as Kriknak.
He rescued his team from a crisis.
We have to credit Best
for his choice of players too.
It was brilliant!
Told you to let Ohm play.
Ohmgaga opts to ban Kriknak,
played by SonicFighter.
He was so good that
the character is now banned.
We call it a respect ban.
It happens when a team bans
another team's hero
out of respect for exceptional skills.
Kriknak is now out of the game.
But banning Kriknak means
they've freed other
often-banned heroes like Elsu.
Let's see if this ban is the right move.
Because Higher is the Blue Side
and will pick first.
Ohmgaga had no idea that
Higher would play Jungle Elsu.
But Ohm SonicFighter will have
to play in a new style,
because usually,
he prefers to play the assassin.
Now he's moved to play the marksman.
Let's see if Ohmgaga
will be able to handle him.
Why did he pick this hero?
Ohm SonicFighter is a genius player!
He's just unbelievable.
This Jungle Elsu is really something!
Maprang with a great run here.
Bank with a slam-bang Cataclysm!
That was smooth.
Bank almost got hit but he backed away.
A chance to use Ulti anyway.
Did Romeo get his target?
It's his payback from the last shot.
Well, now what? There's a duel happening.
A duel between AutoQ and Enictuz.
Can he handle that?
A terrible miss!
It doesn't look good in mid lane.
Max in the top lane.
But SonicFighter is ambushing him.
Max is down.
It's going to be a tough call from there.
A duel in Dark Slayer…
AutoQ bamboozled him.
Dead on the ground!
Higher seems to enjoy
more and more advantages.
BenJay is farming too much
in the mid lane.
KritNgi came in from the left
and solo-killed her.
That's bad.
BenJay is the team's main attacker.
Ohmgaga are being taken out one by one.
Their backs are against the wall.
Why didn't Ohm finish off Ms. Ben himself?
Let's keep going.
AutoQ up against SonicFighter.
It's a duel.
But no, he's out!
Higher finally did it.
They beat Ohmgaga two games straight.
The score is tied at 2-2.
SonicFighter was instrumental
in the turnaround of the game.
They have won two games in a row,
and now we're going into the final battle.
What the hell was that, huh?
I paid a lot for this jacket!
Don't worry. I have a plan for Ms. Ben.
We're going into the do-or-die final game.
The winners will be
the champions of Thailand.
Ohmgaga has picked Raz.
I don't know what they're thinking.
Will they put Raz up against Nakroth
played by SonicFighter?
It doesn't look good
because BenJay will play Raz.
Unusual, because so far
she has only played the marksman.
This game is going to be so unpredictable.
Raz versus Nakroth!
It's BenJay against SonicFighter.
Higher are switching plans.
They know we know their moves.
I'm fucked.
Top Lane! They're heading to our Core!
I'll warp there.
You can't! It takes time to recall!
DarkBlood alone
won't be able to stop them.
It's relentless!
AutoQ as Volkath comes charging in!
But hey, look at this battle.
SonicFighter and BenJay,
the son against the mother!
If BenJay can stop SonicFighter's Nakroth,
her team will have a chance
of coming back.
Can BenJay stop her son?
Go for it, Mom.
Don't let me down.
Finally, we have the winner!
BenJay took down SonicFighter,
but it was SonicFighter's trap
so that he could send minions to the Core,
and AutoQ couldn't stop them.
The winner is Higher!
I'm sorry.
I really sucked.
You beat your son to a pulp.
It's all right, Ms. Ben.
We got further than expected.
Ohmgaga is the coolest team anyway.
Was it fun?
You're so awesome, for real.
How many math teachers
have ever been in an RoV final?
Right?
Thank you.
Give me a hug.
So tell me, what is E-Sports?
Sometimes people watch us play
and say we are stupid
for choosing wrong characters
or taking impossible risks.
But the thing is
we can always try to stick with our style
and strategy, adapt to our opponents,
or deal with whatever's in front of us.
FEBRUARY 8: OHM'S MATCH IN KOREA
But still, there's no guarantee
that we're making the right choice.
We may think
that a certain plan will lead to victory.
But even with the best plan,
we can still lose.
Actually,
E-Sports is like life.
Why do you think
you've been named the MVP
or the most valuable player
in this tournament?
Of course it wasn't just me.
My teammates are valuable players too.
We're different, but we're a team.
STUDY HARD. OKAY?
I'LL CALL YOU WHEN I GET THERE.
We fight in different lanes,
but we always support each other.
COME BACK SOON. I MISS YOU ALREADY.
Whether you win or lose,
they're always there for you.
I'm the MVP
because of them.
And who is your MVP?
My mother.
After ten minutes, stop playing.
Leave your phone here
and retrieve it after school.
SPORTS CLUB
LOOKING FOR NEW CLUB MEMBERS
APPLY NOW TO KOBSAK WONGVIJITSUK