The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Thanks for coming.
I never want us to part ways.
I want to take care of you like this forever.
But now I can't.
I can't choose.
Mek, I need to tell you something.
Don't you worry.
Just follow the dreams
that you want to pursue.
I love you, Mek.
I'll go now.
[FLUK
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[Finally, we meet.]
Q, have you prepared everything already?
Yes, mom.
All the stationaries too?
Mom, we don't need many of those at university.
True.
Some of my friends just showed up without any of them.
If you have any problem at university,
you can always talk to me.
Okay, I will talk to you,
former Head of Student Club, Mr. Kimhan.
Kim! Don't mess with my hair!
Don't worry too much about your look.
I don't want anyone to fall for you.
If there's any freshmen activity, you should join.
- So you can meet new friends.
- Alright, mom.
But if it looks dangerous or shady,
you'll leave right away.
Understood?
Sure, mom.
Here's for you, Kim.
Oh wait. Your brother's gone?
Perhaps he has something to do.
Anyway...
Where is dad?
I asked him to buy stuff for me.
Hurry up and finish this. It's your first day.
- You shouldn't be late.
- Alright, mom.
[First day at work.]
May I come in?
Hello. Hello.
Sit over there.
Thank you.
You're Kim, the new AE, right?
Yes.
I'm Orn.
I'm a senior AE here.
Any work you got, you must run it through me.
I'll keep that in mind.
I read your resume.
You graduated with honors, didn't you?
But this line of work isn't what you studied for.
You think you can handle it?
I believe I can handle the job.
I've seen so many people talk like this.
But in the end, they fail.
I'll let you start with trivial assignments then.
You saw that?
Just take out the staples and separate them.
Do this first.
And then you wait for my call.
Absolutely.
Kimhan.
Yes?
Can you take this to HR?
Yes, ma'am.
Kim, take this to the art director's table, please.
Which one is it?
Go find it yourself.
Just put it down over there.
Kim!
Yes?
Take this to Finance, please.
"Today's your first day at work, son?"
"You can do it!"
It's tiring, huh?
Thank you.
What's your name?
I am Nui.
You can ask me about anything.
Don't be shy.
I know how you're feeling.
Does Orn act like this all the time?
Just don't care much about her.
She's always gatekeeping.
Don't pressure yourself too much, okay?
No one has sky-high expectations for a new kid.
We all know we need to guide you.
Got it. Thank you.
Whoa, whoa, there's no need for that.
Just saying thank you is fine.
Bye. Fighto.
Yes. Thank you.
Fighto.
"Shall we hit Bomb Bar tonight?"
"Sure. Let's meet there."
"First day of work isn't like what I thought it'd be."
"Just keep your chin up."
"Real life has just started."
Kimhan!
Yes?
Come here, please.
Here. This is what we've prepared for you.
What do you think?
Park, this product of ours...
is designed to look fresh and bright.
So I think I want the visual to...
reflect this fresh and bright concept.
while also maintaining the color of our brand.
But the brand's color is black.
Yes, it's black.
Can you make it black but also bright then?
Make it refreshing and easy on the eye.
Like pastel black, perhaps?
Pastel black?
You mean gray color?
No. Not gray.
Pastel black.
Do you understand what I mean?
I do.
Then, could you please get back to me at the latest by...
Today?
Let me consult with my team first.
Sure.
"I just had a bad briefing."
"This client wants my design to look bright."
"But the only color that she allows is black."
"Since when was black considered bright?"
"She even mentioned 'pastel black'"
"but said it's not the same as gray."
"Calm down, my friend."
"You'll find a way."
Mama Bear, wake up!
Can I sleep a little longer?
Wake up and go open your bar.
Otherwise, you won't have enough time to prepare.
And your friends are coming this evening.
Aren't you gonna get up?
Are you seriously doing this to me?
You're the owner. You can't be lazy.
Come on.
Get up.
And why are you home today?
Day-off?
No.
I was just checking on my work there.
Go.
Get up now.
Quickly.
Pull me up, please.
Alright, alright.
What's this?
Alright! I'm awake now.
Thank you so much.
Please come again.
Bear, can I take a photo with you?
Sure.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Should we call you Boss Bomb now?
Boss what?
You're being so extra.
Back in the day, all you cared about was lotto.
Who would have thought you'd win it for real?
And he won the first prize too.
When it was announced, he cried like a river.
I got the winning number from Mek's license plate.
Lee...
We're here to party.
Stop working!
Just a minute.
I need to send this to the photographer today.
Actually, on the set where I assisted today...
I met Tim.
He was the model.
Seems like he's still doing his channel.
Does that mean he's not working for his family hotel anymore?
Perhaps he wants to do something on his own.
His channel is quite popular.
But not as popular as Bear's Experiment, I'm sure.
You see the people who come to this bar?
All of them are your fans.
If I ever break up with you,
my bar will be out of business.
Bomb, don't you ever think that way.
They come here because it's a good bar.
Stop thinking that way, okay?
Believe in yourself.
Understood?
Yeah.
What about you?
How was your first day at work?
Still need to adjust.
It was tough.
Just take it easy, my friend.
Don't be stressed.
Alright.
Let's drink.
Come on!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait for me!
Park!
Come on in.
Now, see this!
Hey, wait.
You got a new haircut?
Yeah.
How do I look?
Good?
Can I have a look at the back?
You're right.
It looks good.
Bear, check that out.
Cheers!
Yeah!
Hold up.
What are we celebrating anyway?
We're celebrating...
the fact that Kim got his new job.
After he's been finding a job for so long.
Okay, cheers!
Cheers!
I'm sure one day your dad will understand
and accept the path you choose.
Until that day comes,
I'll always be here for you....
and support you like I always do.
Are you sure you can carry him home?
Yeah.
I've been through tougher situations.
What kind of situation?
Mama Bear, you don't need to know that.
Just let them go home.
It's late.
There might be no cab to call.
Bear, have you been in touch with Mek lately?
He's been busy.
He said he had a lot of work.
A lot of projects to do.
I miss him.
I thought he'd come back once he finished his degree.
Instead, he stayed there for so long.
Yeah.
Perhaps he likes kangaroos.
Kangaroos?
What's wrong with you?
I feel heavy now.
Well...
Let's say goodbye from here.
Okay.
See you later, Kim.
Bye.
You think they're gonna make it home?
Kim, can you go home on your own?
If not, you can stay with me.
It's okay.
I'm totally fine.
My car's here.
Okay, go home safe.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
"How was your first day at work?"
"Pretty tough."
"I still have a lot to learn."
"That's normal."
"This thing takes time."
"Don't pressure yourself too much."
"Thanks."
"What about you, Tim?
How's your channel going?"
"It's going fine."
What have you been doing lately?
Well...
I'm working on my channel just like before.
Have you ever thought of coming to help me at our hotel?
I don't want to do it, dad.
I didn't ask you whether you want to do it or not.
No matter what, you must do it.
I don't trust anyone to do it but you.
I only have you.
Stop making those non-sense contents already.
No.
I built it myself from the ground up.
Just like what you did with your hotel.
Tim!
I will prove it to you...
that what I do...
is not worthless.
All my life...
you and mom always chose the path for me
and it's enough.
Now I want to choose my own path.
Please excuse me.
You gave me a fright.
What happened?
Just same old stuff.
With your dad again?
Do you want me to talk to him?
He wouldn't understand.
I'll handle it myself.
It's okay.
I'm sure one day your dad will understand
and accept the path you choose.
Until that day comes...
I'll be here for you...
and support you like I always do.
I don't know what to say to you
except thank you...
and thank you.
What's this?
Are you feeling sentimental lately?
Nope.
I really mean it.
Ever since the day you became my friend
all the way until today...
you've always been by my side.
You always support me on whatever I want to do
among other things.
You made me feel like I'm the luckiest man.
For that, I thank you.
Come on.
Don't be so sentimental.
You're gonna make me cry.
I'm tired.
Can I recharge my battery?
With a power source like you,
I can never get enough.
Kim.
Why do you come home so late?
I went to Bomb's bar earlier.
You went to party with your friends?
Yes.
And...
How are you today?
How was your first day at work?
What is your job position?
Which company do you work for?
I'm just a regular office worker.
Do they pay you well?
Can I be excused?
I have to wake up early tomorrow.
Kim, wait.
Do you want anything special for breakfast?
Whatever Q likes.
I can eat everything.
Honey.
Why don't you come to bed?
I'm thinking about Kim.
Do you think I'm a bad mother?
It's his first day at work
and I didn't know.
No, you're not.
You just found out a little late.
That's all.
I'm afraid that he and I are getting estranged.
And he's a person who thinks a lot about everything.
Don't worry.
Kim is all grown up now.
He's at the age where he would want
to make decisions himself.
You can't treat him like a child anymore.
If he wants to tell you something, he'll tell you.
You really think so?
When you make a proposal for a client,
you need to have a main idea first.
You must study the client.
Learn about what they want.
Then list them out.
One, two, three, four, five.
- One, two, three, four, five.
- Exactly.
Make a list.
Yes, like that.
Kim.
I have a big assignment for you.
I want you to be in charge of Mr. Mega's account.
You must take on this client.
And your probation will be evaluated by it.
I'll give you his contact info.
You can reach him right after.
You think you can handle it?
Yes, I can.
Nui.
Hmm?
Do you know who this Mega guy is?
Mr. Mega is a landscape artist.
But no one has ever seen his face.
I heard he's a difficult to work with.
And most importantly, he's very thorough.
What should I do?
It's my first account and I already got a tough client.
Darling.
Don't lose your confidence just yet.
When you work for tough clients,
you need to think harder.
Try to figure out how you can win him over.
I've been there.
WIth tough clients,
once you understand their nature...
things will get easier.
But I've never had such experience.
There's always a first time for everything.
I believe you can do it.
Don't give up.
Fighto!
That's the right attitude!
Okay.
Go on.
Do what I taught you.
Landscape.
[An up-and-coming landscape artist
who made a debut in Australia.
He never shows his face to the press.]
"Dear Mr. Mega,"
"My name is Kimhan."
"I'll be your coordinator for this project."
"If there's anything you need,"
"please don't hesitate to let me know."
"Best regards,
Kimhan."
Kimhan!
Yes, Orn.
Did you send an e-mail to Mr. Mega?
Y...yes.
What's wrong with it?
Did you know he filed a complaint?
You didn't check the time to be in contact with him.
Didn't I tell you to study him first!?
The time in Australia now is...
He's in the U.S. now.
He's having an exhibition in New York.
Next time, if you don't know, ask me first.
So you don't make a mess like this again.
I am sorry.
How was your work today?
It was good.
Kim.
I know you're tired. Come eat this.
I made you your favorite dish.
It's fine.
I already had a meal.
Kim.
He told me his flight is tomorrow.
Not anymore.
He'll have a meeting with us today.
"When will you be home?"
Babe, why do you come home so late?
I've just finished my editing.
You must be exhausted.
Come.
Let me make you feel better.
I can't. I'm too tired.
You don't have to do anything.
I'll do it for you.
I'm really tired, babe.
Let's do it another time.
Okay.
Thanks for understanding.
I'll go take a shower.
Is the meal too bland?
It's okay.
- Not too bland?
- Nope.
Kim.
You're heading out now?
Yes, dad.
Have breakfast with us first.
No, thank you.
Let's have dinner together then.
I don't think I can.
Is there anything troubling you?
No.
You don't have to worry, mom.
Kim.
If work is too much, you can take a break.
I said I'm okay.
Please excuse me.
He's probably in a hurry.
Come on, honey, let's finish this up.
Don't think too much.
Kim.
Why didn't you pick up Mr. Mega yesterday?
Pick up?
Pick him up where?
At the airport, of course!
Do I have to tell you everything?
He made a complaint again
because no one was there to take care of him.
He told me his flight would land tomorrow.
And that he would come directly to our meeting.
Not anymore.
He'll come and have a meeting with us today.
Oh, here he is.
Mr. Mega, please have a seat.
Our boss will be here in a few minutes.
Mr. Rich, this is Mr. Mega, our new client.
You can call me Mek.
Oh.
Why do you use the name "Mega" then?
It comes from my first name, Meka.
Let me start by introducing our team.
This is Mr. Rich, our big boss.
On this side, this is Kimhan.
Our new AE who will be taking care of you.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Rich.
Nice to meet you...
Mr. Kimhan.
Nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you too, Mr. Mek.
I'm so delighted to have you as our client.
I'm gonna need a lot of your help.
And I expect a lot from you guys.
You don't need to worry.
Anything you want,
you can let our team know right away.
I want to raise public awareness on my work.
My trees. My gardens.
Not who I am.
As you know, I want to keep my identity private.
Sure.
Our team will work on that.
It's my pleasure to work with you.
I'm looking forward to our collaboration, Kimhan.
From now, I'm gonna need a lot of support from you.
"Can I have today's meeting report?"
"I already sent it to you."
"I can't find it."
"Can you send it to me again?"
"Can't you wait until tomorrow?"
"Sure. I can wait."
"I want more ideas from the creative team."
"I want you to contact the organizer for me."
"I want to see their portfolio."
"Please answer me!"
"Hello?"
"Kim."
"?????"
"This lunch, I want medium-rare ribeye steak with caesar salad."
"There's no restaurant that serves steak around here."
"Can't you find one for me?"
"Sure. I'll find one for you."
Okay, I'll stop working.
I'll give you my full attention.
All night?
All night.
I don't believe you.
Try me.
Why does he have to bully me like that!?
I'm already doing my best!
I think I've listened to you enough.
Who's bullying you?
Mek!
- Mek?
He's now my client.
This world is so small.
Indeed.
It's exactly like what happens in those TV series.
And what did you do?
Didn't you feel happy at all to meet him again?
And he's bullying you?
How did you respond?
I didn't do anything.
My company sees clients as gods.
So I just pleased him as he wished.
Guys, I have something to talk to you.
It's about Park.
You want us to help you
tone down your sweet couple life?
No.
I just think...
Park is probably seeing someone else.
And I'm about to propose to him.
You really are something.
But I don't think Park can ever cheat on you.
He seems to be consistent and truly in love with you.
I'm not sure but...
lately, he's been avoiding intimacy.
Also...
He seems to have something going on behind my back.
But nothing has happened.
Don't be anxious about it.
Look at me.
All these fans come to see Bear.
Everyone here in my bar is his fans.
I want him to chase them away
but he won't do it.
I mean, why would he do that?
If one day he falls for his fan,
what am supposed to do?
I'm sure he won't date his own fan.
Well, he's dating me.
I used to be in his fan club, too.
You told me not to think too much.
But you're the one with a wild imagination here.
What else am I supposed to do then?
I can't help but feel jealous.
How was it?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
I need to go now.
I'll make a cup of coffee.
"I don't think Park can ever cheat on you."
"He seems to be consistent and truly in love with you."
Lee.
Would you marry me?
No.
You don't want to marry me?
No. No. No.
I mean, it shouldn't happen this way.
Why did you ask me before I do?
My plan is ruined now.
It's all okay, my love.
This is nice.
It means we think alike.
But I want to be the one who proposes.
I'll take that as a yes then.
Mm.
Yes!
Shouldn't you say anything
before putting the ring on my finger?
I don't want to say anything.
I prefer doing something else.
Bear, come see this!
Park has proposed to Lee!
Here.
Bear.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You're all about work and work and work!
Go live with your fans.
Don't waste your time with me.
I'm so sorry!
Don't be mad at me.
I'm not mad.
I told you the truth.
Alright, then...
I'll stop working now.
I'll give my full attention to you.
How does that sound?
All night?
All night.
I don't believe you.
Try me.
After receiving your feedback last time,
our team has taken your comments and got the plan revised.
Since you don't want to reveal your identity,
I decided to propose my ideas to the creatives,
suggesting that we should showcase your works
through a terrarium garden video.
That means only your hands
and your work will be displayed on the video.
Next, let me show you our presentation.
Well...
We did some research and found that you have a hobby
of making terrarium gardens.
For me, I think it's a lovely and relatable activity.
And that concludes our presentation today.
From what you presented,
I'm okay with the idea about the video.
But about the script for magazine interviews,
it still looks redundant to me.
Have you considered cutting some parts?
I think I'll keep all of them but shorten the words.
But we need to focus on the main point.
So readers will get our message.
I think you can discuss that internally.
From what I've seen, it's thorough enough.
You have done well with your research.
Orn, I think...
I do think  some of it can still be improved.
And I want Mek to share his idea with us,
so maybe it's better that we discuss it here.
Well then, in my opinion...
I think Kim's research is what makes this project go smoothly.
If it wasn't for him,
all those ideas would still be scattered
and not this well-arranged.
And I disagree about cutting the script.
Because I was the one who told him to put those parts in.
Got it.
In short, I like it and I prefer Kim's approach.
Anyone wants to argue with that?
We all agree with you.
If you like it, I like it.
Well done, Kim.
Thank you.
If there's nothing further,
I'd like to end our meeting here.
Mr. Rich, since Kim has done a great job today,
we should go celebrate.
Sure.
Let's also make it a welcome party for him.
Mek, would you like to join us?
You know what they say, the more, the merrier!
Sure, if you don't mind.
No, not at all!
It's our pleasure to have you with us.
Where should we celebrate then?
I'm so tired of these fancy restaurants.
I have a place to recommend.
It's a casual place to chill out.
Sounds great!
Cheers!
Cheers to our Kimhan's success!
Bottoms up!
It's a pity Mr. Rich couldn't come with us.
Although our boss is not here with us,
his credit card is!
We can go full force. No worries!
Kim, may I ask you one thing?
I heard that...
back in college...
you and Mek were paired up as a BL couple.
Is that true?
- Well...
- Yes.
But it was just for show.
We were never a real couple.
It was just a job.
Nothing special.
Oh, I see.
He's right.
There was nothing special about it at all.
In fact,
he didn't even like me.
We actually hated each other.
Look who's talking.
Old habits die hard. Both of them.
I can't with you two.
Let by gones be bygones.
Don't let the past ruin great vibes here.
Let's drink. Cheers!
Drink up so you guys will be fond of each other after this.
If you can't get along with Kim,
you can get along with me instead.
Cheers!
Bottoms up!
Want another drink?
Yes.
Let's go on!
You said you didn't have feelings for me.
Why do you still keep it?
Do you still love me?
I never stop loving you.
Kim.
But today's our anniversary.
Why did you agree to the job?
You forgot it, didn't you?
I'm sorry, Bomb.
I just want you to find time for me.
Back then, why did you push me away?
Because I love you.
I didn't want you to hesitate because of me.
Kim, you're the only one...
...that I never hesitate to choose.