The people, places, organizations, events,
groups and professionals
depicted in this program are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Do you know who this Mega guy is?
He's a landscape artist.
No one has ever seen his face, though.
You said you didn't love me.
Why do you still keep it?
I've never not loved you.
Well, well.
Look who's finally calling me.
How are you? Have you got settled yet?
I'm getting used to the life here.
I even almost got into a fight with kangaroos.
I miss you guys so much.
Oh, you do?
I remember someone said he didn't want to go to Australia
because there're no friends like us over there.
By the way...
Are you dating someone?
I'm not ready to open my heart to anyone yet.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
At first, Bomb and I wanted to keep it a secret.
But judging from your condition now,
I think I should tell you.
What is it?
The thing is...
before you left...
I dropped by Thong's restaurant.
And...
he told me that...
Hey, Kim.
Why are you here alone?
Where is Mek?
I haven't seen you for several days so I haven't got a chance to ask.
On that day...
Did you drop him off at the front door?
Or did you go all the way up to his room?
Kim, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
You can tell me.
I don't know if I did the right thing.
I let him go,
so he can pursue his dream.
I don't want him to hesitate because of me.
Was it really the right thing to do?
It's okay.
Did I make the right decision?
Easy, Kim.
I think the reason Kim went to Thong's
is because he had no one to talk to about this matter.
If he'd told us,
you would have found out.
If he'd talked to Q,
Dao would have found out.
I feel so bad for him.
Bomb, which company is Kim currently working at?
Why did you ask that?
I'm going to go see Kim.
[FLUK
Chatchawal]
[EARTH
Teerapat]
[BEW
Sitthikarn]
[DANIEL
Cheng Yu Chang]
[BOAT
Yongyut]
[KENJI
Siwarut]
[POR
Passakorn]
[YUT
Kritsadayut]
[Directed by
NATTHAMON YIMYAM]
[The end of secret love]
Kim.
Are you awake, son?
Kimhan...
If you have anything to say, just say it, mom.
Why did you say that?
I'm not giving you a telling-off.
I thought you wanted to talk about him.
I'm sorry...
for disappointing you.
Kim.
I never expect anything from you.
When it comes to love and relationship,
the decision is yours to make.
Still, one thing that I feel sorry about
and really want to get straight with you is...
the fact that you never talk to me about anything.
You see, I've always asked you questions.
But it's not because I want to interfere with your life.
I just want to know how you are doing.
You think I don't know...
how much you're stressed about work?
This is your first job.
I know what kind of a person my son is.
I'm sorry, mom.
I just thought that...
you always ask me questions because...
you have expectations for me.
Before this, I always had my life all planned out.
I do want to help lessen your burden, mom.
But as I grow up,
life hasn't turned out the way I planned
Just getting through each day...
is already hard enough.
It's okay, sweetie.
I never want to pressure you.
No matter what your job position is or how much you get paid,
I never want your money.
I just want you to fill me in sometimes.
You don't have to tell me everything.
All I want to know is whether my son is feeling happy or not.
Can you do that for me?
Yes, I can.
That'll do.
Come on. Let me give you a hug.
My son.
You always think too much.
Smile for me.
Look at this handsome boy!
I really am sorry.
It's okay, my dear.
Let's eat, shall we?
You too.
Have breakfast with us.
Thank you.
What's your name?
My name is Mek.
Mek.
Next time you come here,
make sure you do it properly, okay?
So I'll know what goes on.
Don't worry, I'm not going to mess with your personal life.
You too, Kim. Got it?
- Yes.
I must apologize to you, ma'am.
Never mind.
You two are grown-ups now.
I'm sure you can take care of yourself.
By the way, what do you do?
Where's your home? Who are your parents?
I'm a landscape artist.
I'm currently working on terrarium projects.
Terrarium? I see.
Well...
We never met before, but I actually live next door.
Your place is just right here.
Why didn't you stay at your house last night?
Are you two dating?
Enjoy your meal.
Feel free to tell me whenever you're ready.
Here. Son-in-law egg.
Do you like it?
I do.
I do like it very much.
I was talking about the egg.
Do you like it?
I like it too.
Mek.
You better hurry up.
Or you'll be late for work.
You still didn't eat that.
I did. A tiny bit.
You're still not going?
Can I get a hug?
Have a nice day.
Sure.
Oh!
Mek.
Why are you here so early?
- Good morning, Nui.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
I...
I'm looking for a pen.
Just a pen? You could've just called.
We could get one for you.
I don't see any pen around here.
I should get going.
Okay.
Bye.
Next time, you can just come looking for me instead of pens.
Kim!
Mek is so cute, don't you think?
Well, he's kinda so-so.
I did some digging on his background.
He's the son of a resort owner.
Hot. Stylish. Classy.
Basically a whole package.
Anyone who has him as their boyfriend is so lucky!
I guess so.
Right?
With that kind of artistic temperament...
I'm sure he's still single.
And he's probably hard to approach.
I think I might have a chance with him.
Because I'm beautiful.
I heard he's dating someone, though.
Huh?!
He's already in a relationship?!
Mm.
Oh my.
You know what...
ever since I started working,
he's the first guy
who's made my heart beat so fast.
Why, oh why?
Why can't you be single?
I heard the person he's seeing is cute too.
Say no more!
Guess I'm gonna have to go back and just focus on my work.
The world is so unfair to a pretty girl like me.
Who is his date? Do you know their Instagram account?
I have no idea.
I already bought movie tickets and reserved a table at your favorite restaurant.
Why did you chase me away like that?
Because I love you.
[We're closed today.
The owner is taking a leave to go crazy in love.]
See you later, Bomb.
Where are you going?
Well, I have a shoot today.
I'm scheduled to do a review video.
But today's our anniversary day.
Why did you agree to the job?
You forgot it, didn't you?
I'm sorry, Bomb.
I got the dates mixed up.
My work schedule is completely messy.
What should we do then?
I already bought movie tickets
and reserved a table at your favorite restaurant.
Well...
I'll just go and finish the shoot real quick then.
I'm sure I can get back in time.
Today's a very important day.
I can't miss it.
Please don't be mad at me.
I'll come back in time for sure.
Don't be mad at me, okay?
I'm not mad.
I just want you to make time for me.
I know.
I won't let it happen again.
I promise!
I better get to work now.
"I suspect Bear forgot our anniversary."
"Apparently, he agreed to a job today."
"What a bummer!"
"If I let him know that I'm upset,
I'll look like a fussy boyfriend."
"When it comes to relationship, it's important that you can accept the bad side of your partner as well."
"Or maybe you can just talk it out with him."
"Agreed."
"Don't be too upset."
Congratulations, Kim!
You have passed your probation.
Really?
Yes!
Thank you!
Well done!
You did a great job.
Thanks to you,
Mek has now signed a contract with us.
And our company will handle all of his projects from now.
You did an excellent job, Kim.
Orn, how about we go celebrate today?
Well, Boss already gave us his credit card.
What should we eat then?
How about something expensive?
I'm sorry, Kimhan.
I'm afraid you can't join us.
Why is that?
Here.
Because you must go...
have a meeting with Mek.
Actually, I was supposed to go.
But he requested you specifically.
Life is so unfair.
Orn, let's get something to eat, shall we?
Why didn't he pick me?
Have some extra portion for me then.
We won't!
"Kim, make sure not to be late."
Mr. Mek is ready to see you now.
Thank you.
What are you doing, Mek?
You are being so extra getting me here.
You and I haven't got a chance to catch up
about the past two years.
There's nothing to talk about.
Stop being so stubborn.
Why did you chase me away like that?
Why did you do it?
Because I love you.
I didn't want you to hesitate because of me.
You had the chance to follow your dream.
You should not waste your time hesitating.
Do you remember...
you once said that...
when you hesitate about something,
that means you care about it?
Kim, you're the only one...
that I've never hesitated to choose.
You mean so much to me.
And I love you too.
Mek, can you be my boyfriend?
All these years...
I missed you so much.
And now...
I don't want lose you ever again.
Please don't leave me anymore.
Stay with me, will you?
I'll never leave you again.
No matter how hard you try to shun me away,
I will never go away from you.
Mek.
Would you like to live together with me?
I don't want to have the fence between us any longer.
I, too, don't want anything
to come between us again.
Mek!
What are you doing?
Why do you have to be so extra?
Since I am going to be your boyfriend,
I need to be a little bit extra.
Let's go.
Thank you so much for having us.
So you'll send the footage to me later?
I need to forward it to our editor.
Yes.
I'll upload the footage for you ASAP.
Thank you so much.
Long day, huh?
I could hear you sigh all the way from there.
It's nothing.
I just felt that...
what I did...
may not get dad's approval.
You have to take a shot.
When you put your heart into something,
it can never go to waste.
I'll help during the editing process.
I'll check if there's any more image...
or information to be added.
Okay.
Keep your chin up.
You've been doing well with your channel.
You are not going to fail with this hotel content, I'm sure.
This time, I have to prove myself to my dad.
That's why I'm not feeling so confident.
You've done a great job so far.
And this content...
is based on the thing that's very personal to you.
You've grown up with it.
There's no way it can go wrong.
Whenever you feel like giving up,
just look at me.
I'm always here.
Indeed you are.
You're feeling better now, yes?
Not yet, actually.
Satisfied now?
Are you hungry?
How about we grab something to eat first
so you can take a shower right away
when we get home?
Sounds good.
Let's grab something to eat.
We're already closed, Mr. Tim.
Oh.
But you're not usually closed at this hour.
We sincerely apologize.
A guest has rented out the whole place
to surprise his boyfriend.
He's over there.
Would you like to go say hi?
Nah.
I'll just let them have a good time.
Look at them.
They are smiling from ear to ear.
What kind of hotel owner can't get into his own property?
Are you hungry much?
Yeah, a little.
I can just eat at our condo.
But I'm not talking about food.
You're unbelievable!
Where are you going?
So you two walked in here hand-in-hand
to ask for my permission to move in together?
Our houses are not close enough for you?
"Hello, Bomb."
"I'm at the restaurant."
"Why is it closed?"
Bear.
Our reservation was at 8pm.
It's almost midnight now.
The restaurant is closed at 10pm.
I was waiting for you for two hours
until the staff asked me to leave.
"Where are you now?"
"I'll come pick you up."
I'm home now.
"I'm so sorry, Bomb."
"I'll be there in a minute."
You don't have to.
I know you've had a long day.
I understand.
I have to go now.
[We're closed today.
The owner is taking a leave to go crazy in love.]
I...
I'm sorry, Bomb.
It's okay.
What is this?
So you two walked in here hand-in-hand
to ask for my permission to move in together?
Our houses are not close enough for you?
You see?
I'm sharing things with you here, mom.
I didn't want to do this behind your back.
Where are you two gonna live?
Are you sure you can take care of each other?
How can I be sure that you will be okay?
You don't have to worry, ma'am.
When you were away,
I always took care of Kim.
Now I remember.
Q did tell me about
how you two were a BL couple.
So you're that guy?
Now I get it.
I saw your picture on the t-shirt I washed.
Yes, that was me.
I've been courting your son for a while.
So...
Are you going to let me live with him?
It's no different from living in a dorm.
Please, please, please.
Please, mom.
Please.
Kim.
You used to tell me...
about how you and dad ran away together, remember?
You were around my age now, weren't you?
It's time for me to do that too.
You really are something!
Who taught you bring up my past?
Since you are begging me this hard,
if I don't allow it, I suppose you'll end up running away together.
Look!
Someone's already prepared his luggages.
Why don't you just leave already?
Can I really?
I'm kidding.
Go.
Enjoy your life together.
Mek, please take care of Kim for me.
Take good care of Kim.
Sure I will.
Thank you so much, mom.
I'll see you later.
That's a lot of stuff over there.
Are you going to live there forever?
Well...
I'll call you when I get there.
Bear, can you go see who's at the door?
Bear.
"Please, read this."
"I have nothing to say except 'I'm sorry'."
"I'm sorry for keeping you waiting."
"I'm sorry for being negligent."
"I'm sorry for making you sad."
"And I'm sorry for being too cute."
"Yay! You're finally smiling.
I'm the one who makes you smile, right?"
"But I can smile because of my fans."
"And there's one particular fan
whom I want to dedicate myself to."
"Because this fan lights up my soul each and every day."
"Do you want to know who this fan is?"
"It's this one."
You're always important to me, Bomb.
I am sorry
that I let my work ruin things for us.
I will improve myself.
I will foster a better work-life balance.
Can you forgive me, Bomb?
Mm.
"Papa Bear has just asked me to forgive him. So cute!"
"I'm happy that you two finally made up."
"By the way, Park and I will buy a house together."
"Really?"
"You two have been together for so long.
This is the right time."
"Anyway, I have something to tell you guys."
"I'm excited."
"Mek and I are official now."
"Also..."
"We've moved in together."
How about we have green curry as usual?
That sounds great.
But this time...
you don't have to do anything.
I'll take care of it.
I can do it.
It's okay.
Just sit and wait.
I can do it.
It's done.
Careful, it's hot.
Is it that bad?
You're scaring me.
How is Somchai today?
He doesn't look so fresh.
Mek, what are you doing?
Mek, stop it!
Mek!
Enough!
Give it to me.
Why would I?
Let me have it.
Give me.
Don't try to hide!
You're the cutest.
Oh, my God!
Seriously?
I have a question.
How did you guys become Thunderous Sky?
Now, it's time for the grooms...
to exchange heir vows.
Seriously?
Even in the office's elevator?
Can you please stop it?
You're acting like a kid.
Look who's talking.
My friend has really changed.
Starting from Mek of Thunderous Sky...
now he's Meka, the landscape artist.
Now that you brought that up,
I do miss the old days.
We sure were a piece of work.
It's been almost 7 years now, right?
Do you think there are any Hailstones left?
Why?
Are you saying that you miss the fans?
It just occurred to me.
I wonder how they are now.
Park.
When is your wedding?
Next month.
I only invite close friends.
Park.
Do let me know if you need any help.
Right. I asked you because I want to help.
[Absolute Tim  channel is still going strong as Tim steps in to run his family's hotel business.
The family didn't support his content-creator endeavor at first but with support from his boyfriend, Mai, he can finally make it happen.]
The food is served!
Looks yummy.
I made the dish myself.
It was a practice so I can cook for you in the future.
So you'll no longer have to buy takeaways.
I think you and Park should become relationship coaches.
You've been together for so long
but things between you two still look fresh as ever.
Or perhaps you should write a book about it.
You're exaggerating.
Not at all!
Can I take your order?
Enjoy, guys.
This meal is on Lee.
Cheers!
I have a question.
How did you guys become Thunderous Sky?
Hello, I'm Mek of Thunderous Sky channel.
I'll take you guys to meet my new friends.
Hello. What's your name?
Where are you from? Please introduce yourself to my viewers.
I'm Bear. Freshman. Comm Arts.
I'm a fan of Thunderous Sky channel.
Really?
Now you're my first university friend.
Nice to meet you, Bear!
Nice to meet you, Mek.
Do you really like my channel?
Yeah!
How about this?
Since you enjoy my channel,
why don't you join me?
Really? Can I?
Of course.
But...
You must pass the test first.
You have to come up with one prank content.
Sure, my friend!
You look like a real ghost.
Anyone who sees you would be so spooked!
Someone is coming.
Let's go hide.
Boo!
You're not spooked at all?
If I were a real ghost, I'd be out of the job by now.
You should thank me for not laughing actually.
Dude, you have such a strong mentality.
You're not afraid of ghosts?
No.
I saw you guys prepare for this during lunch time.
One more thing...
I watch Thunderous Sky channel too.
Wonderful!
It's a gathering of like-minded people here!
So your name's Park?
Would you like to join our gang?
How many people are there in your gang?
Just me and Bear.
You guys have the audacity to call it a gang.
So, will you join us?
Mm.
Count me in.
That's right!
Thunderous Sky.
Bang!
I'm not surprised you guys get along so well.
Anyway, I have to thank Thunderous Sky.
Why?
This channel brought us together.
And it made me...
love you like a bang!
Bang!
Told ya...
You're gonna love me like a bang!
Since today is a special day,
I decided to bring your perfume with me.
Every time I smell this scent,
it brought me back to the wonderful moments
that we've had together.
You know,
it makes me love you more and more every day.
Ready?
Let's go.
Congratulations.
I wish you a lifetime of happiness.
Now, it's time for the grooms...
to exchange their vows.
I'd like to thank you...
for making me so happy
from the first day
to this very moment.
No matter how life changes
for you...
I will never change.
I always miss you
even though you never leave my side.
I feel grateful
that we always understand each other
even with the smallest things.
Lee...
Whether it is 7 years,
20 years,
or for the rest of my life...
I will always be your Park
who blushes red and gets flustered
and who feels happy every time he's with you.
I suppose this is the beauty of the ceremony.
Because even though you're just a guest,
you can't help but feel emotional
and happy for them
so much that you shed tears of joy.
Why are you sitting here all alone?
Don't you want to take pictures with your friends?
I was just letting my mind wander.
What were you thinking about?
I was thinking about the first time we met.
It was awkward, wasn't it?
Back then...
Nothing seemed to work out for us.
But look at us now.
It finally works out thanks to both of us.
We fulfill each other.
If it wasn't for you,
I'd still be a brat
who can't take charge of his life.
You're the only one
who truly understands me.
You make me feel so warm.
You're not the only one who feels that way.
I also feel warm every time
I have you by my side.
I've learned...
how to let go
and go easy on myself.
Or sometimes,
just thinking of you
or...
the things you do for me
is enough to make me happy.
Every time I look at you,
there's always this thought at the back of my head.
I think I want to be with you forever.
Are you reserving me for yourself?
No.
I'm keeping you with me for good.
Look at Mek.
He's stealing the spotlight for himself
right here at Park's wedding.
That's okay. I allow it.
Kim, I think I'll have to throw the flower bouquet to you then.
Kim, would you marry me?