In 1974 B.E.,
in the reign of
King Borommaracha Thirat II,
the Ayothaya royal court
seized the territory of Sukhothai
and has expanded its power
across the highlands
to the east.
After a seven-month siege,
Ayothaya captured the divine city.
One year and three months later...
Take care of yourself, young master.
Shoot!
Get the boy.
Hey! Stop!
Go!
Go! Faster!
Faster!
Go!
Hurry up!
Faster!
Move!
Hey! Come down quickly!
Get down!
Hey!
Let me go!
Let go!
Hey!
Let go of me!
I said let me go!
This boy is the next one.
-Hey! Go!
-Let go of me!
Move!
He's the next fighter.
Hey!
I will give you a chance, kid.
Let's see if you can make it out alive.
Hey! Let's start.
Begin!
Hey!
Your life
depends on yourself, kid.
Tien.
I want to be a great warrior
like my father.
How long will you be away?
I hate you!
Father!
Is this the boy?
That's right, Father Sengpa.
A light in his eyes
when he was fighting
reminded me of someone.
Even the spirits don't dare to touch him.
He has a powerful destiny.
His hands.
Whenever he holds a weapon,
he will be the best of the best.
I'm Chernung.
I'm leader of
the Garuda Wing Cliff outlaws.
I am impressed
by your brave and unyielding
fight with the crocodile.
If you want to train your weapon skills
and learn about martial arts at my camp,
I will allow you to.
If you don't want to stay
and will go elsewhere,
I will not stop you.
Shoot!
Unite your body and soul.
Merge the rules of weapons.
Set your mind on the path of power.
That is what you need to practice.
Each weapon has its own
strength and weakness.
Long or short.
Sharp or blunt. Soft or hard.
Light or heavy.
A weapon
is a tangible form of power.
Anyone who can merge
his body and soul with it
will possess the greatest power.
The world and everyone in it
will yield to your power.
I, Chernung,
leader of the Garuda Wing Cliff outlaws
have given you a new life.
From now on,
you will always remember
that you are one of
the Garuda Wing Cliff outlaws.
In the test of
agility and cleverness,
Tien passes.
The next challenge
is the test of
fighting.
Yes!
That's what I'm talking about, my son!
This place
will test the power of your mind.
Help me!
Let me go!
Don't be afraid of me.
Don't be afraid.
I will set you free.
Come with me.
I will help you.
Don't be afraid.
Your life
depends on yourself.
Killing
and being merciless
are the last things
a leader must learn.
My people, my children!
Now,
the deity from heaven
has sent this black-tusk elephant
as a sign of blessing
and auspicious glory
of the king of elephants.
This magic animal
will bring prosperity
to our community.
Yeah!
Now,
I, Chernung,
hereby proclaim that
in all raids
and from now on,
Tien
will replace me
as leader.
Why doesn't Dad teach me
the art of weaponry?
I don't want to learn the dancing art.
I don't want to go.
I want to be with Dad.
You have to go study, you know?
So you'll be a great man.
Believe me, my son.
Pay respect to Master Bua.
You have had a long journey.
Let's go inside.
It's been more than three months
since Ayothaya took control
of the vassal states.
The situation in the capital
is still in disorder.
But the Crown Prince
is behaving impetuously.
The royal command
has been given to me
to suppress resistance
in the protectorate territories.
Ayothaya is in such a rush
to expand its power.
Didn't the city administrator,
Lord Rajasena,
seek to oppose the Crown Prince?
Everything
was Lord Rajasena's idea.
Power is terrifying.
But those who abuse power
are even more terrifying.
This country will be aflame.
Innocent people
in every corner will suffer.
In this uncertain situation,
only to you and the master
of this distant land
can I entrust
my son's life.
Brother Bua.
I feel like my heart has been pulled out.
May you take pity on me
and take care of him?
I will try my best.
You take care of yourselves as well.
Muen Sri. Luang Krai.
Take us out now.
Yes, sir.
My name is Pim.
My parents are both dead.
Master Bua
has raised me since I was a baby.
How about you?
My father is Siha Decho.
He's one of the four Eastern commanders
of Ayothaya.
I told my father
I wanted to learn about weapons
and fighting,
to be a great warrior like him.
But instead,
he brought me here to learn about dance.
How can I fight anyone then?
What a hoarse flute.
Mhen!
Huh?
Oh, itchy. Scratching your balls too?
I'm not itchy. Why am I scratching?
Huh?
I have it too. The same.
Throw it up.
Huh? Throw it away too.
Throw.
Spin. Spin.
Oh.
He disappeared?
Oh, he's really gone.
Gone.
Tien.
Do you think a person
who learns about weapons
can bring peace to the land?
I only think that
learning about weapons
to protect myself,
to help good people
and vanquish bad people,
should contribute to bringing about peace.
Good.
Well said.
Tien.
There are a lot of weapons in this world.
Which one will you use
to help your people and country?
You don't have to answer me now.
Take it.
Let the slave trade begin.
-Hey, come here. Come.
-Let me go!
Mom!
Let me go! My son!
My son!
-Go!
-My son!
-Mom!
-Go!
Hey! Silence!
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Ouch!
You bitch!
Mom!
Who the hell?
Was it you?
You?
Hey!
You want to drink?
Huh?
Drink it! Drink! Drink! Drink! Drink!
Come here!
Please spare my life.
I don't want to die. I have money.
I have gold and slaves.
You can take them all if you want.
Okay.
I'll give you a chance.
Like the one you gave to me.
-Throw him into the crocodile pit!
-Huh?
No!
I don't want to die!
I don't want to die.
Release all the slaves.
My son.
It's all right now. Don't cry.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Tien.
How long will you be away?
Are you really leaving, Tien?
Who will play with me if you're gone?
I won't let you go, Tien! Tien, don't go!
Don't you worry.
I'll be back soon.
Hurry, young master. We'll be late.
I have to go.
Tien!
Why are we in such a hurry?
Luang Krai!
Where are you taking the young master?
How dare you betray the commander?
Traitor!
Young master, get away!
You!
Yah!
Let go!
Let me go!
Let me go! Let go!
Let go of me!
Dad!
Let me go!
Let me go! I said let me go!
Dad! Don't fight him!
Let me go! I said let me go! Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Let me go.
You will die like your master!
Rajasena! You bastard tyrant!
Kill him!
Dad!
Get him!
Take care of yourself, young master.
Shoot!
Get the boy.
Are you sure?
The day I met you at the crocodile pit,
you reminded me of someone.
That someone
was me when I was young.
That day...
your eyes were sun-parched.
The light in your eyes was strong
like fire in the wind.
Today,
it still shines in your eyes.
Actually,
I was going to make you
the outlaw leader today.
But since you have
something on your mind,
you should go and finish it.
I...
and everyone at Garuda Wing Cliff...
will be awaiting your return.
Yah!
Honorable governors,
ministers,
royal advisors
and valiant commanders.
Now is an auspicious time
destined by heaven.
I,
as the first monarch
of the Garuda Deva dynasty,
shall commence the holy ritual
to pay homage to this divine monument.
It shall stand as a symbol of the power
of the Garuda Deva dynasty
forever and a day.
This is for my mother.
Guards!
This is for my father,
Lord Siha Decho!
Guards!
Father Chernung!
I have returned!
My blood is not for your sword to drink.
Guards, you don't have to waste
your energy.
I have someone who wants to kill him,
who has been waiting.
Now, the clan of Siha Decho
has been wiped out.
The only one left is his son.
He is standing right there.
You shall hurry to finish
what you still owe me.
Father.
A king shall never go back on his word.
Your Majesty must keep your promise
and spare the lives of my people...
whether I live or die.
The man in black in front of you
is the one who killed your father.
Kill him.
Kill him!
If you still have your strength.
Rebel!
Your clan deserves to be exterminated.
Had I known you were one of them,
I would've killed you long ago.
I'm the one
who killed your father!
Let me repay your father's life
with mine,
my dear son.
Chernung!
Take him away.
But don't let him die too quickly.
Punish him and make him suffer.
Put him through the pain he deserves
until his last breath.
Tien's life has come to an end
because of his cursed karma.
If you all
could unite the power of your minds,
your strength of faith,
to prolong his life,
then his mind can be released from torment
and return to his body.
Subtitle translation by:
Chaimas Sainampueng