He's the next fighter.
I'm Chernung.
I'm leader of
the Garuda Wing Cliff outlaws.
My blood is not for your sword to drink.
The man in black in front of you
is the one who killed your father.
I'm the one who killed your father!
Let me repay your father's life
with mine,
my dear son.
Chernung!
According to the law of this land,
all his rights have been revoked.
This rebel shall receive 13 punishments
until he breathes no longer.
Start the punishment.
Crush every one of his bones.
Let him follow his vicious father to hell.
Add one part sweet sedge
and three parts salt.
Don't forget to
put in some chili peppers.
The angels will protect you.
You'll get well soon.
Hey. Take a look at each patient.
Why do they have similar symptoms?
Hey. Don't you know? They were cursed.
I see. That's why Master Bua
made a pilgrimage to the mountain
to find a way to break the curse.
The curse. The curse.
-Mhen, go away!
-Go! Mhen!
-Go! Go away!
-What the hell?
I wasn't making any trouble, you guys.
Tien.
Are you really leaving, Tien?
Who will play with me if you're gone?
I won't let you go, Tien!
I won't let you go!
I curse you.
You will meet a calamitous, miserable end.
Let this decree be uttered
with these sacred words,
in front of all the gods
who bear witness to this holy ritual.
For those who are loyal to me,
may the gods protect them.
But anyone who thinks of betraying me
and this land shall be cursed
to meet a calamitous, miserable end
and shall be tormented forever.
-What's wrong with you?
-Dad, what wrong?
-Dad! Dad!
-Help!
I curse you.
You will meet a calamitous, miserable end.
I curse you!
Your fighting skill is terrific.
Great fighters like you
are difficult to find.
If you come to work for me at the palace,
I will grant you everything you wish for.
What royal grace
you've bestowed upon me.
But I...
desire nothing from you, Your Highness.
Take your reward.
And remember,
you are not in any position to negotiate.
You're just a crow.
How dare you negotiate
with a King Garuda like me?
Have you been having nightmares lately?
The curse in your nightmare
will haunt you for the rest of your life.
He is the one who brings the curse.
Only I can break that curse.
You must come to me. You must come to me!
Cut off this rebel's head tomorrow.
Executioner.
Kill him.
Halt the execution!
Bow to the Royal Decree!
I have come to take this prisoner
by the command of the King of Ayothaya.
How could Ayothaya do this to me?
I believe there must be a traitor...
who has been plotting
against Your Highness.
Rest assured, Your Highness.
I have sent the assassins
to take care of this matter.
I curse you!
-I curse you!
You will meet a calamitous end!
Bring the injured in here quickly. Go!
Please heal this man.
This way.
Give me a hand.
Quick! Bring me some medicine,
water and clean clothes.
Come and help him. Quick!
This is for my father, Lord Siha Decho!
Take the rebel's head!
My Lord.
Do we still have any hope?
Tien was born under an ominous sign.
It is his old karma
that causes him to suffer in this life.
The corporeal body is still waiting for
the mind to be free of wrath.
Wandering around,
fending off the revenge of karma.
I'll have to try
to alleviate his tortured fate.
If you all
could unite the power of your minds,
your strength of faith,
to prolong his life,
the merit created
might please the enemies of his past life.
Then his mind can be released
from torment and return to his body.
Here. I give you everything.
Oh, he's alive. He's waking up.
He's waking up. He's alive.
Anyone who thinks of betraying me
shall be cursed to meet
a calamitous, miserable end
and shall be tormented forever.
Don't worry, Tien.
You're much better now.
It won't be long.
It won't be long
before we can dance together, Tien.
Get out!
-Are you crying?
-Go away! Leave me alone! Go!
Crying...
Leave me alone.
Oh, it's high.
Okay. I'll go with you.
We can walk together.
Quickly.
Quickly. Let's go.
Come on. We can walk together.
Oh, wow. It's high. It's high, huh?
I said go away.
I said go away!
No. I've changed my mind.
Back off.
Go away!
Don't cry.
Laugh. We should laugh.
Go!
Go ahead and jump.
He's not going to follow you.
He hasn't got any hair.
Because an insane person like Mhen
can understand the world better
than a sane person like you.
Staying up there is better than jumping.
My life is hopeless.
I'm alive, yet my life is worthless.
You were born with an ominous fate
that causes your suffering.
But now, my name
can not help to rectify my fate.
I can't accept having to live like this.
Your name only symbolizes
its meaning, "light".
Tien.
Take a look in front of you now.
The light is driving away the darkness.
Look at the ground.
Now you can see your own shadow.
If you have been scared by
the shadow that has been following you,
just remember,
wherever the shadow is,
the light is always nearby.
Father,
what should I do now?
Follow me.
Seek solitude. Practice meditation.
Enlighten your mind.
Tien, do you want to train
your weapon skills?
I want to be a great warrior
like my father.
Your father is a great warrior.
But that didn't help him
to find peace in his life.
A weapon is a tangible form of power.
Anyone who can merge
his body and soul with it...
will possess the greatest power.
Do you think a person
who learns about weapons
can bring peace to the land?
Chernung!
Leave me alone!
My life is in the dark. It's hopeless.
Tien, your name means "candle".
It's a symbol of light in Buddhism.
Light means the wisdom
that eradicates the darkness of ignorance.
The benightedness of the mind.
Wisdom can bring
enduring peace to this world.
I brought someone to see you.
She's pretty. Do you want her?
I can dance alone.
What are they doing?
I know.
Now I understand
what your intention was,
why you taught me the art of dancing.
It is to cure the body and mind.
I'm thankful to you for changing my life.
It's your mind that accepted the change.
Change the enemies into dancing partners.
There are many things in this world
that you have yet to learn.
Greed. Wrath. Infatuation.
Desire. Lust. And ignorance.
Always be careful.
Because these things
are the causes of karma.
They cause all living creatures
to be stuck
in the perpetual cycle of birth and death.
How can I stop these things?
Through practice.
Practice cleansing and purifying
deep into your mind.
The mind is the master,
the body is the servant.
The consciousness controls your mind.
The mind comprehends. Be aware,
then let go.
Your mind will remain untarnished.
My castle welcomes only you,
Your Highness.
You all wait for me here.
Thank you for visiting me, Your Highness.
-What do you really want?
-Power...
and everything you own.
I curse you!
The power... is mine.
Kill him! Kill him!
All of you, go inside and kill him.
Kill him!
Power should be possessed
by those who deserve it.
You rebellious crow. Traitor!
I curse you.
You will meet a calamitous, miserable end.
A calamitous, miserable end.
Submit yourselves to me!
I am your king now.
I brought someone to see you.
Come on!
Here he is.
Why are you hiding? Over there.
-Capture him!
-Why? What did I do wrong?
Oh, many people.
I stamped on your foot.
I'm taking it off.
Your nose is bleeding. Your mouth too.
Don't draw your sword.
There is a rope. I'll pull it.
Got it.
Must have broken his balls.
Oh, the same rope.
Where are you going?
You are the chosen one
to fight and drive away ignorance.
Stop your evil acts.
Finally, you have come.
I'm here to stop you.
You? Stop me?
There is no way you can stop me.
Look.
None of your mighty gods
can withstand my power.
I can smell
the bitterness and vengefulness in you.
Move! Go! Move!
Let me go! Let me go!
Tien!
Let me go! Tien!
Your fate
belongs to me.
Tien.
Your life is coming to an end.
You don't have a choice.
No!
The bitterness
and vengefulness in your heart
give me power.
You can never overcome me.
I have come from emptiness.
I shall return to emptiness.
You don't have a choice.
Subtitle translation by:
Chaimas Sainampueng