Quiet, please!
The winner this year is young Ting!
Welcome, people of Nong Pradu,
and all who have come for the presentation
of robes to our revered Ong-Bak.
Ong-Bak provides us with moral support
during this ceremony.
I'd like to tell you that
the great festival of Ong-Bak
will commence here in seven days,
which is held only once
every 24 years.
It marks the start of
another cycle of good fortune.
Where's the amulet?
It's quite damaged
and there's a mark on its head.
Hardly perfect condition.
It's worth around 200,000,
which is not bad.
Why won't you just sell it?
All right. Name your price.
-Don, it's not for sale.
-What?
Why not?
I came all the way from Bangkok,
I took time off work.
I didn't promise you I'd sell it.
I'm keeping it for my son
for when he decides
to become a monk for Ong-Bak.
Just give me a call
if you change your mind.
No. I don't have a phone.
You can take my address.
If you need that money,
you can send me a letter.
Isn't it beautiful, Granny?
I'll make Ting wear it.
Yes, it is.
Ting's birthday is on the same day
as Ong-Bak's ceremony, isn't it?
It is.
He's such a poor guy.
He was left at the temple
when he was a baby.
The senior monk found him,
so he decided
to adopt him as his son.
Anyway, he seems like
another version of Ong-Bak.
The front kick.
The back kick.
A jab with a kick.
The double uppercut.
Knee up to defend.
Kick backward and then uppercut.
Flying knee.
Forward elbow.
Backward elbow.
Elbow attack on thigh.
Upward elbow.
Flipping elbow.
Elbow cross.
Elbow swing.
Elbow swing and knee up.
Defend and push.
Knee uppercut.
Flying knee.
Elbow upward.
Elbow and back kick.
Elbow forward.
Punch and elbow.
Elbow and knee defend.
Cross elbows.
I have taught you the art of Muay Thai.
Now I ask you never to use it.
Do you understand why, Ting?
I do, sir.
Good.
Good for you.
You don't really understand, do you?
Right?
Before he became a monk,
your master
learned Muay Thai martial arts
from Master Dam's book.
He was eager to test his skills,
so he fought in a street fight.
He killed his opponent.
He was overcome with guilt...
so he became a monk.
Muay Thai is extremely dangerous.
He doesn't want you
to walk the same path he did.
Got it?
You still have doubts, don't you?
Fine. Fight me.
-Ting.
-Uncle.
Motherfucker!
What the hell are you doing?
Quick!
Don.
He's the one who cut
Ong-Bak's head off.
Take the donation money
and bring the statue's head back.
Don, you son of a bitch!
Without Ong-Bak's head
our village is doomed!
Calm down, people.
We have to find a way
to bring Ong-Bak's head back
before the grand ceremony.
Who's going to bring it back?
I'll bring it back.
I know where Don lives.
The people of Nong Pradu's
fate lies in your hands.
This amulet provides spiritual protection.
My grandfather told me
it belonged to Master Dam.
You should keep it with you.
Here's Don's address...
and a letter.
Please give it to my son.
Bring Ong-Bak back, son.
For the village's sake.
Take my money.
My hope goes with you, son.
My mom gave me this ring
before she died.
Wan, take good care of Granny.
Everyone give what you can.
For the journey.
Damn! I lost the bet.
Hey! Hey!
Damn it!
Come here, Bus.
Who's the loser you brought
to join the race?
Hey! What're you talking about?
It's normal to win or lose a race.
How can you say that?
You brought a girl?
So?
What's wrong with me being a girl?
Bitch. Do you know who I am?
Shame you don't race
as fast as you talk!
Jerk!
Hey!
-You're not paying me in cash?
-You bet with some crank.
You told me that it's
either crank or cash.
Yeah.
I'll give you ten grand.
The other ten grand
is security for your debts.
I pay you interest every month
and it's not due yet.
Can't you just give me that money?
-Take it or leave it.
-Hey!
It's better than nothing.
Give it back.
Give it to me.
You got your money.
Just give my boys some crank,
will you?
You can find it anywhere you want.
You don't need that.
My crank's too strong.
Your boys can't handle it.
-Trust me.
-Hey!
Son of a bitch!
Yes! My bro, George, is back.
Come on, give me some money.
Give me my share.
Quick. I'm in a hurry.
We were caught in the act.
Peng knew our crank was fake.
He took all the money.
What? Don't joke with me.
It's not funny, man.
Look. Look at my face.
You think I did this to myself? Bitch!
What's that for?
It's swelling!
-Can't help it. What did you do?
-Fuck it.
Do you have some cash?
What the hell! I lost my share,
and now you want some cash from me.
Look, Muay.
You always take your share from me.
Just give me some.
You're the one who got caught.
That money was in your hands.
I'm stupid, huh?
You're a fucking genius.
What should we do now?
Peng's given me three days.
If I can't pay him back, I'm dead.
I'm in trouble!
Humlae!
Is that you, Humlae?
Hello.
Muay, is he your friend?
-Do you know him?
-What do you mean?
He called your name, didn't he?
You know this hillbilly?
Do you recognize me?
-I'm Ting from Nong Pradu.
-Hey!
I don't know you, redneck.
Got it? I don't know a redneck like you.
But I recognized you, bro.
I'm not your fucking bro!
Who's Humlae? Sounds horrible.
Don't call me that or I'll beat you up.
Stop teasing him, Humlae.
No. Sorry, George.
You're such an annoying bitch.
Get out of my face.
Come on.
Where are you from again?
-Nong Pradu village.
-Right, Nong Pradu.
Right, I'll leave the Nong Pradu boys
to it! You'll have lots to talk about.
None of your business.
Go away and give me some cash.
Here. For your painkillers.
-Right.
-See you, Humlae.
You, redneck,
go back to your stupid village.
Humlae, your dad gave me a letter for you.
I said I don't know you!
This is my apartment.
You're not offended, right?
Close the door.
Mosquitos.
I was a little upset...
and in a bad mood.
Humlae.
Well...
Do you know that our village
is in a big trouble?
Don and his men
cut Ong-Bak's head off.
Your father told me
to find you
so we can get the head back.
I have Don's address.
No more talking.
You drop your things here
and take a shower. Go.
Take a shower first, come on.
Right here.
That's the shower.
Go on. Go.
Can we go and find him?
No. Shower first.
Use this towel. Go.
Go. I'll turn on the light for you.
Go. The soap is on the left,
a toothbrush is on the right.
No jerking off all over the floor, okay?
Hello, Muay.
Yep. Meet me on Khaosan Road.
At the underground boxing. Yeah.
Can I make a bet?
Is it too late?
Sure.
All in.
Hey! That's right.
Exactly. That's right.
Yeah. Right.
Where's the amulet
you talked about?
Well, the stupid owner
refused to sell.
So I got Ong-Bak's head
for you, boss. Here.
The villagers worship this.
It's the village's sacred statue.
It's obviously damaged.
Why did you bring it to me?
You want to upset me?
Throw this crap away
or I'll be really upset.
Your boys keep letting you down today.
Now watch your Pearl Harbor
get the kamikaze treatment
from my boy, Ali.
Your boy is totally done.
I have no money.
I'm trying to make some.
I didn't come for money.
I can make a living on my own.
Now you're a drug dealer?
Yeah.
You're so confident about your boy.
Right.
If you think your boy can win,
up the stakes as much as you want.
I have no limits.
Don't say a word.
You don't know me.
One asshole
can make you a slut, huh?
Muay, you're not my mom!
Of course not. Mom wouldn't
let you to behave like this.
Right. A slut like me
has taken care of you.
From now on, a good girl like you
can just leave me alone.
Let me know if you want anything.
Get up! Get up!
Next.
If you're still up for it,
just let me know
if you want to raise the stakes.
Fuck you!
He has won three fights in a row.
Hey!
Where's our people's money?
What money?
-My money pouch.
-I have no idea. It's not me.
Over there.
He's won three times in a row.
Three times in a row, people.
Who's next?
The next opponent.
BETS ON 3-1
Put your bets on!
What?
What's that redneck
doing in the ring?
Right. You're dead, Ting.
I give you ten to one.
I don't think
you should bet on this.
Fine. I'll give you a million
if you dare.
Deal.
I'm not here to fight.
I want my money.
Easy, dude.
I'll find your money.
Fight!
What's your name, bro?
I'm Ting from Nong Pradu.
I'm gonna...
Ting, Pradu's Pride.
I'm not taking it.
I just want my money pouch back.
What an idiot.
Wait. Wait.
Why didn't you take that money?
Are you that stupid?
Let me know if you want to fight.
You're great.
I can tell you, if you win
you'll have lots of money.
You'll be rich.
I don't fight for money.
Humlae, why did you steal
the villager's money?
I didn't steal it. I invested it.
When we're rich
I can help you find Ong-Bak.
-Will you help me?
-Sure.
This is Don's address.
Please take me there.
Keep it. I'll take you there later.
Can I borrow the money?
I need to make an investment.
When I get some extra money,
I'll give it back to you.
I'll take you there for sure.
Go away!
Go away, asshole!
You redneck!
I was nice to you, idiot.
Where is he going to spend the night?
Fuck it,
or let him stay with you!
You're crazy.
What now?
Peng is going to kill me.
Hey, Muay.
You bring some crank
to Lao's casino, okay?
Then we can share some cash.
I know the owner.
You've just been beaten up.
Want some more, George?
I told you I don't want to
get involved with your crank.
Will you give me a hand?
You want me to get beaten up?
Will you?
I'll get the money for you,
but not tonight.
That's my girl.
Don't give me your puppy dog eyes.
About our shares,
you get 30 and I get 70.
Muay, it's 50-50.
-70-30
-50-50
70-30
The money you asked for
for your business in Bangkok,
I can't give it to you right now.
Our village is suffering from
great drought
and Ong-Bak's head was stolen by Don.
I want you to help Ting
find Ong-Bak and bring it back.
It's bad luck...
Nonsense.
Wan, the water in the well
is running out. What should we do?
Dear Lord,
please bring Ong-Bak back soon.
Amen.
Yong, you got lots of customers?
-Priew, you win?
-I lost, bro.
Hello, bro.
Hello, George.
Where the hell have you been?
Doing my business.
You know my casino
needs more customers.
-Come and help me.
-Not today.
I have plans with my friends.
Shut up. Help me out right now.
-I will, next time.
-No. I said now.
Quick!
Here, take it.
Go away. You're a lame dealer.
Right. Bets on.
Uncle, put your bet on.
-What are you waiting for?
-How much?
You should be at home.
I want some fun before I die.
-What you looking at? Fuck off!
-To that table.
Take the dye out of your hair.
Don't copy me!
Here.
Bets on, you know.
It's your chance to loose,
not mine.
Don't change your cards.
Nine, double.
You have to pay me double.
Next round.
-Bets on.
-Deal the cards.
-Call.
-Can I play?
-You have money?
-Three grand. Enough?
Let her play.
She might want to lose some.
All her money will be gone
in a sec.
-Two hundred.
Here.
Don't you change your cards.
Eight, double.
Pay me.
Give me your money.
Wait, bro.
Nine, double. Pay me.
Make that 400.
Cool, bro.
Put your bet on.
I got six!
I got nine.
I got eight, triple.
I got nine, bro.
How can she get those?
She's got some luck.
The odds are in her favor,
I can tell.
Nine points.
What?
-Got eight again.
-Got nine again.
Fuck you! Here!
Give me more.
-My money.
-Here!
Got eight again.
I won.
My money, please.
Eight points again, double.
Nine points. Look.
-What?
-Yes.
Everyone, hold your cards.
I need to know
if she's cheating or not!
She's only got nines.
I lost to her 15 times in a row!
Is she cheating?
I want to prove it this round.
If you get nine again,
you're cheating for sure.
Look, I'll get eight again.
If you get nine again,
you're definitely cheating.
-What?
-You're wrong, bro.
She got four.
-See?
-I can't believe it.
She must be hiding some cards.
-I need to find them.
-Hey, bro.
Easy, bro. I'll take care of it.
Check her, George.
You hiding cards?
-I'm not.
-Let me see.
I have nothing. No cards.
Look in her pockets.
-I'll do it.
-No need, bro.
Here. Take these and leave.
-Go away.
-No. Look closely.
-Check on her.
-I did. I did.
You, go away.
Just go. Don't come back ever again.
Bitch.
He makes money every day.
You made him lose.
Come on, bro.
Let's make some money.
How? They've lost their money.
That bitch took it all.
Why you mad at me?
We've got eight grand.
Here, three grand for your tuition.
-What? Just three grand?
-Don't spend too much.
-Damn. It's nothing.
-Right. Just take it.
-Don't spend it all.
-Can I have one more grand?
That's enough. Three grand for you.
-That's it.
-My tuition.
Hey!
You've got a lot of money.
That jerk's here.
Can I borrow some?
That's mine!
I'll take care of it.
I'm about to pay you back.
There you are. Here.
-That's mine.
-What?
Here.
Eight grand.
I'll give you the rest later.
Don't give me that look.
You scare me.
I don't care about your debt.
You two made a fool out of me
the other day.
I can't take it.
-Don't hurt me!
-Break his arm.
Ting! Ting!
Asshole!
Don't hurt me!
Hey!
You betrayed me, huh?
Who is he?
It's none of your business, jerk.
You'll regret this.
I'm grateful, Ting. Thanks.
I'll help you find Ong-Bak.
Can you fight for me just once?
Wait. Listen to me.
You know that I got beaten up.
If I can't pay him back,
I'm a dead man.
Please help me.
Just once, one last time.
-Easy.
-Okay.
Fine. Forget it.
You idiot, all of you.
Screw your stupid village!
Sending one guy against a whole gang
to recover Ong-Bak? Crazy!
If Ong-Bak is truly sacred,
how could it be beheaded?
It's just a lump of rock!
Damn you!
How dare you?
-You hit me?
-Hey!
-You want to kill him?
-He hit me!
Forget it. The one who wants
to kill you is over there.
Peng!
You never learn, do you?
Want him to kick your ass again?
You bring the whole gang?
George!
You should know by now
what to do.
Muay, you know what to do, right?
I'm good at this.
Wait.
Get them!
You follow him.
The rest of you follow me.
-You...
-Goodbye, bro.
Move. Move, asshole.
Hey!
Wow. How did you do that?
My butt is safe.
How could I jump like that?
Hey! Follow him!
Can I borrow this?
One more step
and I'll cut you into pieces, jerks.
Knives! Good knives!
Knives!
CHIILLI FLAKES 10 BAHTS/GRAM
It burns!
Kill him now!
Damn!
Hey!
Ting! Help me!
I won't. You're as bad as Don.
Don...
I know where he's at.
Ting! I know where Don is.
Who's next? Come on!
I saw Don selling drugs around here.
You can ask Muay.
Today we...
What? Damn it!
That guy's here.
If I can find someone to fight
with Big Bear,
you want in?
If you have the guts, I'm in.
Big Bear. Big Bear.
Come on!
Hey! You! Stop it!
-Let me.
-You're crazy!
Welcome back, champion.
Ting, Nong Pradu's Pride.
-What's that, George?
-That's Big Bear,
he's challenging Ting.
Come on. I'll fight you.
I'll teach you some Muay Thai moves.
-You see Don?
-I don't.
I can only see a poor Thai guy.
You're such a coward.
Are you not gonna help him?
If you don't, he'll be dead.
Ting!
If you don't help him,
I'm not gonna help you find Ong-Bak.
Just do something. Quick!
Help him first.
Bets on! Bets on!
Bets on!
I'll put my bet on 2-1.
What do you say?
I call three million.
Front kick to the face.
High kick with knee.
If my boy wins,
I'll take the money.
Yeah. I know.
That's it?
Ting! You're the best!
That's enough, bro.
Let's call it a day.
Ting, Pradu's Pride and Toshiro!
Well done. Great!
-Enough!
-One more time.
I just need half of it.
-Are you sure?
-Trust me.
-Just half of it.
-Yeah.
Another challenger?
I'll make it even.
Fine.
Ten million for this.
No problem.
Are you all right?
Get off me! Let me go!
Ting! Help me!
Don't miss this time.
Excellent! Ting! You're the best!
I told you, Muay.
All in and we're rich.
You are all stunned.
Make it rain. I'm rich!
Muay! Collect them all!
That's enough, bro.
You've had no luck today.
He's a mess.
Ting, you're so great.
We're going to be rich, Muay.
You're so good.
Don!
Hey! Cops!
Follow him!
Move! Move!
Go!
I'll deliver the stuff on Sunday.
Get your men ready for the job.
Don't cause any trouble.
Yes, sir.
How do you know that redneck?
-Humlae.
-What?
Where can we find Don?
Not now. You eat first.
Don't worry. We'll find him.
Everyone here on Khaosan Road
knows him.
Eat. Dig in.
Hey! Muay.
You come with me tomorrow.
We may have a way
to make some more money.
No. I have a test tomorrow.
What test?
You never go to school.
How can you have a test?
Are you the teacher's pet?
Damn.
I'm kidding.
You're smart. Smart girl.
Let's eat. Dig in.
Thank you, Humlae,
for helping me find Ong-Bak.
-That's all right.
-If your father knew--
George!
You owe me three months' rent.
What you gonna do?
Can you give me three more days?
Three days and I'll pay you.
I promise.
You promise me all the time.
If you don't pay me today,
you can pack up and leave.
Take this ring instead.
Fine.
I give you seven days.
Get me that money.
If you can't, all of you are out.
Got it?
I want you to come back with Ting.
Don't worry about the money.
If you don't want to be a monk,
I won't blame you.
All I want is for you come back
to visit me. I miss you.
What?
What's wrong?
I'm not as good as your ex?
You turn me off.
Don.
I'm not smuggling crank for you.
Why not?
I want to quit.
You want to quit?
Come here.
You think you can quit easily, huh?
Quit, if you can.
If you can, go ahead.
Yeah?
Who the hell?
What? Ting! George!
Ting!
You!
Ngek!
-Where's Ong-Bak?
-No idea.
-You stole it!
-I said I have no idea.
Ting!
Back off!
Ngek!
Move! Move!
It's too late. Come on!
Wait for me.
Get off! Get off!
Call an ambulance. Room 212.
Someone might die. Quick.
Hurry! Get in.
Why is he still following me?
-Come on!
-Die!
Hey! Ting!
Ting!
Ting! Hit the break.
Hit the break now!
My goodness!
Don't lose him. Go.
Hey!
-No!
-Stop it!
I'm falling, asshole!
Fuck you! I almost died.
Go!
Hey!
Remember this,
you need to check every inch of it.
No mistakes at all
and the most important thing is
don't let anyone in. Got it?
Damn! He's still following me.
Get in.
The police and Fine Art Department
have recovered many artifacts
submerged in the Chao Phraya River.
This recovery is priceless
as every one of these artifacts
is a national treasure
that will be registered
by the Fine Art Department.
Chantana Khunsungnoen,
reporting from the crime scene.
I told you not to cause any trouble.
I didn't.
They came to find Ong-Bak.
What is Ong-Bak?
The statue's head that I brought back.
This son of a bitch
won't stop bothering me.
I lost ten million because of him.
Now he's ruined my business
because of that stupid statue?
HOSPITAL
I'm sorry, I couldn't save her life.
Ngek! Ngek!
You can't just leave me!
Who is she?
Muay's big sister.
I'm alone here.
You left me.
I have no one but you.
Muay.
Here.
Ngek left this for you.
FOR MUAY'S TUITION
No! I don't want it.
I want nothing!
I need her.
Please don't leave me!
Get over it, Muay.
People die. It happens.
I'm not going to leave you.
Hey! What's going on?
Quick!
What're you doing?
I'm not going with you.
Quick! Come on!
Let's go!
You played with fire,
you don't know who you're messing with.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
It's between Ting and Don.
It's true. I have no idea.
I know you guys are looking for this.
You want it back?
If you do,
I have a game for you.
I've seen Ong-Bak with my own eyes.
Just say yes to join an underground fight
and you can have it back.
Muay will be safe as well.
What do you say? Yes or no?
I'll do whatever you want.
I just need to take Ong-Bak home
to our village.
I would do anything.
Why hold this fight
all the way at the border?
I needed a new place
for my underground fights.
And out here, if anyone dies,
it won't be my problem.
Oh, you've really got a grudge
against that redneck.
If you're feeling lucky, name the stakes.
Now you like the underdog?
It's time for tonight's highlight.
In the east corner is a Thai boxer
named Ting, Pradu's Pride.
He's a rookie. He's a rising star.
A Burmese boxer is in the west corner.
He's a skilled boxer from Myanmar.
Showtime. The fight has begun.
Saming Tiger is making his
return to the ring.
He has been away from
underground boxing
and now he's back, people.
Watch closely.
Ting gives him a front kick,
a sidekick and a left kick.
Right kick, but misses.
They're both great and fearless.
A right kick from Ting.
Another right kick,
but it's nothing for Saming.
Another kick to the chest.
Front kick to the chest.
One more front kick.
Saming is perfectly fine.
He's unbreakable.
He's calling his opponent out.
They're watching each other.
Ting gives him a kick,
again and again.
Saming is so calm. Why?
He was kicked in the neck!
Wow! He's roaring.
He's going to make a move now.
Ting steps backwards
then punches him in the stomach, his face
and an elbow blow to his stomach again.
Saming is boiling up.
He gives him three punches in a row
and then a kick to the neck.
He was thrown
and now he's being pinned down with knees.
The judge is trying
to separate them and...
What's that?
The judge was thrown, too,
and the other judge is kicked in the neck.
Wow! What's going on here?
Ting strikes with his elbow.
Saming lunges for his throat.
He's ruthless.
Saming hits out with his knee
again and again,
another strike with the elbow.
One more back kick,
Ting bounces back into the punch.
He's spinning around
and down to the ground.
Hey! Ting!
He gives up!
Saming is the last man standing.
Our judges are knocked out.
He turns to his opponent's coach.
He's so furious.
What's wrong with him?
Ting falls out the ring.
Hey!
Hey! If you want Ong-Bak, follow me.
Go!
This is your prize
for making the redneck lose the fight.
Hey! That's the Lord's statue!
It's the piece of crap
you've been looking for.
I don't worship lumps of stone
like your stupid people.
I worship myself.
You should worship me, too.
I'm the one who decides
whether you live or die.
Son of a bitch!
You betrayed us.
You told me to make Ting lose the game.
You're not giving him Ong-Bak.
Damn you!
You son of a bitch!
Take it easy.
I lost millions because of that head.
You can't have it back
until I get my money back.
Remember this, I am the Lord.
Finish them off
and meet me at the cave.
Hey! Kill him.
George!
Damn it!
I said make it quick and quiet.
Come on!
The cops will be here in a minute.
You, go over there. Go!
Where's Ong-Bak?
Hey! Take me with you.
No.
I won't let anyone die for Ong-Bak.
But if anyone does, it'll be me,
no one else.
Damn it.
Ting.
Let me help you.
Everything I've done,
I didn't mean it.
I apologize to you.
Just let me do it
for people of Nong Pradu.
At least let me start the engine for you.
I, Humlae, from Nong Pradu.
Don said that there's a hidden cave
around the other side of the mountain.
Hey!
Why can't you just die?
I just cut this off
and you risk your life for it.
How about this giant statue's head?
Hey!
Ting! Ting!
Ting!
Humlae! Are you okay?
Go get Ong-Bak. Go!
Don't worry about me.
Get Ong-Bak. Quick!
Hey! Where are they going?
Keep doing your job!
Cut the head off!
Be careful.
I made him lose the fight last time.
It's nearly off, boss.
Good. Cut it off.
Hey!
You really want this?
If was broken into pieces...
would you still want it?
Humlae!
Humlae! Are you all right?
Take...
Ong-Bak...
home. Our home.
George!
Why are you such a mess?
Get out.
Muay...
go...
to school...
and study.
Find a job when you graduate.
Ting, tell my father
I...
can't be a monk for him.
What are you talking about?
Just go to a hospital
and you'll be fine, George.
Humlae!
George! My bro!
You can't just die!
You promised me
you would take care of me!
You can't die like this.
You can't die for me.
You can't die before I do.
You can't, got it?
You promised me.
I have no one left! No one!
You come back right now!
Don't do this to me.
You can't leave me!
Wake up now!
George! You can't die.
You promised me.
No!
No! You can't die.
I'm not gonna cry for you.
Wake up! Now!
Talk to me. I will behave.
I have nobody left.
I said wake up!
No!
Wake up! You promised me
Don't you dare lie to me.
Translated by: Chutarat Banthakit