I'm Anna Troyev, the art therapy instructor.
Arms up.
I trust we won't go through this every day.
Anna?
Welcome, are you ready for your first day? Hmm.
I think so. Please.
Do you live far? Uh, somewhat, but it's worth it.
Always wanted to use art to help people.
Wonderful.
Please.
This way.
Those are our security procedures.
Learn them backwards and forwards.
Most of our patients are quite docile, but others--
Doctor, it's Leena.
She's not in her room. Nobody can find her.
Lock it.
Who's Leena?
Our most dangerous patient.
In fact, she's the reason for the opening you're filling.
Your predecessor underestimated her
and ignored protocol.
Did not end well.
Listen to me. Do not leave this room.
Don't worry. You will be safe here,
and I 'll come back after we've found her.
Please, please--
Hello, there.
Does your mum or dad work here?
Can I see?
I-- Is that me?
That's very good.
I'm Anna. What's your name?
Leena.
You didn't a-- answer me before.
Do your parents work here?
Why would you think that?
Because you're-- I'm what?
Leena?
Put it down.
Leena, put it down, now.
You didn't tell me she was a child.
That's because she's not.
Leena suffers from a gland disorder
which causes, uh, proportional dwarfism,
essentially halting her growth around age ten.
Make no mistake.
Leena may look like a child, but she is a grown woman.
Thirty one, to be exact.
When Leena first arrived,
she struggled so hard against her restraints
that she would bleed severely.
It was a lesson for all of us
on the depths of her will to be free.
Much of Leena's early life
was spent doing whatever she could to survive.
But she never grew older, at least not on the outside.
Imagine going through your whole life,
the world seeing only a child.
It is very important that you do not see her in that way.
Leena uses her affliction as much as she suffers from it.
She's a exceptional con artist.
Two years ago, Leena wormed her way
into this family by posing as a runaway.
This family took her in. They fed her. They clothed her.
Normally, Leena would simply steal whatever she could
and then disappear, but this time,
she, um...
Well, let me put it this way.
She lives here now.
Idti.
Idti!
She does that.
How much longer have we got, Daddy?
We have two minutes, darling.
You're learning me by heart, little Sara.
No, Daddy. I know you by heart. You're inside my heart.
We're gonna be brave, aren't we?
Yes, Daddy.
Yes, Daddy. Hello, Dmitri.
You're on time.
It's perfect.
I can't tie these myself.
I want to do something nice for you.
You can come in.
Yeah. Yeah. What are you doing?
My daddy has to go away. He'll return most any day.
I can't do it.
I can do it now.
Any moment I may see my daddy coming back to me.
My daddy has to go away.
Idti, do you want some candy?
Idti!
She cut the feed.
I'm so sorry, Anna.
Hopefully, the police will find her
before anyone else is hurt.
Not quite the start we had hoped for, I'm sure.
This job isn't for me.
Oh, Anna.
It usually takes only one.
Huh?
Don't be frightened. I am police.
Uh, where are your parents?
My parents are in America.
Sw-- sweetheart, what is your name?
My name is Esther.
♪ Coming with me ♪
♪ Through the aging The fearing, the strife ♪
♪ It's the smiling On the package ♪
♪ It's the faces in the sand ♪
♪ It's the thought That moves you upwards ♪
♪ Embracing me with two hands ♪
♪ Right will take you places Yeah, maybe to the beach ♪
♪ When your friends They do come crying ♪
♪ Tell 'em Now your pleasure's set ♪
♪ Upon slow release ♪
♪ Hey, wait ♪
Fence!
♪ Sensitive to fate, not... ♪
♪ The long way back ♪
Yeah!
♪ Sandy, why can't we Look the other way? ♪
Killed it. Thanks, man.
I'm so proud of you, sweetheart. Mm-hmm, yeah.
Great job, pal. Thanks, guys.
How long do you think you'll be?
Actually, a bunch of people are getting together tonight.
Well, congrats.
I'll, uh, see you guys back at the house.
I mean, this was supposed to be family night.
What, is he not supposed to have fun with his friends?
Oh, God. All he does is have fun.
No, Gunnar works his tail off.
When he's not studying, he's fencing.
He's living his life.
Don't do that. Don't go into your head.
I need you to be present. Gunnar needs you.
Oh, sorry. Was I not at that match?
Esther's not coming back, Allen.
I miss her too. I do.
Every moment of every day.
What is he doing here?
Hello, Allen.
We have an update on your daughter Esther.
From the little we've gotten from Esther,
we believe a woman abducted her, brought her to Russia
and passed her off as her own child
until Esther managed to escape.
We haven't gotten many specifics yet.
Perhaps when she's feeling safer,
she can shed some more light on what she's been through.
We have a child therapist that she'll be working with.
Good.
What she needs right now is her family.
Be prepared for changes.
Four years is a long time in the development of a child.
Esther?
Sweetheart, it's me.
It's Mommy.
Can I-- can I see you?
Sweetie, it's--
it's Mommy.
I thought I would never see you again.
Everything is right, now.
It's been so long since you've seen any of us.
Let's see if I can-- Oh, there's Daddy.
This was one of our charity events.
He looked so handsome that night, didn't he?
Can I grab you anything else?
No, thanks.
Oh, speak of the devil.
Your brother is probably a foot taller than you would remember.
Oh, there's Mup-Mup. She's been so good to us.
Oh, I can't wait to see her.
No, sweetie.
She passed. Remember? It's just the four of us now.
I have to use the restroom.
Uh, is the restroom over there?
No, it's just right back over there.
Over in the back? Oh. Mm-hmm.
Thank you. You're welcome.
"Can't wait to see her." So stupid.
Oh, Daddy and Gunnar are just downstairs.
Do you think Father will recognize me?
Uh, maybe not if you keep calling him "father."
Dad. Yeah, that's better.
Here. Let me look at you.
Oh, my God. You look...
like a little lady. You've grown up so much.
Take this off.
That's better. It's less austere.
This is--
Sorry. No, I-- I'm sorry. I--
Come on. Let's go.
I think I'm nervous.
All right, big step.
Daddy?
I'm so sorry.
Can't believe it's really you.
I always knew. I always knew.
Hello, Gunnar.
Hey.
I think we could do a little bit better than, "Hey."
Don't you think? Come.
Glad you're back.
Me, too.
How about we go home, huh? Yes.
Let's go home.
Welcome home, Esther.
We left it just as it was.
We always knew you would come back home.
Hmm.
I mean, you've probably outgrown so much,
but we have a lot of Christmases and birthdays
to make up for,
so just let us know what you're into,
and you might get it.
I like painting. You like to paint?
You were never interested in painting before.
Well, maybe you two
can spend some time in your studio.
Nothing would make me happier.
So, um, plan is,
tomorrow you're gonna talk to Dr. Segar.
Do you remember her?
She had the parrot named Sydney. Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Well, if you need anything...
We're right down the hall, all right?
♪ And let your poor heart Break a little ♪
♪ That's the story of ♪
♪ That's the glory of love ♪
♪ You gotta laugh a little ♪
♪ Cry a little ♪
♪ Before the clouds Roll by a little ♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
Okay, you can go in.
Dr. Segar will be right with you.
I'm seeing her in a few minutes.
I think it's too soon for you to get involved, Detective.
I'd like to talk to her alone first.
Look, I have to go.
You have no idea
how happy I am to see you, Esther.
Welcome home.
Well, now, you're certainly not the little girl I once knew.
You're a young lady now.
Do you remember what I told you
when we first began our sessions?
I told you if I ask any questions
that make you uncomfortable, we'll stop.
I wish my parents were like you.
How so?
They keep asking what happened to me,
but I'm not ready to tell them about it.
And that's perfectly fine.
I am hoping you'll talk to me about it,
but only when you're ready, okay?
Having said that,
is there anything you want to tell me
about your time away?
You want to play, Sydney?
I think Sydney wants to play with me.
Hello, I remember you.
You remember me?
Your turn. Esther, you can wait out here.
I'm just going to need to talk to your mom for a moment.
Hello. Hi.
I like your earrings.
Oh, thank you, honey.
What are you writing? Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. I'm sorry.
Let me go get this cleaned up.
She seem the same as you remember?
Different?
Well, of course she's different.
She has an accent now.
Is that unusual, considering where she's been?
Not necessarily.
She was there a long time when her speech
was still developing.
But I will tell you, she is in far better shape
intellectually and emotionally than I would expect.
Well, that's good, right?
I did notice some inconsistencies.
For example, she said that was Sydney.
Sydney was a macaw.
Bright orange and four times the size.
Yet, today, she addressed this bird as Sydney
with complete confidence. What are you getting at?
To me, it felt like a performance.
He hit me and ripped my dress!
I want to go home.
That's enough for today.
Uh, of course. We'll reschedule.
Esther, you all right? Uh, yes.
Hey.
Morticia, get Gunnar for me, would you?
What did you call me? Mike, that's her. The sister.
Oh, shit.
It's my bad. Um, get Gunnar, pozálujsta.
Is that Spanish or something? I don't--
Hey, let's go.
Your sister's a fuckin' trip, man.
Seriously, dude? My dad is right there.
I don't care. Mike!
Fucking idiot. I am what I am.
Hey, honey, you okay?
Uh, my dress is ruined. I'll buy you a new one.
I was thinking, uh,
I was thinking we could go to the studio.
I would love to.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think you'd never been in here before.
So beautiful.
What's the light for?
What's the light for? Mm-hmm.
You don't remember? It's what your papa's famous for.
Hmm.
Here.
Press on this.
Yeah, I always tried to fit so much into one canvas,
you know? So, I resorted to a-- a hidden layer.
Nothing is ever just one thing, right?
So cool.
You haven't been in here in a while.
No, I haven't.
What's this one?
Oh, no.
It's, uh, I should've gotten rid of this.
Who-- who's-- who's that?
There's no use dwelling on the past.
You're home now. That's all that matters, right?
So, I was thinking we could dust off some canvasses, you know?
See what comes of it.
I would love to. Yeah?
Um, what's your poison? Oil, watercolors?
I-- I got it all. Charcoal?
Charcoal? Okay.
Pick an object, and-- and we'll sit down
and we'll-- we'll draw it together.
I want to draw you.
You want to draw me? Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay.
Well, this is a first.
How do you want me?
I can-- I can do The Thinker.
The way you were when you were looking at that.
That's not a place I want to live anymore.
There.
Just like that.
You learned to paint while you were over there?
Mm-hmm.
Would you just draw, or was it-- was it also--
It wasn't what you think.
It's still happening, despite everything
that's going on. Allen? No, he won't be there.
You know how he feels about these things.
So, I'll see you at the gala tomorrow, then, okay?
It's for a good cause.
Beth, just bring your checkbook and Jim.
It's for pediatric cancer, for Christ's sake.
Okay, that's better. Thank you.
I'm finished.
Already? Mm-hmm.
Do you like it? I love it.
It's-- it's incredible.
Okay, 30 seconds, all right?
And then we're gonna see what you can do with paint.
That's private. Oh, I'm sorry.
I-- I saw that you brought it back with you.
I thought it was special. You don't knock?
I was looking for, um, my gold watch.
I-- It's okay. I'm sure it'll turn up.
Sorry.
"Property of Esther."
"Mummy took me to Wicked."
"Mummy." Hello, Mummy.
Thank you, Mummy.
I know, Mummy.
Mummy.
You're not gonna believe what Esther can do.
We spent the afternoon in the studio.
She drew a portrait of me.
She's got more talent than I had when I was in my 20s.
How's that possible?
Four years ago, she was still drawing stick figures.
Easy. What?
Think about where you were four years ago.
Now you're a fencing champion. Yeah, just-- It's impressive.
Hmm.
Maybe you can make a portrait of me.
This is delicious, Mummy.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
No, no. I'm just--
You expecting someone?
I thought I'd pop in to...
Look who came for a visit.
Oh, I'm sorry to interrupt dinner.
This is a police officer
who helped us when you went missing.
He's a friend.
I just, uh, came to say welcome home, Esther.
Thank you.
Excuse me for a moment.
You should know, um, our child psychologist feels
Esther should tell her story within the confines of--
And not with a cop like me.
Don't worry. I get it.
But Esther did vanish from our little town,
and that remains a concern.
I need to know if there's still a danger.
I spoke to Dr. Segar this morning.
Is that appropriate?
She told me she's open
to group discussion tomorrow morning,
just to see if everything's all right.
Mummy, your gala is tomorrow.
We'll do it the following day, then.
It's important.
I mean, sure. If it's that important, we'll be there.
You forgot to fill your glass.
Well, uh, welcome home, Esther.
You said that already.
Esther-- Oh, it's okay. She's right.
I'll walk you out.
I'm sorry you live here.
Yeah.
I think I'll stay here for a while.
I think something's going on with Dr. Segar.
She seemed to be implying in our last meeting
that Esther is lying.
That's insane.
Maybe she needs to see a therapist.
I know, right?
What-- what is this?
Your date.
You're coming? Yeah, of course I'm coming.
You're my wife. I can deal with a few rich pricks for you.
And what about Esther?
Well, Gunnar's here. She'll be fine, right?
What, do you want me to stay home?
No, no.
Oh, you know, it seems like since we got Esther back,
we got us back, too.
I couldn't agree more.
How long do you need to get dressed?
I can be quick. Yeah?
I can be quick, too.
I'm sorry, but they're cute.
Let's just close the door.
Just close the door.
What? No. No, no, no!
Oh, my God.
Do you know how much I spent on this dress?
Let me look. Oh, man.
I can fix that.
With a safety pin. Right, or staples.
Staples would work.
You're responsible for looking after your sister
while we're gone. We're trusting you, okay?
Yeah, Dad. I got it.
You look incredible.
We're off.
Probably won't be home until after midnight, okay?
So, don't let her stay up too late.
You have the keys?
Copy that. Hmm.
You look nice. Thanks.
Have a good night, honey.
Ciao. Night.
So what are we going to do?
We?
♪ We got a lot of time And it sure feels right ♪
♪ 'Cause you reached In your pocket ♪ ♪ You've got to win a little ♪
♪ Lose a little ♪
♪ And always have The blues a little ♪
Oh, it's-- Oh, shit, guys. I'm sorry.
I was holding onto it for too long.
Okay. So, Gunnar,
is your sister different than you remember?
I mean-- What do you think?
She's been at some Eastern European sex gulag.
Mike.
But, uh, yeah. No, she, uh, she's different, all right.
She's got an accent now.
And she dresses like Lizzie Borden.
It's so fucking weird.
Who's Lizzie Borden?
♪ Sha la-la la... ♪
Some crazy chick who killed her parents with an axe.
Uh, hey, Esther,
why don't you, uh, go watch a movie or something?
No.
Esther, this isn't your scene.
Go watch a movie. Go fuck yourself.
Hey, Gunnar, you know what? I like her.
Oh.
Go.
Anyway, cheers! Cheers.
Yeah. I'll fucking drink to that.
Um, what we were talking about?
Who's that?
Evening.
Hey, my parents aren't here. They're at Mom's gala.
Just my luck. Yeah.
Having a party?
No, it's just a few friends.
Smell the weed from the street.
What? Um, I don't know--
I don't know what you're talking about.
Um, look, nothing's going on here, okay?
So um, why don't I just tell my parents
that you stopped by, and we can just forget all about this.
Cool?
Cool. Good.
You mind if I hit the restroom before I go?
Yeah, whatever. Yeah, sure.
That was a blast.
No wonder those uptight millionaires line up
to give the foundation money.
Oh, no. It's the booze.
It's not the booze, hon.
It's the host.
You bring the best out of people.
Aw.
I just hope the house is still standing.
Ugh.
I mean, when I was 16, I-- I nearly...
...I nearly burnt the house down.
No, Gunnar would never do that.
Who says I'm talking about Gunnar?
Esther, we're home.
Esther?
"Saarne Institute?"
If you're not Esther, who the hell are you?
How did you know that I'm not Esther?
Her own mother doesn't even know.
Yeah, kid, she does.
Damn it.
Mummy?
The fuck are you looking at?
So, let me get this straight.
You're a grown-ass woman and a wanted criminal?
That is beyond fucked up.
This is all I ever do anymore, by the way.
Clean up after my kids.
Don't worry about it. Mommy'll take care of it.
Mommy takes care of everything.
When Gunnar told me Donnan came to the house,
I knew I'd find you here.
You could have robbed us blind and disappeared
the second you had a chance, but you didn't.
Why is that?
You're thinking bigger, right? Play the part, manipulate us,
and a year from now we meet with some tragic accident.
Am I getting warm?
Let me go. You'll never see me again.
That's exactly what I'm afraid of.
We can't have Esther disappear twice now, can we?
She didn't disappear.
There was nothing that I could do for her,
it was too late.
Gunnar, he was always way too rough with her.
That night he just went too far. What was I supposed to do?
Hand over the only child I had left over some
sibling bullshit that went too far?
I loved my daughter with all my heart,
but a mother protects her family, no matter what,
and if you think... ...that I'm going to let some
psycho dwarf destroy what I have built...
you're mistaken.
This family came over on the fucking Mayflower
and built this country. We matter. Allen matters.
When he got the news Esther was alive,
the happiness on his face, I had to make this work.
Allen doesn't know what happened to Esther.
And you are gonna help me make sure that he never does.
There's only one thing worse than the death of a child,
and that is a child who is missing.
Esther's disappearance changed Allen,
changed who he was, who he is supposed to be,
but you are the answer.
You and I have a chance to turn this mess
into a mutually beneficial arrangement.
Esther's down there, isn't she?
Don't you fucking say her name.
Okay.
You conned your way into my family.
You chose this role,
and now you're gonna fucking play it.
So, you can be Esther for now,
and live a life that anyone would kill to have,
or you take the fall for this
and get shipped back to Estonia in handcuffs.
What do you say?
I'm sorry I scared you. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We should have never left you alone.
What happened? She fell off her bike.
I found her by the side of the road.
Honey, what are you doing on a bike?
Come here, let's-- let's get warm.
Mom, I'm so sorry. Stop.
What the fuck? Yeah.
So what does this mean?
Well, it means she's not a kid.
She is a grown woman and we cannot underestimate her.
No, she's more than that, Mother.
She's a psychopath living in our fucking house.
So we just have to live with this person?
I didn't say that. So then, can we just, you know?
Make it look like an accident.
It's too soon. We need to think about this.
So she just owns us now?
No, no, she has just as much to lose as we do.
Look, neither of us were expecting this.
So, for now we just keep an eye on her,
and when the time is right, we'll end it.
This is insane, even for us.
Okay, see that? It's gonna fire.
Uh-huh. Pull it back. Just like that.
And you get the bow, flip it in, slide it.
See this? Are you watching? Yeah.
Yeah, and you--
Nice!
You see that? Yeah, yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Our meeting with Dr. Segar is today.
A problem we wouldn't have if you hadn't talked
to the parrot.
Sydney was a macaw. Oh.
All macaws are parrots,
but not all fucking parrots are macaws.
What are we gonna do about that?
Oh, we make her believe. Together.
One of our goals here is helping Esther acclimate
back into life within the family unit.
Part of that is remembering your shared history.
Moments you had, the fun things you did together before.
Mr. Albright, what's a memory that means a lot
to you and to Esther?
Oh, God, there are so many.
Um, there was Christmas in Paris.
The summer in Tuscany.
Yellowstone. Yeah, that's up there.
I was six.
We saw bears and a-- a chipmunk stole my sandwich.
Oh, my God. There were so many chipmunks.
What else, Esther? Be specific.
We stayed at Elk Ridge Ranch and rode horses.
Mine was a pony named Nugget
and Daddy's horse was called Stretch,
and this one time when Stretch leaned down to eat grass,
Daddy fell right over his head onto the ground.
He had dirt all over his face. It was even in his teeth!
I can't believe you're telling this story.
Oh, my God. It was in your teeth for days.
In summary, Esther exhibits a healthy outlook on life,
especially re-entering into this family unit.
She is highly functioning,
emotionally well.
That is all.
There are people coming over today
just to see you.
They're friends of ours who knew Esther.
So enough with the glowering, okay?
Esther is a lady.
Hmm.
I think I'm gonna have to do some damage.
Okay.
Think we did good.
Everyone expects Esther to be broken.
What they really want is a happy ending.
We are gonna pretend
that pink is your favorite color.
Ooh, velvet.
The secret is to give them a story they want to believe.
This one is my favorite.
What's your favorite color? Pink.
Very, very good.
Now, you say you can paint. What else can you do?
I missed my family very much.
It's lovely to be back.
And what are your plans now, young lady?
What are my plans, Mummy?
Absolutely nothing.
I'm not letting you out of my sight.
Aw.
So let me get this straight...
you're 30?
Get out of my room now, please.
It's not your room. It's my dead sister's room.
You're not her and you never will be.
Is that perfectly clear? Fuck off.
Watch your mouth, freak.
You know, I'm glad everything's out in the open now,
'cause I'm done pretending like you belong here.
You don't.
This is my house, my family, it'll never be yours.
As long as you're under this roof,
you and I will have an understanding.
Here's what it is.
I fucking own you.
Do that again and I'll kill you like I killed Esther.
One call from me,
and you're right back in that gulag.
You'd go down, too.
Why, because of what the illegal immigrant, fugitive,
mental patient said?
Good luck with that.
This is America.
People like me matter,
and if you're not Esther,
that just means Esther's missing again.
Mom has a problem with that.
I don't.
See you later, freak.
You are gonna sleep like a fucking baby tonight.
I made roast lamb with rosemary and tapenade.
And I know Esther doesn't like it,
so I made your favorite.
Aw, just like the old days.
I'm really excited about going
into the city tomorrow.
I'm gonna show the gallery what I've been working on.
That sounds wonderful.
Well, it's all thanks to you. Oh.
I rediscovered the joy I once felt doing what I love.
I feel like a kid again. You want to come?
I would love to!
Oh, Esther and I already have plans.
Oh. What plans?
It's a surprise.
Okay, well, another time then.
It's great that you're painting again, Dad.
Well, yeah.
May I be excused?
Oh, don't forget your--
You can eat upstairs. It's okay.
Honey, hey, what's wrong?
Dad, she's fine.
Just give her some space. She's fine.
Yeah, she's probably tired from all that piano playing.
Can I come in? Mm-hmm.
Are you okay? What happened down there?
I, uh, I don't really like Mummy's cooking.
Well, can you keep a secret?
I'm not crazy about it either.
Well, listen, um, nighttime's my favorite time to paint.
You-- you want to come join me?
Yes, I would love to. I'll see you downstairs.
This is a such a great space. I'm glad you like it.
Every artist needs a space to let their inner weirdo out.
We get to see beauty and passion
where others don't even know to look.
I really like that.
So much paint.
Yeah, I'm a messy painter.
Drives your mother crazy.
I think I'm-- I think I'm done for the night.
Just turn the lights off.
Have a good night.
Looks like you two had fun.
He's right, you are talented.
He is something, isn't he?
Are you so utterly delusional to think that he would want you?
"Surprise, I'm not your daughter,
I'm a mutant grifter."
He would be as repulsed by you as I suspect most men are.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go upstairs and fuck my husband.
He really is a new man since you came back.
Thanks for that.
Hey, you.
I think Esther's really bummed about not coming
to the gallery with me.
Listen, I love that you and Esther
have painting in common. I just--
I don't have anything like that with her.
I was hoping that I could spend the day with her
and maybe we could find something to share.
Plus, it would be good for you to be focused, right?
I mean, if Sal likes what he sees,
then maybe you get a show and get back out there.
Yeah, okay. We're not hurting, are we?
No, no. Not at all.
You are a great painter.
People miss seeing your work.
Thank you.
Is that bacon?
It's heaven.
Good morning, Daddy. Crepe?
Yes, please. Is there anything you can't do?
Mummy?
Oh, no, thanks. I'm gonna make my usual--
Smoothie?
Greek yogurt, kale, flax seeds, and lemon juice.
Just the way you like it.
Try it.
I'm not really that hungry.
I'll-- I'll have it. Here.
No, this is special just for mummy.
I made it for you.
Oh, sweetie, that's so nice of you,
but I prefer to make my own.
Tricia, come on. Try it.
Good.
Mm, delicious.
Thank you.
Tricia, you okay? I'm good.
Yeah?
I know you wanted to come with me,
but I think it'll be really good for you to spend the day
with your mom. I wanted to show you something, though.
Here.
It's the one in the center.
Dean at Woodley is a friend of mine.
Woodley is the best art school in the country.
You're scary good, Esther. Can I show it to 'em?
I would love it. Thank you.
Can you bring this up to the platform?
I'm just gonna get some coffees for Mom and Dad.
Mm-hmm.
All right, I'll see you up there.
Jesus Christ! Watch where you're going, kid!
Does she belong to you? Yes, she does.
What happened? Oh, nothing. It's fine.
Esther tripped. Sorry, it took forever.
No, no! Knock 'em dead, okay? Yeah.
Daddy, take me with you!
Oh, honey, I wish. Next time.
You're gonna miss your train. All right, see you later, honey.
Ciao.
Easy, Mom.
You think you can fucking kill me?
Take this.
Tastes like fucking garbage.
Our arrangement is over. You're fucking dead.
Hey!
Mom! Mom!
Fuck! Bitch!
Open the God damn door. Esther!
Sweetie, come on.
Don't you dare!
♪ Just a steel town girl On a Saturday night ♪
♪ Lookin' for The fight of her life ♪
♪ In the real-time world No one sees her at all ♪
♪ They all say she's crazy ♪
♪ It can cut you like a knife ♪
♪ If the gift becomes the fire ♪
♪ On a wire between Will and what will be ♪
♪ She's a maniac Maniac on the floor ♪
♪ And she's dancing Like she's never danced before ♪
♪ And she's dancing like... ♪
I'm sorry. Was I driving too fast?
You must be Esther.
I need to go to the hospital.
You're fine.
Feels like I'm being stabbed a 1,000 fucking times.
Officer Leahy. Oh, my God.
Can you just be quiet for, like, two seconds?
What? We've located Esther.
You did? I'm bringing her home.
Oh.
Oh, and I've informed Allen as well.
Okay, bye. Fuck!
You're okay. You're okay.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my goodness. Oh.
Esther's behavior has been so erratic since she got back.
To be honest, it's been really hard.
I mean, there's constant lying and these outbursts of anger.
Sometimes she even jokes about hurting herself
and I don't think she's really joking.
You have her in therapy? Yes, yes.
Look who's back.
Get up. We're doing this. Now.
Well, it's about goddamn time.
Fuck.
I am done with you.
Nothing is worth having you in this house.
Your suicide is gonna break Daddy's heart,
but he'll get over it.
Ugh.
Just die, you freak!
Where is she?
I-- I-- I didn't mean to.
Oh, that's just brilliant.
It just happened.
Tricia. Hi, honey.
The police just called me.
Oh, I know. I'm-- I'm sorry. It was my fault.
Esther wandered off at the store,
and I just-- I panicked,
but I called Officer Leahy... Mom.
...and they found her.
Oh, good. Mom.
Well, I'm on the train. What?
She's-- Hold on.
I'm-- I'm coming back home.
I'll be...
Go downstairs and finish it.
What? Go downstairs and finish it.
Tricia, are you still there?
Tricia, is everything okay?
Tricia, I-- I'm coming home now.
What? I'm coming home.
What about your meeting with Sal?
Forget about that.
No, sweetie. I swear. Everything is fine.
Esther is here, all is well.
Look, I'm almost at the station in town.
Okay, well, can you please take a cab home?
Because I really have my hands full here.
Ow, fuck it.
There you are.
Esther.
Come on out, Esther
or whatever the fuck your name is.
You know, it doesn't have to be like this.
Really, Gunnar?
I'm sure we could figure something out.
You really believe that?
Honestly?
No.
Me neither.
Shit.
Gunnar?
No.
No!
What have you done? What have you done?
You've taken everything.
Allen will never be yours,
but I can I promise you this, he will know who you are.
The deformed freak who manipulated our grief,
murdered my son, and tried to kill me.
Until I did what had to be done.
Call the fire department!
Gunnar!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Help! Daddy, Mommy tried to hurt me!
Allen! Please help!
Allen! Don't let go!
I can't hold on much longer.
I'm losing my grip!
Daddy, help! Honey, hang on. Hang on!
I'm coming.
She is not Esther! She is a grown woman!
She's lying! What?
She tricked us! Mummy's lying!
Give me your hand! No, Daddy! Please help me!
Tricia!
What the fuck? I did this for you. For us.
So we could be together. Allen, I love you.
Who the fuck are you? You're a monster!
Allen!
♪ You've gotta give a little ♪
♪ Take a little ♪
♪ And let your poor heart Break a little ♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
♪ You've gotta laugh a little ♪
♪ Cry a little ♪
♪ Before the clouds Roll by a little ♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
♪ As long as there's The two of you ♪
♪ You've got the world And all its charms ♪
♪ And when the world is Through with you ♪
♪ You've got each other's arms ♪
♪ You've gotta win a little ♪
♪ Lose a little ♪
♪ And always have The blues a little ♪
♪ That's the story of That's the glory of love ♪
Fire took everything from Esther.
Her home, her family.
The whole situation is so tragic.
It's horrifying.
I know.
As if Esther hasn't been through enough already.
Abducted and now an orphan with no family to take her in?
What will happen now?
I've reached out to a reputable adoption agency.
I'm confident we'll find a home
where Esther can get the support and love she deserves.
After all, who wouldn't want to adopt her?