WHILE PARIS WAS SLEEPING
You always keep your eyes shut?
I'm with you.
It helps me be with you.
I want to look at you.
Harder. It's good.
Harder. Harder.
Right, 11... and ten.
Number 11.
HM.
- Your initials?
- TD.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thanks. Bye.
I'll wait outside.
Bye.
Ten.
With a gin and tonic?
9.90, thanks.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Come on.
There's a bike station that way.
It's where I park,
so I can stretch my legs.
I'll check for bikes.
Before it loads, we'll be there.
I think...
your dick is beautiful.
It is, it's beautiful.
I don't know how to say it.
I liked it straight off.
And I swear,
your cock is perfect
to the touch.
Come off it.
No, I really mean it.
A guy's dick is so important.
I think you can fall in love
with a guy's dick.
I mean it.
And...
I can't wait to see yours again.
Can't wait.
I want to touch it...
Kiss it.
Suck it.
Ooh... Off the top of my head,
I'd say 11 bicycles.
That's what the app says.
Sorry, I'm obsessive. I can't
help checking everything.
Only with bikes.
Don't jump to conclusions.
This one will do.
A little more love in the world.
Tonight, with you,
it was different.
Huh?
What did you say?
When we made love,
it was unusual.
Because with you...
I made love.
We fucked and it was...
I mean, it was like
we were producing love.
We made love,
see what I mean?
I couldn't hear you.
But I agree, it was...
I think we made a big
contribution to world peace.
What we did
was pure love creation.
We need to start over.
For the good of humankind!
Don't you think?
We have to start over?
- We're going to my place.
- I got it.
Straight ahead.
I'll say when to turn.
I can't lose sight of you.
I don't want you to think...
or imagine...
It was strange for me, too.
I'd never done that before.
It was my first time like that.
- Uh... At the Impact?
- Yes.
I had a boyfriend before,
for a few months.
Of course we didn't bother.
But, like that,
it was the first time.
It was good.
Better, even. Don't you think?
I prefer it that way.
With you, it was really good.
Because it was unusual.
Like you said: unusual.
Wait, what do you mean?
No way!
You mean you fucked me
without a rubber?
You fucked me without a rubber?
Fuck!
What were you thinking?
You're insane!
You're not two years old!
What the fuck!
You know sex clubs.
Un-fucking-believable!
Right.
I'll call the AIDS hotline.
They'll tell us what to do.
Unless you're positive?
I knew it.
Hello?
Hello.
Uh... Speedy response. Perfect.
Uh...
The thing is...
I just fucked a guy
without a rubber.
I can't remember.
Uh... Probably.
Is he HIV positive?
I think so.
Yes, he is.
Uh... Emergency room?
I'm near Saint Louis hospital.
He should come with me. OK.
I get priority?
I tell them at admittance?
I just say ASE?
They'll understand?
I tell them I had an ASE.
OK.
And then what happens?
OK, right now. Of course.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
We're going to Saint Louis.
- They said...
- You're not coming.
- She said to go.
- Is it necessary?
- It's better.
- Then I'll go alone.
I don't know, your phone call...
it was too weird.
You're too weird.
I want to be alone.
- I just wanted...
- Stop it!
I fucked up.
No need to hold my hand.
You're mad at me?
I don't know. Maybe.
It's not fair, but, hey...
Whatever you feel.
We need to swap numbers.
To work out your treatment,
they'll need my results.
You need to be able
to contact me.
- Go ahead... 06.
- No, it's 07.
- 07?
- It's a new number. I changed.
OK, 07...
06...
So is it 07 or 06?
0706. It's my number.
07 06 86 77 99.
The unknown caller is Hugo.
Théo.
- Take rue de Lancry.
- I know.
Take the rue Vellefaux
entrance...
I set it!
I'm not following you.
I take the first right.
Rue Albert Thomas.
I'm with you.
It helps me be with you.
Harder.
WHERE ARE YOU?
Emergency room.
CALL ME!
WHY DON'T YOU ANSWER?
I LEFT YOU A MESSAGE
IT'S IMPORTANT!
Here are your papers.
You can wait over there.
- The intern will call you.
- OK, goodbye.
Good bye.
- Hello.
- Hello. I had an ASE.
OK. How long ago?
Under an hour.
Is your partner here?
- No.
-OK.
- Do you have any health issues?
- No.
- Allergies?
- Any medication?
- Nothing.
So I need some identification:
your ID card
and your health card
if you have it.
- Still the same address?
- Yes.
OK.
Here are your papers.
You can wait over there.
The intern will see you soon.
- Thanks.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Cellphones are forbidden here.
Even text messages.
I didn't know. Thanks.
I'M HERE. WHERE ARE YOU?
- I can handle this.
- I know. I'm sure... I guess.
- Did you get my message?
- I ignored it.
You were so stressed out,
I forgot.
Tell the intern
I'm in treatment.
I consult regularly and my viral
load is undetectable now.
That's all.
- What's the difference?
- Just tell him.
The AIDS hotline
said it was important.
Great.
OK, I admit it.
I thought I should come,
to be with you now,
so you have someone to talk to.
If you want, I can leave.
No problem.
Or I can stay.
It's up to you.
If you want to know,
I'd like to stay.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
Then I'll decide for you.
Let me see.
What are you doing?
I'm reading your mind.
Your eyes don't lie.
Look me in the eye.
No, better than that.
Look at me.
Straight in the eyes.
OK, then. Stay.
It won't take long.
Mr Vinaver, please.
See you later.
I understand. I've been there.
What?
You're scared?
Yes, I'm scared.
- You stayed to tell me that?
- No.
I wanted to keep you company.
I was alone
when I got my results.
And before that, too.
I don't want you
to go through that.
It's not allowed.
Really? Where did you hear that?
Look, I wanted to show you this.
They say,
when there's active penetration,
the risk of infection
is 0.06 to 0.62%.
Hey, that's not allowed.
I told your friend earlier.
- I told you?
- You told me.
I knew I told you. You should
have told your friend.
It's OK, I'm done. Relax.
They don't mess around
with that here!
Good... Good.
You can make calls over there.
Over there, it's allowed.
After all, people need
to be able to make calls.
We're in ER. Things happen.
Deaths, sometimes.
Then you need
to make a phone call, right?
Do you come here often?
No, it's the first time.
I need to make a call. Sorry!
Coming?
I need a coffee.
You're not nice.
We could have listened to him.
Did you hear him?
"Do we come often?" Like
it's a café or a restaurant.
He's nuts. Keep your distance.
Or he's just lonely.
My treat.
If you want.
- No sugar?
- As much as possible.
Show me again... that website.
Really?
- It was a stupid idea.
- Show me.
So?
Thanks.
It's loading.
Show me.
Take a look.
I'm no maths genius.
A risk of 0.62%
is almost nothing.
But people get infected anyway.
Give it back.
It was a stupid idea.
Statistics don't mean a thing.
And that's ugly!
Take you, for example.
That's different.
Because you were passive?
No need to be an asshole.
It wasn't the same...
because it wasn't the same.
The difference is
I'm in treatment.
I take my drugs.
And my viral load
is undetectable.
I had just got my licence.
I'm from Lons-le-Saunier.
Not even Lons.
Can you imagine?
I don't know the regions.
Maybe Normandy but on vacation.
And Berry.
I'd never met a fag.
And I was 18.
But I knew where they fucked.
At a highway rest station
with toilets.
It's a nice place, really.
With big trees.
It's all I could think of
during the test,
that I could go fuck, too.
I waited three days
for the pink slip.
It came at last. That night
I borrowed my mum's car
and went out and got laid.
It was pretty lame.
A quick fuck.
Sort of shameful.
No talking. No eye contact.
They don't even know
what a rubber is.
Tell them they're gay
and they'd beat you up.
See what I mean?
They don't get treatment.
They don't know
they're HIV positive.
It makes it riskier
for the partner.
It was your first time?
I'm not helping.
I shouldn't have told you that.
It's easy to use a rubber,
right?
I'm so stupid.
No, it can happen to anyone.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'll make you miss your turn.
Mr Daumier? I was waiting.
- Sorry, I was...
- Let's go. It's an emergency.
Unbelievable!
They give priority to faggots?
Ignore him. He's a regular.
- Is it normal...
- Let's go.
...to let perverts go first?
Do you want him to come?
Yes.
Go in and sit down.
So what happened?
- I had an ASE.
- I see.
Can I have the details?
- A broken condom.
- OK.
You two. You're the partner?
- Yes, the sexual partner.
- Right.
I'm HIV positive.
OK. Are you on
a triple therapy?
Yes, I'm in treatment.
Have you consulted lately?
About three months ago.
OK. Do you know your viral load?
It's undetectable.
OK. That's a good thing.
Um... Do you know your status?
Yes, I get regular tests.
- I did one two months ago.
- Which was...?
- I'm fine.
- Negative. OK.
I don't take risks.
OK.
One more thing.
Uh... who was active
during intercourse?
- I was active.
- OK.
When the condom broke,
did you pull out immediately?
No, I didn't pull out.
So there was an ejaculation?
OK.
In any case,
since your partner's positive,
treatment is advised.
An emergency triple therapy.
The idea is to stop the virus
reproducing in your body.
Uh... It's pretty
heavy-duty therapy.
It lasts 28 days.
Three pills a day,
at the same time,
every 24 hours.
Do you agree to the treatment?
Yes.
I'll go get the pills
and I'll explain everything.
Are you OK?
This is the kit.
Here's how it works.
There's a bottle of water
and a cake,
because it's better to eat
at the same time.
For now you have
four days of pills.
On Monday, you have to go
to the screening unit,
here at the hospital.
No need for an appointment.
Explain what happened.
They'll see you right away.
It's best if you come, too,
with your results.
OK, I'm free on Monday.
- Right.
- Yes.
On Monday,
we'll do new blood tests.
The doctor will decide if
you'll continue the treatment.
He'll see how you tolerate it.
The side effects
are mostly digestive.
Nausea and diarrhoea
- and maybe some fatigue.
- OK.
If you really react badly,
we can change.
But the symptoms
usually improve.
- OK.
- It's mostly the first days.
Right. Let's start right now.
It's best to start
as soon as possible.
One of each colour today.
Afterwards, you take the rest.
- Do I start by eating?
- If you want.
All of it?
I need some water.
Now, take the three pills.
- One of each?
- Yes.
You're OK?
Yes.
Good.
Here's the kit.
It's for four days.
It's not a nice thing to go
through. It's a bit stressful.
But you can get help on Monday.
The two of you are here, now.
It's good if you support him
during this ordeal.
It will be OK because
we're within the time frame.
If you take the treatment
every 24 hours,
there's a very good chance
the virus won't spread
and at the end,
you'll still be HIV negative.
OK?
Right...
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll see you out.
- Good bye.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Did you notice?
- Hm?
- Women run this place.
- Yeah.
Guys leave the worst jobs
to women. What a shitty world!
Yeah. Women and fags.
The night belongs
to women and fags.
And night watchmen.
That's a position of power.
Limited power but even so...
He's black.
Of course.
Like I said, limited power.
Are you a hairdresser?
What makes you say that?
Is it my nail polish?
No, it's Monday.
Hairdressers always close
on Monday.
Lots of stores close on Monday.
You can't buy food,
except in supermarkets.
So are you a grocer?
A baker? A cheese seller?
No. I'm a notary's clerk.
My boss gives me Monday off.
Sometimes, in exchange,
I stay late
or I finish work at the weekend.
Either way, it works for me.
I love not starting the week
with everyone else.
More than having Friday off.
Seriously?
You're a notary's clerk?
I know, it sounds impressive.
But it's a job like any other.
Better than many others.
I want to be a notary.
But you have to study for
a long time and it's expensive.
I had to get out of my village.
I needed to work.
I became a clerk
to become a notary.
It takes longer,
but I'm independent
and I got out of the Jura.
I'm happy with my life.
It's weird.
We turned left
out of the hospital,
without thinking.
Where are you going?
I don't know. I'm following you.
I'm following you, too.
We'll go round in circles.
It's late.
You're heading home?
You're not exhausted?
If you want me to go,
just say so.
That's not what I meant.
But if you want
to go get some sleep...
I like being with you.
Even if... the circumstances
could be better.
I don't feel like sleeping.
Do you?
I'm hungry.
Do you think
the bakeries are open?
Let's try over there.
We'll find something.
It does me good being with you.
You're good for me.
Why are you going this way?
It's random.
There's nothing on the canal.
Do you think?
Probably.
But it's beautiful.
Is this a romantic walk
or a food hunt?
We can do both.
I'm not so sure about the walk.
Feels good, doesn't it?
It's a new concept:
the romantic sprint.
Very funny.
We'd have more luck
on the other side.
Let's not cross the canal.
OK, why?
It's a game.
Let's go that way.
It's worse over there.
There's nothing.
Let's try Stalingrad.
No!
Did you have side effects?
I want to know what's coming.
It's dead here.
Civilisation starts
at Stalingrad.
You didn't answer.
The drugs are not the problem.
You get used to taking them.
It's not so unmanageable now.
You can skip a pill,
but not too often.
When you have a normal life
with a job,
it's part of the routine,
like a habit.
The side effects go away,
or you change treatment.
The problem is the virus.
I mean...
even if it's undetectable.
Even if I'm not scared any more
that it will kill me.
It's there.
I think about it.
Often.
They say, "Live with it."
But I can't.
I live against it.
I try to live against it.
I'm probably wrong.
I should live with it.
Make my peace with it.
But I can't.
Is this the right direction?
I'm a stomach on legs.
If there was food,
my instinct would tell me.
Where else is there?
It's civilised that way.
- My instinct?
-No such thing.
I can't explain it.
I want to kiss you
and punch you.
I want to hit you now.
Hard, really hard.
That's nice.
Would you feel better?
I don't know.
I want to.
I'm itching to do it.
Itching all over.
Want to try
a 24-hour kebab joint?
A kebab? If I have to.
Who eats kebabs at 6:00
besides fags just out of ER?
Night workers or guys who
start work on a full stomach.
You could have said
you had a plan.
It's more fun this way.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
You're right. What time is it?
5:30 but I'm running early.
You're out of kebabs?
Sorry, all sold out.
I have other things.
- I'll have chicken.
- One chicken?
- No, two.
- Two.
Running made me hungry.
But you're right.
A kebab is good after partying.
I only work weekends.
I serve the party-goers.
- No onions.
- Me neither.
It's dead now but until three or
four o'clock, I'm really busy.
Where I'm from,
you have tea after.
- Where are you from?
- I'm Syrian.
With my university buddies,
it was a ritual to eat a kebab
after a night on the town.
It's not exactly
the same as here.
The meat in Syria...
Are you here because of the war?
No.
I studied architecture
in Damascus.
The war is horrible.
But there was
too much injustice.
After a while,
people can't stand it any more.
Forty-five years...
It's a long time.
I didn't live there.
I survived.
I guess you can't understand,
because you're free here.
We couldn't talk.
Not to anybody.
Not even my university buddies.
A life without talking
is unbearable.
About politics,
or even just what we feel.
Our desires...
Here you are.
Twelve euros.
I'll get it.
- Thanks.
- Goodbye.
- Have a nice day.
I bet you're still a student.
No, not exactly.
Uh... How about we go eat
somewhere calm?
I know. Over by the canal.
Tell me, what do you do?
You ask all the questions.
What do you want to know?
Well, first up, what do you do?
An internship.
I have a master's
in industrial design.
I'm an intern in a big company.
It's interesting.
You don't sound convinced.
I am, but right now
I want to do other things.
I want to be an aid worker.
Yeah... I can't see
the connection with design.
There isn't one.
I feel like I need
the experience.
A few months. A year, max.
OK, so I haven't done
any research. It's a pipe dream.
Let's go up there.
I don't know
humanitarian causes,
but I guess
there's plenty to do.
At least in logistics.
- You like to travel?
- Yeah.
But there's more to it.
You think it's ridiculous?
Sentimental?
No, I don't know. Why?
Anyway, signing up for...
any cause is sentimental.
Sentimentality is beautiful.
Yeah.
I feel ridiculous
when I tell you that.
If only I could say which cause,
or which country.
Like some student.
"I'll do this, I'll do that!"
They never get off their asses.
They pissed me off!
If I'm HIV positive, that's
the end of the wild ideas.
No visits to countries
without aspirin.
I'd need emergency care myself.
Would you go?
No, of course not.
What else
did you want to know?
OK, why does
your phone number start with 07?
- It's unusual.
- Look at you!
You tried for an easy question,
that can't hurt anyone.
- Bad move.
- You think it's funny?
Yeah.
You tried to be nice
and made it worse.
You tried so hard,
I can't be mad at you.
Should I stop asking questions?
For now, yes.
Let's go to the end.
I love this place.
- It's nice.
- Yeah.
Come on.
Let's eat.
Can you hold this?
Thanks.
It's early
but it doesn't matter.
I always have them on me.
That way, I can't be caught out.
Even when you fuck
at the Impact?
You never know
when you'll find love.
Sometimes I get home late.
I can see that.
It's happened before?
It's not the first time.
Yes.
No, it's never happened before.
Usually...
Listen, I don't know...
Something happened between us,
something big.
That's all.
Something big?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
Something that made me...
lower my guard.
What do you usually tell them?
How does it go?
Wait, where are you going
with this?
What do you want me to say?
Hey, wait a minute!
What do you want?
For me to tattoo HIV+ on my ass?
Because idiots like you
don't take precautions!
It takes two to screw up.
I didn't have to beg you!
I never asked you to do that.
Of course not. "Harder, harder."
You didn't ask me,
but you said, "Harder, harder"?
It's always our fault.
You're a dumb asshole.
What am I doing here?
I promised to come on Monday.
I'll be there with my results.
If you don't want me to stay,
fine!
You have my number
if you need it.
I'm sorry.
Don't. No apologies between us.
- We both fucked up.
- Both of us.
- At the same time.
- Hand in hand.
I think I felt safe with you.
I didn't really think.
I felt good, calm, happy.
It seems irrational now.
It made sense then.
Yes, it made sense.
Made sense.
Between us,
everything made sense.
We got careless.
We wanted each other.
Wanted it too much.
We didn't realise.
Desire is stupid.
But it's good
to want you like I do.
- Were you drunk?
- Not really.
Me neither.
But it was like being drunk.
See? Desire is stupid.
I have a monster hard-on.
Strange way
to start a relationship.
- Relationship?
- Yes. Why not?
You're crazy. Stop it.
I'm going home now.
Can I come too?
If you want.
If we rush,
we can take the first metro.
I love the first metro.
After the first
comes the second.
That's the one we need to take.
I know it.
Trust me.
- How do we know it's the first?
- I know. But we can check.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Is this the first metro?
Yes, it's the first.
See? It's the first.
She said it's the first.
- You're not regulars?
- No.
I take it every day.
I'm not the only one.
I know everyone... by sight.
I'm a chambermaid
in a fancy hotel.
I didn't work long enough
to get a decent pension.
That's all I could find.
I'm not from around here.
Yvetot. Do you know it?
- No, I'm from Lons.
- I'm from Paris.
Before, I mostly worked
in retail.
In sales.
La Chapelle.
I've had a hectic life.
I fell in love too often.
The job centre
can't handle people like me.
So, of course... it's cleaning.
It's good with my cousin.
We've made ourselves a life,
just us girls.
No, but... it's not so bad
when you think about it.
I like Paris.
It's... it's big.
It's anonymous.
I think you're better off
in anonymous places.
- Right?
- Yeah.
The first metro...
is not so bad.
Barbès-Rochechouart.
I get off here.
- Goodbye.
- Have a nice day.
- You, too.
Thanks.
Anvers.
- It's here.
- Anvers.
Let's go.
Being a notary is weird.
How do you decide
to be a notary?
It doesn't come to mind
when you plan your future.
People mostly lack imagination.
I got the calling
from reading Balzac.
Mauriac, too.
I haven't read much Balzac,
but aren't notaries
lame pencil-pushers?
I mean, in novels.
In real life, it's so...
exotic that it's sexy.
It's over there.
It's not the characters
that inspired me.
It's that...
Well...
Balzac is life inside families.
He goes to the heart of things:
money matters, property.
Everything we never mention.
Everything essential to society.
- For rich people.
- Not only.
It's true, our clients
are not often labourers.
But they can be low-income.
All it takes
is a tiny inheritance,
a little house
or even a bit of land.
You can't imagine
the emotion involved.
It can break your heart.
They're stories
nobody can tell you.
You can't make them up.
- Unless you're Balzac.
- Yeah. Or Mauriac.
Balzac wrote a novel called
The Seamy Side of History.
That's exactly it.
From where I am,
I see the seamy side of history.
Can I come upstairs?
To see where you live.
It's just a maid's room.
It's six flights up.
- No big deal.
- It's nothing special.
It has to be special.
You leave your mark
where you live.
In some homes,
it's like no one lives there.
Ever noticed?
I know what you mean.
It's a bad sign.
You want my interior to prove...
That you are.
That's it. That you are.
People with nobody home are not,
or not really.
- What if I'm like that?
- Impossible.
But if you are,
you'll never see me again.
Maybe I'll study urban planning.
- Notaries can specialise.
- Really?
- Isn't seamy history your thing?
- That too.
It's an idea that just hit me.
I think it has legs.
- It's a good idea, right?
- Sure.
It's the door at the end.
It's quiet here.
I warn you, it's tiny.
I know what a maid's room
looks like.
The 07 is because of my father.
My parents separated
when I was a kid.
My father's
psychologically unstable.
When I did my coming out,
he freaked.
He'd call me all the time.
Nothing nasty.
He'd just rave on:
fags, the end of the world,
Martians...
It was unbearable.
He called non-stop.
He'd leave hour-long messages.
It couldn't go on.
I didn't want
to get the police involved.
Imagine, lodging a complaint
about your dad.
He wasn't threatening me
or being homophobic.
Nothing.
He was just ruining my life.
So I changed numbers.
My mom and half-sisters
changed, too.
We're an 07 family now.
Sometimes I call him,
by Skype!
When I have plenty of time.
You're beautiful.
I like your body.
Behind your ear, it's soft.
Your stubble...
it scratches.
I like how it scratches.
Your neck.
You smell so good.
Your nipples.
Your stomach.
I like your dick.
It's really beautiful.
I don't know how to describe it,
but I like it.
I like looking at it.
I like taking it in my hand.
I like kissing it.
Your balls are beautiful, too.
Here, in my hand,
they're delicate.
Yet they have weight.
I kiss them.
They're soft.
So soft.
Sh... Stop it.
Should we make love again today?
I don't think so.
Let's leave it at that.
Time to go.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We can meet up before.
Good idea.
I'll call you.
Or you call me.
Whoever gives in first?
I'm going.
Want to come to my place?
I was leaving
and in the staircase...
I can't leave you like this.
Till tomorrow,
when we go to the hospital.
My place isn't huge, you'll see.
But it's...
a bit more...
- Do I get dressed?
- Uh, yes, get dressed.
Then what?
And then?
You'll take your treatment...
and I'll be there.
For 28 days?
It's not long.
Then what?
You'll do the test
and we'll wait for the result.
And by that time,
after three months
and 28 days together,
we'll be strong enough.
Even if I'm sure
you'll be negative.
After that,
if you still want to have sex,
if you're not scared,
we can keep going.
Then what?
We'll keep going.
There'll be no reason to stop.
We'll stay together.
For a long time.
How long?
A long time. I don't know.
Let's say... 20 years.
In 20 years, we'll do so much.
We'll go...
to the supermarket.
Or maybe something huge.
We'll save whales,
or just a kitten.
A cause,
or a world-changing invention.
I don't know... something.
Then what?
After that...
we'll break up, I guess.
Like everyone else.
And we'll be sad
but that's life.
You're sure it's worth it?
Breakfast?
Something sweet this time?
Wait, I forgot my phone.
You're with me.
Who would you call?
Even so...
If you go back, I'll leave.
- It's over.
- You mean it?
I mean it.
If you turn back,
if you look behind you,
you lose it all.
Everything I promised.
Let's go forward.
We're not afraid.
Can I use your phone to call
my mum? I call every Sunday.
Keep it until Monday night.
Wait.
Look.
See?
This is when it all starts.