-Hey!
Do you even know how to drive? Idiot.
-I'm sorry, Sergeant.
-It's "Senior Sergeant."
I was driving fine
until that fat man cut me off.
Now take a look at
what's wrong with my bike.
A familiar face.
-Hello, Officer.
-You again, Jey?
You silly toad.
-Officer...
-Give me your license.
Whenever you see me,
you always ask for my license.
If you need one, why don't you
go and get one yourself?
You committed a traffic violation.
Just hand me your license
and I'll give you a ticket.
Please, I'm begging you.
I have to deliver more flowers.
Delivering flowers has nothing to do
with traffic violations.
-So are you going to arrest me?
-Yes.
-Catch me if you can, boss.
-What are you doing, Jey?
What am I going to do?
I'm going to go full speed!
Bye, boss.
You just insulted an officer.
I'm going to catch you on the other side.
That won't be easy.
Stop!
Hey! Are you a policeman or a slingshot?
You're way too fast.
How can you drive like this, Jey?
What? If you're brave enough to stop me,
you had better arrest me.
Don't push me, Jey.
You have a lot of offenses already,
like scraping a motorbike
and bumping an officer.
And driving too fast.
How did you speed up to 180km?
-A hundred and eighty? Are you crazy?
-Why?
This tuk-tuk can only reach 80km
You can't arrest me for that.
Oh, really?
I will find a reason for sure.
Sergeant, you don't have to look around.
What?
I already renewed
my license and registration.
-And the insurance papers are here.
-Really?
-Are you hiding drugs in here?
-I have to go.
That hurt!
Jey!
-What?
-Come back here!
What's wrong?
Do you want me to go or to come back?
You're giving me a headache.
You drove over my foot! See?
I couldn't have done that.
Even if I could, I wouldn't have done it.
Stop being a smart-ass.
-Can you see it now?
-Okay, I will buy you some medicine.
No!
-Jey, you did it again!
-I'm sorry, Sergeant.
I wanted to know
if you are allergic to any medicine.
No, I have never been allergic to anything
in my whole life except my own hair.
-Oh, okay.
-Just go!
Jey, you!
Look at that guy driving the tuk-tuk.
That's no way to drive.
Look, he's turning right,
but he's signaling for the left lane.
I need to know
how he passed his driving exam.
Did his license fall from a tree?
Hey, Fatty, do you know how to drive?
Just wait and see.
Boss, just follow him. Hurry up.
Wait for us, Fatty!
-If we catch up to you,
-Just shut up!
-we will kick your butt.
-You will?
Damn you, Fatty!
Fatty!
So you think you're fast? Let's see!
Hey, boss. He just cut us off again.
Hey!
Hello, Ms. Kamhom.
Stop. I'm Ton.
-It's Ton.
-Here!
It's not going to get in your eyes.
Not in my eyes, but in my heart, okay?
Why are you here?
-You're not fixing cars today?
-Kamhom.
How many times have I told you?
I'm not a mechanic.
Whatever. It's none of my business.
Anyway, why are you here?
The flowers are here.
Wow, Jey, you always arrive on time.
You are so cute!
She pinched my cheek.
Hey.
Are you selling scraps?
How much will you pay me?
I will use the money to build a tombstone.
What?
You have got too much attitude, Jey.
I'm your uncle.
You better show me some respect.
I know you're my uncle.
If you weren't my mom's brother...
-So what?
-we wouldn't live together for this long.
-What are you doing to help me out?
-Help you out with what?
You get free rent, free food.
I pay for everything.
Do you pay for anything?
Hey. Don't you appreciate
the kindness I show you?
How much did you love your wife?
Of course, I loved her so much.
Here is a real gentleman.
If you loved her so much,
why didn't you follow her when she died?
I was going to follow her,
but I couldn't catch the bus.
Klod, you have to win.
Knock him down!
Klod, beat him to death!
Kill him!
What?
-Come on.
-Knock him out.
Good job, Klod, my best friend!
Move.
Pay up. You bet 3-1. I remember.
Keep your promise.
If I win, you stop bothering
my shop and my family.
Leave me alone.
I hope you understand what I'm saying.
It won't be that easy.
-Kamhom?
-Klod!
Let's go. Quick.
-Go where?
-I'm being chased.
-Let's go. Quick!
-Hey!
Stop! Klod, I'm warning you!
Quick!
You're going to die!
How long are you going to hug me?
We're already here.
Where am I? This is not my house.
Your house is over there.
Oh, right.
Okay, I will get off now.
Are you going to go now?
Wait!
Klod!
Klod! What about this flower?
We are now back at
the Kaeng Krachan Circuit in Phetchaburi
for Thailand Auto Car Racing.
A lot of people have turned up today,
including many fans
of the Singha Racing School.
Here is number 11, Mr. Karan Supapong.
All the cars are at the starting line.
Jack Lamwatt is off first,
with Gunnasak in second.
This is the Thailand
Touring Car Championship
of the Pro Racing Series program.
Jack Lamwatt is in the lead,
followed by Umar Earaman.
-Umar is trying to get the lead right now.
-You dare cut me off?
Somchai Saksriwejkul
has just passed Jack Lamwatt.
-Somchai is now leading the race.
-You can't outdrive me!
Karan Supapong is now leading...
Victory will be mine on the next curve.
...and behind Karan is Jack Lamwatt,
followed by Umar Earaman.
-Jey!
-Hey!
What are you doing, Jey?
-Jack is keeping up with Karan...
-I...
-but Karan still manages to lead.
-I just...
I am...
I...
I didn't know
you wanted to be a race car driver.
-I do.
-That's awesome.
You can practice with the TV.
All right. Is there something
I can do for you?
I was just wondering if you went
to the boxing match last night.
I was. I almost got my money.
There shouldn't have been
a shoot-out last night.
I didn't want to get caught
in the crossfire, so I left early.
Well, why are you asking?
Uma Earaman is just right behind Karan.
Oh, that. I'm glad that you're safe.
-I was wondering
-There, the chase is so exciting.
-if you could do me a favor today.
-He's lifting one wheel, look at Jack.
Sure. I would do you a thousand favors
for you, Kamhom.
Please give this to Klod.
Sure.
Thank you so much, Jey.
Don't forget to give this to Klod.
I will.
I'm leaving now.
-Don't forget to give that to him.
-Sure.
Give that to Klod.
All she thinks about is Klod.
Oh, my...
You seem happy, don't you?
You are always out all day
delivering flowers.
Why don't you stay
and look after our shop?
I have errands to run too, you know.
I know what you mean
by running errands, Mommy.
It's gambling, right?
They're just brain exercises.
I'm afraid of getting Alpheimer.
Hey.
-It's "Alzheimer's."
-Whatever.
At your age,
your brain can't get any better.
Stop making fun of me.
I know who you sent those flowers to.
You know what, Kamhom?
He's not interested in you.
No matter how many flowers you give him,
he won't appreciate them.
But I hope that, one day,
he will realize the meaning
of the flowers I gave him.
Fai, could you wrap the flowers for me
and bring them to the car, please?
He's fast, isn't he?
Too fast.
Klod has always been so aggressive.
He can't control his emotions.
You can tell how he drives
just by the noise.
His mind is much faster than his car.
Each loop is never completed
in the same amount of time.
But this other guy,
his car is faster than his mind.
You have the skills, Ton,
but you're not brave enough.
I want to know what's on your mind.
To be a good driver, you must be decisive.
-That's true.
-Klod, you are way too reckless.
Your driving skills aren't there yet.
Not only do you look horrible,
but your driving is also horrible.
You bastards.
Don't dream of the trophy yet.
Klod, you're way too aggressive.
And you, Ton, you keep hesitating.
You had better try to finish a race first.
I better not see such a performance
from you guys again.
Just look at those guys
who dream of being race car drivers.
Their only opponent
is their self.
The most ambitious one,
the one who tries the hardest,
will become the best.
Choo, here are the flowers you ordered.
Choo.
-Choo.
-Hey. Who's there?
You scared me.
-Hello.
-It's you, Kamhom.
You shouldn't have come all the way here.
It's no problem.
You're a regular customer.
I'm happy to be of service.
You're lovely as always.
Here are the flowers.
They are very beautiful.
-Hey.
-Yes?
-Let me find you something to drink.
-No, thanks.
-I insist.
-I'm just here to deliver them.
I will get you some coffee, okay?
-Don't bother.
-You came all the way.
-Let me do something for you.
-No need. I was obligated to bring them.
Amazing.
Tod looks super cool.
Look at him.
Kamhom.
Choo.
You're such a klutz.
-What?
-A klutz.
-I have to run to the bathroom.
-Okay.
Why am I always so clumsy?
It won't wash off.
You pervert! Why are you in here?
Ask yourself. Why are you here?
Am I there yet?
Put the expensive one down first.
One.
Two.
Three.
Put it nicely here.
And four. Okay.
It's done.
These trophies.
Oh, my!
They're all here.
Mr. Tod!
You're so cool, Mr. Tod.
Oh, this is the one from the Royal's Cup.
A trophy here, a trophy there.
There are trophies everywhere!
Amazing.
It would be an honor if I could touch one.
Yes!
-How do you like my trophy?
-It looks great. Can I take a look?
No, it's mine.
-Please. Can I take a quick look?
-Don't touch it.
-Please let me take a quick look.
-No. Let go of it.
-Jey, let me see it real quick.
-It's mine. Give it back to me.
-Just a small peek, please.
-If you don't let go, I will kiss you.
Why did you slap me, girl?
Do I look like a girl to you?
I guess he has never
greeted anyone properly.
Hello, sir.
I am...
I'm sorry I touched the trophy
without permission.
There are a lot of trophies.
All the best racers
must be from your team.
I believe your team
is the leading team in Thailand, sir.
I would love to touch these cups
because I don't have one at home.
-What? You don't have one?
-I don't.
So what do you use
to drink your coffee, then?
Whatever. What's your name?
My name is Jey.
You stopped laughing so suddenly.
-Kamhom and I are friends.
-I see.
When I have free time, I drive her
so she can deliver flowers.
To be honest, sir,
I have no limit when it comes to driving.
I can even speed up to 120kph
at a 90-degree bend
without touching the brakes.
Would it be possible
for me to be on your team?
Well, you see...
I'm going to be honest with you,
man.
You can't be a race car driver.
How come?
To be a race car driver,
you must have discipline.
And you must practice regularly.
If you don't show up to practice,
you will get cut from the team.
And if you get cut,
can you stand
being even shorter than this?
If you were my manager,
I would beat you up.
What did you say?
Choo!
Choo, the manager asked you
to mop the floor.
And have you prepared the cars
for the drivers yet?
Don't just stand there.
Jeez.
So you're a slave.
"Servant" sounds better.
-Can I tell you one thing?
-Sure.
Your jokes don't work, jerk.
Noted.
Why are you scratching it like that?
This is a race car.
What should I do?
I really want to be a race car driver.
-Do you have heart?
-Absolutely.
-Do you have any money?
-Less than 100 baht.
Oh, dear. Just keep that for the arcade.
Why?
Does having no money mean you can't dream?
Just go to sleep and dream at home, then.
Stop touching the car.
I will get in trouble if someone sees you.
Oh, look.
Look at that guy, boss.
I think I have seen him before.
Who is that? He is really familiar.
He's the guy I told you about.
-Really?
-Yes.
Hey, you.
-Our boss would like to talk to you.
-Yes.
-Oh, no.
-Choo! Get him!
-Hey, fatty! Come here!
-Come here!
-Wait a minute.
-Bring him here, Choo!
-There. I'm in trouble.
-He's such a troublemaker.
Oh, Choo.
We'll be right back.
-Wait!
-Quickly! Run!
Stop it!
Get up!
Hey!
-Damn!
-Hey!
Kamhom!
Kamhom, we need to leave.
-Get in the car.
-Wait. What happened, Jey?
The racing mafia is about to kill me.
Get in the car. I will drive.
-Really?
-Get in now.
Fatty! Stop!
-Where is he going?
-Fatty!
What the hell?
-Stop the car!
-Stop!
Fatty!
My boss just wants to talk to you.
What's wrong with you, Fatty?
You better come back here.
He's not a fatty.
He's just chubby like me.
Whose car is this? It's so beautiful.
It's an Audi. It's gorgeous.
You're Jey, right? We need to talk.
I'm so sorry. I'm in the wrong house.
Your uncle has already told us
how fast you drive.
Him? He's not my uncle.
He's a security guard at this garage.
You damned nephew.
I'm a security guard now, am I?
-You're in a lot of trouble.
-Who slapped me?
-He's gone.
-Only a loser would hit me like that.
Jeez.
If you are a real gentleman,
race me in the circuit,
don't slap me like that.
What can you do?
So?
Back elbow strike!
Hand me a weapon.
You're going to get it.
-That one is too small.
-What?
Hey!
What's going on?
-So what can you do?
-Nothing.
-What?
But I will fight to the death.
Hey!
SINGHA RACING SCHOOL
Welcome to Singha Racing School.
-Thanks, Klod, my dearest brother.
-I'm so happy for you, Jey.
Me too.
-Is this the new idol?
-Shut up.
You're just a servant.
Dealing with me isn't so easy.
Not easy, is it?
-You have got some guts.
-Don't touch me.
Easy come, easy go.
-Why?
-Jey.
-You should get to know Choosak.
-That's not necessary.
He's the chief mechanic.
Hello, Mr. Choo.
I bought some food for you.
You're such a nice guy. Come on, smile.
You're pretty smart.
You know how to kiss ass straight away.
I'm yours now, sir.
We won't have problems
if you keep bringing me food.
-Where is the living room?
-Over there.
-May I be excused?
-Sure.
Wait a minute.
Jey, there's the car
that needs an oil change.
It's hoisted over there.
-Here--
-Hey, Ton. Let me go.
-Why?
-I'm not a mechanic.
I'm the next champion racer of Thailand.
Everyone, make way for me.
-Go right ahead!
-Shut up!
Shut up! No one move!
You're a mechanic.
You're just a delivery guy who got lucky.
The boss saw something in you,
so he put you on our team.
Stop dreaming and get back to work.
"Welcome to Singha Racing School."
Why do I have to clean the tires?
Hey. Move.
I haven't liked the look of him
since day one.
That fat dwarf.
Not you.
Hey, Jey.
What are you doing?
Are you working?
There's no need to work today.
I said no work today.
Don't be such a workaholic.
Just like what that scholar said,
"No work today."
We can relax today.
There's no need to work.
-Relax?
-Yes.
-How exactly do you relax?
-With this.
No.
I don't gamble.
If you don't gamble,
then that means you don't respect me.
All right, then. For your honor.
On second thought,
I don't have any money to gamble.
Hey. You don't need money for this.
We just gamble, man to man.
If you lose, I punch you.
Do you want to play rummy?
-There's too much thinking involved.
-Poker, then.
-I don't know how to play that.
-Make Ten?
-I'm bad at math.
-Blackjack?
-That's too fast.
-So what do you want to play?
War.
Be prepared to get punched.
Son, you have no idea
that I was born for this game.
Set up the table.
-Use the tablecloth.
-Quick.
-Where is he?
-Hey!
-Are you here?
-Who turned the lights off?
Just set the table!
-Go ahead.
-You do it.
Do you want to cut the deck?
There's no need.
Are you scared I might cheat?
If you know how to cheat,
you would not be working here.
You go first.
-Two of clubs?
-That's the lowest.
Three of spades.
Four of diamonds.
Five of hearts.
Six of clubs.
Seven of diamonds.
Eight of hearts.
Nine of diamonds.
-Nine of spades.
-You only won because of the suit.
Do you want to play some more?
Of course.
You go first.
Nine of clubs, two of hearts.
My score is 11.
Ten of spades.
Hey!
Why did he turn two cards at once in War?
You don't need to be here.
Just go work at a casino.
Hey, go check that.
It's locked.
Go ahead.
Stop!
What are you doing here?
I'm going to call the police.
"Call the police"?
You nosy bitch.
Klod, watch out!
Damn you.
Klod!
-Police! The police are here!
-Guys!
There's the police!
Klod, are you hurt?
I'm okay.
Klod, you risked your life to help me.
It wasn't because of you.
I was worried about my shop.
We're at your house now. Get off.
Now.
You saved my life again.
Aren't you scared at all?
What's wrong with you?
You're always in danger.
But you're always there for me.
Do you even realize
that I'm scolding you right now?
I should have left you with the mafia.
Are you leaving now?
Klod.
JAMNONG REPAIR SHOP
Why are you thinking so much?
Kamhom is getting annoying.
Don't you understand?
I can't even help myself.
And now with Kamhom...
I don't know what to do with my life.
Jey.
Please convince Kamhom to leave me alone.
-Hey!
-What's that?
Is that what you think of her?
Take it easy.
But it's okay.
I plan to adopt a sugar baby.
And I will take care
of Kamhom for you, okay?
How about taking care of yourself first?
I don't have to worry
since I live with you.
Even though I don't want her
to get involved,
Kamhom is not an object
that belongs to anyone.
Listen to him. Use your brain.
Hey. Don't be selfish.
If you don't like her,
why did you protect her?
Slow down.
-Why don't you ask your heart?
-Uncle.
-What are you thinking?
-That's good.
-I'm talking to him.
-Good, Uncle.
-What?
-Stop talking.
Jey, Kamhom is the only one
who can encourage me.
Jey, you must help me
because you are so close to her.
Why do I have to help you?
Because we are colleagues.
-"Colleagues."
-Yes.
I might not pass the probation period.
We are like brothers.
We are both humans.
-We're both males.
-If we're both males,
that means we are even.
And why do I have to help you?
Because you and I look alike.
That's true.
So that means you agree to help me?
You know what?
Nothing in this world is free.
That means
you have to do something for me.
-We will start with the first course.
-Okay.
This is the standard course
that teaches you how to drive safely
under traffic regulations.
Hey, Ton, I don't need this course.
This is for kids.
So you want a harder course.
The next one is for an aspiring racer.
Wait. Were you on Broadway?
-It's important.
-What's that?
This course will teach you
both the theory and the operations.
You will know about pit stops,
the manner of racing,
and all the signs and signals.
That sounds good.
And after this course,
you will become a professional.
-The hardest course.
-Yes.
I would really love to learn this course.
-Let's start with the hardest course?
-Yes.
You're a real man.
Please, Mr. Choo.
Why are you talking so politely?
Help me. Please.
Mr. Choo. Help me.
You're paying for the course in full?
-What's wrong with your voice?
-Hey.
Teaching is not that hard,
but Jey, will you have time to work?
It's fine.
I work Mondays to Fridays,
so you will teach me on the weekend.
Everybody else is resting,
but I will be studying.
Is that okay with you?
Sure.
How about the car?
The car?
If you're going to have a race car,
the car must belong to you.
There are fixing and modifying costs.
Do you have any money?
I didn't think so.
Go back to being a mechanic, then.
Hey.
It's not too difficult, Jey.
Just save some money.
If you want to own an expensive car,
just save one baht a day.
It will only take 2,739 years.
Can I wait that long?
Do I need to remind you
where you came from?
You're just a tuk-tuk driver.
Do you understand?
Don't even dream
of being a race car driver.
Hey, man.
You have talked to me that way
so many times.
So what?
Have you seen yourself?
-You're an ugly toad.
-You're crossing the line.
You dream of becoming a racer.
I don't understand.
-Do you even have a brain?
-Hey, man.
-Can your leg even touch the gas pedal?
-That's rude.
-Can you reach the radio?
-That's enough.
If you want to be a race car driver,
you might have to use a walker
to step on the gas.
You're an idiot. Do you understand?
You hurt my leg, Jey!
There's no need to be upset.
Jeez.
Every problem can be solved.
This isn't so difficult.
To be a race car driver,
I must have my own car.
Being a driver
who doesn't have his own car,
is like having a heart
that has never been in love.
Yuck!
I can help with the car.
-Really?
-Yes.
Don't tell me you're going
to steal someone else's car.
I don't want it. I'm a good person.
Have you become a good person already?
All right.
For the car, you can talk to Ton and Klod.
Okay?
-Sure
-It's time.
Time for what?
Give it to me.
-What?
-The plastic bag.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why do you need the plastic bag?
You're the only one
I can trust these days.
You have to keep this a secret, okay?
Don't tell anyone at all.
Come here. I want to tell you something.
What?
You want me to be...
A love consultant?
-I want to tell you something.
-My ear is up here.
They don't have anything large
for the drivers.
How can I fit in this size?
Jey, the uniforms are custom-made
for starting racers,
not substitutes.
-Okay.
-It's good to see you today.
Last time, I passed by Kamhom's shop.
I saw you and Kamhom
eating dinner together.
You told me you would help me,
but I haven't seen Kamhom at all.
Everybody should do
everything by themselves.
What did you say?
I want to help you, but I have no time.
I see.
How about helping me
find the uniforms, then?
How about being a wrestler?
Let's do this like sumo.
-Wait. Is this going to work?
-Push it.
I'll hold my breath
and you press my tummy, okay?
-One, two, three.
Zip it up.
-Stay still.
-Zip it up.
That hurts! My skin! It hurts!
-I told you to press this first.
-Let's try this again.
Wait.
My arm!
-My arm hurts.
-Put it in.
-There you go.
-Put it in. Okay, the other one.
Are you okay?
-Pull the sleeves up. Yes.
-How is that?
Zip it up now. On my count.
-One, two.
-Yes!
-Yes! We're done!
Believe me,
I am happier to fit in this
than to be a champion.
Love consultant!
I swear on a bunch of olives,
I'm the number one love consultant.
I hereby proclaim the oath
of love consultants...
Rule number one.
I must be the reflection of the problem.
What kind of person is Klod?
I sent him flowers,
but he didn't even smile at me.
I think I'm doing my best
as a woman in love.
Jey, what should I do?
-Jey.
-Yes?
Jey, you're not helping me
with my problems.
I would like to help,
but to solve your problem,
I need to have more information.
Can you give me more information?
Rules of love consultants.
There are too many rules.
If I follow only a few of them,
no one would know.
2. GIVE CHOICES, NOT ANSWERS
Rule number two.
Love consultants must give choices,
not answers.
I have a way to get Kamhom
out of your life.
What's that?
The only solution.
Tell her the truth.
You don't like her and you hate her.
Just tell her. It's as simple as that.
Are there any other solutions?
I'm not a good person,
but I don't want to make a woman cry.
How manly of you.
Come on. This is the best way.
It will be quick.
Rule number three, don't force things.
You said that rule number three is,
"Don't force things."
Just listen. Do as I told you.
-You don't like her, right?
-Yes.
Didn't you tell me she's annoying?
She's over there. Go tell her.
Are you scared?
Are you a real man?
-Hey.
-What a coward.
-Don't waste time. Go tell her now.
-What are you doing here?
-Klod.
I have told you so many times.
Leave me alone.
Sure.
-Peekaboo!
-Oh, jeez!
I'm back.
I'm used to that now.
Flowers for you.
Hey! I'm serious this time.
You should find someone who loves you.
Don't waste your time on me.
I have never loved you.
I have never cared about you.
Hey.
You're so mean.
Are you really mad at me?
If you didn't care, why did you ask?
Stop crying.
Were those crocodile tears?
Were they?
You're so cute when you're being kind.
Excuse me.
Oh, jeez.
Does it hurt?
Here's an ointment.
Kamhom.
I think
you should look for someone else.
If there...
is another guy who might like you,
you should give him a chance.
Jey.
Why do you like forcing me
to do this and that?
That's the guy
who told you to tell me this, right?
If he's going to tell you something,
what would you say?
If he's brave enough,
he can come inside. I'm right here.
The weather is so nice today.
Here is a flower for you, Kamhom.
Thanks.
Kamhom!
Why did you do this to me?
-I'm in a bad mood today.
-Look at all this blood.
"A bad mood"?
-Jey.
-What?
Didn't even check her mood?
Look at all this blood.
How about you leave
and wait for me at home?
I will be there.
Is he crazy?
He came in here when I was in a bad mood.
Take it easy, Kamhom.
I...
Take it easy.
Jey.
I don't understand why the person I like
won't even look at me.
Yes.
Why does the person we like
never ever look at us?
But it's all right.
I can wait.
I will wait
and be beside you forever.
Jey.
You sound like you're my boyfriend.
No, not at all.
Rule number four.
Love consultants
must always be encouraging.
You deserved it.
I told you not to see
Kamhom during that time.
I kept telling you
until my mouth almost exploded,
but you never listen to me.
-When the hell did you tell me, dude?
-What?
When did you tell me, sir?
You told me you would be on my side.
To be honest with you, I can't do it.
Rule number five,
love consultants must not take sides.
Jey.
Why are you here? Move it. Move.
I can't take sides, you know?
I must be right in the middle.
So you're true to your words?
It's great that you're sitting right here.
-I feel so comfortable.
-Sure.
Now you're leaning on her.
COFFEE HOUSE
A cup of coffee, please.
Out of all the coffee shops...
-Klod!
-And now she left for him.
-What?
-Have you already ordered something?
-I already did.
-Hey, Klod. Where have you been?
-Excuse me, Kamhom.
-Jey.
Oh, dear. Sorry. Have you had breakfast?
-I have.
-You have?
-Yes.
-Good.
What did you eat? Was it yummy?
-It was good.
-Okay.
Chai has just finished fixing a car.
I plan to do a test drive.
I wonder if anybody
would like to come with me?
Intrega DC5, turbocharged.
It's so fast.
-Are you tired?
-I want to drive that.
-A little...
-I want to.
-Like always...
-You want to drive, right?
-There. You better help me first.
-I should order some coffee.
-I will take care of it.
-Do your job.
Klod.
Rule number six, love consultants
must build other people's confidence.
-Ton.
-What?
Seriously, do you really like Kamhom?
Of course.
I have liked her since the first time
I met her at the parking lot.
-What? The parking lot?
-Yes.
That's so romantic.
It may not really be romantic,
but it's always been in my heart.
Have you ever thought
that Kamhom might already
have someone else on her mind?
What type of person does Kamhom like?
I think that she might like a short guy.
Maybe a tall guy?
She might like a dark-skinned guy.
No, a light-skinned guy.
Maybe a chubby guy.
No one likes a chubby guy.
Maybe she likes someone
with a perfect body.
What if she already has a boyfriend?
I don't really care. I can wait.
If you love someone,
you need to be patient.
That's how you show your love, you know?
You will have more enemies, then.
Jey, I want to talk to you about Kamhom.
What kind of man carries a handkerchief?
Hey, in movies,
the hero tends to carry a handkerchief
and he hands it to the heroine
when she cries.
Here. Thank you.
Also, in movies,
the heroine tends to tease the hero
by blowing her nose on the handkerchief
and handing it back to him.
Have you been reading too many novels?
I could say the same for you.
You also read Broken Heart Club.
That's even more melodramatic.
I'm just killing time.
It's a bit sad, really.
Well, I'm still glad
I could help you stop crying.
Rule number seven,
love consultants cannot be too emotional.
Why do I have to be sad?
There's no need to be sad.
-What are you guys doing?
-What?
What are you guys doing?
-Nothing.
-Hey, Jey.
I was just talking to Ton.
Talking to him makes me feel pretty good.
It makes me feel comfortable.
-Like being a child again, right?
-Yes, I feel like a kid.
By the way,
Kamhom and Ton
kind of look like each other.
-What?
-Like siblings.
You should ask your dad
if he left any babies around.
No, Jey. No way.
I have to tell you something.
Seriously, we are all like siblings.
Jey, I really respect you.
And Ton, you're like my little brother.
You're so cute.
Jey, you're also so cute.
I have to go now. Bye.
Being called "little brother"
by the one you love
hurts the most.
I agree.
What a sad life.
Working during the day
and being a security guard at night.
Poor me.
Hello, Tee.
Yes, it's me.
It's a big match tonight.
I bet Manchester United will win.
I'm confident.
Manchester United will surely win.
Okay.
If they win,
you can get the money I owe you
from the money I win.
That's the deal, all right?
It's a win-win for both of us. Deal.
But who has Alex Ferguson's phone number?
-I need to tell him.
-So he bets on football.
The boss must know about this.
Hey!
-Who's there?
-That hurt.
Was it just a dog?
Why are you howling at this time?
I'm scared.
You won't stop?
Hey!
That hurts!
You stammering dog.
Why do you howl when you stutter?
Did he just break my head?
Where is he?
He's so fast.
I will let the boss know.
-Hey. Jey!
-What?
What did you do?
He's not going to die.
I didn't really want to bet tonight.
I always lose money.
My eyes are somehow twitching.
I don't think Lady Luck is with me.
I'm getting scared
for tonight's Bayern VS Munich match.
-Choo.
-Yes?
No. Listen to me first, Klod.
This isn't what you think.
Klod, listen to me first.
Wait.
I'm running out of blood.
Oh, dear. Why did you punch him?
This is between him and me.
-Why didn't you tell me first?
-I tried to tell you.
I called your name.
I said, "Klod!" repeatedly.
Did you listen to me at all?
First, you told me your plan
was not to hurt me.
I don't mind being hurt,
but I'm afraid that Vichakarn
will see the blood on the floor.
-Has the bleeding stopped yet?
-Not yet.
A thousand baht for the blood to stop?
1,200 baht?
1,300 baht?
1,700 baht?
Okay, how about 2,000?
The blood has dried.
Okay, 200 baht for now, then.
Damn!
-You said 2,000.
-Take it easy.
I will get some wipes
and clean up the blood.
Let me take the car first.
You're a pain in the ass.
Jey, I got punched
too many times last night.
I can't even use face cream.
-You better pay me.
-Klod was the one who did that.
I didn't do anything.
Whoever did this must pay.
Klod did it,
but I have to be the one who pays.
Just give it to me.
Hey, you guys.
You all look suspicious today.
-What's going on?
-Nothing.
Be careful about what you say.
We are not gay.
I hate homosexuals.
Ton.
Well.
Don't tell me you guys
tried to do something here.
Don't let me find out.
So what?
Or do you like swing parties?
I can help.
How about a threesome?
Would you like that?
Are you okay?
-Take your hand off my butt now.
-Look at him.
You grabbed my butt.
You're insulting me,
an assistant team manager.
He's right.
Jey! Just you wait.
I will squeeze your balls.
Stop! Don't do that!
-How was that?
-Well?
How do you feel?
My weapon.
-Vichakarn.
-What?
We shouldn't fight.
-Why do you guys have to fight?
-So?
-Vichakarn? Sit down.
-Yes.
-No one cares for me except you.
-Correct.
I love you.
-We can talk properly.
-Here.
Who hit me?
It was someone behind me. Who was it?
Who did it?
Who was brave enough
to hit me on the head?
That hurt! Who did that?
He should die.
Hey!
-Stop! Just go, guys!
-Hey.
-That's enough. We don't need him dead.
-Let's go.
We need to cover this up.
I bet you don't recognize me.
Who was that?
Let's go.
-Quick. There's a CCTV here.
-Move the car.
-Oh, no.
-Isn't it obvious?
-They're also topless.
-They ran like mice.
We have try-outs next week.
What should I do with you guys?
Boss, it's obvious.
I think you should fire them.
I never give anyone a second chance.
Unless that person shows me his potential.
The three of you still have this chance.
An opportunity like this
doesn't come often,
so do your best.
Wow, Jey!
I can't believe you guys
did such a great job!
-Teach me sometime.
-Sure.
Unbelievable. What I taught you
were just the very basics.
-Is that true?
-Sure thing.
-Just the basics?
-Yes.
-I forgot to tell you.
-What?
-I only pressed the pedal during the race.
-Amazing.
-I didn't even step on the gas.
-Really?
When I checked it again,
the hand brake was still in my hand.
Hey!
You shouldn't brag before you win.
Jey, your time isn't bad.
I want you to be our substitute for now.
Yes.
I'm so happy today.
We all became race car drivers.
I'm going to sing now.
There are a lot of songs available.
For real? Don't lie, okay?
Sure. I'm not lying.
Look, this is a new one.
This machine has it?
Your dream finally came true!
He's not a race car driver yet.
Only a substitute.
Aren't we all substitutes, Mhee? Shut up.
-He's right.
-Hear me out.
Remember this.
The boss picked you
-because of your personality,
-Which is terrible.
-skill,
-You don't have much.
-experience,
-Very low.
-manner,
-Very uneducated.
-and development.
-Slow like a traffic jam.
-Just take the tollway then, idiot.
-What?
You know everything, don't you?
The boss isn't looking
for any of the things you just said.
If he's going to choose one racer,
he must pick the best gentleman
who is skilled and improves on his own.
-Cheers to the new race car drivers!
-Cheers!
Grilled pork for our victory.
-We have waited for so long.
-That's right!
-One, two, three!
-Wait.
-What?
Where's mine?
You ate too fast, Jey.
I didn't eat too fast.
Who ate my damn pork?
Whoever took the pork
-must be looking guilty.
-Yes.
Why are you shaking?
-Your hands are shaking. Why?
-Choo, are you shaking?
-It's so cold.
-"It's so cold."
-It's so cold I can see your breath.
-"Cold" my ass.
This is amazing.
We can save a lot on wages this month.
You're being stingy.
Oh, I'm stingy?
I have to save up for my daughter
who spends so much for love.
I'm not as mean as you, Mommy.
Here, pick one. A small one or a big one?
I know why you put this pot
in front of Daddy's picture.
Because there is a meaning, right?
This cactus has a meaning.
"Toughness."
It doesn't need water.
And the most important thing is,
it's perfect for a skinny
and stingy person like you, right, Mommy?
I wanted to tell you the meaning
of the cactus a long time ago.
This is so stupid.
Like father, like daughter.
Mommy.
-Go.
-What are you doing here?
You have to tell your son
to close this shop.
My boss doesn't like anyone
getting in his way.
My shop is legal.
You guys are breaking the law.
-Would you like to die? Would you?
-Leave my parents alone.
You have to tell your son
to close this shop.
If you're going to drive like that,
you should take a vacation
and drive along the beach.
I lost 200 baht because of you.
You had better pay me back.
I hate gambling.
The reason I race
is because I love to drive.
Is that so? That's too bad.
Your dad was a legendary race car driver,
but you're nothing like him.
Be glad he's already dead.
Otherwise, he would have to hide his face
in shame for having a son like you.
Why are you such a shitty person?
Are you protecting him?
What is your relationship with him?
I don't like people who are all talk.
Hey!
You know what?
Smart-asses like you
should be knocked down a peg or two.
-Hey! Don't pick a fight with me.
-Hey!
Hey!
Take it easy!
Are you crazy, Klod?
Can't you just keep it cool
when there's a problem like this?
If you're still aggressive,
then you can't be a driver.
Choo, if Klod gets fired,
they will have to find
another race car driver.
-Will they?
-Hey.
Jey, what do you mean?
I... worry about the team.
-Why am I stuttering?
-You...
Why are you stuttering like me?
I'm so sorry, boss.
I don't know why I acted like that.
-I'm so sick of the wealthy.
-Why?
They have all the money,
but none of the emotions.
Yes...
Those... people,
they don't even have money
and they don't have feelings either.
They have such foul mouths
and they never learn their lesson.
Who's that?
I don't know if you have noticed,
but people like them tend to be loners.
They don't have many friends.
I'm so glad I still have friends.
Do you know why you're in this team?
What do you really want in life?
Are you sick?
You're always following people around.
Klod is at the usual place.
Just meet him there.
-He's at--
-Klod, everyone is worried about you.
Who would care about me?
No one is worried about me besides you.
I know what happened to you.
I know that you're confused
and need to get things off your chest.
Let it all out. Go ahead. Vent on me.
Do whatever you need to.
You might feel better.
Crazy woman.
You always show up at the worst times.
From now on,
just stay away from me.
This song is for Kamhom.
Ton asked me to sing this song for you.
If you have a change of heart
I would be sad for sure
But it won't be too long
Before the pain fades away
This pain will last
This pain, I won't forget
This pain cuts me deeper
-Will you forget this pain?
-"Will last."
No.
You have to sing, "I won't forget."
Those are the lyrics.
It hurts.
It hurts more than you can understand.
It hurts more than ever.
More than anyone.
You have no idea. You don't understand.
I totally understand.
You don't understand.
Because you have never loved anybody.
You would not understand.
Yes, I do.
This pain will last
This pain, I won't forget
Now they're hugging.
This pain cuts me deeper
Damn it! Turn it off!
Hey, Ton.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you hugging her?
Take your hands off her.
Kamhom, are you okay?
I will take care of her.
Hey, you told me you would help me.
I can take care of her.
But her mother asked me
to take care of her.
And now she's drunk,
so I have to take care of her.
Jey, this is my only chance
to get close to Kamhom.
-You have to help me.
-You'll get a lot more chances,
but not this one because she's drunk.
Let go of Kamhom. Kamhom, come back here.
-Jey, let me--
-Ton, you have to listen to me.
No. Stop crying.
Oh, shit.
All over my face... Wait.
I need to puke too.
Ton, hold her.
Hey.
My favorite shirt is dirty.
My shirt!
What should I do?
Kamhom.
Hey, Ton. Please watch her.
I will be right back.
I have to clean my shirt real quick.
-Jey, you can take my shirt.
-Hey! Don't do that, Kamhom.
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, Ton, please take care of her.
I will be right back. Do you understand?
You don't need to come back.
What?
-Just hurry back here.
-Okay.
You're tender like always
You're taking care of me like always
Those eyes are familiar
And I realize you're changing your mind
You may want to end things between us
Then be with your new man
But you still pity me
And don't be hard
On the one you used to love
The weaker I am for your tenderness
The longer it will hurt us
Please say goodbye if you fall out of love
And quit hurting my feelings
Please tell me the bad news
That you're getting rid of me
If you don't care, don't stay around
Just say it once and for all
Say goodbye and end things
You don't have to care even if it kills me
Even if it kills me
Kamhom, Ton was so mad at Klod
that he dared him to race him.
I want you to be there.
Hey, are you ready, Ton?
-Hey.
-What?
I think something is wrong
between those two.
It's pretty odd. Stop talking. Come here.
Oh, dear.
Whoever loses the race
has to stay away from Kamhom.
Jey, why did you bring me here
to watch this?
Well, because...
I don't really know.
It's ridiculous, don't you think?
Are you ready?
-One hundred percent.
-The finish line is where Jey is.
If you have to choose,
which one will you choose?
Will you pick the winner or the loser?
But if I were you,
I would pick someone who's not competing.
What?
For real men like us,
off-track racing is perfect.
I have to be their referee.
I was forced to. I have to go now.
Would you like to come with me?
-Peekaboo!
Hey. What are you playing at?
Is that your scared look?
The war over a girl begins.
-Are they fighting for this princess?
-Yes.
-Choo!
-I thought you would hit me on the head.
Hey, referee!
The racers are ready!
What are you waiting for?
Wait a minute.
What is he looking for?
Look at him.
Why did he grab those napkins?
-So he could blow his nose?
-"Blow his nose..." Hey!
-He's using them as flags.
-What flags?
There are no flags, so he's using napkins.
-That's shabby. Hey!
-Just use them for now.
I have nothing else.
Stop talking. Take a look.
-How about you use your tooth as a flag?
-Are you nuts?
Klod is here!
Faster, Klod!
Now Klod is at the finish line.
Yes. That went exactly as planned.
The beginning of a breakup.
Ton.
-I lost.
-No.
You're the winner.
Thank you for your kindness.
After hearing that,
now I really know
that we can only just be friends.
Listen to me.
You showed me
how fervent the efforts
of someone with a brave heart can be.
We can be friends, okay?
Klod.
Klod!
Klod! Just stop!
What are you doing?
This is so stupid.
What's going on between us,
it's all in your head.
Have you ever asked me about it?
Have you ever listened to me?
How can you explain this?
Jey.
I would like you to tell Klod
that I'm sorry.
I can now accept the truth
that Klod will never understand
the meaning of the flowers
I have been giving him.
Kamhom.
I have to confess something.
I want to tell you that I caused the fight
between Klod and Ton.
But I did everything because...
I'm sorry.
Whatever happens, I want you
to be there at the race tomorrow.
Please forgive me.
You showed me
how fervent the efforts
of someone with a brave heart can be.
We can be friends, okay?
Ton.
I don't want to talk.
Ton, I'm sorry
for being such an idiot.
Your apology is not necessary.
The only thing that you should do
is take care of Kamhom.
-Ton, but Jey...
-I know.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
A real man like me
will always forgive you.
I totally understand.
The heart can't be forced.
But you...
punched me pretty hard.
The Singha Racing Team is proud
to introduce our newest driver. Not you.
-It's Jey!
-Jey! Yes!
-Hey, where is he going?
-Jey!
Why didn't you walk this way?
-Look at him.
-Hey.
A real racer doesn't race off the track.
-I can win everything by myself.
-Amazing.
You're the man, Jey!
You won this match
even before it had begun.
Not at all.
-Not because of your skill...
-What?
but because of your heart.
-That was so cool.
-So we three have to win today.
-What? Three people?
-What?
Then that means
you will let me race today?
Yes.
-Really?
-What?
You're not kidding, right?
-Yes!
-Jey! Klod!
Quit it already!
Listen to me.
-Please get ready for the race now.
-Yes. Go.
-Go right ahead.
-Go.
What are you saying?
-They already left?
-Yes.
-Go. Just go.
-Stammering like this...
I don't want to talk to you.
-Go!
-I want to tell you...
-There's no need to. Just go.
-But...
What is it?
I'm sorry.
I have been cruel to you,
even though you have always cared for me.
From now on,
you don't have to follow me around.
I will take care of you.
Welcome back to the Thailand
Super Cars Championship 2011.
There are 20 race cars in the race.
Today's race is very intense.
And above all, today is the debut
of three newcomers
from the Singha Racing School,
Jey, Klod, and Ton.
These three used to race in club races
before they got in the Thailand
Super Cars Championship this year.
Now I think everyone
is ready to watch the race.
One minute until the race begins.
I'm going to win.
All the drivers are ready.
And the lights are off!
The race has begun for the Thailand
Super Cars Championship 2011.
Car number 44 had a good start,
getting to first place beautifully.
He's taking the first spot.
Oh, Klod from Singha Racing School
is coming up to the lead.
Jey is trying to get ahead of another car.
And now he is in third place,
with Ton in second place
and Klod in first place.
If he can hold that position to the end,
he is going to be the champion for sure.
Is he going for it?
He is still leading this race.
Go, Klod.
Klod, you can do this!
Oh, there it is. What happened?
Klod's car is off the track
and the crowd is really disappointed.
Now the crowd in this stadium is bored.
So that makes Jey the leader,
with Ton in second place.
The crowd is cheering.
Ton is racing for first place,
and Jey can tell.
There are just a few laps left now.
This is the last corner in the Thailand
Super Cars Championship 2011.
He is going into the straight part soon.
Ton is still coming along the left side.
Can he make it? Yes, he can!
He's in first place now
and Jey is in second place.
Those two racers
from Singha Racing School are awesome.
I lost.
No one is a loser.
There are only winners.
In every race, everyone is a winner.
And you're a winner too.
All right.
She's cute.
Excuse me, but are you flirting with me?
I really admire you.
You're so handsome.
Pointing at my heart too.
Sorry for being direct,
but do you have a boyfriend?
No answer means she really likes me.
I want to ask you a direct question.
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
No answer means "yes."
Jey, I forgot to introduce you.
This is my girlfriend.
Here she is.
Jey, have you met my girlfriend?
He's the one I told you about. He's...
-Hello.
Ton, you jerk.
You already know him, right?
He's my brother.
-Jey.
-Hey.
We will be your love consultants.
-You two are working as a team?
-Yes.
-Were you trying to fool me?
Is it fun to play with someone's heart?
You two are not related.
If I can't kill you two today,
don't call me a real man.
-An elephant is coming after us!
-Jey!
Run away! Run!
-Catch me if you can!
-You bastards!
-Be careful! Hey!
-Hey, wait for me, Ton, Klod!
How can I find a wife
if my legs are like this?
Wait for me! Klod, Ton!
Damn your long legs! Come pick me up!
Hey! Jey!
What a reckless driver!
Step on the brake!
Hey! Are you a policeman or a slingshot?
You're way too fast.
Dad, you're the best!
You won the trophy again!
-Here's the trophy...
-Amazing!
and the olive wreath.
Dad, one day,
I'll become a great racer like you.
Please always be there for me.
-I believe you can do it.
-Yes, Dad.
Kick!
You!
What are you trying to do?
Don't! Can't you see my leg cast?
God! Give me back my crutch!
-Let's go.
-Why me?
Scene 87. Cut 1. Take 3.
End slate. Camera AB.
Where's the microphone?
That's a wrap!