Sometimes loneliness makes us depressed,
happy, strong, and weak.
“Loneliness may weaken one’s heart or make it be strong when he left”.
Sometimes we yield to the heart.
But if one day he's gone,
we need to learn to live by ourselves.
Oh.
Hello.
Hi.
How could you get up here?
I just... asked the security guard.
Really?
Then,
How do you know my room number?
I asked if he know who came from Chachoengsao.
And he said you're in this room.
Correct?
Yeah.
Have you eaten yet, Korn?
Do you want to eat something
before the afternoon class?
I'm so hungry.
If you're not done preparing yourself,
I can wait inside.
No, it's alright
I'm done. Just give me a second.
You don't have to hurry.
Wait.
Let's eat something.
Now?
Yep.
[The story of love]
[that once happened]
[was filled with smiles and tears]
[It's like the stars]
[so beautiful]
[and was filled with fond of memories]
[It's like the season]
[that our heart felt lonely]
[You're the breeze I missed in summer]
[The warmth that was there every time I wished for]
[It made me wet on a rainy day]
[Please let me escape from here]
[from those good memories that I still remember]
[Please let me disappear]
[Because you stay and don't go away]
[Be a flower as lovely as a shining star]
[and still live in the dark lonely planet]
[It always has me, a keeper]
[who never walked away]
[The story of love]
[that once happened]
[was hidden even after a long time]
(Remember Me Episode 5)
[The photos from the past]
(First year, second semester)
Hello, grandpa.
How are you doing?
Lately? I'm doing great.
But I have to study quite hard.
Can I call you back tonight? I'm late now.
Tell everyone I miss them all, bye.
Hey, don't you have classes today, Chompu?
I only have the afternoon classes today.
How about you, Nuck-Nan?
If I remember correctly,
you have classes today, right?
You memorize details about me so well.
Is it because you have feelings for me?
You're imagining things.
Should I answer your call?
Sorry, my hand slipped.
Lol, you're too good at flirting.
Hahaha.
We've been talking for weeks,
but you never ask me about the research.
Have you forgotten about it?
The professor is staring at me, Chompu.
Let me pretend to study.
I'll text you again at night.
Let's make a video call this time.
Changing the subject, huh?
I'll do that if I'm free.
Alright, students. That's it for today.
Let's meet again in the next class.
Hm.
Hey.
What should we do tonight?
Wanna hang out and dance with us?
Not tonight.
Why? What happened?
Yeah, you were not going anywhere these past few days.
It's weird.
I just...
Just what?
I'm tired of going out.
Is that true? I bet it's because of a girl.
What? Do I know her?
Hey! What girl? It's not that
I'm sure of it!
No.
Let's go eat. I'm hungry.
Booo.
I'm certain it's a girl.
Let's find out who it is.
Can I eat fish?
Golf? Are you going to eat?
Yes.
Do you want fish?
Yeah.
Whoaa.
Is it good like the pickled fish in our province?
How could it be that good?
That's true.
Look.
Now, there's a new constitution for people.
This changes nothing.
They will revise it anyway.
It's better than having no hope at all.
Golf.
Huh?
About our assignment...
Do you wanna do it at the faculty building
at night like always?
I think today...
we should work in your room.
I want a change of mood.
Um.
Sure.
My room?
Yeah, you room. What else?
So I can look at something new.
Hurry up. We have to go to our class
I don't want to be late.
The professor gave us lots of homework today.
We just met only a few times,
but he gave us a month load of work.
Well. Just do it.
It's hard.
Korn.
Can I use your internet?
I want to search for something.
Go ahead.
You didn't leave any work unfinished, right?
I'm gonna try doing question 8.
Hey.
Wait.
- Are you okay?
- Just a moment.
Ehh.
You can continue.
Here is the internet.
Right here.
This one.
Here.
Okay. So I can use it now?
Yes.
[Please let me escape from here]
[from those good memories that I still remember]
[Please let me disappear]
It's connected. Champ!
Hehe.
Hi, everyone.
How is it, my grandson?
Does studying make you tired?
I'm fine.
But...
It's like what sis told me... it's a lot.
Speaking of sis...
Why are you there?
You're still not graduated, aren't you?
No. I'm here for the internship.
Internship?
Is there any place for that near our house?
Cool, right?
Well.
Is it me or Champ looks thinner these days?
A little bit.
Yeah.
I rarely have time to eat.
Because.
I have to wake up and do everything by myself.
It's...
That's it.
I think I'm doing good.
Hahaha.
Good boy.
By the way.
Lucky is healthy, don't worry about it.
But it waits for you in front of our house every day.
It misses you.
Where is it?
Lucky! Stop it!
Lucky! No!
Are you sick?
It's just a normal cough.
Grandpa.
You're old. Please take a good care of yourself.
Avoid fried foods.
Champ.
Living there,
you must be exhausted.
All of us
are always by your side.
If you're tired,
you can come home and relax at any time.
Champ.
No matter what happens,
you have to be strong, got it?
And no matter where I am,
I'll always cheer you up.
What's that?
You make me get emotional.
I have to go.
There're a lot of assignments
I have to submit tomorrow.
Then
I'll end the call. Let's talk again next time.
[The pictures of you still look the same]
[But we can't go back again]
[To the time when we were close]
[If we could turn back time]
[I would love to go through everything with you again]
[Those familiar words]
[I can still remember them]
Hello.
How is it?
Do I look the same as my photo?
You're pretty, Chompu.
You're exaggerating.
Hey, Nuck-Nan.
So what I want to ask is...
Nuck-Nan.
Nuck-Nan!
Hey!
What?
Who is it?
You keep smiling all week.
Is it your new girl?
Fuxk you.
Let me talk to my brother first.
Let's talk again next time, bye.
Do you really have to scold me?
Just you wait.
There's a law for Computer-related crime 2007
I'll sue you. Just wait and see.
You once cursed me in Hi5.
That's the end of you.
You're going to use law against me?
How dare you?
Take care of yourself first.
How many times did you stand Name up?
More than 10 times.
You're the one who will be sued.
Nuck-Nan.
Huh?
Can I borrow your computer?
I'm tired for real.
Go ahead.
New mic and new camera. Try it out.
I'll go pee.
You have unread messages.
Sorry, I didn't have time to use computer.
Sorry, I was busy studying.
I'm sorry, Name. Let's talk later.
What are you doing?
I'm really exhausted.
I didn't intend to ignore you.
Let's wait for this period to pass.
Let's talk later, Name.
I don't want to pick up a fight with you.
Food is ready! You can come get it.
Come here.
Can I come in?
Let's eat.
What's wrong?
Did you have a quarrel with Em?
Em is studying.
It's normal to have new society and friends.
(He promised me.)
But he didn't break your promise.
He still talks to you.
Just less than before.
(He promised me. He promised to me!)
(He promised! He promised!)
He has to live his life!
And you have to live yours too!
You can't stay in your room forever.
I tried everything I can to help you.
Every way that is possible.
But you never try to help yourself.
If you still be like this,
You'll be the one who loses
I'll let you figure it out yourself.
And if you don't want to eat,
then don't.
Em.
[If we could turn back time]
[I would love to go through everything with you again]
[Those familiar words]
[I can still remember them]
Em.
Huh?
This is for you.
Thank you.
Whoa.
Good thing I was around, so I bought it for you.
Yeah.
You see,
I studied very hard
and joined extracurricular activity.
Hm.
Damn it
I have a quiz today too.
Can I ask you something?
Um.
Are you fighting with Name?
You got the news quicker than ITV.
Ha.
You fool!
It's not ITV, but TITV nowadays.
You're old-fashioned.
Oh.
How is it, then?
What are you arguing about?
Is it because you don't have time?
Yeah.
You know.
I don't even have time to eat.
And I have books to study.
Lots of them.
I think...
You haven't tried hard enough.
I understand Name.
He is the one waiting.
I understand his reason.
How so?
So...
Think about it.
Whether you have time or not,
at least you should let him know.
But you just let him wait and feel neglected.
If it were me, I would run away
I'll surely leave you.
There, there.
I said it because I mean well.
Alright
I'll figure this out.
Let's talk about you.
About what?
What?
Of course it's about how you lied to Golf
that your name is Korn
not "Gun".
Keep it down!
You bastard.
How do you know?
Whoaa.
Sir Gun.
How long have we been friends?
I asked you classmate if they know Gun.
And no one knows.
There's only Korn and Korn alone.
Be quiet!
Shh.
I don't have the guts to tell him.
I'm scared.
Okay.
Get a grip on yourself.
Tell him the truth when you're ready.
Don't lie for too long.
It'll be a problem later.
Um
I know.
Hey.
Why the sullen face?
Stop it
I'll buy you a drink.
Um.
But you have to buy me food next time.
Deal?
What?
What kind of bullshxt is that?
I already bought you this sandwich.
Come on.
No, you fool.
What?
I already treated you.
Do you want me to shout?
I'll shout out your name.
G... G
Read!
Korn.
Hey.
I said the right one.
Shut up.
Hi, Mr. 8.
Long time no see.
Hello there.
Yeah. It's been a long time.
There's a lot of things to change
when you went to university.
How have you been?
Well, I have to adjust a lot.
Fortunately, I have a good friend.
Is that friend better than me?
Mr. 8, you're always number one.
Mr. 8.
There's...
something I want to tell you.
What is it?
Actually,
I...
I may not be available these days
because I have lots of work to do.
No, you're good.
Just text me when you're free.
Hey.
Do you want to eat mango with me?
Oh, right.
Em told me he won't be online in MSN for a whole month.
(Why did he tell you?)
He is like in a different time zone with you.
So he asked me to tell you.
But that's all.
(Why didn't he tell me?)
He's acting like normal people.
And you should do that too.
(Why did it turn out like this?)
You chose to live like this yourself
and you should accept it.
(Why?)
(I don't understand.)
Are you really not going to talk to me?
I talked to the doctor.
She said you can talk.
But you chose to use sign language.
Now you're going as far as writing it down.
Why?
You really don't want to talk to me?
Or do you want to be mute for real?
[If we could turn back time]
[I would love to go through everything with you again]
[Those familiar words]
[I can still remember it]
Nid?
You're staying up late and doing the laundry like me!
Are you alright?
You can tell me anything.
It's nothing.
Forget it.
Hey.
Although I'm not your family member,
if you're facing any trouble that I could help,
you can tell me right away.
So.
We're single moms. I understand you.
We have almost no one to rely on.
When Em's dad passed away,
Em was still a little kid.
I had to work hard like you.
Even though we're now a mother
there's still a little girl inside us.
I never understood my mother.
Until I became one.
I missed her.
If she was still here,
I would be scolded for
doing the laundry so late at night
I'm sure of it.
Nid.
If you're really tired
and your mother is still there,
you can ask her for good advice.
Alright?
Yes
I'll go to sleep.
Thank you so much.
Hello.
How are you, Nid?
Hello, mom.
Are you still up this late?
I already slept.
How about you?
I answered your call as soon as I saw it.
What's wrong?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
When I had a fight with you
and refuse to talk to you,
does it hurt?
Of course.
But you are my daughter
I'm fine the second you smile at me.
Then, when I was pregnant before graduation,
were you mad at me?
No.
But I was afraid...
that people would look down on you.
I don't want you to overthink it.
I was afraid you were not ready.
But for me, I'm always ready.
Ready for all the problems that come at you.
At that time, instead of the graduation gown,
you saw me in the maternity clothes.
In the past, no matter what problem I had,
I always vented my anger on you.
I never understood you.
But you always try to understand me.
If I could go back in time,
I wouldn't do that.
I'm really sorry, mom.
Never mind. I understand.
Even though you're now a mother,
you'll always be a little girl in my eyes.
You can call me whenever you want.
Okay.
It's late. You should go to sleep.
Okay, bye.
[If we could turn back time]
[I would love to go through everything with you again]
[Those familiar words]
[I can still remember it]
Hi, mom.
What's up? I'm practicing cheerleading.
It's almost midnight and you're still practicing?
Are you applying for world cup or something?
It's almost the Freshy Game day.
Take care. Eat properly.
Don't die before me.
Ehhh.
Em.
So... I want to ask you something.
Um.
What is it?
The thing is.
So.
Look at this.
What's that?
My academic record.
Look.
And...
why are you showing me this?
Because
I want to show how good Tutor Chompu is.
Ever since you tutored me
and I stop going to night club,
My grades have improved a lot.
So I'm not only your friend, but your tutor too?
Then.
Do you want to be anything else?
Stop daydreaming.
Thank you, Chompu.
Don't mention it.
You're good at it too.
Chompu.
What?
Can I ask you something?
Soo.
We've talked for quite some time.
And see each other's faces several times.
I would like to meet you in person.
Sure.
But before that,
I want you to know something.
What is it?
[Writing until it become stories]
[before the day we shall be far apart]
[Keep our memories all along]
[knowing how precious they are to my heart]
[That familiar embrace]
(Next Episode)
You got a spaced-out look
I just think aimlessly.
Sorry.
Is there any way, professor?
Surprise!
Sis!
How did you get here?
Why are you stressed?
Hello, Chompu.
Hello, Nuck-Nan.
[Writing until it become stories]
[before the day we shall be far apart]
[Keep our memories all along]
[knowing how precious they are to my heart]
[That familiar embrace]
[I can still remember it]
[The photos of you still look the same]