[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
-[ringing continues]
-[music playing on stereo]
[ringing continues]
[ringing stops]
-[inhales]
-[phone ringing]
[Tara sighs]
[ringing continues]
-Hello?
-[caller] Hello. Is Cristina there?
No, she's not available.
May I take a message?
Uh, yeah. Um...
Yeah, sorry. I'm a friend of hers
from group-- Oh, shit.
From her shit?
Um, look, just, uh,
tell her I'm from group.
I'm Charlie. She's got my number.
-Oh, she goes to your group?
-Look, I shouldn't have...
Just tell her that Charlie called.
And I will do exactly that, Charlie,
once you tell me
what kind of group we're talking about.
Is it AA? NA?
Well, you sound
exactly like she describes you.
She talks about me in group?
Look, I don't think
[ can really talk about that.
-What does she say about me?
-Well, she loves you very much.
Oh. What does she love about me?
Uh-- Okay, well,
she loves that you're creative.
You love art and TV and movies.
Well, lots of people love movies.
Yeah, but she says you love scary movies,
and that you guys have that in common.
She's proud of making a fan out of you.
-She is?
-Yeah.
She told me the other day, she wonders,
what's your favorite scary movie?
Uh, The Babadook.
It's an amazing meditation
on motherhood and grief.
[caller chuckles]
Isn't that a little fancy-pants?
Well, it's elevated horror.
Uh-huh.
What does that mean, "elevated horror"?
It's scary but with complex emotional
and thematic underpinnings.
It's not just some schlocky, cheeseball
nonsense with wall-to-wall jump scares.
Hmm. That sounds kind of boring to me.
Have you ever seen Stab ?
Once, I think.
At a sleepover when I was, like, 12.
You live in Woodsboro,
and you don't know Stab ?
Your mother loves that movie.
She talks about it all the time in group.
How well do you remember the original?
-I don't know. I mean, it was super '90s.
-[caller chuckles]
It was really over-lit,
and everyone had weird hair.
[chuckles] Do you remember the beginning?
Not really.
It started with a kill scene, right?
They always started with a kill scene.
Yeah, that's right. That's right.
It's a girl at home, alone.
She answers a wrong number
and starts talking with the killer,
who makes her play a game.
Would you like to play a game,
Tara?
[computer voice] Systems armed.
[dog barking in distance]
-[phone rings]
-[gasps]
[panting]
[ringing continues]
This isn't fucking funny, Amber.
[caller] / fold you, this isn't Amber.
[phone beeps]
Amber's looking
particularly fetching tonight.
She really shouldn't leave her phone
lying around for anyone to clone.
What do you want?
I told you. I want to play a game.
Stab movie trivia, three rounds.
You call the cops, she dies.
You get a question wrong, she dies.
Her parents aren't home.
[ can be in that room in 15 seconds.
-[gasps, sobs]
- You want a warmup question?
I told you I don't know these movies!
Ask me about something I do know.
Ask me about It Follows.
Ask me about Hereditary.
Ask me about The Witch.
-In the first Stab movie. ..
-[gasps]
...what Woodsboro native was introduced
as the franchise's main character?
It's Sidney Prescott!
It's Sidney Prescott,
and she lived on Elm.
Correct.
You see, you're gonna do great at this.
Okay, question one--
No, no, no.
I got that one right. It should count.
Anyone could have gotten that one right.
Sidney's in every movie but the last one.
Question one:
Who wrote the original book
that the Stab movies are based on?
Um...
[stammering] The chick from TV.
“The chick from TV"
ls not gonna cut it, Tara.
Oh! Gale Weathers!
It is Gale Weathers, you motherfucker!
Correct.
Amber might live to see the sunrise.
Question two: Who played the dumb bitch
at the beginning of Stab 1
who answers the phone
and gets carved up by the killer?
Fuck you.
ls that the answer you're going with?
[sobs]
A non-answer
counts as a wrong answer, Tara.
Time's running out.
Ticktock, ticktock, ticktock,
ticktock, ticktock, ticktock,
ticktock, ticktock...
Heather Graham!
-Correct! You pulled that one out.
-[gasps]
Now for the final question.
Who was the killer in Stab 17?
Oh, I know this one, you fuck.
It's Billy Loomis!
He was Sidney's boyfriend,
and he was played by Luke Wilson,
and I got you, asshole!
I got it! I got it right!
Oh, I'm sorry, Tara,
but that's just not correct.
What?
No, no, no, it is. It is. That is right.
The correct answer is Billy Loomis
and Stu Macher.
There are two killers
in the original Stab.
I'm afraid someone's got to die now.
No, no, no. Amber, I'm coming.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck--
[screams, gasps]
-[lock clicks]
-[doorknob rattles]
-[beep]
-[computer voice] Systems armed.
-[pounding]
-[gasps]
The police are on their way, asshole!
[pounding stops]
-[lock clicks]
-[computer voice] A/I systems disarmed.
[panicked gasping]
-[lock clicks]
-Systems armed.
-All systems disarmed.
-Oh, my God! No!
Systems armed.
All systems disarmed. Systems armed.
All systems disarmed.
Systems armed.
-[phone rings]
-[screams]
Hello?
Bonus question, Tara.
Please stop.
Do you think I made it inside your house
before you could rearm?
-[bone crunches]
-[screaming]
Help!
[siren wailing]
[screams]
[Tara] No, no, no, no!
-[knife slices]
-No/
["Just Us" playing]
Excuse me, miss?
-What'd you just take?
-Your boner pills.
Good luck getting it up now.
You, um...
You are my boner pills.
[chuckles]
No. No.
[song continues playing]
-[phone vibrates]
-You okay?
Yes.
You don't have to check on me
all the time. I'm not breakable.
Yeah, this I know.
Shit.
[line ringing]
-[Wes] Sam?
-Hey. What's going on?
Uh, Tara... was attacked.
What? Is she--
She's alive, but in bad shape.
She was... stabbed.
Stabbed? What the fuck?
She made it through surgery,
and the doctor said it went well.
She's resting now.
I know you guys
aren't on the best terms, but--
I'm on my way.
She's gonna be okay, Sam.
We'll see you soon.
Hey, wait. Wes...
Yeah?
Do they know who did this?
It's probably better
if you just come here.
Wes.
She said it was someone
in a fucking Ghostface mask.
[phone beeps]
My sister was attacked.
I gotta go.
Wait, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm going with you.
No. No, Richie--
No, no, Sam. I'm coming with you.
-Okay.
-Okay. Yeah.
[person over PA] Attention, Panthers.
A reminder that all classes
and school activities
are canceled tomorrow
due to public-safety concerns.
That was Sam.
She's coming?
Yeah.
Watch everything get worse.
Listen, all I'm saying is,
with everything going on now,
I think it's time we take our relationship
to the next, most intimate level.
He wants me to accept
his Find My Fam request.
It's the smartest option
with a would-be killer on the loose.
You know exactly where I am,
and I know exactly where you are.
Aw, you can stalk me
like a jealous boyfriend.
And you can stalk me
[mock gag] Is this because
you two aren't having sex yet?
You actually bring up a very good point.
Not that I want to sound
like the stereotypical jock
trying to get into his girlfriend's pants.
-Great!
-Don't do it, Liv.
There's a psycho out there.
Make yourself harder to find.
Delete social media,
tape over your phone camera, disable GPS.
Yes, thank you very much, Edward Snowden.
Actually, your mother just interrogated me
about Tara's attempted murder,
which was very fun.
I'm sure she's asking everybody.
I mean, Ghostface is back.
The press still isn't saying Ghostface.
My mom doesn't want to cause a panic.
It'll get out by the second
or third killing.
Jesus, Mindy. There wasn't
a first killing. Tara's alive.
Mm, that means she could still die.
-What the fuck?
-Or the killer could come back for her.
Fuck! Mindy, come on.
I'm just telling you, arm up, okay?
Pepper spray, check. Taser, check.
-Girlfriend repellent, check.
-[all chuckle]
Nice. Thank you.
Oh, shit. Is that... Vince?
Wait, the creep
you hooked up with last summer?
-Yeah, he worked with me and Tara.
-He worked with Tara?
He's been stalking my Instagram
the last couple weeks,
posting the creepiest shit.
Probably time to introduce him
to Hobbs and Shaw.
Maybe not the best idea to incite
violence right in front of the sheriff.
Looks like he's leaving.
Thanks anyways, boys.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
-[vehicle engine starts]
-Hmm.
Tara says she fought back hard.
You've got bruises.
It's from football practice.
-Oh, sure.
-Tara's awake. She just texted.
-I'm going to the hospital. You coming?
-Yeah.
Oh, uh, I can't,
but I'll meet you guys later.
All right.
-I've actually never seen Stab.
-You've never seen Sfab?
-Mm-hmm.
-Not even the one that came out last year?
I've never seen Gone With the Wind either,
but I don't consider it a huge hole
in my cinematic education.
Most of the Stab movies
are based on things that happened here.
Define "things."
Things like...
a guy named Billy Loomis and his friend
carved up a bunch of high-school kids
while wearing this Halloween ghost mask.
You mean like in Halloween?
-No. Not like in Halloween.
-Oh.
Sounds a lot like Halloween.
-All right, it's a little like Halloween.
-Okay.
And every decade or so,
some idiot gets the bright idea
to put on the mask, kill his friends,
and get famous too.
The last time it happened was in 2011.
And we came here voluntarily?
Well, I got to make sure Tara's okay.
Yes, of course.
And I got to make sure
we don't get sliced up by some lunatic
who saw Friday the 13th and thought,
"You know what?
That Jason guy,
he's got some pretty solid ideas.”
Can I just ask you one question, though?
Yeah.
Do you have any idea why
someone wearing that mask
would want to kill your sister?
No.
[indistinct conversation]
How are you feeling?
You came.
Of course I came.
This is my boyfriend, Richie.
It's so nice to meet you.
I'm so sorry if I'm intruding.
Nice to meet you too.
-Hi.
-Thank you for calling.
-Of course.
Look at your hair. I like it.
These are Chad and Mindy, the twins.
And Wes.
I used to babysit them all.
Which is always how
I like to be introduced.
[people chuckle]
And Amber. Hey.
Hi. Nice to see you.
-Hi. I'm Richie.
-Hi.
-Where's Mom?
-She's stuck at a conference in London.
She called me earlier.
Yeah, for all of ten minutes.
Uh, look, guys, Tara's really tired.
Maybe we should just give her some space.
-Yeah.
Not you, Sam.
- Want you to stay.
-Okay.
-But the rest...
-Yeah.
If it's okay with you,
I could sleep here tonight.
-I'd really like that.
-Okay.
-Do you have your extra inhaler?
-Yeah, I'll be fine.
Okay.
-Honey? Okay, I'll just be right outside.
-Thank you.
Bye.
[door closes]
-Sam, I was so scared.
-I know.
It's okay.
[sobbing]
So what is she like,
-the sister?
-[billiard balls clacking]
Sam? Sam is so cool.
You only say that because she let you
wear Pokémon onesies to bed for a year.
-That's true. That's a true statement.
-[people chuckle]
No, trust me, Sam is not cool.
Her dad left her mom, right? Walks
right out when Tara's eight, Sam's 13.
Sam started acting out,
getting in trouble with the cops.
And then, on Sam's 18th birthday,
she leaves.
Ghosts them all.
Maybe Sam's changed.
I just don't want to see Tara hurt again.
So what, you're protecting Tara
from her own sister now?
Well, someone has to.
Okay, so no guys are good enough for her,
and now her family's off-limits too?
Mm, motive.
"If I can't have her, no one can."
-What?
-We all know you have a crush on Tara.
Okay. Come on, Mindy.
But we're all suspects.
Hmm?
-Except maybe Liv.
-Thank you.
-You're way too boring to be a psycho.
-Yo, Liv. You want a real drink?
Or are you happy sitting
at this kids' table?
Listen up, Uglier Michael Myers,
it was a summer fling. It meant nothing.
-Was I talking to you?
- I don't care who you're talking to.
-Liv, let's go.
-Don't talk to her!
- I don't want to hear your voice.
-Shut your mouth.
-Better shut the fuck up.
-Hey!
Get out of here, or I'm calling the cops.
Go!
-I'll see you soon, sweetheart.
-Hey, man, fuck you.
[bartender] You kids too. Let's go.
Did you see that shit?
[urinating]
Fuck this bar, man.
[thunder rumbles]
Fuck you.
Fuck it!
[vehicle engine starts, revs]
What the fuck?
-[engine revs]
-[zipper zips]
[engine revs]
["Red Right Hand" playing on stereo]
[revving continues]
What the fuck?
Is that you, pretty boy? Huh?
Get out of my fucking car!
-[engine off]
-[song stops playing]
[song resumes playing]
[choking gasps]
[gasps]
Hey.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
Just a bad dream.
What are you watching?
Oh, uh, Sfabis on Netflix.
What? I want to be prepared.
I got to go find something to eat.
Yeah, okay.
How you doing, Sam?
Mm. Antipsychotics aren't working
as well as they used to, are they?
Fuck you.
You can't run from who you are, Sam.
I'm just trying to help.
Hey, when are you gonna tell her
why all this is happening?
[phone ringing]
Hello.
[Ghostface] Hello, Samantha.
Who is this?
Someone who knows
your little family secret.
You're the fuck who hurt my sister?
Oh, she's not the only one I'm gonna hurt.
I had to get you
to come back here somehow, didn't I?
You want to fuck with me, asshole?
I'm right here. Come and get me.
With pleasure.
[gasps, screams]
Help!
Help! Help!
Somebody help me! He's trying to kill me!
Hey! What's going on? You're okay.
Somebody tried to kill me
in the break room!
I've got a body outside a bar on Main,
and then you get attacked here.
You said the call came
from Amber's number?
So”? We know he cloned my phone
before when he attacked Tara.
Or-- and, um, I'm just spitballing here--
you're the Killer.
And where were you when all this happened?
I was... watching Netflix.
-Ooh, yeah. Super-solid alibi, bro.
-So where were you?
I was questioning Amber and her friends
at the sheriff's station.
Yeah, I came as soon as I heard.
But, you know,
the Netflix alibi is good too.
Both of you, stop it.
You're gonna put more cops
on her room, right?
Yes.
And I can move you to a private floor.
Deputy Vinson knows what he's doing.
You'll be safe.
Like we've been so far?
Samantha, let's step outside.
Nice to see you, Deputy Hicks.
-So many fun memories.
-It's "Sheriff' Hicks.
I remember you too,
and all the trouble
you used to cause your family.
Your presence here is not helping.
So maybe when the sun comes up,
you and your boyfriend can hit the road
and leave it to people
who actually care about this community.
Well, she remains a delight.
Are you okay?
Um, would you mind giving us a second?
I need to talk to Tara.
-Come on, Netflix. Let's go.
-[scoffs]
Do you remember when Dad left?
Parts, sure.
I was eight. I don't know
what that has to do with anything.
It has to do with it.
Do you remember how Mom used to
keep those boxes up in the attic?
Well, I was up there once--
When I was 13,
looking for Christmas presents.
And I found these old diaries
that she kept from high school.
-Sam, what is--
-Please.
I have to do this.
So I found these old diaries.
And I knew it was wrong,
but I read some anyway
because Mom got pregnant
with me in high school,
and I thought it could be cool to find out
how she and Dad got together.
How romantic it must have been.
So I read some.
Only it wasn't romantic.
Mom was dating Dad, but...
she was in love with this other guy,
and he got her pregnant.
She told Dad it was his,
and that's why he proposed senior year.
-Sam, what are you talking about?
-And I'm sitting there, in this attic,
and I'm 13,
and I just found out my dad isn't my dad.
So I go find Mom in her bedroom,
and I'm screaming at her
and shoving this diary in her face,
and I didn't even realize
that Dad was standing right behind me.
[sighs] He didn't know.
He found out right then from me.
He left that night.
I'm the reason he left.
No. No, Sam--
Mom never forgave me.
Then she made me promise never
to tell you because you were so young.
And that's why I changed,
and I got distant and weird with you.
And I went out and I started doing
every drug that I could get my hands on
until I couldn't take it anymore,
and I left town.
I just couldn't be around you
anymore, Tara.
Not only because I destroyed our family
that night, but because
those diaries told me
who my real father was.
It was Billy Loomis.
And somebody knows,
and I think that's why you got hurt.
And I'm so fucking sorry that
I never told you, and then I ran away.
-I'm so sorry.
-Get out.
Tara.
You're gone for five years--
Five whole years-- and then I get stabbed,
and you want to come back
and drop all this shit on me?
-I thought I was protecting you.
-Protecting me from what?
The truth?
No. No, I...
-Sam--
-Please, Tara.
-Sam, I need you to get the fuck out.
-I'm so sorry.
-Sam.
-Please.
Get the fuck out!
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sniffling]
-[gasps]
-Hey, hey. Hey. It's okay. It's me.
Were you listening at the door?
No, no. Of course not.
Okay, yeah, I was listening at the door.
It doesn't freak you out
that my real father was a serial killer?
I mean,
yeah.
A great deal, yeah.
Okay, well, then go. I get it.
I just got to stay and figure it out.
I'm not leaving you here, Sam.
You know that part in horror movies
where you want to yell at the characters
to be smart and get the fuck out?
This is that part, Richie.
You should get the fuck out.
But I'm staying.
I love you.
-You're such a dumb-ass.
-I'm such a dumb-ass.
So,
your sister won't talk to you.
The police aren't gonna help.
What's our next move?
We go talk to an expert.
(voice on radio) ...a few temperatures here.
Tuesday, Wednesday in the mid-50s,
and then finally well see
those mid-60s returning info next week.
And just one night after a local teen
was attacked in her home
by an assailant wearing
a Ghostface costume,
Sheriff Judy Hicks has now confirmed
two more late-night attacks
that have left Woodsboro reeling.
The first victim, Vincent Schneider,
was found dead
behind the Corner Pocket Pool Hall,
and a second victim, as yet unnamed,
was attacked
inside Woodsboro General Hospital,
but she escaped without injuries.
Needless to say,
Woodsboro is on high alert today--
[TV announcer]
Live from Studio 71-A in Rockefeller Plaza...
Good morning. I'm Gale Weathers.
Before we dive in,
[ want to tell you a little story
that happened on the way
info the studio this morning.
- I stopped to get...
-{knocking)
[groans]
Go away!
[Sam] Sorry to bother you, Mr. Riley.
We just want to ask you a few questions.
[Dewey] I don't give interviews.
We're not looking for an interview.
Give me one good reason
why I should talk to you.
I'm Billy Loomis's daughter.
That's a terrible reason
for me to talk to you.
My name is Samantha Carpenter.
I was attacked last night at the hospital.
The night before that,
my sister was stabbed seven times.
I know you know what that's like.
I'm just trying to protect my family.
Five minutes. That's all I'm asking.
I'll give you two minutes.
I'm missing a show I like.
...bangs again,
someone stage an intervention.
Gale Weathers.
-Weren't you two, um...
-Yeah.
Who's he?
-Uh, this is Richie, my boyfriend.
-How long have you known him?
Six months?
Did he know who your dad was when you met?
Express any interest in Woodsboro
or the Ghostface killings?
What the hell are you talking about?
Your killer's obsessed
with the Stab movies, right?
Well, there are certain rules
to surviving a Sfab movie.
Believe me, I know.
Rule number one:
Never trust the love interest.
They seem sweet, caring, supportive.
Then welcome to Act I,
where they're trying to rip your head off.
I was with Sam in Modesto
when Tara was attacked.
And let me guess:
You were just in the other room,
conveniently unaccounted for
when she was attacked at the hospital.
Do I have to take this from
shitty Sam Elliott over here, or what?
Rule number two:
The killer's motive is always connected
to something in the past.
I'm related to Billy.
Right, but then why Kill
that random Vince guy?
That's for you to figure out.
And rule number three--
and this is the most important rule:
The first victim always has a friend group
that the killer is a part of.
Does your sister have
a close-knit group of friends?
Yeah.
She does.
Then look for the killer there.
If you can find out why they're doing
this, you can figure out who's next.
So help us.
Help us figure out who is behind this.
Oh, you kidding me?
I've been stabbed nine times.
I've got permanent nerve damage
and a fun little limp.
You think I want to do that again?
You just said it always goes
back to the past, right?
So if I'm in danger,
that means you're in danger.
Come on.
Let's do this together.
Your time's up.
Jesus!
Yeah, he's way more fun in the movies.
Hey, uh, what's next?
The friends.
Thanks so much for that Kevin.
Coming up after our local weather,
the pros and cons
of reuniting with old friends.
[sighs]
[quits calling]
[phone rings]
Hello?
[Dewey] Hey, Sid, it's me.
Dewey?
Oh, my God. How long has it been?
I'm trying to get a run in before
I take the girls to school. How are you?
I'm good, really good.
How are you? How's Mark?
I think I'll keep him.
How are things in the sheriff's business?
Uh, they're...
-They're fine. But, Sid--
-Have you talked to Gale lately?
No. Not in a couple years.
I know things didn't end well
with you guys, but--
Sid, it's happening again.
What are you talking about?
Some idiot in a Ghostface mask.
Three attacks so far. One dead.
Something about this one
just feels different.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. You know me.
Yeah. I do. That's why I'm asking.
I'm fine.
I just want you to be safe up there.
Do you have a gun?
I'm Sidney fucking Prescott.
Of course I have a gun.
Good. That's good.
Does Gale know?
No. She's my next call.
But, Sid, promise me:
No matter what you hear or what you see
on the news, don't come here.
No offense, Dewey. I have no intention
of ever setting foot in that town again.
Good.
Dewey,
whoever this killer's after,
I'm glad they have you to protect them.
You be safe, okay?
Will do.
It's good to hear your voice.
You too, Sid.
Come on. Get it together, Dewey.
[sighs]
Probably shouldn't have sent
the smiley face.
[phone clatters]
Holy shit. He came.
I've decided to temporarily assist you
in your investigation.
Thank you.
Look, just because that guy showered
doesn't mean he should have a gun.
-Oh, yeah.
-Yeah.
[indistinct conversation]
[door closes]
Person| So how do you know so much
about the Stab movies?
[person 2] Runs in her family.
Randy was our uncle.
RIP.
You said to bring everybody.
Hey.
Whoo. Suspects!
My brother would be so proud.
Hey, Martha.
Dewey! Hi!
You look...
Yeah.
-How's the wife?
-Okay, Mom, we're good. Thank you.
All right, kids. Have fun.
I asked Mindy to call everybody here
because...
there's something I have to tell you.
So let me get this straight. You're saying
that you're the daughter of Billy Loomis,
and, what, that one of us is the killer?
The killer told me he knew my secret.
He attacked Tara to lure me back here.
But then why immediately go and murder
some douche nozzle that was stalking Liv?
Why does it have to be one of us?
What about Deputy Dewey here?
Maybe he's the killer.
No offense.
None taken, but what's my motive?
You got stabbed a billion times,
got dumped by your famous wife
and crawled into a bottle.
I think it's safe to say
you're on the suspect list.
Well, maybe you're the killer.
Because that cut deep.
That douche nozzle is connected.
I googled him. His mom is Leslie Macher.
-Stu Macher's sister.
-Who's Stu Macher?
He's Billy Loomis's accomplice.
A real loony tune.
Okay. Okay.
So the first three attacks are all
on people related to the original killers.
Oh, my God. He's making a requel!
A what?
Or a legacyquel.
Fans are torn on the terminology.
God. Please speak English.
Remember the Stab movie
that came out last year?
Oh, yeah! The one
the Knives Out guy directed, right?
I actually really liked that one.
Of course you did.
You have terrible taste.
I hate you.
The point is,
the hard-core Slab fans hated it.
You go on 4chan and Dreadit,
all they're talking about is
how Stab 8 pissed on their childhoods.
How they crammed in social commentary
just to make it elevated.
How the main character's a Mary Sue.
-What's a Mary Sue?
-You really don't want to know.
What's wrong with elevated horror?
I mean, Jordan Peele fucking rules.
Uh, obviously, but that's not Stab.
Real Stab movies are
meta slasher whodunits, full stop.
-Come on, it's just a movie.
-No, it's not.
To some people, the original
is their favorite thing in the world.
The movie that made them love horror.
That Mom or Dad showed them when
they were ten that bonded them together.
And God help anyone who
slightly fucks with that special memory.
Who makes a movie
they think disrespects it.
It sounds like our killer is writing
his own version of Stab 8,
but doing it as a requel.
Which is?
See, you can't just reboot a franchise
from scratch anymore.
The fans won't stand for it.
Black Christmas, Child's Play, Flatliners...
that shit doesn't work.
But you can't just do
a straight sequel either.
You got to build something new.
But not too new,
or the Internet goes bug-fucking nuts.
It has to be part
of an ongoing story line,
even if the story shouldn't have been
ongoing in the first place.
New main characters, yes,
but supported by
and related to legacy characters.
Not quite a reboot, not quite a sequel.
Like the new Halloween, Saw,
Terminator, Jurassic Park, Ghostbusters,
fuck, even Star Wars!
It always,
always goes back to the original!
Are you telling me that I'm caught
in the middle of fan fucking fiction?
Not just in the middle, Sam.
You're the star.
So, not to put too fine a point on it,
but, according to requel rules,
[sighs] who's next?
Going by the pattern,
whoever it is has to be connected
to someone that came before.
-I'm starting to regret coming here.
-My mom was a character in one of them.
No one cares about the shitty
inferior sequels, Wes. You're safe.
With Randy as our uncle, though,
you and I are probably screwed.
Wait. What?
Or you're the Killer,
and this whole elaborate monologue
is just to cover your tracks.
I think it's pretty clear
who the killer is at this point.
Who?
You.
Wha...
It makes perfect requel sense.
-That actually does make a lot of sense.
-Yeah.
[scoffs] Fuck this.
-Meet you back at the motel.
-[Richie] Sam, wait.
Sam, wait.
The first fucking rule of these movies
is don't split up!
The nerve of that girl, right?
I'm really not in the mood right now.
Sam, Sam, Sam.
There is a killer on the loose.
He's threatening you.
He's threatening your sister.
Are you gonna run away
from who you are like you always do,
or are you gonna use it?
I'm not like you.
Really?
And how else are you gonna survive?
I say accept who you are,
let's get out there,
find out who's doing this,
and cut some fucking throats!
-No!
-[horn blares]
[tires screech]
[gasps]
Mm.
And extra edamame. Please.
Thank you. I'll be there in ten minutes.
Bye.
[door creaks]
That you, tiger?
[lock clicks]
-[gasps]
-Jesus!
[clears throat]
Are you being safe out there, honey?
To the point
that all my friends mock me, yes.
Good boy.
-What's for dinner?
-Sushi. I was just leaving to pick it up.
Oh. Why don't you just Postmates it?
Oh, it gets all smooshy
by the time it's here.
I know you hate that.
-Go take a shower. I'll be back soon.
-Okay.
-Can you put this away for me?
-Yes.
Okay.
-Love you.
-Lock the door.
- I will.
[water running]
[chatter over police radio]
[phone rings]
-Sheriff Hicks.
-[Ghostface] Hello, Sheriff Judy.
-Who is this?
- I think you know.
I'm a fan of scary movies. And knives.
What's your favorite scary movie?
I prefer animated films and musicals.
Why are you doing this?
I'll tell you all about it.
I'm calling to turn myself in.
I think that's a great idea.
Well sit down at the station, and I/
tell you about the two people I've killed.
-You've only killed one person.
-[laughs]
By the time I see you,
I'll have gutted your baby boy.
-No!
-[siren wailing]
Whoa!
[pedestrian] Fuck you!
[line ringing]
Pick up, Wes!
-[vibrating]
-[shower running]
[whistling tune]
[siren wailing]
This is Sheriff Hicks.
I need units to converge on my house ASAP.
-[officer] Copy that. We're on it.
-[phone rings]
[Ghostface]
Can't get him on the phone, can you?
He must be busy.
How do I know you're anywhere near him?
Ever seen the movie Psycho ?
Please,
don't hurt my boy.
Why not?
-He's a good kid.
-Is he, now?
He never hurt anyone.
That's not enough.
-Please! I'll do anything!
-[chuckles]
You're not gonna make it in time,
Sheriff Judy.
Wes!
I'm coming!
-Wes!
-[knife slices]
[gasps]
Help!
[gasping]
[low growl]
[knife slices]
[footsteps]
[humming tune]
Okay.
[door creaks]
Mom?
[gasps]
Fuck... you!
[chatter over police radio]
[siren chirps]
[people chattering]
-Miss, you can't be here.
-What?
-You can't be here.
-No, I'm sorry. I know her son.
-Her son, Wes. Is he...
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Oh, my God.
You're...
Well, you're you.
Last time I checked.
Are you okay? You seem like
you're having a bit of a moment.
Did you know the sheriff?
Sort of.
She didn't like me very much.
Well, she didn't really like me either.
Um, I'm Samantha-- Sam. Carpenter.
My sister and I were attacked.
Oh. Sorry to hear that.
I'm Gale...
Riley.
Weathers. I'm Gale Weathers. Excuse me.
What time did they find
the sheriff's body?
6:00. Gale?
-A text?
-Ow!
You tell me the killer is back in a text?
-Ow, that hurts.
-Good!
-You were on the air.
-How do you know?
A hunch.
You look good. Are you still writing?
No time.
You were always happiest
when you were writing.
[person] Sir, it's okay.
We're here with Gale.
[person 2]
I can't release anybody right now.
Couldn't resist a good story, could you?
Don't be an idiot, Dewey.
I'm here because I was worried about you.
-[scoffs]
-Okay, yes.
My producers wanted me
to cover this, for obvious reasons,
but 90% is because of you.
Well, I feel 90% better.
Don't be so sensitive.
Since when did you care about my feelings?
-Hey.
-Especially not in the last couple years.
Listen. Let's not pretend
I'm the one who ended things.
No one's pretending, Gale.
I remember what happened.
Why aren't you in uniform?
I retired.
Since when?
Since they asked me to.
Oh, Dewey.
I don't need your pity, Gale.
I made my choices. So did you.
It was my turn.
It was a great opportunity.
-You said you'd try.
-And I did.
For two whole months!
Listen, if you want to make me feel worse
than I already do, good luck.
The mornings aren't so bad,
'cause I get to see you.
Pretend I'm still back there in New York.
But then I remember...
that I couldn't hack it.
I left in the middle of the night,
like a coward.
Why wouldn't you tell me that then?
It would have mattered.
You are a lot of things, Dewey,
but you are not a coward.
You just...
You just were meant to be in Woodsboro.
And you weren't?
Promise me you'll leave
as soon as you can.
You know I can't promise that.
I'm sorry about Judy.
Yeah, me too.
But she'll make a great chapter
in your next book.
And don't even get me started
on Ghostface's signature new weapon.
That shit is it
And can we talk about the title? Stab ?
What, just like the original?
Just call it Stab 8. It's fucking Stab 8.
You're not fooling anyone.
[person 1] It's such bullshit.
[Richie]
Where have you been? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
That Mindy girl wasn't kidding.
Stab 8 is not like the others.
I mean, no connection to the other movies.
-No legacy characters at all.
-Richie--
This franchise goes off the rails
with number five.
Richie, listen to me.
He killed two more people.
Wes and his mother.
He killed the sheriff? You can do that?
[stammering]
! mean, are you okay? Where are you?
-I'll call you right back.
-No, Sam--
-We should be out looking for him.
-Who's at the hospital?
Who's watching my sister?
I just heard about the sheriff.
They needed me here!
-Where are you going?
-My sister's in trouble!
...where Judy Hicks
has just been brutally murdered.
[car door shuts]
What are you waiting for?
Drive!
Come on. Let's go!
[dialogue on TV]
[faint grunt]
Hello?
[dialogue on TV continues, indistinct]
Fuck this.
-[gasps]
-[monitor beeping]
[groans]
Fuck!
[gasping]
[cries out]
[whimpers]
-[phone rings]
-[gasps]
Damn it!
Should you be making a call right now?
-[line ringing]
-Please, please.
[Tara gasps, sobs]
[gasps]
[choking gasps]
[horn blaring]
Stop!
You know we have to live
through this to help her, right?
-Just hold on.
-[shouts]
[whimpers]
[door opens]
[door creaks shut]
-[door opens, closes]
-Holy shit.
[whimpering]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Ow! Ow! Goddamn it!
Richie?
What are you doing here?
Sam called.
She said that you were in trouble.
-Did you hit me with the phone?
-Look out!
[exclaims]
-[shouts]
-[groans]
[phone rings]
Richie!
-Are you at the hospital?
-Hello, Samantha.
[Sam] No.
Richie can't come to the phone right now.
He's finding out what happens to people
who stick their noses in business
that doesn't concern them.
-Please don't hurt him.
-I'll tell you what.
You can choose. I'll only kill one.
What? What? Tara!
Who do you want to hear die?
No, please. I'm begging you.
Please don't hurt them.
Really? You can't save your own sister?
-All you have to do is say, "Kill Richie."
-No! No!
No! Tara! Don't touch her.
Please, please, please, I'm begging you.
Or say, "Kill Tara,"
and I'll make sure to hit
all the organs I missed last time.
No. Fuck you!
I'm begging you. Please don't hurt her.
Last chance to save one.
Choose.
Why are you doing this?
You want to know why, Sam?
Maybe it's because you're a selfish bitch
who can't even make a decision
to save the life of someone you love.
Maybe you're too weak for this franchise.
Maybe you're right.
Or maybe I'm just stalling for time,
fuckhead.
-[elevator bell dings]
-[gasps]
-I'll get Richie.
-Tara!
-Come on, Richie.
-[grunting]
It's okay. I got you.
It's gonna be all right.
Get the elevator!
[grunting]
Not today.
Richie.
Let's get out of here.
[Tara sobbing]
Come on, hurry up.
-The head.
-What?
You have to shoot 'em in the head,
or they always come back.
Dewey! Who gives a fuck?
-I do.
-[Sam] No! Dewey!
[phone rings]
[groaning]
Yes, today.
[screams]
[groaning]
[ringing continues]
It's an honor.
[siren wailing]
[indistinct police radio chatter]
No!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know him well, but...
he helped me.
That's what he did.
He helped people.
I should've stopped him.
If you had, my sister would be dead.
[nurse] Samantha, your sister's awake.
[Sidney] Gale.
Sidney.
I came as soon as I heard.
I'm so sorry.
You shouldn't be here.
You shouldn't be here either.
-Mark and the kids are okay?
-Yeah, they're safe for now.
I'm here to make sure of that.
Come here.
How are you feeling?
Every time I get attacked,
they give me better painkillers.
So there's that.
I'm sorry.
For what? You saved my life.
For not telling you sooner.
For being the reason Dad left.
You're not the reason Dad left.
You didn't choose where you came from.
Or who you came from.
I don't blame you for that.
I blame you for leaving me too.
That's never gonna happen again.
I know.
But why didn't you come to me back then?
I could've helped.
Because...
I was scared.
Of what?
I was scared
that I would turn out just like him.
So |I ran.
To protect you.
From me.
Sam,
you could never be like him.
-You're so high right now.
-I'm so high right now.
I'm not even gonna lie.
I love you.
I love you too.
So what do we do now?
What nobody ever does in these situations.
We're gonna get the fuck out of Woodsboro.
-That's her?
-Yeah.
Samantha?
It's Sam.
-I'm--
- I know who you are.
I hope you're okay.
-Listen, I'm sorry--
-You're Billy's daughter.
Uh, we'll bring the car around.
Yeah. I'm his daughter.
I'm sorry if that's weird for you.
No, no, it's...
I've been through this. A lot.
You want to talk?
I appreciate it.
And I'm...
I'm really sorry about Dewey.
But I'm taking my sister away
from all this.
I tried running too.
It doesn't work. It always follows.
All due respect,
that's your life, not mine.
-I'm not so sure about that.
-What do you want from me, lady?
Hey! Watch your tone, new girl.
You know how they always say
it goes back to the original?
Here's the original.
I want your help.
Because you're wrong,
this is your life now.
Which means whoever this is
is gonna keep coming for you.
-So?
-So I want you to help us kill him.
You want me to help you and the host
of a morning show commit murder?
-Correct.
-Yeah.
And I'm what in this scenario?
The bait? The helpless victim?
-If the shoe fits...
-You're not helpless, Sam.
He killed your friend. He killed ours.
And I have kids, which means
I won't sleep until he's in the ground.
Look, I'm sorry about
what this has done to your lives.
But no matter what you
or the killer or anyone says,
this isn't my story.
-[horn honking]
-All right.
Let's get the fuck out of town, huh?
Sorry. That's my boyfriend, Richie.
Nice to meet-- We met.
Sam, please get in the car so we never
have to see these people again.
-Sam--
-No. We're leaving.
That's the only way I can protect Tara.
Okay, good luck.
You too.
-[car drives away]
-Well, that went fucking horribly.
Don't worry, I have a plan.
She seems really tough.
Honestly, Sid, who gives a shit?
You said it yourself,
he's gonna go after her.
I put a tracker on her car.
You did what?
It seemed like something
Gale Weathers would do.
Take that as a compliment.
I left a message for Mom.
I told her where we're going.
You good back there?
Fuck, where is it?
Where's what?
My inhaler. I usually keep an extra one.
-Should we go back?
-Whoa. Okay.
I vote for not going back
to the murder hospital.
-You want to stop at a pharmacy?
-I'd need a prescription.
But I left an extra one at Amber's.
Her house is on the way.
No. No. No, no, no.
I'd be in and out.
-Could you hold out till Modesto?
-I don't think so.
Okay, what's the address?
123 No Fucking Way Lane.
Richie, she needs it.
Yeah. And I need to keep all the blood
inside my body. So do you.
Richie, please.
It's okay.
Okay, yeah. Fuck.
What's the goddamn address?
[speakers: hip-hop music playing]
[people chattering, whooping]
Hey, thanks for coming.
Keep pouring, Wheeler. Thank you.
Hey.
To Wes!
-[all] To Wes!
-Beautiful son of a bitch.
Shots? Really?
This is supposed to be a memorial.
Well, this is how I mourn
and distract myself
from the looming specter of Death.
Hey, we're low on beer.
There's more in the basement.
I'll go get some.
[gasps]
What the fuck, Mindy? Jesus!
That was a test. And you failed.
Never go off on your own
when there's a masked killer around.
You're the one that said
we needed more beer.
And you should have asked me
to come with you.
You know what else you shouldn't do
when there's a masked killer around?
What?
Follow someone into a dark,
creepy basement alone.
I mean,
how do you know I'm not the killer?
Because I am.
I'm not, actually.
But let that be a lesson.
Don't trust anyone.
Then how can I trust you
when you say you're not the killer?
Exactly.
You're learning.
Now let's go back upstairs.
You first.
Very good.
[speakers: ballad playing]
I think I'm ready.
I mean, I think we should.
Like now. You want to go upstairs?
Like-- Like upstairs?
Uh-huh. Right now.
Um--
Don't take this the wrong way,
but I think I have to pass on that.
What?
Why?
Well--
You know, I'm not, like, entirely sure
that you're not the...
killer.
"Don't take this the wrong way"?
No, no, no, look. I'm almost 100% certain
that you are not,
but the safest option is to be down here
with all the people...
Fuck you.
...and the potential witnesses.
That is a completely valid
emotional response to have.
-That too.
-Fucking asshole.
Good job.
Fuck you, Mindy.
If I hadn't have written that book
about your mother,
-none of this would've happened.
-Gale.
- I started all of this.
-No, you didn't.
Billy Loomis started this,
and we're gonna end it.
After tonight, no more books,
no more movies, no more fucking Ghostface.
-Don't you know the rules?
-What rules?
You don't--
[laughing]
There are certain specific rules
that one must abide by
in order to successfully survive
a horror movie.
-For instance--
-Okay.
-Number one: You can never have sex.
-Ugh. Don't do it.
-Don't go outside after her.
-She's not texting me back.
Because she's probably dead.
Jesus, Mindy.
That's my girlfriend, and I love her.
Was your girlfriend.
You're just gonna sit and watch a movie
about our uncle getting stabbed?
It calms me down, okay?
I'm also gonna smoke some weed
and possibly hook up with Frances.
Have fun.
Oh, my God,
at least take some sort of weapon.
Here you go.
All right.
[chuckles]
What?
[beeping]
Liv?
Yo.
[beeping continues: higher pitch]
[rapid beeping]
All right. Okay, yeah, no.
[cries out]
[groans] Fuck!
[phone beeping]
-[beeping accelerates]
-Please, please, please, please.
No.
[rapid beeping]
Whoa! Stop! Wait!
[groaning]
Well, perfect. She's having a party.
Who has a party in the middle
of a killing spree? I'm aborting the plan.
No, we're already here. I'll go in quickly
and get it. I'll be back in five.
I'm coming too.
If you think I'm waiting out here
just to get murdered,
you're out of your mind.
[speakers: hip-hop music playing]
-Tara's here!
-[whooping, cheering]
Tara!
What are you doing out of the hospital?
Should you even be up and around?
- I need my spare inhaler.
-Why? Where are you going?
No, it's fine. Don't tell me.
I get it. Just be safe, okay?
I think it's in my room.
All right, everyone!
Thanks for coming, but the party's over!
-Time to go!
-No!
But it's so early!
Let's go.
[partygoer] Come on, Grandma!
[Richie] Hey, hey, hey! Hello!
Can we cut the music, please?
[music stops playing]
Uh, hi, Gen Z. How are you?
Both Sam and Tara here have been attacked
by the killer twice.
Now they're here, which makes this place
a huge murder target,
so if I were you, I would probably leave.
-Fuck you.
-I tried to be nice. Get the fuck out!
Please get the fuck out.
-Sincerely, get the fuck out.
-Buzzkill!
Thank you. Thank you all.
I'm saving your life. I promise.
-[partygoers grumbling, jeering]
-Thanks, teens.
-Thank you so much.
-[cup clatters]
Great. Thank you for leaving the cup.
Thank you.
Saving your life.
-I'm saving your life.
-Bye!
-You're a wet blanket, man.
-Saving your life. Thank you.
And number three:
Never, ever, ever,
under any circumstances,
say, "I'll be right back."”
'Cause you won't be back.
Somebody's goofy-ass dad
is kicking us out.
Goddamn it.
Thank you.
Thanks, guys. Have a good night.
-You have my number. Bye.
-Bye.
-[scoffs]
-[partygoer] Jeannie, come on!
[chuckles]
Hi.
Uh, do you know if there's any beer left?
There's none in the kitchen.
Yes, Richie, there's beer in the basement.
Right behind you. Basement.
Yeah.
Do you wanna, uh, come with me?
[chuckles] No. But you were right to ask.
-Yeah. Um--
-Mm-hmm.
Okay. I'll be right back.
[mock laughter]
Yeah. Yeah.
-[door opens, closes]
-Well, he's dead. [gasps]
The goddamn fucking Uber canceled on me!
Great. Now I can't have sex,
and I can't get a ride home.
Could this night get any shittier?
Liv, where's my brother?
What? I don't know, Mindy. Probably off
accusing everyone of being the killer!
He actually went looking for you.
I didn't see him. Okay?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Just revising my suspect list.
Fuck this.
Are you afraid of me, Mindy?
[laughs]
You think I did something
to your brother? Huh?
You think I'm gonna cut you up?
A little bit now, yeah.
I thought you said
I was too boring to be the killer.
Maybe that's the twist.
What do you think, huh? You're the expert.
You know what eventually happens
to the expert?
What?
Enjoy your stupid movie.
Fucking psycho.
They stopped.
-Gas station?
-No.
-Oh, shit.
-What?
Oh, shit. How far are we?
Too far.
-Damn it.
-[line ringing]
Tara, we're leaving!
[phone rings]
Hello.
You need to get out
of that house right now.
How do you know where I am?
You're in Stu Macher's house,
where your dad and Stu killed everyone.
Someone planned to get you there.
You need to get the fuck out, Sam!
No, Jamie. Watch out.
-[chuckling]
-Watch out Jamie.
You know he's around. You know--
-What?
-There he is.
Come on, man, turn around!
Turn around! Dude!
I told you. I fold you,
he's around the corner. Jamie.
-Look behind you.
-No, Randy, look behind you.
Come on, man, turn around!
-Dude, what are you doing? You can do it!
- Turn around! Behind you!
These are your rules! Own that shit.
Behind you! Turn around.
Look behind...
Jamie!
Oh, shit!
[clattering]
[grunting, shouting]
Mindy.
That's a lot of blood, Sam.
-No, Mindy. No, Mindy. Stay with--
-[Amber screams]
-What did you do to her?
-Nothing.
No, I didn't do anything.
-The killer, he--
-Is she okay?
-What the fuck?
-Richie, where the fuck were you?
I went into the basement to get beer.
You went to the basement alone?
I asked her to come with me!
She said no! Fuck!
Stay the fuck back.
Jesus Christ!
I was with Tara, but the rest of you
were wandering around.
One of you is the fucking killer!
Fuck you, Amber. Fuck you!
-Why is there blood on your hands?
-What?
- I found Chad. I found Chad--
-Chad?
-You're fucking lying.
-No.
-You're the killer.
-No, I'm not.
Liv, stop.
-Fuck you!
-Liv, just stop!
Fuck you, Amber.
I'm not the fucking killer!
I know.
[all gasp]
Welcome to Act lll.
Run!
-Holy shit!
-[Richie] Sam, come on! Come on!
Run! Go, go, go! Go! Go!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, shit.
-Oh, my God-- Tara!
-Wait, no, Sam. She has a gun.
There are always two killers.
Sam, please put the knife down.
Look, I think...
- I think the other killer might be Tara.
-What?
She's the one that brought us here,
and you two have been estranged for years.
I mean,
how well do you really know her?
Better than I know you.
Sam, wait. Sam! Sam!
[person screams]
Sounds about right.
You ready?
For this? Never.
Here we go.
[gasping, screaming]
Help me, help me! He stabbed me!
-What do you think?
-Trap.
-Fuck it.
-[groans]
Gale. Gale.
Wait. Let me see. Let me see.
-You got to go to the hospital.
-No.
You said we were gonna finish this.
Go finish it, Sidney.
Gale.
For Dewey.
Anyone hiding, killer or not,
you have five seconds to show yourself!
[thudding]
[gasps]
-[gasps]
Oh, Tara.
Oh, my God.
[muffled] Sam.
Sam, please.
[sobbing]
[phone vibrating]
[Ghostface] Hello, Sidney.
Hello there. Where'd you go?
Oh, this isn't Amber. I'm the other one.
Oh. There's two of you. Again.
I've seen this movie before.
Not this movie, Sidney.
You really need some new material.
I got you here, didn't I?
You might actually be
the most derivative one of all.
-I mean, Christ, the same house?
-Maybe so.
But you forgot the first rule
of surviving a Stab movie.
-Never answer the--
-I'm bored.
Wait!
-[screaming]
-[clattering]
Put your hands up! Show me your hands!
What are you doing in there?
-H-H-Hiding from murderers.
- I told you to come out!
I'm not gonna come out!
You're shooting everything!
Holy shit, it's Ghostface!
Richie! Gun. Get the gun.
Yeah. Kind of hard
since you shot me in the leg.
-Yes! Yes!
-Shoot him!
Thank God you're okay.
Because I really,
really wanted to be the one to kill you.
Sit the fuck down, Prescott!
[groaning]
I can't believe this worked.
I know. It's a bummer it's me.
[device whirs]
But it really was
the best choice for the movie.
This isn't a fucking movie!
No. But it will be.
-That's the point, right, Amber?
-Right, hon!
Third Act bloodbath, check.
Killers revealed, check.
Time for the big finale!
[chortles]
-Richie...
-Shh, shh. shh.
Okay. Okay.
Let's get 'em into the kitchen.
Let's go, bitch!
Someone has to save the franchise.
You see, no one has made
a great Stab movie since the first one.
Not really.
Hey, baby, you want to go get
the very ex-Mrs. Riley?
Yeah, I do.
Hey, hey!
Whoa. Whoa.
Sidney Prescott.
You know,
I'm a really big fan.
Go fuck yourself.
-You see the last Stab movie?
-Not really a fan of scary movies.
That checks out. Anyway, it sucked balls.
Because nobody takes
the true fans seriously. Not really.
They just laugh at us. And why?
Because we love something?
We're just a fucking joke to them?
How can fandom be toxic?
It's about love!
They don't fucking understand
that these movies are important to people.
-Richie...
-And we're gonna help them!
Hollywood's totally fucking out of ideas,
so we decided we'd give them
some new source material to follow.
You know? Bring it back to basics.
"Cause that's how you make
a great Stab movie, Sam.
-"Based on actual events."
-[Gale groans]
-Gale.
-Sit the fuck down!
[Richie] Back up. Back up.
[Richie chuckles]
Eee! Eee! Eee!
You did all this just to make me
the hero of your fucked-up movie?
Sweetie, you're not the hero.
You're the villain.
The daughter of Billy Loomis who sees
fucked-up visions of her dead dad.
Sidney Prescott killed your father.
You did all this
just to get her back to Woodsboro.
You know what the biggest problem
with the Sfab movies is?
There's no Michael Myers
or Jason Voorhees.
No bad guy to keep coming back.
But the illegitimate daughter
of the original mastermind?
[scoffs] Now, that's a fucking villain.
-How did you know?
-Oh, about your father?
It's a small town and your mom's a drunk!
I met Richie on the Sfab subreddit.
I've been obsessed ever since
my parents bought this house.
We realized pretty quickly
we had similar ideas.
Wasn't that hard for me
to find you in Modesto.
It wasn't that hard for me
to fuck you either.
I guess being a sexually available woman
is supposed to be empowering these days.
Fuck you!
Well, now you're just
quoting the original.
But it wouldn't work with just you, Sam.
See, we had to bring the legacy characters
back to make it matter.
Can't have a bona fide Halloween
without Jamie Lee!
-[Richie] Nope!
-Dewey had to die to make it real.
To show that this
wasn't just some bullshit,
cash-in, run-of-the-mill sequel.
Because our movie has fucking stakes!
'Cause anyone can die in a requel.
-No!
-[Richie] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[Richie] Goddamn it. Whoa, whoa!
No, hey! Sit the fuck down.
I'm so sorry, Sid.
We can't let you live either.
I mean, surviving this many times--
That would just be ridiculous.
This time the fans are gonna be
the ones who win.
-That about cover it?
-Nailed it, baby.
Get Tara out of the closet.
We got to start staging the bodies!
Stay with me, Sid.
Stay with me.
[Richie]
You really should've listened to Dewey.
He nailed it in one!
Dude, look at the love interest!
Are you fucking stupid?
I even had you convinced
it could be your sister.
[Amber] Um, she's not here.
What the fuck do you mean, she's not here?
[Amber] She's not here!
I untied her.
Guess you're not
as persuasive as you thought.
[phone rings]
That's for you.
[scoffs] Yeah, like your gimpy
little sister's gonna make a difference.
She's our fucking pincushion
at this point.
Amber! Fan out.
She couldn't have gotten far.
I can't find her!
Amber?
[gunshot]
[screams] No!
[groaning]
[Richie] Sam! Where you going, huh?
Your big scene's coming up!
Fucking kill you!
The fucking hand sanitizer?
No, no, no, no, no!
It's not my fault! It's not my fault!
Let me guess: The movies made you do it?
No, it was the message boards!
I was radicalized.
-By movie fans?
-Yes, they're so mad!
It's not my fault. I'm just a dumb kid.
I wanted to be a part of something.
"A part of something"?
You killed my best friend!
Yeah, and he died like a pussy.
[screaming]
That's the thing about slashers, Sam.
So many blood trails.
This one yours?
Only one way to find out!
I was the last thing Dewey saw
before he died too.
I can't believe I get to do you both.
No last-minute saves this time.
Your story's over!
Time to pass the torch.
It's all yours, bitch!
-You want to do the honors?
-This one's yours.
No, stop, stop, stop!
I'm sorry about Dewey.
Fuck you.
[screaming]
Enjoy that torch.
-[screams]
-[grunts]
[groaning]
Stop...
fucking up...
my ending!
[both coughing, gasping]
Sam?
Sam!
[Richie] Okay.
What are you gonna do now, huh?
Make a scary phone call to me?
Pop out of that closet
in a Ghostface mask?
No.
Because you're the villain!
And the villain dies at the end.
Those are the rules.
I'm introducing a new rule.
And what would that be? Huh?
Well?
[cackles]
Never fuck with
the daughter of a serial killer.
Huh? Oh!
[groaning]
Wait, wait, wait.
What about... my ending?
Here it comes.
Careful. They always come back.
Okay, then.
-[screaming]
-[all gasp]
[gunshot]
[body thuds]
I still prefer The Babadook.
Are you okay?
-Are you good?
-Mm-hmm.
I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
Excuse me, sir.
Hey.
-Hey.
-She's gonna be okay.
Can you take us
to a different hospital this time?
Of course.
You ready to go?
I'll be right back, yeah?
Your vitals look good.
You sit tight for a draft, okay?
Sidney. Gale.
Thank you both.
For everything.
Are you gonna be all right?
I'll survive. I always do.
You were right
about not running.
Sorry about that.
How are you doing?
Ask me in a few days.
But at least I know
what I'm gonna write about.
What's that?
Not this.
Those fuckers can die in anonymity.
But maybe something about a good man
who used to be the sheriff here once.
I'd like to read that story.
Can I ask you a weird question?
Yeah.
Am I gonna be okay?
Eventually.
-Hey.
-Hey, Sam, Sam, Sam!
Thank you.
Well, you're not going anywhere
without me.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna hold your hand
all the way there.
I can take care of her and her sister.
She's all ready for transport.
Twenty-five years ago, almost to the day,
in this very house, a tragic story ended.
Tonight, a new chapter came to a close.
Police do not have
a lot of information right now,
as they are still collecting evidence.
As you can see,
this is a very active crime scene here.
An unknown number of fatalities,
several injuries,
some people being taken off
by ambulance right now as we speak.
This is a developing story...
[whip-poor-will calling]
["Fall Out of Love" playing]
[song ends]
["I Don't Want to Talk" playing]