I hate scary movies. I should be studying.
You know I got a bio due.
Baby, did I mention
that these tickets were free?
- Free.
- Sandra Bullock is playing down the street.
Nobody wanna pay 7.50
to see some Sandra Bullock shit.
Unless she's naked.
But you will sit through
a movie called Stab?
It's adrenaline, Maureen.
It's good to be scared. It's primal.
You know what I'm sayin'?
- No, I'm gonna tell you what it is, okay?
- What?
It's a dumb-ass white movie
about some dumb-ass white girls...
gettin' their white asses
cut the fuck up, okay?
Yeah. I suppose Sandra Bullock
is Miss Ethnicity, right?
No. All I'm saying is that
the horror genre is historical...
for excluding the African-American element.
When the hell you get your PhD
in black cinema, Sister Souljah?
Listen. I read my Entertainment Weekly, okay?
I know my shit.
Yeah, Maureen.
I read my Black Beat too, homey.
Tonight we're gonna
have an all-black movie,
all-black cast,
all-black wardrobe, black eyes—
Everything. Black-eyed peas. Black cats—
- Crazy girl.
- Thank you.
- Hi. Here you go.
- What's this?
Stab souvenirs. The studio sent them.
And it's white.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Very romantic.
- Yeah.
- All right. She doesn't stand a chance.
Take it off!
Yeah!
Why has she gotta be naked?
What does that have to do with the plot
of the story, her being butt-ass naked?
I don't know about the plot,
but I got a stiff one.
You better loosen up that wrist.
Hello?
- Who is this?
- Guess.
- No, really. Who is this?
- Were you expecting somebody?
No.
Bitch, hang the phone up
and star-69 his ass! Damn!
- Who is this?
- Who would you like it to be?
I don't like games. Who is this?
Look out back.
Do you see your boyfriend anywhere?
I don't even have a boyfriend right now.
Would you like one?
Damn it all. Give me some money.
I need to get some popcorn.
- You got money.
- I got my money. I asked for your money.
What do you say?
Cheap-ass.
- Thank you.
- Come on.
Cat got your tongue?
I don't even know you,
and I dislike you already.
Come on! We're missing it!
We're missing it!
- Hey, we're sold out.
- Cool!
Hello.
Hi.
Can I have a medium popcorn,
no butter and a small Diet Pepsi?
- You got it.
- Thanks.
That's it. I am not going back in there.
Come on, you chickenshit. It's just a movie.
No, it's not just a movie. It's a true story.
All these kids got killed
a couple years ago in California.
- Here's the popcorn.
- Thanks.
God. I was so scared,
I almost had a heart attack.
Stab you, man!
- You ass!
- I'm sorry. I had to, baby.
- Why are you playing?
- Would you relax?
- God. What's wrong with you?
- I don't like being scared.
- I don't like that.
- Baby, it's just a movie.
Besides, scary movies are great foreplay.
Excuse me?
- Let's go see Sandra Bullock.
- No, no.
Sandra started already. We can stay.
Just stop playin' so much.
All right.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
See ya inside.
Come on!
Die! Die! Die!
Sorry.
Hello?
No. I didn't mean it. I didn't mean it.
I swear. I swear. I'll be good.
Please, don't, Mommy. No.
I'll be good.
You want to know why?
Why I did it, Mommy?
I'll tell you. Really.
I'll tell you, Mommy.
Really. I'll tell you
why I did it, Mommy.
Listen, Mommy. Listen, Mommy.
No! No, no, no!
Don't do that!
Move! Move! Go!
Run. Go!
Baby, give it up.
You came back just in time.
It looks like she's about to get it.
Want some popcorn?
See, if that was me,
I would be out of there.
Here it comes!
Here it comes, baby!
Kill her!
- Yeah!
- Nice goin'!
Hey. What are you doing?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Hello, Sidney.
- Yes?
- What's your favorite scary movie?
- Who is this?
- You tell me.
Cory Gillis, 555-01 76.
- Oh, shit!
- Hot flash, Cory.
- Shit!
- Prank calls are a criminal offense...
prosecuted under penal code 653-M.
Hope you enjoyed the movie.
Time to change numbers again?
No. It'll die off.
It's opening weekend. We'll see how it goes.
Okay.
You know, Ron, it's not an easy thing...
to be accused of a crime you didn't commit,
particularly one as heinous as murder.
But how do people treat you now that
they know the truth about your innocence?
Most people are cool. There's some
who still keep a safe distance...
which is odd for me, 'cause I've always been
sort of a people person.
But you were wrongly accused.
You were fully exonerated.
Yeah. That and a nickel will get you a cup
of coffee. Even that's not true anymore.
Certainly, with Gale Weathers's book,
and now the movie...
it's set the record straight
for Cotton Weary.
One would think. But Gale's been terrific
throughout this whole thing.
Hey. Move your ass, okay? You're late.
Don't forget about that martini mixer
tonight at the Delta Lambda Zetas.
I don't think I'm gonna
be able to make it, Hal.
What?
Don't even try to bag, okay?
'Cause you promised me.
- A vague promise at best.
- Nobody's asking you to join, okay?
It's a party. Free beer, meet the girls.
Hallie, you know me and organized religion.
- It's a sorority.
- Worse.
Look, Sid. Just lower the walls
for the next few days, okay?
This self-induced isolation
you got goin' is not healthy.
- I'm fine.
- “I'm fine.”
Yes, I know. “I'm fine”
is stretched tightly across your face.
Like that.
Check out the news.
The two Windsor College students
were murdered last night...
during a sneak preview of the new movie Stab.
The police haven't released any information
except for the victims' names...
but a press conference
is scheduled for later today.
The victims,
Maureen Evans and Phil Stevens...
were both Windsor seniors.
- Where's Randy?
- He's got Film Theory this morning.
... ended with the brutal murders
of two promising young—
- Sidney! Sidney!
- Sidney.
Sidney, did you know the victims?
- Do you feel threatened by the murders?
- No comment.
- Do you think there'll be more murders?
- Sidney.
- What can you tell us about the victims?
- How about the police?
- We just need one statement.
- Please talk to us.
You could say what happened in that theater
is a direct result of the movie itself.
That is so Moral Majority. You can't blame
real-life violence on entertainment.
What? Wait a second. Yes, you can.
Don't you even watch the news?
Yeah. Hello! The murderer
was wearing a ghost mask, okay?
Just like in the movie.
It's directly responsible.
No, it's not. Movies are not
responsible for our actions.
It's a classic case of life
imitating art imitating life.
This is not a hypothetical.
It's not about art.
I had Biology with that girl.
This is reality.
Thank you. I agree with you.
Let me tell you about reality, Mickey.
I lived through this. Okay?
Life is life. It doesn't imitate anything.
Come on, Randy. With all due respect...
the killer obviously
patterned himself after two
serial killers who have
been immortalized on film.
- Thank you.
- Right.
Are you suggesting that someone's
trying to make a real-life sequel?
Stab 2?
Who'd want to do that? Sequels suck.
- Come on, man.
- Please. Please.
By definition alone, they're inferior films.
It's bullshit generalization.
Many sequels have surpassed their original.
- Oh, yeah?
- Name one.
Yeah.
- Aliens. Far better than the first.
- There's no accounting for taste.
Thank you. Ridley Scott rules.
Name another.
No. Aliens is a classic, okay?
“Get away from her, you bitch!”
I believe the line is “Stay away from her,
you bitch.” It's film class, right?
- He got you.
- You know what I mean.
- Another.
- T2.
- You've got a hard-on for Cameron.
- Big one.
But wait a second.
The first Terminator is historical.
Yeah.
“Sarah Connor?”
“Yes.”
All right. Okay.
House II: The Second Story.
What?
The entire horror genre
was destroyed by sequels.
I got it, by the way. I got it.
The Godfather: Part II.
Very good.
That's the Oscar-winning exception.
All right. That's enough.
That'll be a wrap.
The sequel discussion to be continued.
Oh, no!
So, Mr. Originality,
how would you make it different?
I'd let the geek get the girl.
Three hundred people watched.
Nobody did anything.
They thought it was a publicity stunt,
for Christ sakes.
And it would have been a good one too.
- It's starting again, Randy.
- It's not.
A lot of shit happens at the movies.
People get robbed, shot, maimed, murdered.
Multiplexes is a very dangerous place
to be these days.
Yeah, and you are in extreme denial.
And you should be too.
This has nothing to do with us.
Randy, a guy in a ghost
mask hacked up two people
in a movie theater
telling our life story.
- Coincidence?
- You know what happened at Woodsboro, Randy.
- You can't ignore it.
- I know, Sid...
but I don't want to
go back there again.
Can't we just go back to
our pseudo-quasi-happy existence?
- Hello, Derek. How ya doin'?
- Hey, Sid.
- Hey.
- I've been looking everywhere.
- I heard. You weren't in class.
- Yeah, I know.
I skipped. I couldn't take
all the “that's her” looks.
Is there anything I can do?
You got any tricks for getting me back
to a pseudo-quasi-happy existence?
- You know, I might just have one for that.
- Yeah?
Oh, yeah? What is it?
Oh, Christ.
That was pretty good.
Get a room.
Hey, guys. Wait up.
- They're threatening to what?
- Pull the damn thing.
- Are you kidding me?
- No!
They'd be stupid to pull this movie.
With all this free press,
they're gonna have huge numbers this weekend.
- You think so?
- It'll break box office records.
Remember, we need an exclusive.
Don't forget.
- Consider it done.
- Yeah, but I need—
Miss Weathers? Hi. I'm Joel. The affiliate
sent me. I'm your new cameraman.
Yeah. You got experience?
Yeah. I'm local,
but I shot the bingo finals.
- Great. Great.
- I almost got an award for that.
All right. Listen, Joel.
This is how it works.
I point, you shoot.
You stay focused and fast on your feet,
and we'll get along fine.
You're playing with the big boys now.
You got it?
Got it. Got you covered. I'm all over it.
Hey, look. Don't worry about a thing.
How hard can it be?
You point, and I shoot. I'm there!
Excuse me. Miss Weathers?
Could I have a minute?
- No.
- Just one second.
I know you probably
get this all the time.
I just wanted to say I am
a big fan of your work.
I just finished you book.
I couldn't put it down.
Insightful, probing—
I just really, really loved your book.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
I'm a writer myself. I just write for
the local paper. For the Post Telegraph.
I'm Debbie Salt.
I took your seminar in Chicago last year.
I was the one in the front row
asking all the questions.
- Right. I thought you looked familiar.
- Thank you.
Can't wait to see the movie. You must be
getting quite a lot of flak on that, right?
With all the violence-in-cinema issues.
What is your position going to be?
- No comment.
- Miss Weathers, please—
It would be such an honor for me
if I could get a quote from you for my story.
- Okay. Begin quote.
- Great.
“Your flattering remarks
are both desperate and obvious.”
- Ouch!
- End quote.
Gale, what are you doing here?
Do you think
these murders are connected
to Sidney Prescott?
Miss Weathers, what's your theory on these
murders? What's your feeling about this?
May I have your attention?
- My name is Chief Louis Hartley—
- Chief Hartley.
Hi. Gale Weathers,
author of The Woodsboro Murders.
Do you think the killer will strike again?
We have no evidence
that this is a serial killer.
- I'd like to read from a prepared—
- Can you tell us of any...
precautions that you're taking?
First of all, we think it's just
an isolated incident, and we will be—
Ladies.
Oh, my God. This is huge.
Do you have any suspects?
- Sidney, look. It's Gale Weathers.
- What?
Star of the Gale Weathers press conference,
based on the book by Gale Weathers...
soon to be a major motion picture
starring... Gale Weathers.
Be kind. She saved our lives.
She had calf implants.
Chief Hartley, do you plan
on giving the town a curfew?
I'm gonna get closer.
- So that's her?
- Yeah.
And, of course,
we're questioning all the students—
Hello, girls. Enjoying yourselves?
- Hello, Sister Lois, Sister Murphy.
- Hello, pledge.
Hi, Sidney.
Hey.
This must be flat-out hell for you.
How are you holding up?
I manage.
It's really weird, isn't it?
To think this fuss is all because of you.
I mean, not directly, but in some
Six Degrees of Kevin Bacon way.
- Yeah.
Now, Hallie, are you gonna bring your friend
to our little martini mixer tonight?
- I have a lot of work to do.
- We'll be there.
Good. Because, Sid,
we have our eyes on you.
You hang in there,
and if there is anything we can do—
The Delta Lambdas
are very sensitive to your plight.
- Yeah. Bye.
- Bye.
You gonna start to dress
like that once you get in?
That's not gonna happen.
The Delta Lambdas
are the biggest bunch of fuckin'—
Hey! I'm pledging Delta Lambda, thank you.
Oh, my God.
Who's that?
Dewey?
Hey!
What are you doing here?
- I was worried about you.
- Yeah?
I heard about what happened,
and I was on the next plane.
- Can we talk?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, Dewey.
Or I was.
I mean, things were okay until now.
But theater's going great.
I got my first starring role.
We open in two days.
- That is great.
- Yeah. I'm loving it.
And I've got some great friends...
and... I'm seeing someone.
Nice guy. Premed,
no apparent psychotic tendencies.
I was just worried.
Look, Sid.
If there is some freaked-out psycho trying
to follow in Billy Loomis's footsteps...
you probably already know him.
Or her.
Or them.
They're probably already in your life.
They get off on that.
I just want you to be careful, Sid.
You think I don't know that, Dewey?
What am I supposed to do?
Just cut everybody off?
Crawl under a rock? What?
Just watch out.
Keep an eye out.
I'm gonna talk to Chief Hartley
and the local police.
I'm gonna just hang around.
I wanna make sure you're safe,
if that's all right with you.
Yeah. I'd be honored.
All right, Sid.
Hey.
- You okay?
- Uh-huh.
- Who is that guy?
- An old friend.
Deputy Dewey, Woodsboro's finest.
What's he doing here?
He's worried.
Our surrogate big brother.
God. Nothing like a funeral
to bring the family together.
I'm gonna go say hi.
- Chief Hartley said the girl was stabbed 7—
- Drop it.
Hello, Sidney.
- How are you?
- Hi.
What do you want, Gale?
I was hoping I might
get a few words with you.
- Cotton.
- Hi, Sidney.
Here we are at Windsor College,
where Sidney Prescott...
has just been reunited
with Cotton Weary for the first time...
since she wrongly accused him
of murdering her mother.
- What the hell are you doing?
- We want to know how you feel.
Tell us everything that's happened,
looking back on the last two years.
Sidney, I'd just like to say
that I forgive and forget.
Just like you, I'd like to get back on
with my own life.
- Do you have any comments?
- You bitch!
- Hey. Deep breaths. Lot of deep breaths.
- Sidney, share with us, please.
- I'll share with you!
- Okay, okay.
- Did you get that on film?
- Yes, I got that on film.
Sid? Wait, wait, wait.
Where's she going, Gale? Sidney?
Where's she going?
Gale, I thought we had an official interview.
What's going on? She didn't know?
Man, that was cold.
You need to check your conscience at the
door, sweetie. We're not here to be loved.
Gale, you promised me
10 minutes of national coverage.
You'll get your 10 minutes
when I get my goddamn interview.
Don't walk away from me, Gale. I'm still—
Gale, I did my part.
Joel!
Dewey.
What are you doing here?
Why don't you just leave her alone?
Hasn't she been through enough?
And my name is Dwight.
I was just doing my job, Dwight.
No matter who gets hurt in the process?
Hey.
Who got punched here— again?
I don't condone violence,
but maybe you deserved it.
Page 32:
“Deputy Dewey filled the room
with his Barney Fife-ish presence.”
- You read my book.
- Yes. I do read, Miss Weathers.
Dewey, don't take it so seriously.
It's a character in a book.
Page 41:
“Deputy Dewey oozed with inexperience.”
Don't you think you're overreacting
just a little bit?
No. What I think is that
you're a money-hungry,
fame-seeking and,
forgive me for saying...
mediocre writer...
who's got a cold storage shed
where her heart should be.
No offense intended.
Dewey, I never meant to imply—
How do you know that
my dimwitted inexperience...
isn't merely a subtle form of manipulation
used to lower people's expectations...
thereby enhancing my ability to effectively
maneuver within any given situation?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what else to say...
except... I'm sorry.
No. I'm the one that's sorry.
I misjudged you.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
I have some oozing to do.
One more thing.
Nice streaks.
Well.
Hey, I am not a sorority pusher.
I just think, despite its trivialities...
it is a life-affirming, mentally stable,
healthy environment for you.
I mean, look at this friggin' place.
I think you're taking your psych major
a little too seriously, Hallie.
I'm fine.
Yeah? That's beginning
to become your theme song.
“I'm fine.” Yeah— “Fucked-up,
insecure, neurotic and emotional.”
Sidney, you made it!
Hi!
No, I really mean that.
- Hi.
Do you girls want a drink?
Actually, yeah, but you know what?
We'll get it ourselves.
I love those guys. Are they still together?
I haven't seen it in, like, three weeks.
- No, they broke up again.
- Really?
Sarah found out
that Bailey slept with Gwen.
She dumped him, like, two episodes ago.
I wish she'd get her shit together.
Hold on. Someone's calling.
Omega Beta Zeta.
Hello?
- Yes?
- Who is this?
- Cici. Who's this?
- Who do you think?
Ted?
Where are you?
Are you drinking? Hold on.
Ted's on the other line.
He sounds drunk. I'll call you back?
That shit only calls you when he's drunk.
- Don't go over there, Cici.
- All right. I'll call you back.
Okay, Ted.
You sound loaded. What's up?
Who's Ted?
I'm sorry. My bad.
- I thought you were someone else.
- That's okay. I am.
Who are you calling for? Nobody's here.
Where is everybody?
We're cosponsoring the acid rain mixer
at Phi Gamma Alpha tonight.
- Why aren't you there?
- I'm “sober sister.”
I need to be here in case
a drunk sister calls and needs a ride.
That's too bad.
“Drink with your brain.” That's our motto.
- Who are you calling for?
- What if I said you?
- What if I said good-bye?
- Why would you want to do that?
Why do you always answer
a question with a question?
I'm inquisitive.
Yeah, and I'm impatient. Look.
Do you want to leave a message for someone?
Do you want to die tonight, Cici?
Omega Beta Zeta.
So, was it Teddy?
No. It was some creep asshole
trying to scare me.
That movie Stab, bringing out the crazies.
- Shit.
- What is it?
- I heard a noise.
- Where?
Upstairs.
Shit!
Hello?
Kill, kill, kill.
- Hello?
- Die, die, die.
Stop it!
I can't believe you're alone in that house.
I don't think I'm alone.
I'm out of here.
You're breaking up. Where are you?
- Outside.
- Don't panic, Cici.
- Call campus security.
- Okay.
Campus security.
- Hi. I'm calling from the Omega Beta—
- Can't hear you. I'm sorry. Hello?
Hello?
- Can you hear me now?
- Hello?
Hello? Shit!
- Campus security.
- Yes. I'm calling from—
I can't hear you. Hello?
I'm calling from
the Omega Beta Zeta house.
Look. Someone's harassing me.
Hello? Shit!
Hey!
- Jesus, Dawnie. You scared me.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Did anyone call for me?
- What are you doing here?
- I live here, remember?
I just thought you were going to the mixer.
Yeah, I am.
I had to change, so I'll be out of here now.
Omega Beta Zeta.
- Is Cici there?
- Who's calling?
It's Ted.
It's your ill-conceived boyfriend.
I'll see you later.
Don't forget to set the alarm.
Bye.
Hello, Ted.
You wish it was Ted.
Don't forget to set the alarm.
Hello?
No! Please, no!
No!
Everyone thinks that sororities
are just about blow jobs, but it's not true.
We only promote safe, condomed sex.
See, we're about love,
respect and responsibility.
Harmonica style is okay, right?
- Yeah.
- Cocktail?
What took you so long?
And you know Derek is
a Delta Lambda big brother.
And we like to keep it all in the family.
Wow. You girls have really
given me a lot to think about.
Thanks.
- Sorry I'm late.
- It's working. It's working.
- Hey, babe. You wanna dance?
- I'd love to—
with that tall,
wide-shouldered fraternity boy.
- Think you can go arrange that?
- That hurts.
Go play.
Empire Strikes Back.
It was a better story, improved effects.
Not a sequel.
Part of a trilogy, completely planned.
Yeah, I like those little furry things.
Ewoks. They blow.
Hey.
- How ya doin'?
- Good.
- Twits being nice to you?
- Painfully nice.
I take it you will not be pledging
Delta Lambda Zeta.
I think not.
I'm crushed.
Hey, guys.
Something is up at Omega Beta Zeta.
- Police are everywhere.
- Hurry!
You hear that? Let's go!
Here. I'll drive. Let's go.
- Way to break up the party.
- Shit! I should have brought my drink.
- Jack, hurry up! Come on, man.
- Yeah, yeah.
Death by blunt trauma,
and there's a double stabbing.
So it's definitely not suicide.
Okay. Thank you.
Gale, hi.
You're just getting here. It's not good.
It's a single victim. Sorority girl.
I gotta go. I've got a deadline.
- Joel, let's go.
- In a minute.
It's happening again, isn't it?
You'd love that, wouldn't you?
Better hurry, Gale. Might get scooped.
Move it, Joel.
Gale.
I have to be honest with you.
I'm not cut out for this.
I was brought here to do an interview,
not Faces of Death 14.
Do not fuck with me.
Come on.
Get your jacket. Let's get you home.
Yeah.
You about ready?
Almost.
Hello?
Hello, Sidney.
Remember me?
- What do you want?
- I want you. It's showtime.
Then why don't you show your face,
you fucking coward.
My pleasure.
Derek!
Sid? Sid?
Sid?
Sid!
- It's me. You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
No, Derek! Don't!
Sid!
Dewey!
The killer's in there. And Derek.
- You all right?
- He went that way.
Sidney, he's in here!
Is everything okay?
He got me. He got me.
- Apply pressure to it.
- No, Jesus—
Come on. Hold it there.
All right.
The police are on their way.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Hallie, we'll be with you
in a few minutes, okay?
No problem.
That's the easiest interrogation
of my crime-filled life.
I'm gonna go get a quick cup of coffee.
You want?
No.
You want some, Sid?
How you doin'? You all right?
Not at all.
You know, I knew this was coming.
- I knew this wasn't over.
- You are not alone, Sid.
Okay? We are all here for you.
All right? Whatever you need.
That poor girl.
I know.
It's crazy, but—
- Derek could've been killed, you know.
- But he wasn't.
He's fine.
He just needs to realize
the '90s is no time to play hero.
Why would anyone go back
in that house anyway?
I went around to the back of the house
and ran into Sid there.
That's when she told me the killer was
inside, so I went in to see.
You're lucky there's no nerve damage.
You're gonna have to take it easy though.
- Then you went back inside the house.
- Yeah.
No struggle?
He just cut you and ran away?
- You're lucky he didn't kill you.
- Yeah, it's awfully convenient.
Say what?
Nothing.
It's just a shame he got away so easily.
It's just a shame you got there too late...
right after he disappeared.
Yeah, it is.
We got three victims.
Maureen Evans, Phil Stevens...
and Cici Cooper.
Is Cici the girl's real name?
No. It's Casey. Casey Cooper.
As in Casey Becker?
Excuse me?
She was a young victim in Woodsboro.
As well as her boyfriend, Steven Orth.
As in Phil Stevens.
Maureen Evans—
Maureen Prescott. That's Sidney's mother.
Do you think someone's
trying to duplicate Woodsboro?
It looks like it.
I think you have a copycat
on your hands, Chief.
Jesus Christ.
What are you doing to keep Sidney safe?
I got my two best detectives guarding her.
Do these guys have to
follow you around everywhere?
We're attached at the hip.
How am I ever gonna get you alone?
To be honest, Derek...
I think it would probably
be in your best interest to...
stay as far away from me as possible.
I hope that was an off-the-cuff remark
that holds no subtext whatsoever.
No, actually...
I mean it.
I mean, look at you. You already got hurt.
I don't want to see that happen again.
I'll take my chances.
Derek, I'm serious.
This is serious.
You are concerned
with my personal well-being...
and not with trusting me or anything, right?
Like I said, I just don't
want to see you get hurt.
And I don't want to see you get hurt.
Okay, Sid?
- Take care, Miss Weathers.
- All right.
- Dewey.
- Chief.
Hi.
So I'm heading over to admissions
to do some legwork. You game?
I'm not here to write a book, Miss Weathers.
I'm here to help Sid.
I want to help her too.
And help myself, of course.
Come on, Dewey.
Smile just once. Please?
I'll smile when I catch the killer.
Gale, hi.
So who do you think did it?
What about Sidney's father?
Has he been ruled out as a suspect?
He's supposedly
out of the country on business...
but that sounds a little fishy,
don't you think?
- I'm not here to do your job, Miss Salt.
- What about this ex-cop, Dewey Riley?
- It's kind of strange that he showed up.
- Yeah, what's he doing here?
Dewey's a good guy...
unlike some of us.
Really?
It just seems to me that if the killer
is repeating what happened in Woodsboro...
it's quite possible
that the killer could be from Woodsboro.
That's all.
Derek, you think Sid
will let me interview her for my documentary?
Yeah. She turned down
Primetime Live, 20/20 and Dateline.
- But for you, yeah.
- Drop it.
I've been thinking about
this whole murder thing.
- Have they checked out Randy?
- What?
I know he's an innocent victim
the first time around, but he's a little off.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Come on. Randy? The guy's harmless.
- That's what they said about Dahmer.
- Guys, keep it down.
Come on. What's up, Sid?
- Hey, Sid.
- How's it goin'?
- Where's the Secret Service guys?
- Over there.
And which one is Kevin Costner?
The one on the right is Officer Richards.
He is a Capricorn. Divorced. Father of two.
And the one on the left is Officer Andrews.
He is a Gemini.
He's single, but I think he's gay.
Derek? Penny for your thoughts.
“This morning, I woke up with this feeling...
I didn't know how to deal with.”
And so I just decided to myself
- I'd hide it to myself
- What is he doing?
Tom Cruise, Top Gun, 1986.
- Derek, don't.
- When you walked into the room
- I think I love you
- Don't do this.
I think I love you
Isn't that what life is made of?
And though it worries me to say
I've never felt this way
Hey
I think I love you
So what am I so afraid of?
I'm afraid that I'm not sure of
a love there is no cure for
I think I love you
Isn't that what life is made of?
And though it worries me to say
I've never felt this way
Believe me
You don't have to worry
I only wanna make you happy
And if you say “Hey, go away”
I will
But I think better still
I better stick around and love you
Do you think I have a case?
Let me ask you to your face
Do you really love me?
'Cause I think I love you
Come on.
Come on, people.
Let's show a little love, huh? Stand up.
All right!
Come here. Come here, come here.
Don't worry, Sid.
I know things are a little crazy.
Isn't that a big frat faux pas?
Yeah. That is a big no-no.
You're not supposed
to give your Greek letters to your girl...
no shape, way or form.
The brothers are gonna kick his ass,
but it's tradition.
- It's tradition.
- It's good luck.
It'll protect you.
So, tell us about this part
you're getting rave reviews for.
I play this young girl, Sidney Prescott...
who discovers that her boyfriend
is this crazy serial killer...
who also killed her mother
the year before that.
- What kind of research
did you do for the part?
- I read the book.
I don't get it.
They get Tori Spelling to play Sid...
and they cast Joe Blow Nobody to play me.
At least you get David Schwimmer.
I get the guy who drove Jane Seymour's
stagecoach for one episode of Dr. Quinn.
Let's take a peek at the movie. This is
Tori Spelling starring in the new film Stab.
Billy, you scared me.
- What are you doing here?
- They let me go, Sid. I didn't do it.
- I'm innocent.
- I know.
- Please.
- Why won't you let me touch you?
Look. I've been going through
a lot lately, Billy. And with my mom—
Sid, I think you need to
just deal with that and move on.
I mean, when my mom left my dad,
I accepted it.
That's the way the cookie crumbles.
Moms leave.
Yeah, your mom left town.
She's not buried in a cemetery somewhere.
My mom's dead,
and she's never coming back.
Ever.
Stupid.
I love scary movies.
I'll wait for video.
Okay, let's get down to business.
The way I see it,
someone's out to make a sequel.
You know, cash in on all
the movie murder hoopla.
So it's our job to observe
the rules of the sequel.
Number one:
The body count is always bigger.
Number two: The death scenes are always
much more elaborate— more blood, more gore.
Carnage candy.
Your core audience just expects it.
And number three: If you want your sequel
to become a franchise, never ever—
How do we find the killer, Randy?
That's what I wanna know.
Let's look at the suspects.
There's Derek, the obvious boyfriend.
Hello, Billy Loomis.
The guy's premed,
and his “pity me” surface wound...
conveniently missed
every major vein and artery.
- So you think it's Derek.
- Not so fast.
Let's assume the killer,
or 'ers, has a half a brain.
He's not a Nick at Nite rerun type of guy.
He wants to break some new ground.
- Right?
- Right.
So forget the boyfriend. It's tired.
Who else do we got?
- There's—
- Mickey, the freaky Tarantino film student.
But if he's a suspect, so am I.
So let's move on.
Let's not move on.
Maybe you are a suspect.
If I'm a suspect, you're a suspect.
You have a point.
Okay, let's move on to—
- Hallie.
- Sid's roommate?
Serial killers are typically white males.
That's why it's perfect. It's sort of
against the rules, but not really.
Mrs. Voorhees was a terrific serial killer.
And there's always room
for Candyman's daughter.
She's sweet. She's deadly.
She's bad for your teeth.
Come on, Randy.
These kids are your friends.
- Who do you think's the killer?
- How about Gale Weathers?
Gale? A killer?
Why not?
- She is vicious enough.
- She's an opportunist.
Yeah.
Isn't it conceivable
she's planning her next book?
That's what reporters do, Dewey.
They stage the news.
No. Gale's a lot of things,
but Gale's not a killer.
- Just because you're sweet on her—
- No, I'm not.
Please! This is me talking. Randy...
the unrequited love slave of Sidney Prescott.
I know all about obsession.
And pain.
- You've got your love scar to prove it.
- And so do you.
And what's with that limp anyway,
'cause you were stabbed in the back.
Severed nerve.
Look. Gale's no killer.
Okay, okay. Whatever you say.
But if she's not a killer, she's a target.
Joel, let's get some establishing shots.
Gale, can we talk for a sec?
- What is it?
- Look. I'm a little confused here.
I mean, with your given track record...
why would you want to be here
when the killer strikes again?
Granted, I should've read your book
before I took this job.
But I'm reading it now, and—
I read what happened to your last cameraman.
The guy got gutted.
Now me, I'm gonna do what
any rational human being would do...
which is get the fuck out of here.
First of all, he wasn't gutted.
I made that up.
His throat was slashed.
Gale, gutted, slashed—
the guy ain't in the union no more.
It's a job, Joel.
And like every job, there's a few drawbacks.
You're a professional cameraman.
You've got to act like one.
Yeah, but I wanna report the news.
I don't wanna be the news.
Besides, brothers don't last long
in situations like this.
This is national television. Think about it.
This is a big chance for you.
The story is monumental.
Don't you wanna be a part of that?
Come on.
I need you.
I cannot do this without you.
Good. Come on.
- Let's get some work done.
- Yeah, let's go get killed.
We've been through this before. You know what
I think about your potential as an actress.
I know. I know.
It's just that with the murders...
and the movie and my life—
I do know how difficult it is for you.
Gus, I don't think I can do it.
The battle for the soul
is fought in the forum of art.
You're a fighter, Sid. That's why
you're here. That's why this is your major.
- Yeah, I'm a fighter.
- I didn't hear that.
- I'm a fighter.
- I don't believe you.
I don't.
I'm a fighter.
Okay.
So, at the risk of sounding like
a college drama teacher...
if you've got pain around
this kind of material, use it.
This is your role, Sid.
Cassandra is one of the great
tragic visionaries of literature.
She saw it all coming: the wars...
the murder...
the madness.
She knew she was cursed.
It was her fate, and she embraced it.
None of us can avoid our fate,
but as an artist...
you can honestly face it...
and fight it.
- You're good.
- There's no understudy. I'm desperate.
You can do this.
Okay, everybody. Gather around.
Third Act, one last time.
Cue the music.
All behold the dreaded fate of Troy...
that once stood proud
and light upon the hills of Sparta!
Now shrouded in the deathly smoke of ruin...
her royal children pitched from her walls...
her people driven through her ruins.
And now alone in fate's cruel isolation...
stands Cassandra...
her kingdom, family and friends...
driven to the wind.
No crime against
gods or man have I committed...
save to speak the truth.
And each hideous vision born from my mind...
has come to pass.
Troy has fallen...
not by my hand or wish...
but as I foresaw.
So now, fate's vengeful eye...
is fixed...
on me.
Tell us, O Cassandra...
where has the sweetness of life gone?
What stays fate's hand
from striking now at thee?
What stays fate's hand from thee?
All right. Hold it.
Hold it!
Everyone, take five.
Sidney?
Sid. Your escort has arrived.
- Derek, how long have you been here?
- I just got here.
- Is everything okay? What's goin' on?
- What happened to Mickey?
We swapped. He had to edit.
You get me instead. What happened?
Derek, don't.
Don't. I need to be alone
right now, okay?
Being alone is not the answer, Sid.
Yeah. Well, I think it is.
I need some distance.
Do I get a say in this?
No.
I guess I'm supposed to be... understanding.
Yeah.
You got it.
All right. Let's just assume the killer
is repeating Woodsboro—
- Yes?
- I have Bob calling.
- I'll have to call you back.
- That doesn't explain Sidney's attack.
Sidney wasn't killed in Woodsboro.
It wasn't for a lack of trying.
The killer's trying to finish
what was started.
- Sid's under protection, right?
- Yeah.
What?
- Bob really needs to talk to you.
- Tell Bob I'll call him back.
When'd she start smoking?
Ever since those nude
pictures on the Internet.
It was just my head.
It was Jennifer Aniston's body.
Anyway, you're forgetting something.
In Woodsboro, there were more victims
before the homestretch:
Tatum, my cameraman, Himbry—
Time-out. See, I don't need to be hearing
about no dead cameraman, all right?
I'm warning you guys. I am a verb away
from vacatin' these premises.
I'm gonna go get me some coffee,
doughnuts, Prozac...
see if I can find some crack, Special K,
X— not Malcolm—
I'll be back when you
guys start talking about
something a little more
Saved By The Bell-ish.
All right?
- He seems a little shaky.
- Don't worry about him.
If the killer is following a pattern,
then maybe we can figure out who's next.
I wouldn't follow a killer's pattern.
We were all involved in Woodsboro.
Could be any one of us.
So what do you wanna do, bonehead?
You just want to sit here and wait
and see who drops next?
I don't know... “Phonehead.”
Gale's not here!
I'm not interrupting anything, am I?
You three look deep in thought.
Have you ever felt a knife cut through
human flesh and scrape the bone beneath?
It's him.
- Who?
- The killer.
He can see us.
- Just keep him on the phone.
- What do you want me to say?
I don't know.
Just keep him talking. Come on, Gale.
- What are we doing?
- Hi.
- So—
- Look for somebody with a cell phone.
- What's your favorite scary movie?
- You'll never find me.
Yeah? What do you care?
Let 'em have their fun.
So, what's up?
What's your favorite scary movie?
Showgirls.
Absolutely frightening. What's yours?
- Sorry.
- What's your problem?
Wait. Let me guess.
The House on Sorority Row?
Dorm That Dripped Blood?
Splatter University?
Graduation Day? Final Exam?
- Am I close?
- Closer than you think.
Too slow, geek.
Do you want to die?
Is that the best you can do? Because Billy
and Stu were much more original.
- Give me that.
- Hey!
- Who's this?
Gale Weathers,
author of The Woodsboro Murders.
- Who?
- Come on.
Okay.
He's gotta be around here someplace.
He's just playing with us.
White male suspect, nine o'clock.
- My clock or your clock?
- Your clock.
I'll go around the back.
Why are you even here, Randy?
You'll never be the leading man.
Fuck you!
No matter how hard you try,
you'll never be the hero...
and you'll never, ever get the girl.
- Hey!
- Shit! Sorry. Hey, man—
Wrong guy, dead boy.
Oh, yeah? Let's redirect a moment,
Mr. I'm-So-Original.
- What's she doing?
- I don't know.
Hey!
- What just happened?
- What the hell?
- Dewey. Dewey.
- A citizen's arrest.
- Can I help you?
- No.
- Hello? Hello?
- Sorry.
- Beg your pardon.
Where's your innovation? Why copycat
two high school loser-ass dickheads?
Stu was a pussy-ass wet rag.
And Billy Loomis.
Billy Loomis! What the fuck!
Jesus! What a rat-lookin',
homo-repressed mama's boy.
Why not set your goals higher?
You wanna be one of the big boys?
Manson, Bundy, O.J., Son—
- Where's Randy?
- I don't know. This guy just grabbed me.
- No, I'm okay, Mom.
- I don't see him.
Randy!
What's goin' on?
Yo, man. Who broke my window?
Did your computer just freeze?
You have an instant message.
That's all. Just hit alt-M.
Yeah, but I'm not signed on.
Someone here in the library.
All the terminals are connected.
He's here.
Shit. Get her away from the computer.
Sid, it's probably just a sick joke.
- May I see your screen, please?
- Wait right here.
Yeah.
Shit.
- Sid, you okay?
- Cotton.
- Can we talk for a sec?
- This isn't a good time.
Come on, Sid. You sent me to prison.
I did over a year for you.
You can give me two minutes.
Cotton, I'm sorry. Every day I'm sorry.
I don't know how to apologize any more.
Don't be sorry. Sorry-schmorry, Sid.
I have the solution to all of our problems.
What? What are you talking about?
First of all, forget Gale Weathers.
She doesn't get it, Sidney.
She doesn't see the story.
Between you and me,
she wouldn't see the story
if it smacked her in
the side of the head.
Have you read that book?
Which brings me to my point. Who calls me
out of the blue, but Diane Sawyer.
Believe me, Sid, I was as shocked as you are.
Anyway, she tells me that
if you and I go on the air together...
- she will give us the entire hour.
- What?
We're talking prime time, Sid.
You, me and Diane Sawyer.
- Cotton, I can't.
- No, no. Sidney, look.
If this is about money,
it's not like we're not getting paid.
There's $1 0,000 each,
not to mention what I've
got going on the side
with the 900 number.
Cotton—
I know, I know, I know.
You don't like the press.
I know that, and I respect it, Sidney.
But, Sidney—
It's Diane Sawyer. Hello?
She's a class act. Sidney, this could be
some very, very heavy exposure.
I'm sorry.
Look. Between the movie and the book,
people know the truth.
Let's get on with our lives. There's been
enough exposure. Why would you want any more?
Why? I don't know, Sidney.
Maybe because I fucking deserve
a little exposure?
Come on, Sidney.
You dragged my name through the mud...
everybody thinks
I'm some kind of psycho killer...
and all I'm asking for is one little
fucking Diane Sawyer interview...
to maybe get my side of the story straight.
I don't think I'm being unreasonable
in that request, Sidney.
Do you? Honestly?
I'm... sorry, Cotton, but no.
You're sorry.
Yeah, I bet you're real sorry, Sidney.
Such a good angle, Sidney.
Lovable and fucked-up Sidney Prescott!
Everybody's favorite little victim!
- Ow! What are you doing?
- Relax.
- Put your hands on top of your head.
- Sidney!
- Shut the fuck up!
- Jesus! I'm not Billy Loomis!
You killed him. He's dead. Remember?
Run it by me one more time, will ya?
- Why did you attack Sidney Prescott?
- There was no attack.
We were talking very heatedly.
Miss Prescott and I...
have a very complicated past.
I didn't think that was a crime.
- No, but homicide is.
- Okay. Then book me.
Book me. Okay? Look.
I don't know about homicide,
but you've definitely
got me for raising my
voice in a public library.
We're dealing with four murders here.
You watch your mouth.
It shouldn't have been Randy.
It should have been me.
No.
- I should call his mother.
- Sid, I already made that phone call.
Are you okay?
Stop treating me like glass, Dewey.
I'm not gonna break.
It's okay to break.
That's not gonna happen.
You better hope your alibi's airtight.
Could I please remind everyone here
that I'm an innocent man?
Don't you watch TV? Current Edition?
Thought it was a very insightful program...
on which it was made abundantly clear
that I'm an innocent man.
So until you find me standing over a dead
body with a knife in my hand...
I think you better treat me
with the rights and privileges...
accorded to every innocent citizen
in this country.
Is there some problem
with the word “innocent”?
I know. It's a big one. Chief?
- What's going on?
- We have to let him go.
- Why?
- We don't have anything on him.
Sign here.
Gale.
Enjoying the show? The cops are funny.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Waiting for my 1 5 minutes of fame.
You can understand that, can't you, Gale?
Don't do anything stupid, Cotton.
Gale, you were so instrumental
in my freedom.
You're not having
character doubts now, are you?
Sidney, if you change your mind—
Come on. Take a hike.
Sorry about that.
What a creep.
They're gonna take you somewhere safe, Sid.
Yeah? Where's that?
I don't know, but I'll be there with you.
We should get going.
We'll take you by the dorm.
You can pack some things.
We've issued a campus lock-in this evening.
- No one's allowed out after dark, okay?
- Yeah.
Who's doing this, Dewey?
If not Cotton, then who?
I don't know, Sid, but I'll find him.
- Gale.
- Any leads, Gale?
Do you think the killer will come after you?
How does it feel to be
on the other side of the news?
- There's Cotton. Cotton! Hey!
- How are you, Bob?
- Good. Are you still a suspect?
- It's all been a huge misunderstanding.
- Cotton, have you been officially released?
- Gale. Hang on one second.
How about a photo?
No? You look great.
- How you holding up, Gale?
- I'm sorry, Bob. You were asking?
Must be scary knowing somebody's out there
waiting and watching, enjoying all this.
- How does that make you feel?
- Look, local woman!
I know that you hold me up
as your career template...
and it gives you some sort of... charge
to challenge me...
but give it a rest!
You're right. I'm sorry.
It was the wrong time. I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Let's see.
For starters, they impounded my van.
It's now an official crime scene,
thanks to you.
Here's your footage. Enjoy.
See ya. Wouldn't wanna be ya.
Joel, I need you!
No, you need to have your head examined.
I feel bad, Dewey.
I feel really bad.
I never say that because...
I never feel bad about anything.
But I feel bad now.
Is this just another...
brilliant Gale Weathers performance?
There are no cameras here.
I just wanna find this fucker!
I really do.
Me too.
Could I give you a hand?
What's in here?
Just some crowd footage that Joel shot.
Hey, wait a minute.
If the killer really is watching
and relishing every minute...
then he'd be here on these tapes, right?
- At each crime scene.
- It's worth a look.
It's definitely worth a look.
This way.
Dubbing Room.
Editorial.
- Video Archive.
- Yeah.
- It's locked.
- Can you pick it?
- That would be breaking and entering.
- No shit.
There's gotta be a VCR
around here somewhere.
What's in there?
- Now we're gettin' somewhere.
- Perfect.
Start with this one.
Sorry.
- Ow.
- I'm sorry.
- Did I hurt you?
- No.
- My name is Chief Louis Hartley—
- Chief Hartley.
Hi. Gale Weathers,
author of The Woodsboro Murders.
Do you think the killer
will strike again?
You're a money-hungry, fame-seeking, and,
forgive me for saying, mediocre writer...
who's got a cold storage shed
where her heart should be.
- No offense intended.
- I didn't mean to imply—
Listen.
- You're cute when you're angry.
- I was rude.
I was being rude.
...lower people's expectations, thereby
enhancing my ability to effectively maneuver—
Dewey, I'm sorry.
I never meant to hurt you.
Hey.
Really.
I should be studying.
You know I got a bio due.
Baby—
Dewey.
Sandra Bullock is playing
right down the street.
Dewey.
Sorry.
That's not my footage.
Outside.
Fuck you!
No matter how hard you try,
you'll never be the hero...
and you'll never, ever get the girl.
- Sorry.
- Wrong guy, dead boy.
Stay here.
No, Dewey, don't!
Dewey!
There's no one there.
Gale!
Fuck!
Gale?
Gale!
No.
No!
So.
Listen, Sid.
Hey. Wait up.
- She's fine.
- I'm her therapist.
Bye, Derek.
Bye.
We better get going.
When this is all over...
I'll still be here.
You! Prepare to die.
- You gave up your letters.
- Oh, man.
- Get him, guys!
- I'm not— Guys—
To Troy! We march!
This is so romantic.
And so Greek!
That's cold! That's cold.
Who do you love, baby?
- Sidney.
- Did you say “my Omega Kappa Beta brothers”?
No, I said Sidney!
So, where are you taking us anyway?
If we tell you, we'll have to kill you.
Don't ask, don't tell.
Son of a bitch!
No! Shit!
Help me, baby! Help!
Oh, my God!
Out of the car, you fucker.
Get down back there!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
I'll blow your fuckin' head—
Is he dead?
I don't think so.
No, he's still breathing.
Is he dead?
Oh, God. I think so.
- How are you supposed to get outta here?
- We're not. It's a cop car.
Wait, wait, wait.
- No. Don't touch that, girl.
- Hallie, it's the only way out. Help me out.
Come on.
Okay, okay, okay.
We're jammed up against a wall.
Oh, my God.
No, Sid. Don't. Sid.
God, I hate this shit.
Oh, my God. Don't do that again.
Try the window.
- Shit!
- Get me the fuck outta here, Sid.
I can't. The door's jammed.
You have to go through the front.
- No fuckin' way.
- Hallie, do it.
Go on.
Hallie, go on.
Okay. Okay, that's right.
Okay. Okay, that's good.
Right through his eye.
Come on.
That's good. Easy. Easy.
He's not gonna hurt you.
Easy.
Come on. Watch your feet.
Okay.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
- Hallie.
- What?
I wanna know who it is.
- Oh, no. Come on, Sid. Let's just go.
- I'm going back.
Look. Stupid people go back.
Smart people run. We're smart people,
so we should just get the fuck outta here.
Hallie, I'm sick of running.
- If we know who it is, then it's over.
- No, we can just get the police.
Yeah, and when we come back,
he'll be gone. It'll only take a minute.
- I have to do this.
- Sid.
No, Sid. Come back! Sid!
Sid, come back.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
- He's gone.
No!
Gale.
- No, no, no.
- Get away from me.
No. This isn't what it looks like.
I found Dewey.
I tried to help him. No. Gale, wait.
Gale. Gale, wait! Gale!
Shit.
- The campus is extremely quiet.
- Help me!
The curfew in full effect.
- Give me the goddamn phone!
- Gale. I was right in the middle of a story.
- I've got your goddamn story!
- What's the matter?
Operator.
Operator, this is an emergency!
Get the police!
- What's happening?
- The killer! It's Cotton fucking Weary!
Cotton Weary?
Hello?
Gus?
Derek?
God.
Derek.
Derek!
Oh, God.
Thank you. Thank God, Sid.
Thought I was gonna be up there
till opening night.
- Who tied these? We gotta get outta here.
- The brothers got me, Sid.
- Derek, he's after me. He killed Hallie.
- What are you talking about?
- The killer. He's here.
- Where?
Right here.
- You're fast, Sid.
- Get me down. Hurry!
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
You really wanna trust your boyfriend?
Don't you know history repeats itself?
Sid?
Mickey.
Surprise, Sidney.
What the fuck?
Since Derek here disappeared on my ass...
I've been on my own all fuckin' night.
- Thanks a lot, partner.
- You motherfucker!
Sid, he's crazy.
You know me better than that.
Come on, Sid. I gotta have a partner.
I couldn't have possibly done this alone.
- God. Derek.
- Sid.
No, no. Sid. Sid.
No, no, no.
It's okay, Derek. We got her.
Sid, he's lying!
Sid! Sid! Untie me.
Sid, untie me.
Boyfriend. Killer. Boyfriend. Killer.
Sid, the man is lying! Untie me. Sid.
Untie me. Untie me.
What do you think, Derek?
Sidney experiencing some déjà vu?
No. No. I am gonna fuckin' kill you!
Fuckin' kill you! You are dead! Dead!
Derek.
I'm sorry.
I never...
would've... hurt you.
Never.
No.
You should really deal with
your trust issues, Sid.
Poor Derek. He's completely innocent.
And such a nice boy too.
He's bright and funny and handsome.
Decent singing voice.
And he was gonna be a doctor.
This was just the kind of boy
you'd like to take home to Mom.
- If you had a mom.
- Fuck you!
So vulgar.
Did Billy let you talk to him this way?
Billy was a sick fuck, just like you.
No. Billy was a sick fuck
who tried to get away with it.
Mickey is a sick fuck
who wants to get caught. Yeah!
See, I've got my whole defense planned out.
I'm gonna blame the movies.
It's pretty cool, huh?
It hasn't been done before.
You see, this is just the beginning,
a prelude to the trial.
That's where the real fun is,
'cause these days it's all about the trial.
Can't you see it?
The effects of cinema violence on society.
I'll get Dershowitz or Cochran
to represent me.
Bob Dole on the witness stand in my defense.
Hell, the Christian Coalition'll
pay my legal fees.
It's airtight, Sid.
I'm an innocent victim.
- You're a psychotic.
- Yeah, well—
That'll be our little secret.
'Cause people love a good trial.
It's like theater. They're dyin' for it.
And I've worked hard
to give the audience what they want.
See? That's what Billy was good at.
He knew... it's all about...
- execution.
- Yeah?
You're forgetting one thing
about Billy Loomis.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
I fucking killed him.
You piece of shit!
Sid.
You got a Linda Hamilton thing going.
No, no. It's nice. I like it.
Now, who's doin' that?
Could that be the mystery guest
waiting in the wings?
Told ya I had a partner, Sid.
Surprise cameo just for you.
Gale.
Mrs. Loomis?
What?
Billy's mother!
Nice twist, huh?
Didn't see it comin', did ya?
Jesus. It can't be.
I've seen pictures of you.
This is 60 pounds and a lot of work later.
It's called a makeover. You should try it.
Look a little tired yourself there, Gale.
So you two are in this together?
Yeah, well, had to have financing.
Tuition's expensive.
Deb there, my backer—we met on the Internet.
Psycho Web site. Classifieds.
There's only an estimated 97
active serial killers in the country today.
So Mickey here was quite a find.
Definitely one on the way up.
All he needed was a little
guidance and nurturing.
As only a mother can do.
Told you it was gonna work.
Wait till the trial!
It is gonna rock!
Oh, Mickey. There's not gonna be a trial.
Gale!
Two birds, one stone.
Mickey was a good boy, but, my God,
that whole blame the movies motive—
Did you buy that for one second?
Poor boy was completely out of his mind.
- And you're not?
- No. I'm very sane.
My motive isn't as '90s as Mickey's.
Mine is just good old-fashioned revenge.
You killed my son.
And now I kill you.
And I can't think of anything more rational.
You're never gonna get away with this.
Of course I will.
Everything's traceable back to Mickey.
Including the cop gun
he used to kill everybody.
But let's just suppose that you...
had gotten hold of the other cop's gun.
And you chased Mickey. And there was
a big shoot-out and a big scuffle.
And you shot Mickey, killed Mickey dead.
But not before he got off one shot at you.
Okay. So, have I covered everything?
Are there any questions, any comments?
You know what though?
Who give a flyin' fuck anyway?
Let 'em try and track down the second
possible killer. Debbie Salt doesn't exist.
You're as crazy as your son was.
What did you just say?
Was that a negative,
disparaging remark about my son?
About my Billy?
No, Billy was a good boy.
Billy was perfect.
You did a bang-up job, Mrs. Loomis.
It's not wise to patronize
a woman with a gun, Sidney.
Randy spoke poorly of Billy,
and I got a little knife happy.
I was a good mother.
You know what makes me sick?
I am sick to death of people saying
that it's all the parents' fault.
That it all starts with the family.
You wanna blame someone?
Why don't you blame your mother?
She's the one who stole my husband
and broke up my family.
And then you took my son!
You don't know what it is to be a mother.
To raise a child and teach him...
and guide him—
And abandon him.
Isn't Mickey supposed to be dead?
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
No.
Don't you fuckin' move!
- Goddamn it!
- Cotton.
Okay, okay, okay. Everybody slow down.
I have had a very, very bad day...
and I would like to know
exactly what the fuck is going on here.
- Sidney?
- Cotton, meet Billy Loomis's mother.
She's the killer.
What?
- And who's that?
- The other killer.
Mickey.
Okay.
- Look, Cotton—
- Shut up.
So—
- Hi.
You're not Debbie Salt, are you?
You're not with the Post Telegraph.
No, but I can still help you, Cotton.
You don't need her. Let me kill her!
As long as she's alive,
you're never gonna be the lead story.
That's what you really want,
isn't it, Cotton?
If you really wanna be in the spotlight...
just let me kill her... right now.
Then you're the only survivor.
You're the star!
She sent you to prison for a year!
Personally, I think it's rather poetic.
No. No, Cotton. Don't you listen to her.
It's quite a predicament you're in, Sid.
- Cotton—
- She makes a good point.
Let me think about this.
Maybe you should too.
Bet you that Diane Sawyer interview's
lookin' real good right about now.
Consider it done.
Wow.
That... was intense.
Hey, Sidney—
I want you to know that I would never,
ever do anything to hurt you.
Cotton, give me the gun.
Yeah. Okay. Sure. Take it.
Sid, we should probably talk about
what exactly happened here.
Get our stories straight
for the press statement.
Oh, shit!
- Cotton.
- Could somebody get me outta here?
Gale. Are you all right?
I've been shot. Of course not.
- Help!
- Here. Give me your hand, Gale.
- Ow.
- Jesus, Gale, you scared the crap outta me.
- Isn't anybody else down there, is there?
- No.
So much for reporting from the trenches, huh?
Shut up, Cotton.
- How bad is it?
- Just bounced off my ribs.
Geez, Gale.
You got more lives than a cat.
Give me one of those.
Is she dead?
I don't know. They always come back.
Just in case.
- That about wraps it up, Chief.
- Okay, Frank.
Take it easy.
You got a couple of broken ribs there.
- Greg, I'm okay.
- Sure.
Hey, Gale. Are you all right?
Joel.
I'm back.
I was thinking maybe we could
get the scoop like in the old days.
You're Gale Weathers... at Windsor College.
We got a live one here!
Move it!
- Where's Gale?
- Got room in that one over there?
- Yeah.
- Dewey!
Watch your back! Watch your back!
- Go.
- Oh, God.
- Take it easy, buddy.
- I can't believe you're alive.
- Are you okay?
- Gale.
You hang in there.
He was lucky.
Knife went into some old scar tissue.
Saved his life.
Bye-bye.
I'm coming with you.
How do you feel?
Can you tell us what you saw?
Can you tell us what
happened in there?
Sidney, can you tell us
how it feels to be a hero?
Talk to Cotton.
He's the man you want to interview.
He's the hero.
Cotton!
- What went on in there? What happened?
- Is it true you're a hero?
What really happened inside there?
Any details at all?
- Details, please!
- Tell us what happened.
Look, guys. No one wants to give you
the story more than I do.
Unfortunately, there is a time and a place...
and indeed, a price for everything,
so feel free to call me.
Come on, Cotton. Tell us something.
I'll tell you one thing.
It'll make a hell of a movie. Thank you.