Cheers!
Excellent.
Let's drink until we drop.
-You should save your energy for tonight.
-Mix it.
Are you kidding me, Tun?
Don't you know who I am?
Alcohol energizes me.
The later it gets, the hornier I become.
-Horny?
-Come, come.
-Let's toast.
-Here's another glass. Have a little sip.
So, tell me, Jane.
What year are you in?
I'm in my fourth year.
You're old enough to do what you want now.
So, how did you meet Tun?
Because he's a hunk.
You keep saying that since college.
Jim had to ask for her number for you,
-you pain in the ass.
-Speaking of college, do you remember
when you got your heart broken?
-He was so drunk.
-Which girl left him a drunken mess?
-Her name was Kay. I do remember that.
-It's "Teochew" Kay.
-Ignore them.
-Right. What do you mean by "ignore them"?
-Wait. I have a question.
-What?
How can a guy like you get married?
Why can't a guy like me get married?
After a long tiring day at work,
all I want is to head home
to cuddle with my wife or my dog,
not waste my life,
-partying with you losers, okay?
-I have nothing to do with this, man.
A good man...
went whoring with me last night.
Fooling around so soon?
Here she comes.
Quiet.
What's so funny?
Nothing, dear.
I have one last thing to say to you.
One more glass!
What are we listening to?
Hey. Don't turn it off.
It's beautiful.
You guys seem tight.
How long has it been
since you last saw each other?
What are you looking at?
Someone beautiful.
That's so sappy.
Are you okay?
Tun.
Is she dead?
Jane, wait!
Just drive away.
I said drive away!
Drive away!
Get closer, please.
Okay.
Big smile, Nuch.
Or you won't look pretty.
All Science graduates,
please gather on the stand
for a class photo.
They're calling you.
Where's Jane?
She's probably taking photos
with her friends.
I thought you guys broke up.
Come on. Let's go.
I called you so many times today
but you didn't pick up.
Was your phone on silent?
No, it wasn't.
Nuch asked about you today.
When will you be free?
She said she wants to...
Jane.
How can you act like this?
You're pretending like nothing happened.
Since that night,
I haven't been able to sleep at all.
Well...
You think it doesn't bother me?
We should have gone out
and checked how she was.
It was an accident, Jane.
That's easy for you to say.
You were not the one behind the wheel.
-Hi, Ti.
-Hey.
How's business?
Have you got a lot of customers?
With you here this early,
I don't think
many customers will be coming.
Are my prints ready?
Yes. Just a second.
Here.
Is your processor broken?
Let me see.
You punk.
If the prints turn out nice,
you get the credit.
If they suck, it's my fault.
Just look at the negatives.
This is impossible.
I took them. I should know.
We'll see.
See?
It's your fault your negatives are ruined.
Tun.
Can you hear me?
Help!
Don't be scared. I'm here now.
What's wrong with your camera?
I don't know.
The whole roll is ruined.
That many?
What are these shadows?
My camera must be broken.
I don't know how I'm going to tell Nuch.
Tun.
Look at this picture.
That woman...
Do you think she's dead?
That's enough, Jane.
I'll have my camera fixed tomorrow.
Tun.
Look at this picture.
Are you sure it was here?
Excuse me.
What happened?
A few days ago,
a car ran into the billboard.
The driver must have been drunk.
Was anyone hurt?
No.
Just the broken sign.
Are you sure?
What?
Well...
Nothing, bro.
Thank you.
What?
Are you sure you checked everywhere?
It's nothing.
Thanks, anyway.
My friend called every police station
and hospital around the area.
He said there was no report
of any accidents that night.
How is that possible?
What about the girl we ran over?
Are you sure he called everywhere?
Maybe someone helped her.
Maybe she's fine.
How can she be fine?
We plowed into her like that.
And even if she's fine...
then what's in those photos?
I told you they're not related to her.
They're just bad exposures.
Don't you get it?
Tun.
I think you need to make merit, man.
These pictures...
show that there's a spirit haunting you.
How long have you been
a photographer, you punk?
Why are you showing me these?
I know, but...
Don't you find these shadows strange?
You want to see spirits?
I'll show you something.
Here.
This is Auntie Cham's spirit.
Do you know where she is now?
She's still selling fried bananas
in the next alley.
Here's Auntie Cham. And here.
Those are all Auntie Cham.
They were all taken on the same day.
They're just double exposures,
and out of focus.
Come on. I know that.
Everyone is probably familiar
with this place.
It's just an ordinary location...
that we pass by...
and see every day.
Now look at these pictures.
These are pictures of the same location.
But do you see...
that everything looks better?
That means photography
does not always convey reality.
It depends on how...
the image is framed,
what the photographer chooses to reveal,
and what to conceal.
Your perspective is critical.
SPECIAL SCOOP: SPIRIT PICTURES
Hey, Jane. You're early.
I'll get it.
-Hello?
-Hello, Tun.
It's me, Jane.
I'll come by in the afternoon.
Hello?
Tun, can you hear me?
Tun!
Hello?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
My neck has been hurting
since the accident.
You should go see a doctor.
I'm sure it's nothing serious.
What's the use of talking to these quacks?
REAL GHOSTS, DEADLY SPIRIT,
GHOST STORIES, GHOST PATH
Are you a reporter?
No.
The funeral foundation told us
to come here.
We run a legal operation here.
We have all the permits.
Excuse me.
Are all these pictures fake?
Piak. Go tell our boss he has guests.
Everyone fakes them.
You know,
those photos are always a hit.
Any issues with them sell out.
Do you think...
we can always find real ones?
Isn't that deceiving the public?
Our readers...
want to see scary photos.
They don't want love stories.
Does that mean
all the published photos are fake?
I didn't say that.
Take a look.
Do you see anything?
This is the first photo I had.
I took it at home.
People say the shadow in the back
bears an uncanny resemblance to my mom.
Believe what you will.
But this picture...
was taken years after my mom passed away.
You know,
sometimes
spirits just want to be close
to their loved ones.
The pictures that you see,
for me,
are more than just...
pictures with strange shadows in them.
It's the stories behind the pictures.
Think about it.
Why would the dead...
return to the living...
if they are not trying
to tell us something?
Most importantly,
people also believe
that there are connections...
between the shadows
and someone in the picture.
A father.
A mother.
A lover.
Or it could be someone
whom you've wronged in the past.
How can we be sure
those photos aren't just bad exposures
or were forged?
What do you think about polaroids?
Can you forge them?
You load the film cartridge in,
press the shutter.
And out comes the photo.
Tell me, then.
How can they be faked?
How do we know what they want?
Perhaps the answer is in the photo.
Here's the last two shots.
Big smiles.
Can you change your pose for me?
Embrace her, hold the bouquet
and put your cheeks close together.
Good.
Beautiful.
We're done. Thank you.
Thank you to you both.
Take them to the dressing room.
What the hell?
Who's doing that?
Aum, check the fuse!
Hey, Aum!
Who's doing that?
Is it you, Aum?
Who is it?
Who's there?
I said, who's there?
Where are you, Aum?
Who's there?
Please step off the scale.
Step on it again.
Have you been working hard lately?
Well, not really.
How long has it been hurting?
For quite awhile.
But it's gotten worse lately.
I had a car accident.
A car accident?
I've done the examination
and everything seems fine.
You shouldn't worry.
But it really hurts, doctor.
Your x-rays came back normal.
It might be a muscle strain.
Try taking the medicine I prescribed.
Mr. Tun, your prescription's ready.
Take this medicine
three times a day after meals
until the prescription runs out.
Lying bastard.
Pardon?
Yes?
Nothing.
Lying bastard.
As for this medicine, the doctor said...
Sir!
What's wrong?
...is rarely seen.
When grasshoppers begin mating,
the male can smell the female
from a distance up to 100 meters.
Then, the male will carefully approach
the female
and hook itself onto her belly.
And they will then begin to mate.
The female's response
to this is surprising.
The male will become her prey.
She will slowly eat his head off
while they are mating.
Eventually, the male succumbs to death.
-Excuse me, where is room 301?
-It's upstairs.
Jane.
Who's there?
Ton.
What's wrong?
Tun, I'm about to die.
What's going on?
The photos...
Bring me those photos.
What photos?
Are you drunk?
Those photos...
Where did you hide them?
Give them to me.
Do you remember that bitch?
Calm down, man.
What photos?
Just give them to me!
Calm down, man!
Ton, calm down.
What photos?
Ton.
I'll call your wife.
What are you doing?
I'm just tidying up the place.
Is your neck still sore?
Yes.
Take it easy. Don't work too hard.
MS. NETNAPA CHAN-NGAM
HONOR SOCIETY 1995
Ton.
It's me, Tun.
Are you home?
Ton.
MS. NETNAPA CHAN-NGAM
Ton!
I'm really sorry.
You know, right?
You know what was bothering him.
I don't know. Suddenly he...
It's all because of you guys, right?
Have you all gone insane?
What do you mean?
Why did everyone commit suicide?
Who?
Didn't you know?
The other two
just jumped off the building
and killed themselves.
Which two?
The ones who sat next to you
at the wedding.
Who is this woman?
Where did you get that?
She's the shadow in the photos, right?
Who is she?
How is she related to you?
I knew her in college.
Her name is Net.
She was a quiet person.
She didn't have any friends.
Everyone saw her as a freak.
I felt sorry for her.
We dated but I kept it a secret.
She loved me a lot.
She threatened to kill herself.
I didn't know what to do.
All my friends saw it as a joke.
How were they involved?
Why are they dead?
They...
What did they do?
I don't know.
Ton said he would take care of it.
After that, Net disappeared.
I never saw her again.
Didn't you try to stop them?
How could you let it happen?
What could I do?
Now everyone is dead.
I am...
I'm probably next.
It's funny.
We always say...
if we could turn back time,
we...
we wouldn't repeat our mistakes again.
Do you think she's okay?
Will we see her tomorrow?
Go to sleep.
I'll keep you company tonight.
Excuse me.
Do you have any toilet paper?
Would you mind letting me shit first?
I'm sorry.
What's going on, Tun?
Tun, what's wrong?
What is it?
Is it around here?
Excuse me.
Do you know where this house is?
Mom, do you know this house?
Ma'am.
Excuse me.
Is this Net's house?
What do you want?
Well...
We're her friends.
Net's friends? Come inside.
Have some water. You must be tired.
Did you drive here from Bangkok?
Yes.
Well...
We'd like to ask you about Net.
She's not feeling well.
She's taking a nap after taking her pills.
Should I wake her?
Stay for dinner.
I was about to cook.
I'm making Kang Som, Net's favorite dish.
Net will be so happy.
Her friends don't visit often.
Wait right here.
What are you doing, Tun?
What are you doing?
Did she commit suicide?
We should hold a funeral for her.
No.
I won't cremate my own daughter.
Ma'am.
I don't know if you believe such things,
but I'd like you to look at these photos.
They were taken around campus.
Some of the places...
were rooms Net had been in.
And...
And those shadows appeared.
I think that...
Net's spirit is restless.
Net.
My dear Net.
Why don't you come visit me?
You know what happened to her, right?
And what happened in Bangkok.
Ma'am...
Ma'am.
The reason Net's spirit is still here
might be because
her spirit is not at peace.
We should hold a funeral for her.
Please.
Ever since Net came home,
she seemed different.
She wouldn't talk to anyone.
No one knew what happened in Bangkok.
One day, she overdosed on pills.
Luckily, her mother found her
and got her to the hospital in time.
After she fully recovered,
she climbed on the hospital roof
and jumped off the edge.
Why did Net's mom still kept
her body around?
She went a little crazy after Net's death.
No matter what anyone said,
she refused to cremate her.
The villagers got scared.
No one wanted to socialize with her.
Can't sleep?
Tell me the truth, Tun.
Did you love Net?
I tried to, Jane.
I believed that one day I would.
But I was fooling myself.
When I broke it off,
I was a total asshole to her.
But she still loved me.
I just want this to be over.
If she wants me to die, I will.
Don't say that.
It's almost over.
No, it's not.
I know she'll come for me.
Tun.
We've come this far.
And you're sorry for what you did.
I'm sure she knows.
Don't talk like that anymore.
I'm sorry.
Do you still love me?
You won't leave me no matter what, right?
Jane.
Tun.
Where were you?
Why did you leave me alone?
We've got to go, Jane.
Asshole!
Why did you leave me?
Don't you love me anymore?
Where are you going?
Tun.
How are you feeling?
What happened last night?
Tun.
Jane.
The abbot said Net's body
will be cremated today.
It's over.
-Hello.
-Hello, Jane.
You're here to pick up the photos?
Where's Tun?
He's busy.
Good.
I hope he gets busy often,
so I can see you instead.
You guys went on vacation?
We went to Hua Hin.
When did you go?
Last week.
This photo is...
What's wrong?
Are you getting fatter?
I almost didn't recognize you.
Hi.
-Jumbo prints, please.
-Okay.
Write your name here, please.
Get her!
Jane.
Why are you crying?
Asshole.
How could you be so cruel?
Jane, where did you find these?
-Jane.
-If I didn't find them,
I'd be a fool forever, right?
Let me explain, Jane.
What is there to say?
I've always believed you.
It turns out I don't know you at all.
Tun.
Take her pictures, so she doesn't blab.
Tun, help me!
I know it was wrong.
Take her pictures now!
What's wrong?
I'm your buddy!
Hurry!
Tun, help me!
I never forgave myself.
But I was young and stupid.
Stop talking.
I want to go home.
Come out.
Where are you?
Didn't you say you love me?
Didn't you love me so much?
Till death do us part, huh?
Jane's gone now!
Sometimes, spirits just want to be close
to their loved ones.