By the way, Dad,
do you remember my friend, Dito?
On my first day at school,
you said he'd be my best friend someday.
You were right. How did you know?
ANGGA ADITYO
BORN 15 MAY 1972 - DIED 11 NOVEMBER 2012
Dad...
Mom is getting worse.
She always yells at me.
Whatever I do, it's always wrong.
I have to go home.
I'll see you again tomorrow.
Where have you been?
Answer me!
I'm sorry, Mom.
I went to Dad's grave.
You know you have to come
straight home after school.
What were you doing at your dad's grave?
I'm the surviving parent.
I'm the one
who takes care of you. Not him.
Do I have to be dead
for you to listen to me?
Go take a shower
and come back here for dinner.
Yes, Mom.
Baskara!
Why are you still up?
Go to bed, now.
CILILITAN 01 PUBLIC ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Kids, tomorrow we're going
on a field trip to the Maritime Museum.
But, ma'am, they say there's a room there
that has never been opened
since someone hanged herself in it.
And she haunts the museum
every night ever since.
Calm down, kids. Tomorrow we'll see...
I don't believe anybody
who says they can see ghosts.
I've never seen a ghost in my life.
Once you activate your sixth sense,
you might see ghosts, too.
I don't believe in ghosts.
Do you want to buy some snacks?
I don't know. How much money do you have?
I have 15,000.
Let's go.
Did you laugh at me?
Tell me you don't believe
what I said about ghosts.
You'd better watch your back tomorrow.
-Shut up!
Let's go.
You stay.
Are you okay?
Did you get in a fight?
No, Mom. I was...
What should I do to punish you, Bas?
Don't you have any sympathy
for your own mother?
Your job at school is to study,
not train to be a fighter.
And you ripped your school uniform.
Do you think the shirt was free?
Do you think money grows on trees
and you can waste it any way you want?
Bas.
Do you understand how hard I work
to pay for your tuition
and put food on the table?
I give up. I just can't take it anymore.
ANTON PRASETYO - MELATI STREET 5/R.22
MANGGARAI, JAKARTA 12850
I want you to protect my mother.
I'm going to find my Uncle Anton.
Dear Mom, I'm leaving.
I hope you'll be happier with me
out of the picture. I love you.
Now, kids, this is a model
of our famous tall ship Dewaruci.
This is the ship our Navy uses
for training the cadets.
This ship has three mainmasts.
They're named
Arjuna, Yudhishthira and Bhima.
Now, let's move on to the next room.
It's awesome.
Bas?
This is the room I was talking about.
Now, prove to me
that you don't believe in ghosts.
-Get inside!
-Go!
-Open the door.
-Get in there!
Get in there!
-Close the door!
-You stink!
-Lock it!
-Open the door, please!
-Take that.
-How does it feel, huh?
-Get me out of here! Somebody, help!
-You said ghosts don't exist!
-Now you can talk to a ghost!
-Scaredy-cat.
Take that.
Help! Please unlock the door!
Please, open the door!
Help!
-Take that!
-Does she have long hair?
Help!
Shut up!
Why are you so noisy?
-I don't want to take the blame for this.
-Let's get out of here!
Excuse me, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Excuse me.
Miss?
Can you believe it?
Vera thinks she can replace me.
I'm so pissed.
It was just a misunderstanding.
Dad, since I bumped my head,
I think now I can see...
FEEDER BUS
TRANSJAKARTA
Yes?
-Uncle Anton?
-Who are you?
I'm Baskara, Uncle Anton.
-You're Baskara, Angga's son?
-I am!
You're so big now.
Are you here alone?
Yeah, I'm...
Come inside. I want you to meet
Aunt Ami and my kids.
Come in. Don't be shy.
Come in.
Honey!
Bas, come here.
Who is this?
He's Angga's boy.
Baskara?
Oh, my God, you're Baskara.
You've grown up.
-How old are you?
-I'm ten years old.
-Ten?
-The last time we saw you...
-When was that?
-...you were just this big.
We haven't seen each other for years.
It's been years.
Dinner is ready.
Amel, Lia, let's eat.
Hi, I'm Baskara.
-I'm Amel.
-And I'm Lia.
Amel!
Sit down, Baskara.
You're going to like it here.
Thank you, Auntie.
Thanks, dear.
Your daddy and I have decided
for this year's vacation...
we're going to go to...
Labuan Bajo!
-Yay!
Aunt Ami.
Have you ever yelled at
Amel or Lia before?
Of course I have.
If they behave badly, I scold them.
They should know
what they did was unacceptable.
You always seem to be in a good mood,
and you smile a lot.
Unlike my mother.
She's constantly in a bad mood.
If your mom was in a bad mood,
she definitely had a reason.
I don't know.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Aunt Ami, you seem to love
Amel and Lia so much.
Unlike my mother.
I think she doesn't love me anymore.
All mothers love their children.
I miss having fun with my mother.
You can have fun here.
Don't worry about anything.
-Okay?
-Baskara.
Are you sleepy?
Come with me. I'll show you to your room.
Come here.
When I saw you earlier,
you reminded me of my father.
You look just like him.
I have to apologize.
After the funeral,
I didn't get a chance to visit you.
But I'm glad you're here.
This is your room.
Redecorate it the way you like.
Baskara.
I got you chocolate milk.
-Careful, it's hot.
-Baskara.
Aunt Ami's hot chocolate
is famously delicious.
Thank you, Aunt Ami.
Drink it.
Drink up.
You can stay here as long as you like.
Thank you, Aunt Ami, Uncle Anton.
Bas, one more thing.
To switch off the light, simply do this.
And if you want to turn it back on...
Good night.
-Don't...
-Leave...
-...your room...
-...at night.
Why not?
-Because...
-Daddy...
-...says...
-...so.
Baskara!
-Where...
-Are...
...you going?
-Daddy...
-Told...
-...us...
-...not to...
-...go...
-...downstairs.
Good morning, Uncle.
Good morning, Baskara.
Well, how do you like it here?
I like it, Uncle. I do.
Breakfast is ready.
Amel, Lia.
Let's eat, Baskara.
Bas, have a seat.
You're going to like it here.
Your daddy and I have decided
for this year's vacation...
we're going to go to...
Labuan Bajo!
-Yay!
Don't go there.
There's a...
It's okay. I can see her.
You can see her, too?
Yes. And I know she won't hurt me.
-I'm Baskara.
-I'm Irina.
Do you come here often?
Yeah. I come here every Saturday.
I love the view
and the weather here is so nice.
When did you realize you could see ghosts?
I've seen them ever since I can remember.
I can see them since I bumped my head.
Aren't you afraid to see them?
I was, at first.
But after a while, I got used to it.
And my grandma gave me this, too.
What's that?
This is an amulet.
She told me to throw it
at evil spirits who want to harm me.
Why do you keep singing that song?
I just like it.
My grandma taught it to me.
I guess you can see
the ghosts haunting this house.
I often see the ghost of an old lady
who haunts the yard.
Baskara...
meet my grandma.
How dare you come into my house.
-Where...
-Have...
...you been?
I took a walk in the park.
Thigh.
Breast.
He's going to choke.
Your daddy and I have decided
for this year's vacation...
we're going to go to...
Labuan Bajo.
Labuan Bajo!
-Yay!
Sit down.
Take off shoes.
Take a book.
Read.
I don't know who she is,
but she's not coming for us.
It's up to her.
But we can't keep doing this.
Uncle Anton!
Good morning, Baskara.
Uncle, every night
I'm attacked by--
They're just dreams.
Don't worry about it.
Sometimes when you're tired,
you have nightmares.
Right?
But if what you mean is noises at night...
sometimes I hear them, too.
It's okay. That's normal.
Well, how do you like it here?
Breakfast is ready!
Irina.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Never leave home without this pouch.
Irina! Irina!
Irina!
Baskara? What's wrong?
I couldn't sleep last night.
I was attacked by an evil spirit.
Attacked? They usually don't harm you.
This one is different.
The other ghosts seem to be scared of her.
I think you should go home.
My home? I'm...
Don't worry. I'll go with you.
I'm the surviving parent.
I'm the one
who takes care of you. Not him.
Do I have to be dead
for you to listen to me?
What should I do to punish you?
Grandma?
Irina.
What's wrong?
It's Baskara.
What about him?
He was attacked. He's in danger.
We should help him.
Let's eat.
Well, how do you like it here?
That kid is in danger. He left the house.
I think he finally discovered
that his uncle and his family
are all dead.
I think I know where he went.
Baskara...
Mom?
Mom.
I'm home, Mom.
Mom?
-Help!
-Shut up!
Baskara?
I'm... I'm...
Yes, I know.
Who are you?
What are you doing in my house?
I know you did some kind of ritual...
to bring Baskara back.
You have to stop!
Every time you do that,
you torture Baskara.
But I want my Baskara back.
You can't bring dead people back to life.
Mom. I'm here, Mom.
Mom?
You should bury his body
as soon as possible.
His spirit can't move on.
But I want him back.
I need to apologize to him.
Cancel your deal with the devil.
I wish I could, but how?
Just mean it when you say it.
I want to cancel my deal with the devil.
Mom!
Mom's gone.
Mom? Mom?
Leave her alone! Leave her body!
You have no claim to her body!
The longer you're in her body,
the weaker your powers become.
I've been waiting for the right time
to finally capture you.
This is the moment,
and I'm going to defeat you.
Mom? Mom?
Wake up, Mom. I love you so much.
Irina, give me the pouch.
Pour some in my hand.
Leave her body and enter your new vessel.
Irina, find me a rope!
-Do you know where you keep the rope?
-Yes.
Hurry. Start with the legs.
Ma'am, Baskara's here.
He is? Where is he?
He's right in front of you.
He's standing on my left.
Mom, I'm here.
He said he's here.
You don't have to apologize to me.
You don't have to apologize to him.
I love you.
I just came here to say goodbye.