[female voice]
We're fated to live in solitude.
Because we know something
that's impossible to explain to others.
This world has
more than what we think we know.
My mother was both
a herbal doctor and a witch doctor.
[woman screams from a distance]
Aunt Sroy is a Krasue.
My mother regarded it
as a form of sickness.
If Aunt Sroy didn't have to hunt,
to fight,
and if she didn't have sexual relations,
the transformation wouldn't take place.
It's hard to understand.
The day Father told Mother to choose...
[baby cries]
she chose to take care of me
and Aunt Sroy by herself.
-Do you feel hot?
-[baby whimpers]
Mother must have been too tired and busy
to notice that Aunt Sroy was in love
with Uncle Singha.
Sroy!
-Sroy.
-He was the guy
who brought herbs to Mother.
Aunt Sroy transformed because of him.
-Sroy.
-Because she was in love.
[sobs] Sroy.
Uncle Singha implored
that Aunt Sroy was the love of his life.
I'm sorry.
-[Singha] I love Sroy.
-But Mother wasn't convinced.
She learned that Aunt Sroy was pregnant.
It was too much for her to fight alone.
So, Mother had to teach Uncle Singha
everything.
The spells...
and the herbal medicine.
My sister could turn
into a full-fledged Krasue,
or she wouldn't.
[baby laughing]
It depends on how well
we take care of her.
[crickets chirping]
If we fail, my sister...
-[slurping]
-will turn into this.
When Mother's age-old enemies
knew that Aunt Sroy was pregnant,
-they came after her.
-Kaew.
Leave.
They claimed that
the child was one of their own.
Yes, Aunt Sroy became a Krasue
because of them.
Both Ratree
and Duangdao.
My mother sacrificed her life,
hoping to end everything once and for all.
But she failed.
She couldn't stop them.
-[man grunts]
-[rushed footsteps]
We had to run. And we kept running.
[pants]
-[grunts]
-[screams]
But it was too much for Uncle.
Aunt Sroy fought until her last breath.
Her daughter got infected
with the cursed blood.
And Uncle could never walk again.
Uncle tried to reverse the curse.
He tried the spells,
then the herbal medicine.
[blade swooshes]
He believes there must be a way
to permanently stop
my sister's transformation.
No one knows if it's possible.
I've been trained very hard
because it's my responsibility.
[crickets chirping]
No one knows if I will succeed...
until that day arrives.
[blade swooshes]
My name is Veena,
daughter of a herbal and witch doctor.
What I dream about,
what I want to do,
will mean nothing
if I can't save my sister.
That's her, Mora.
My sister.
Soon, she'll be 16.
That age is critical for us.
I have to go through this.
I must save my sister.
I don't know if I can pull it off.
But I'll give it everything I've got...
because we only have each other.
[rock music plays over headphones]
There are only a few days left
and you're still drawing.
I told you I have to submit a portfolio.
They require ten drawings this year.
I don't have much time for that either.
I haven't finished even one.
If I fail, I'll have to take a gap year.
-Whatever.
-[sighs]
Don't forget,
your sister is your priority.
3Uncle!
[woman screams]
[sighs]
What is she screaming for? So stupid.
If you feel lonely,
why don't you get a puppy
instead of keeping this damn ghost?
It's like a screamfest all day long.
So noisy.
-Don't forget to give her the potion.
-[Veena sighs]
[door creaks]
[water sloshing]
[elevator dings]
[elevator engine whirring]
[Veena sighs]
[clattering]
[soft growl]
[creature growls]
[woman screaming]
[Mora] Will Dad allow me
to stay over this Saturday?
No.
[Mora sighs]
Why not?
You're better off staying at that house.
Why bother coming over?
Because you and Dad live there.
[Mora hisses in pain]
[sighs]
Then get better quickly.
-You think I don't want to?
-[tuts]
You always make a fuss
about taking your medicine.
Now drink it so you'll be cured
and we can be together again.
[hums in distaste]
[Veena chuckles]
Dad said that?
No. I said that.
And I'll do everything to make it happen.
All you have to do is take your medicine
and do as I say.
Promise?
Promise.
I have to go.
Text me when you get home. Okay?
[Mora chuckles]
[creaks]
[sighs] Uncle. All of this? Seriously?
Yes.
What about my own things? Like homework.
Ditch your drawing and music
so you'll have more time.
[rustling]
[chair clatters]
[mortar and pestle clatter]
[sighs]
[crickets chirping]
[footsteps]
[grunting]
[slurping]
[groaning]
[groans]
[groans loudly]
-[creature growls]
-[man groans]
[thuds]
This tastes so good, you'll love it.
You have to eat
so you'll get stronger, you know.
[old lady moaning]
Take this downstairs.
[old lady gasping]
[old lady screaming]
Get out.
Shh... It's okay.
-Just hang in there.
-[groaning]
The person who made you like this...
is going to pay.
You'll be fine soon.
[groans]
You'll be like before.
I promise.
[slurping]
[groaning]
[panting]
[distant wailing]
[wailing continues]
[breathing heavily]
[crickets chirping]
[wretches]
[grunts]
[pants]
[Singha]
I'm sorry to bother you.
[male voice]
Singha.
We've known each other for a long time.
Your daughter is like my own family.
Why don't you all come
and stay at my house?
[man]
I'm hardly home anyway.
These two girls have to be separated.
It's almost time.
[male voice]
For Mora's diet,
I'll make sure there's no raw flesh.
The herbs you require
will be delivered here.
-[Singha] Thank you.
-[Mora] Veen.
[Mora sobs]
Why is Dad sending me away?
Why can't we live together?
[Mora sobs]
[sniffs]
[Veena]
I don't know.
He said there's no other way.
[thuds]
Come on.
We can call each other every day, right?
[Veena sighs]
[Mora sniffs]
Here, here.
-[boy grunts]
-[Veena grunts]
[ball thuds]
Veen, Veen.
Just a sec. Hey!
[breathing heavily]
[exhales]
[pants]
[thuds]
Came for a basketball?
No. I was just taking a walk.
Taking a walk?
In here?
[sighs]
Let's go, Mora. We're done here.
Next time, you can thank me
by giving me your number.
What did Kong say?
You know him?
Hey. I asked you.
Don't change the subject.
[hums]
Nothing.
He just asked
what movie we'll see tomorrow.
Who said we'd go see a movie?
Come on. Let's go.
[car honking]
[Mora giggles]
[Veena giggles]
[Veena laughing]
[Mora hisses in pain]
[gasps]
Are you okay?
I'll get you some water. Wait here.
[inhales sharply]
[heartbeat]
[baby giggles]
[inhales]
-[continuous heartbeat]
-[baby giggles]
[continuous heartbeat]
[door creaks, closes]
What are you doing here? Acne suction?
Hey.
Mo.
[crickets chirping]
This is so refreshing.
May I have some more?
I'll make it for you.
[Singha]
Are you always like this?
[Mora hums]
I must have been hungry.
I could hardly eat anything.
My stomach has been feeling weird.
Dad, can I stay the night?
Hold it.
Don't change the subject.
Let me check.
Open your mouth.
Tongue out.
Chin up.
Dad.
Let me stay the night, please.
Not possible.
It'll be too crowded.
Too crowded is better
than being too lonely.
Please, please.
Please, Dad.
[woman screaming from a distance]
Off you go now. It's getting late.
Veena, take your sister home.
-Let's go, Mo.
-[Mora] I want to sleep here.
Come on. Don't be a drama queen.
Come on.
Dad.
I miss you.
[Singha chuckles] Go, go.
Be patient, love.
[Mora] On my birthday,
I'll come sleep here no matter what.
You think he'll let me?
Sure.
If it's your birthday,
he'll want us to be together.
[electricity crackling]
What birthday present will you give me?
Mo.
[electricity crackling]
[gasps loudly] Mo!
-[female voice] Give me back my child!
-[Mora] Veen! Veen!
[Mora gasps]
-[Mora] Veen!
-[female voice] Give me my child!
[woman]
Give me my child!
[elevator dings]
Mo.
[Veena breathes heavily]
[Veena] Mo.
[Veena gasps]
Mo!
Can you get up?
Hurry, get up.
-[woman screaming]
-[Veena] Run, Mo! Run!
[woman]
Give me back my child.
I want my child!
[Veena]
Go away!
-[Veena] Be gone, devil!
-[woman] Give me back my child!
[Veena] Uncle, I'm staying here tonight
to keep Mo company.
Uncle, why...
Why did she attack Mo?
I've never seen her so aggressive before.
[Singha]
Pregnant ghosts are archrivals.
They become fierce
when they sense one another.
Don't worry. I've blocked it with a spell.
Never thought I could do it.
Are you sure your spell is strong enough
to keep it away?
She's still wailing like hell.
Your mother
would've silenced her completely.
But you're lacking practice,
you didn't learn all the spells.
Don't let it happen to your sister
ever again. Understand?
What did she do to you?
I don't know.
I was in a daze.
But I remember fighting her.
Right. But how?
I can't tell.
All I know is...
I'm-- I'm scared.
Never mind.
Forget it. Leave it there.
Forget it.
Veen.
-What?
-What exactly is that thing?
It's...
Why do you and Dad
have to live in that hellish building?
And why do I have to live with a stranger?
Why can't the three of us
find a place to be together?
Why do we have to be separated?
Be patient. We'll be together soon.
Let's go to bed.
[sniffles]
[sobs]
Veen.
What's wrong with me?
You're sick.
I don't know much.
You have to ask your dad.
[sobbing]
I'm scared.
[sniffles]
Don't be. It's okay.
I'm right here.
I won't let anything happen to you.
[clanking]
Hey, wait up!
Mora's not here?
She's sick.
-You two are sisters, right?
-Right.
But you don't look like each other.
I guess.
Phone number, please.
I mean, Mora's number.
063...
-0808013.
-[tapping]
Thanks.
Hey, Veena.
Can I have your...
your number.
[laughing]
Did she text back?
[phone beeps]
HI, IT'S ME, KONG.
Come on, pick up.
I don't want to do it.
Can we think it over?
I'm scared.
Call me back.
[door creaking]
I'm here for the special acne removal.
First time?
[footsteps]
Your first time?
You're scared, aren't you?
Uh...
It's just like an ant's bite.
You'll be fine.
Ready?
Yes.
[phone vibrating]
[Mook]
Hello?
[male voice]
Mook. Sorry it took me a while.
Don't do it. Come back.
[sighs in relief]
Okay.
Uh, I'm sorry. I've changed my mind.
[stirrups clanks]
I've already got twins
from a first pregnancy.
Eat them to pick up your strength.
-Yes, it's a matter of time.
-[Duangdao gibbers]
Little sis, soon you'll be
as beautiful as before.
-Now, enjoy your meal.
-[Duangdao laughs]
[slithering sound]
[chomping]
When we get a new body,
you'll be complete.
Soon, right?
Very soon, sis.
The smell is getting stronger every day.
[hissing]
Follow them.
[moaning]
-[Veena] Come here!
-[Mora] Veen, where are we going?
-[Veena] Just come with me.
-[Mora] Let me go!
-[Veena] Mo!
-[Mora] Veen!
-[Veena] I said come!
-[Mora] I said let go of me!
What are you doing? Let me go!
[splatters]
[growls]
[growling]
-What's going on, Veen?
-Hurry up!
[Mora grunts]
Let me go!
-[Mora panting]
-[splattering]
I'm tired!
-Where are we going, Veen?
-Hurry up!
[Mora] Let me go, Veen!
What's going on?
Veen!
Veen. Why are we running?
[Krasue snarls]
Just keep running.
[Mora grunts]
[panting]
[Veena grunts]
[Krasues shriek]
[tires screech]
[panting]
[gasps] Ouch. Why, Veen?
-It's my first day out!
-To Park Kred. Go!
-[Veena] Don't come around here again.
-[Mora] Why?
[Veena] Just do what I say.
-You're my dad now?
-Don't be so childish, Mo.
[Veena] Did you hear me?
-Did you hear what I said?
-I did! I'm not deaf!
I'm just sick with some damn disease.
And I'm sick of living with strangers.
Can't do anything! Can't go anywhere!
Can't eat anything!
-I'm sick of everything! Sick!
-Mo!
[scoffs]
[whooshing]
[Veena] Tomorrow, wait for me
in front of the school.
Be on time. Don't make me wait.
-[clanks]
-No.
I don't care what will happen to me!
-I won't follow your orders anymore.
-Look.
Everything I do, it's all for you.
There's nothing in it for me.
Then don't do it. No one's forcing you to.
Veen, no one tells me
what exactly is wrong with me.
But I sense it's something wicked.
I know I'm not normal.
But this is my life.
And if I can't be with anyone,
I accept that.
Easy for you to say after all these years.
Everyone has fought hard for you,
so you should too.
I understand how sick you are
with everything. I feel the same.
But don't say
we'll never be together again.
See you tomorrow after school.
Come on time.
-[paper rustles]
-[panting]
[Mora grunts]
[Mora]
Veen, where are we going?
-[Veena] Just keep running!
-[Krasue snarls]
[sighs]
I was so scared.
I didn't know what to do.
There must've been
three or four of those monsters.
"Monsters"?
Your sister is one of them.
Your aunt too.
Right. I forgot.
What am I supposed to do?
So that means...
Do they live among us?
[Singha]
Yes.
There are probably more of them
than we first thought.
They live in packs.
They reside in host bodies.
They can communicate
and locate one another.
That means they'll know
where to find Mo, right?
As the moment approaches,
Mora's smell is getting stronger.
Why don't you send me to protect her?
[Singha]
You have your own smell, Veena.
The smell of witchcraft
and protective spells.
They fight each other off.
And these days, you and Mo are at odds.
The situation is getting ripe.
Your quarrel today is a sign.
What should I do now?
What if I can't save her?
What if she completely turns
into one of them?
Mo and I, can we be together then?
[sighs]
Your mother spent her life
taking care of her sister.
[Singha]
Every night, she kept vigil
to guard her sister from wandering off
and feeding on filthy stuff.
When one's a Krasue,
the other suffers too.
If you think you can't save Mo,
you have to ask yourself...
if you can do the same thing
that your mother once did.
Don't go back there.
We still have time
because they're still waiting for Mo.
Don't let her out of your sight.
Prepare yourself. Practice all the spells.
[woman]
Take the inner organs out.
Draw what you see
and write down anatomical terms
and functions.
Put everything in your paper.
[school bell rings]
Okay, we'll resume after lunch.
[chair screeching]
[footsteps]
[sniffs]
[slurps]
[slurping]
[school bell rings]
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
[beeps]
You deserve a smack in the head.
[sighs]
[thuds]
[yelps]
I thought you weren't coming.
[thuds]
What?
I asked you to come here.
Asked me?
We just chatted on the phone.
Remember?
Can I see it?
Here.
Mo, R U FREE TPODAY?
NO, I'M NOT. 555
SERIOUSLY?
ANOTHER DAY, OKAY?
MEAN GIRL!
WHAT! 555
MISS YOU.
MISS YOU TOO.
JUST A SEC.
[tapping]
My new number.
Ask again and I'll go anywhere with you.
[elevator dings]
[elevator doors creaking]
[whispering]
[blows]
[Singha grunts]
[woman wailing]
[phone ringing]
-Peek-a-boo!
-Hey!
-Where were you?
-A secret.
You disappeared,
you didn't answer my calls.
Now drink this.
I've had to carry it around all day.
Nope, today I feel energetic
and super-refreshed.
Let's have some ice cream.
No. Drink your medicine and we'll go home.
I have something else to do.
Um, like what?
Chatting with Kong?
I hung out with him today.
He's a cute guy. I adore him.
But he got the wrong number.
So who are you trying to protect?
Me or him?
No one.
Are you sure?
Then I'm going to date him.
Whatever. It's not my business.
Are you sure, Veena?
Mo!
Okay, no ice cream for me.
Only Kong.
I mean, I'm allowed to date Kong.
See you tomorrow, my sister.
[elevator doors creak]
[woman weeping]
[weeping continue]
-[light buzzing]
-[weeping]
[wailing]
Give me back my child!
What the hell?
Let me explain.
Why did you let her out?
Why are you doing this?
If you're scared of her,
how can you fight assassin-ghosts?
[Singha]
She is harmless,
but those are real killers.
-They can hurt you.
-Killer or not, a ghost is a ghost.
You don't have a choice.
[Veena sighs]
Neither have I
nor Mora.
Time is running out.
If you keep drawing
and listening to music,
how can you save your her?
[Singha]
Listen to me. Lay off everything.
And focus on your mission. Understand?
If I was the sick one,
would you ask Mora to do the same?
Would you have her train so hard
and forget her own life?
Would you ask her to abandon her dreams?
Would you beg her
to give up everything for me?
Will you ever love me, your niece,
as much as your own child?
Veen!
-[papers rustling]
-[drawer closes]
[papers rustling]
KONG
BLOCK
[cell phone clicks]
[clock ticking]
[footsteps]
[Veena sniffs]
[Veena pants]
Here. Drink it. For your headache.
[Veena sighs]
I'd carried you in my arms...
before I even had Mora.
[whimpers]
I'd called you daughter...
before I had my own daughter.
Honestly, it pains me
to see you living a hard life.
[sniffs]
But it's our fate...
and we can't change that.
[gasps, sniffs]
I got it.
I'm just tired.
I just want some time for myself.
[Veena sobs]
And I'm scared.
[Veena gasps] Scared that
I might not be able to help Mo.
[Veena cries]
I have a plan.
It could work.
[sniffs, cries]
[Singha]
Go to bed.
-All right?
-[Veena cries]
[Veena crying]
Go to bed, my girl.
[Veena cries, sniffs]
[clicks phone]
[phone dialing]
[Van]
They've gone to the mall.
Who?
Kong and Mora.
Probably wore each other out.
Who?
You and your sister.
No one wants a burden,
and no one wants to be a burden.
Agree?
Well...
it's too late.
Wait. Where did you say they're going?
The mall opposite the school.
Really?
[rushed footsteps]
[phone vibrates]
-[Mora gulps]
-[phone vibrates]
-[slithering sound]
[phone vibrates]
-[phone vibrates]
-[ghost chomps]
[ghost chomping, thudding]
-[ghost chomping]
-[gasps]
-[ghost continues to chomp]
-[phone vibrates]
[flustered breathing]
[Mora pants]
[rushed footsteps]
[gasps]
[Mora pants]
-[Mora pants]
-[Kong knocks on door]
[Kong]
Mora.
Are you okay?
Mora?
[Woman]
The first time always hurts.
[Mora grunts]
-[Krasue screeches]
-[Mora gasps]
[muffled scream]
[yelps, thuds]
[grunts]
Wait, please let us in.
[Veena pants]
[pen squeaks]
[Krasues hiss]
What the hell?
[Krasue hisses]
[man pants]
[Krasues scream]
[Veena screams]
[glass shatters]
[Krasues snarl]
[man whimpers]
[sloshing]
[sloshing, banging]
[pants]
[panting]
[banging continues]
[door rattles]
[door clang]
[pants]
[Singha pants]
[sloshing]
[sloshing, banging]
Exactly as I thought...
you want to destroy us.
[bones crackling]
In fact, I want to cure you.
[unsheathing knife]
What we are is incurable, Singha.
[Ratree]
We're either dead or alive.
But, no, we don't want to die.
[Ratree]
And we're not suffering.
Except some of us
can't accept what we are...
like your wife.
My sister and I have been waiting
for a long time.
Waiting for your daughter...
to be ready.
[grunts]
[Singha grunts]
-[Singha grunts]
-[knife clinks]
[Ratree]
You...
have ruined my sister.
[Ratree]
Now...
you're going to pay...
with your daughter's body.
[shrieking]
[continues to shriek]
[glass crashes]
-[container thuds]
-[shrieks]
[Ratree growls]
[laughing]
Pack your things! They've taken Mora!
[cries]
[sniffs, cries]
[drawer opens]
[knife scrapes]
[sighs]
You forgot your tumbler.
[Van]
Easy.
You'll figure something out.
-[Pregnant Ghost wails]
-Hey! What's that?
[Pregnant Ghost wails]
You.
Can you do me a favor?
Sure.
[lift dings]
Keep the doors open.
[Veena] You must not
let them close. Never.
If you hear anything, ignore it.
Don't poke your head out to look.
If I say it's all right, it's all right.
If you don't hear from me, just go home.
Leave right away. Got it?
Don't try to look for me.
You'll be fucking dead.
[Veena]
Never, ever let the lift close.
Okay.
[clicks]
Just press the button.
Just press the button...
[panting]
[Van continues to pant]
-[Pregnant Ghost wails]
-Shit!
[light flickers]
[wailing intensifies]
[Pregnant Ghost continues to wail]
Damn it!
[panting]
Is everything all right?
[lift doors close]
[Van]
Two heads are better than one.
Trust me.
Fewer heads are better in this case.
But it's late and it's dangerous.
[sighs]
[Van types]
[Duangdao] She looks very much
like her mother.
[Ratree]
Strange, you remember her face.
[Duangdao scoffs]
[Duangdao] I remember everyone
who hurt me.
Too bad I didn't get to see
that prick Singha suffer.
[Ratree] But you can inflict pain
on his daughter.
And also his niece.
Don't use up your strength.
[Ratree] You'll need it
to migrate into a new body.
Do you think it'll work?
Of course.
It has to work.
[Ratree] Go get ready.
[bones cracking]
[footsteps approaching]
[squishing]
[Ratree] Soon we'll walk together
during the day.
And hunt together again
at night, Duangdao.
[Krasues groaning]
[Krasues screaming in pain]
Mo!
Mo.
Wake up.
[frizzling]
[frizzles]
-[bell rings]
-[neck frizzles]
[Krasues wail]
[frizzling]
Mo.
Let's go.
[Krasues wail]
[Krasues hiss]
[chanting]
Go get them.
[wailing]
[snarling]
[hissing]
-[Veena grunts]
-[Krasues scream]
[Krasue shrieks]
[Pregnant Ghost snarling]
[Pregnant Ghost screeches]
[Krasues snarling]
-[Veena grunts]
-[Pregnant Ghost screeches]
[screams, thuds]
-[Veena pants]
-[Krasues screaming]
-[Veena groans]
-[blade clinks]
[Veena grunting]
[Duangdao laughs]
Let go of me.
[bones cracking]
-[Veena grunting]
-[Mora groaning]
[bones cracking]
Veen.
Mo.
[Mora grunting, bones cracking]
Mo!
-[Veena] Mo!
-Veen.
Let go of me.
Veen.
Mo!
Don't!
[bones crackling]
[growling]
Let go of me.
Mo!
[thumps]
[Veena] Mo.
[Veena grunts]
[bones cracking]
[snarling]
[squishing]
[grunting and hissing]
-[Veena cries]
-[bones cracking]
[Veena grunts]
[squelching]
-[Veena grunts]
-[thuds]
[hissing]
[Duangdao laughs]
[Duangdao laughs in distance]
[Mora panting]
[squelching]
[snarling]
-[snarling]
-[thumps]
[Mora groans]
[whooshing]
[Mora grunts]
[Ratree howls]
[Mora groans in pain]
[Mora panting]
[Ratree screams]
[thudding]
[Duangdao laughs]
-[Veena sighs]
-[Duangdao laughing]
[Singha] Stay strong.
You'll be as good as your mother.
And you'll become Mo's guardian.
[Singha] Stay strong.
[Veena] I promise we'll be together again.
[Mora] Veen, I'm scared.
[Veena sobs]
-[Ratree laughs]
-[Veena] Don't be. It's okay.
I'm right here.
I won't let anything happen to you.
-[Veena breathing heavily]
-[Duangdao laughing]
[Mora] Promise me, my sister.
[Duangdao laughs]
[Veena grunts]
[gasps]
[Duangdao screams in a distance]
-[Dungdao shrieking]
-[Veena grunting]
[Ratree screams in pain]
Mo.
[groaning]
[snarling]
[Krasues snarling]
[Veena grunting]
[chomping sound]
[hissing]
[sobs] Mo.
Mo...
[Veena] To part with someone
without a chance to say goodbye
is the most painful farewell.
[whirring]
[Veena] I know my sister is out there,
but she doesn't want to see me.
-No one wants to be a burden.
-[knife whooshing]
I always wanted my life back.
I always wanted to be free.
I thought
I would be happy
if I could follow my dream.
Now I know that happiness is
to see someone you love happy.
-To smile together. To cry together.
-[knife whoosh]
I'm drawing. I'll call you back.
[Veena] Even when the world is crumbling,
-it's still happiness.
-[knife whooshing]
That's Mora, my sister.
The person I love the most.
Mo!
[Veena] There are only two of us...
in this whole world.
Mo! Mo!
Mora!
Mo!
Subtitle translation by: