What are you waiting for?
What kind of camera could kill people?
Do it!
Press the button!
Come on!
Press it!
Hello, professor.
Hello.
Let me ask you, Dan,
why did you choose me to be your advisor?
I want to graduate with honors.
And you think this work…
will get you an honor?
It'd be embarrassing
just to let you graduate.
I don't work in a fashion magazine.
I select artists.
Anybody could take pictures like these.
Are you free on Sunday?
Yes.
Think of a new topic for your thesis,
and we can discuss it… at my place.
All right.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
How did it go, Dan?
Now you're stuck with Professor Aim.
With Professor Win,
you'd have graduated with us.
Well, he wants to be top of the class,
so he has to learn
from the best professor.
Right?
-Fifty-five seconds.
-Dan beat you, 40 seconds. Give it to me.
But it's okay. It's quick enough.
Enough to be the top-of-class
photographer's girlfriend.
Hey.
Are we together? Are we?
What? You guys are not together?
You hang out all the time.
I thought you were.
Or maybe he doesn't let you pass
because they're photos of me?
No. You're pretty.
Oh, my.
A guy thinks I'm pretty.
Does he have a crush on me?
A customer.
Okay, I'll do it this evening.
Come on. One more.
-Let me see.
-Look at this.
What the hell?
Sushi!
-Is this your nephew's toy?
-What are you talking about?
Come on. Let me show you.
You're into photography for real? Look.
Hey.
Why is it only the two of us?
-Should I be in there?
-Yes.
-All of us.
-I'll take it.
Go on.
One, two, three.
-On the other side.
-That side too?
Yeah. Come on.
Ready? One, two, three!
We're going to go to New York together.
You know I haven't graduated yet.
You haven't told him?
Well, Great and I got accepted.
We need to be there next month.
If I pass my project…
I'll get a scholarship to go too.
Hey.
Really?
We'll all go together.
For real?
You're serious?
I'll book you a ticket.
Damn, what's the rush?
Damn, dude!
What?
-Come on!
-New York!
One, two, three!
Hello, Mom.
Your uncle's birthday is next Saturday.
Are you coming?
Well, you can give my best wishes to him.
You can't just not come.
We don't know how long he'll be with us.
Okay.
Besides, he paid for your tuition.
Your friends are all graduated.
Are you graduating this year?
Are you Dan?
Yes.
Hello.
-Come with me.
-Yes.
Professor Aim talks about you a lot.
He said you have potential.
-You must be good.
-Thank you.
Normally, he doesn't let students
come to his house.
So you must be working hard.
Like it?
Yes.
-Hello.
Who painted this?
I did.
For the next month's faculty exhibition.
It was my graduation project
displayed at Tillman Gallery.
Tillman Gallery?
In…
New York.
You get excited when I mention New York.
All right. What's your topic?
Oh, okay.
My topic is "proof."
I want to tell stories of the underdogs
who want to prove something to the world.
Like myself.
I'm going to use this camera.
What's so special about it?
My mom bought it for me
when I was in Grade 8.
Nowadays,
I don't know why we still take photos
if it isn't for capturing moments
or good memories.
When I was studying in New York,
I focused on taking photos everyday.
But at the end,
all of them are just ordinary.
Until one day, I got this camera.
I used this for my final project.
Once our work is sought after,
we can do whatever we want.
Try it.
Use it to take photos of seven people…
in the next 14 days.
Dan,
if you pass this project,
I promise I'll nominate you
for the New York scholarship.
I have to go.
Dan.
Don't give up.
Those who got approved by Professor Aim
are highly accomplished.
Of course.
-Thanks.
-You can do it.
Good. Good time. Great job.
Dan, he's an amazing photographer.
All the photos
in the Humans In the City page are his.
-Who has the most potential for a gold?
-Bomb.
He's a talented athlete,
and is the most experienced
in this competition.
We're hoping
for another gold medal from him.
How's it going, Dan? Are you done?
-Yes, one more shot.
-Hurry, so we can interview him.
-Okay, got it.
-All right. You can move now.
Sorry for bothering you guys. Thank you.
How's it going?
Everything seems fine.
I'll develop and send them to you.
Okay, can't wait to see them.
If they're bad, that's on you.
What is this?
Professor Aim gave it to me.
Nam.
Well…
Do you like my work?
I do like your work.
But I like you more.
-You like that I take nice photos?
-I like your looks.
I'll go develop the film.
-See you.
-Good luck.
Bye, Great.
See you later.
-And send me the photos.
-Yeah!
Roj, hello.
Elite Shungite, the stone of life…
from Russia.
What can it do?
The previous owner told me
that this stone can capture souls.
-That's why it's black.
-Really?
Westerners use it to ward off demons.
This…
is good for young ladies.
White Rose Quartz,
the stone of forgiveness.
Yeah?
If someone's mad at you,
give them the rock,
and they won't be anymore.
-Is that true?
-Why would I lie to you?
How much?
-Are you sure?
-Yeah. How much?
What's this?
For you.
Are you hitting on me?
Am I allowed?
Great,
there's nothing between us.
Nam…
I just want to apologize for what I did.
Is that okay?
Okay, to be honest,
I still love you.
I just want to know
if we can ever get back together.
Great, are you in a music video?
-Nam, I'm being serious. I said I'm sorry.
-Great.
Imagine if I messed around
with another man, told you I was drunk,
and gave you a bracelet saying I'm sorry.
Come on, Great.
Can you imagine?
Do you like Dan now?
Great, you can't be mad at me.
Just keep it. It's expensive.
Fine, I'll keep it.
Hey, Bomb.
Yes, coach.
You were a bit behind today.
Just work harder tomorrow.
I'm sorry, coach.
Hey, it's okay. Don't worry.
Get some rest.
We'll try again tomorrow.
Go on.
Zoom in? Closer.
Try to capture
your subject's moment, okay?
-Hello.
Here.
Good.
You're on the right track.
It's like you're portraying his soul.
More.
Bring me more.
And this is Taew Pad Thai,
which has been here for over 50 years.
It is said to be number one in this area.
One with shrimp!
And the most famous restaurant.
Where would we go?
We've been here for three generations.
And this is our home,
our identity.
Taew Pad Thai Cinema.
Great food that we'd like you
to try yourself.
Okay, turn at a 45-degree angle
and look at the camera.
Give me a little smile.
Ready.
One, two…
Please look this way,
follow my finger. Okay.
Okay. One, two…
Dan.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Dan.
I remember that Jan used this camera.
Jan, the one who…
died from a heart attack?
Yeah.
How did it end up with Professor Aim?
Hello, Great.
What?
Dan.
Bomb, the guy we interviewed,
committed suicide.
RISING WHEELCHAIR RACER
BOMB BANCHA HANGED HIMSELF
Don't you think
Bomb's suicide seems suspicious?
How?
Well, how should I say this?
He's disabled, right?
So imagine, how could he reach the beam?
How?
I JUST WANT THIS TO BE OVER.
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN OBSESSED
WITH THE THESIS,
WE'D STILL BE TOGETHER.
RIN - OCTOBER 6TH.
Rin.
It's Nam.
Are you free tomorrow?
I have some questions about Jan.
Dan.
What are you studying?
What is his major?
Photography.
Photography? Just like you, Taew.
Started learning piano and then quit.
You understand, right?
It's difficult.
You have to practice and be dedicated.
But you didn't give it all, Taew.
That's why you failed.
You and your mother hold our family back.
To be the best, you have to give it all.
You need to practice.
Okay, blow the candle.
Let's take some photos.
Come on, Dan. Stand next to me.
Don't.
Dan, take photos of me.
Let's see how good you are.
Go on.
Let's get…
Let me see if you look good, Dad.
Mom's not here.
Let me go get her.
What your uncle said is true.
If you want to succeed,
you have to dedicate
all of your time to it.
But you also need time
for other aspects of life.
Let me go see your uncle.
Excuse me, I'm here to pick up
Bomb's belongings.
I'm sorry about what happened.
Athletes with high expectations
are always under pressure.
But I never thought
Bomb would kill himself.
Did he seem depressed or anything?
Not that I know of.
Bomb was very ambitious.
So much that his teammates
didn't like him.
I don't think
he would've made a decision like that.
Professor,
I wonder…
if there's something about this camera?
I mean,
when I take photos with it, I see…
What do you see?
Are you stressed about the thesis?
The people I took photos of,
one of them died.
And you know him?
No.
So what?
We all die someday, Dan.
The question is,
how are we living while we're still alive?
How do you want to live?
I want to give it all.
Take these photos for me,
and I will…
make the world accept you.
Where are you going?
-What do you want?
-Nothing.
I haven't seen you for days,
so I stopped by.
Wait.
-We have a photoshoot today.
-I know.
I'm not coming. Will you cover for me?
-Yeah.
-Dan.
Are you going to use that camera again?
Why?
Well, it belongs to a dead person,
and you still dare to use it?
We all die someday.
It has nothing to do with it.
Why are you being like this?
You never treat me like this.
I'm here because I care about you.
Here is Jan's notebook.
Take a look and see what you can find.
And, did Jan have symptoms like…
feeling unwell or acting weird?
She seemed sluggish…
and in poor health.
I told her to go see a doctor,
but she wouldn't.
She was obsessed with her thesis.
Jan actually had a lot of energy,
and was very confident.
But while working on her thesis,
she looked totally consumed by it.
She wasn't the Jan I knew.
Ever since she got that camera.
Thank you.
Don't you feel that nowadays,
we only use photo apps
to take photos, edit…
That is Porch.
…share, and follow others?
He graduated overseas.
What's up?
He's the founder of this startup.
Hard working. He's our funding source.
All right. Come on.
Wouldn't it be better if we had
a more versatile application?
Pic Me allows you to edit photos
as if they were taken with film…
-She's Minnie.
-…without photo studios.
You can tell that she's important.
Her friends are all celebrities.
And when it comes to work, she's the best.
Can you reset the lighting?
Our Rendez-Vous system allows everyone
to create appointments for photoshoots.
That guy is Ten.
He's the brains of the team.
Whatever you want, he can make it happen.
With this, anybody can be
a professional photographer.
Rich people can do whatever they want.
When you already have everything
in your hands,
you don't have to fight for anything.
So what's the point of living?
-Can I see another one?
-Sure.
-If that's all, I'm going to take off.
-Of course.
-Thank you.
-Thanks so much. Bye.
-You'll see the final version soon.
-Yes.
Be right back.
Is Dan off work?
Yeah. He left right after he was done.
He was acting weird today.
Which camera did he use?
Our camera.
No, I mean which one of them?
-Nutt.
-Yes?
-Which camera did Dan use?
-Digital one.
He took the memory card
to get the photos tonight.
Let's go.
Whose notebook is it?
Jan's.
The dead Jan?
Yeah.
Is it possible that a camera
could kill someone?
Could be a coincidence.
Or Dan is a jinx.
Anyone he takes photos of dies.
That's why you took Jan's notebook?
Come on.
-Nont.
-Yes?
-Did Dan send the photos?
-Not yet.
What? He's never late.
How are the photos?
No. No rush. Just wondering.
Okay. You're developing them?
Okay.
Wait, develop them? Dan…
Developing what?
He said Porch asked him to use
the film camera,
and he just developed them.
But the three of them were just…
How could a camera make people die?
If we modify the codes,
it'll be easier for users.
I'm tired. Let's take a break.
Ten minutes?
Let's make it 15,
just in case Porch goes for a smoke.
What's with the shitty traffic?
What the hell?
Dan, we need to talk about that camera.
What about it?
Porch, Ten, Minnie,
they all jumped off the building and died.
Both owners of the Pad Thai restaurant
died too.
I think your camera is cursed.
Are you're saying it kills people?
I don't know, but…
There's something about it.
Dan,
Jan used this camera and she died.
The three people
she took photos of died too.
Yes, Mom.
What's wrong with him?
Hey, what are you going to do
with my camera?
I'm going to go ask
your professor about it.
Nam!
Do you know
about the death of Jan and Milin?
How did you get this camera?
I let Jan use it.
It's mine.
Did you know?
Dan used this camera on six people,
and all of them died.
Are you saying that it can kill people?
Seriously?
A camera that kills.
A camera that kills anyone
it takes a photo of.
How about this? You…
take a picture of me.
Come on. Give it a shot.
And see…
if I die.
Wait.
Why aren't you taking it?
The film ran out? One second.
Nam?
What's wrong?
Are you all right?
Nam.
Dan.
Nam!
-What happened, Nam?
-That painting on…
Dan!
Didn't you see it?
No.
No?
That was…
No, you must've seen something.
-We have to throw it away.
-Give it back.
Dan!
-Throw it away!
-That's enough, Nam!
-Dan?
-Dan!
Dan. Come in, your uncle's waiting.
He's in a coma.
He might not make it through the night.
Hurry up.
He asked about you, Dan.
Say goodbye to him, okay?
Uncle.
It's me, Dan.
Thank you for everything
you've done for me.
Dan.
You only have only five days
to submit your work.
Just one more.
-Uncle?
-Go find a doctor.
Nurse!
-Doctor!
-Go find a doctor. Uncle!
Come on, find a doctor!
NAM
Dan.
Dan, are you okay?
How did you know I was here?
What happened, Dan? Are you okay?
I've found something.
I think…
it might belong to you.
Just one more!
CAKE: DAN, DO YOU DO MODEL PHOTOGRAPHY?
HOW MUCH DO YOU CHARGE?
SLR: YES, I'LL DO IT FOR FREE.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
Hey, Dan. Am I here too early?
No, you're fine.
What should I do?
How do you want me to pose?
However you like.
Leave us now.
-Excuse me?
-Leave.
I'm not saying it again.
Looking for a model?
Take a photo of me then.
What are you afraid of?
Go on.
Well, there's nothing wrong
with this camera.
What kind of camera could kill people?
Press the button.
Press it, Dan.
Press it.
Dan!
Come on, do it!
Press it!
Fuck!
Nam, I didn't mean to kill them.
I didn't mean it.
Nam…
Everything will be okay.
You'll always have us.
We're in this together.
HOLE IN THE DARKNESS
This…
was the last website Jan visited.
Is this… the painting we saw
at Professor Aim's house?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Do you see him?
Yes.
I took a picture of him.
Dan!
-Hey.
-Wait.
These two didn't die.
The eyes.
These are the only two
where you can't see their eyes.
But we can see the eyes
of the people who died.
I think we need to find help.
Demons…
always manifest in unexpected forms.
Haven't you heard
that some people believe
cameras capture souls in them?
That cameras are used to kill people,
to sacrifice souls to demons.
Does this panting
have anything to do with this?
Professor Aim is displaying this painting
at the exhibition.
Do you believe in satanic cults?
During that time,
whoever owned this painting…
was the most powerful.
It says here
seven souls must be sacrificed.
If you come up short,
you have to sacrifice your own soul.
That means Dan has to die?
Is there anything we can do?
Tomorrow's the day
that the gate in hell opens.
Demons will come for their sacrifices.
Here, this can protect you from demons.
Wear it and don't take it off.
Great, do you still have
the stone I gave you?
Hold onto it. It can protect you.
This is all I can help you with.
Do whatever you have to, fast.
What if he's really a demon?
How are we going to fight him?
The inspiration that I have…
We'll give him
a taste of his own medicine.
Can you tell us where you got
the inspiration for this show?
My mother.
My mother came from a small family,
oppressed by her extended family,
but my mother refused
to lose her identity as an artist.
She did what she was good…
I can't take the shot.
Let me clear the path.
This is my father.
Dan!
Why don't you join us inside?
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Look at Great.
It's very ambitious,
and I can tell it's not difficult
to capture his soul.
There are more photos
inside the exhibition.
Please look around.
I hope you enjoy.
Shit! His eyes were closed.
What's that?
It's not very clear, is it?
Help!
Great! Great!
I saw a big creature right on my face!
What is it?
Great.
Calm down.
-Calm down.
-You've seen it before, right?
Shit.
Dan, you have less than an hour left.
But Great is still alive.
What does it mean?
His eyes are clearly visible in the photo,
but he's not dead.
Does it mean there are other factors?
I think Roj's amulet is the real deal.
Six people have already died.
Now, Great is going to be the seventh.
I won't let that happen.
Dan, what are you doing?
You can't.
I started this, Nam.
I'll be the one to end it.
Why are you doing this?
Don't you want to go to New York?
I'm submitting my project.
It's just one more person.
Let it be me.
Do you know…
what's going to happen if you do this?
Everything you sacrificed for your dream…
Don't be stupid, Dan.
Just one more step.
One more step.
Yes.
Just one more step.
What are you waiting for?
For you to get in the frame.
Dan.
I'm so disappointed in you.
What can you do?
Can you develop it in time?
Catch me if you can.
Hey, let's develop it.
Shit.
-Shit!
-Dan!
-Damn it.
Let go of me! Let go!
Nam, watch out!
Dan, come on, get up.
Nam, run!
Get her out of here, Great.
-Shit!
-Can't open it?
God damn it!
Is it gone?
I don't know.
Bitch!
Great!
Nam, run! Quick!
Great, it's me!
It's me.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry!
Two minutes past midnight.
Your time's up, Dan.
But…I can help you.
Just give me the film.
Dan.
What you're trying to do
can't change the fact
that you've killed six people.
Just one more…
to get what you want.
That's right.
Just one more…
and it will be me.
So heroic.
So goddamn heroic.
To sacrifice your own life?
Dan, you are so brave.
But do you think if you do this,
it will be over?
You forgot about the people
who do everything to support you.
Dan.
I know you're different from me.
Don't let go of your dream.
Dan.
We made a promise
to go to New York together.
Dan.
Please do this for me…
so we can be together.
You understand it now, Dan.
You still don't get it, do you?
Dan, you always surprise me,
but your time is over.
Fuck!
Shit!
-Dan!
-Dan, wake up! Dan!
Dan, wake up!
-Dan!
-Wake up, Dan!
Dan!
Shit, Dan! No, don't do this.
Dan…
We got his photo, Dan.
Dan!
Sometimes, our dreams can be a burden.
We just want to do what we love…
because sometimes, life throws us
the unexpected and makes us distracted.
Take good care of yourself in New York.
I'll be fine.
We weren't born equal.
I'm glad I have you guys.
We have to do the best
with what we're given.
Damn it!
I don't want this to happen…
Dan…
What's the meaning of its brand?
And we won't regret it,
because…
we gave it all for…
our lives.
Want me to look at the camera?