[phone ringing]
A NETFLIX SERIES
[phone continues ringing]
[pop music plays on speakers]
Bar Bero?
[ethereal music plays]
Hello?
[pop music resumes]
[knife banging]
-[Bruno] Let it go.
-Please, just let me open it.
BRINGING UP BABY
[bells chiming]
-[Álex] Where are you going?
-To find Ramón.
[bells continue chiming]
[bells chiming rapidly]
Happy New Year to everyone!
[Álex exclaims]
[groaning]
[ethereal music plays]
[groans softly]
[ethereal music intensifies]
-[door creaks, clacks]
-[bells jingle]
[gasps]
[tense music plays]
[cell phone chimes]
[Yessenia] Well, my love,
guess who I saw yesterday? Marco Antonio!
-[Vero and Patri chuckle]
-He immediately asked me about you.
And, of course, I told him about
your new status as a lesbian, and all.
-[chuckles quietly]
-And you know what he told me?
That you'd get over it.
[Yessenia laughs]
Your dad and I
are still laughing about it.
Mom, look. You don't have to tell
the whole town about it, okay? [chuckles]
Honey, if someone asks me about
my little girl, I tell them the truth.
And with my head held high, all right?
-Where's Vero? Isn't she there?
Vero.
Hey, Yessenia!
Happy New Year, my love.
-[blows kisses]
-Thanks. You too.
-Hi, honey. How are you?
-Very good.
I'm doing good.
Everything's great, thanks.
That's wonderful.
And, plus, today we're getting
the keys to the new apartment.
That's a great way
to begin a new year together, isn't it?
Congratulations, my girls.
-Thanks, Mom.
Thanks.
-[man] Yessenia!
-[shouts] I'm coming, okay?
Your dad's a real pain in the ass.
More than a toothache.
[both chuckle]
Kisses, honey.
-Talk to you soon.
-Bye, Mom. Kisses
-[Vero] Ciao.
-[chuckles]
-[laptop chimes]
-[Vero chuckles]
-When are you meeting the architect?
-Uh, later at four.
Mmm. I don't think I'll make it.
Mmm. Doesn't matter.
I'm just checking that everything's
in order so I can get the keys back.
You don't mind if I miss it?
The apartment will be there.
[melancholy music plays]
We'll have to start
organizing the move, then.
Yeah. I can look for movers
a little later on today.
'Kay, thanks.
-Hmm.
-[cell phone chimes]
IBRA:
GOOD MORNING, CAN I ASK YOU A FAVOR?
[lively music plays]
[keys clicking]
Yep.
YEAH, SURE
IT'S ABOUT ÁLEX…
[Diego] Good morning, Rosa.
How are you, Diego? What can I get you?
Nothing, I just came to bring you this.
Ramiro asked me to give it to you.
Do you know what it is?
He just told me
that he is leaving Barcelona tomorrow.
Okay, thanks.
Cut it out.
[tense music plays]
-[Albert] What?
-[Sunyer] That's not what matters.
-[Albert] What do you want me to do, huh?
-That's enough! Now, look.
Calm down, okay?
If you need something else,
send me an e-mail.
I already have.
I've said I was sorry by e-mail,
by WhatsApp, even in a text.
-What else can I do, Ramón?
-You could leave me alone.
I can't just leave you alone.
We work together.
And even if we didn't… Listen, Ramón…
[shouts] Will you listen?
[Albert muffled] Do you hear me? I'm sick…
Look. I understand
that what I did was awful, okay?
That I…
I shouldn't ever have been with you
without knowing exactly how I felt.
-I was an idiot.
-And selfish.
Yes. And I am very sorry.
-But…
-[Albert muffled] You don't understand.
[sighs] I don't know. We could…
-[Sunyer] This is unbelievable! Enough!
-[Bruno] We could… try to fix this.
-We're done discussing this.
-How exactly?
-[Sunyer] You're not leaving.
-I really like you, Ramón.
[Albert] You won't understand, but…
I'd like to think
we could maybe still be friends.
[scoffs] You really think
we can be friends now?
-Well, at first it'd be a little--
-Look, Bruno.
Friendship is not a comfort prize,
especially not if you're offering it
so you can feel better.
-[Bruno] But…
-I thought you were different.
-[Albert] Painting is booming!
-[Ramón] I really did.
And that's what I liked about you.
-But you were a cliché in the end.
-A cliché? Are you serious?
You spend all day whining
'cause no one loves you
and when someone is willing to
you treat him like shit
because, turns out
you have a crush on a hot guy.
[Albert] All right.
Maybe that was a little out of line.
[Ramón] So just forget about it.
You're not forgiven,
and we can't be friends.
[Albert] I've already talked with Núria.
I'm done, for good!
[Albert huffs]
[Sunyer] Everyone,
if I could have your attention.
As you know, my son-in-law, Albert,
has decided to leave the studio.
And that means the management position
needs to be filled.
And, uh, after careful consideration…
I have decided that, uh…
that the best person to fill this role
is our best architect.
-And that is Ramón Martínez.
-[gasps]
-[Sunyer] A round of applause, please.
-[workers applauding]
[cheering]
[elevator bell rings, door opens]
[ethereal music plays]
[woman] That's what I told Sunyer.
[Sunyer] That's what I'm saying to you.
It's about relationships…
[wistful music plays]
[cell phone buzzes]
-[gasps]
-[cell phone continues buzzing]
[sighs]
Hey. What is it?
[Álex] "If you don't want to listen to me,
at least listen to Juan."
When we were both younger,
your father used to make cassette tapes
with the music that he and I loved.
He would always make a commentary
between songs like he was some sort of DJ.
And is this one of those cassettes?
Well, I didn't dare listen to it yet.
-Álex…
-[breathes unsteadily]
[sniffles]
[Spanish rock song plays]
[sighs]
Good evening, this is Juan,
DJ-ing for his dear friend Ramiro.
And you're listening to "En el límite"
by La Frontera.
-[sobbing]
-[song continues]
[Rosa chuckles]
[Juan] You always said
that this was our song
because we both lived on the edge
between friendship and love.
[song continues]
[Juan] That edge separated us,
but I want to do away with it.
I love you, Ramiro. Don't ever doubt it.
But not like I love Rosa.
[Juan] She is my whole world.
From the moment I saw her,
-I knew I'd be by her side all my life.
-[crying]
[Juan] And I'm convinced that one day
you will find a love
as big as the one I feel for her.
[song continues]
Because nothing would make me happier
than you being in my life.
And in Rosa's and in our son Álex's.
[song continues]
[both chuckle]
[Lis] Whoo-whoo!
[song ends]
VERO AND PATRICIA
SEVEN YEARS GROWING TOGETHER
[Bruno] Everything all right?
Patricia?
-Everything look okay?
-Yes.
Yeah. You did a really nice job.
I'm glad you like it.
I just need your signature,
and I'll get outta here.
Yeah. Of course, of course.
-All right, just here and here.
-Sure.
I'm sorry the budget went up so much.
-No, that was us. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
But everything came out amazing.
Hey, wait. I think that… that I saw you
at Bar Bero on New Year's Eve, was it?
Uh, well, I was just there for a minute.
You were there that night?
Yeah. [chuckles] Yeah, uh,
my girlfriend's an owner there.
-Vero?
-Yeah. Do you know her?
Uh, no, we just talked for a second,
but you…
I just had no idea.
I mean, you've always handled
the renovation on your own. [chuckles]
Sure. Yeah.
Have you been together for a long time?
-Um, seven years, like the lemon tree.
-Oh…
[both chuckle]
Yeah. On our first date, I planted
a lemon seed in my gin and tonic.
[both chuckle]
I never thought
it would germinate, but, well,
they say that love takes root
in unexpected places.
Uh, you know what…
[chuckles]
You know what I love most
about being an architect?
What?
This.
-Renovating apartments like this.
-Mm.
We get all these big projects
at the studio.
Theaters, hotels… pavilions, but…
nothing is as exciting as…
building a home. [chuckles]
Well…
Thanks again.
-Great meeting you.
-You as well.
[melancholy music plays]
[sighs]
I don't know what I was thinking
when I took it, to be honest.
In all these years,
I've never had a photo of your father.
I hope you don't mind
sleeping with these sheets.
I only have these
from when Álex was little.
Anything is fine.
I've spent years sleeping on a ship.
Well, that's the point.
You need something comfortable.
Well, maybe we can buy some new sheets
and even a new bed later, if need be.
But, nowadays, they just sell cheap ones
that you have to assemble on your own.
Rosa, it'll just be a few days
till I find my own place.
You don't have to set up a new room.
And I'm getting you a blanket.
I turn off the heat at night.
-I don't want you catching a cold either.
-[Álex chuckles]
You know what you've signed up for?
-I don't really think I do. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
But I promise you now… that I'm done.
No more lies.
It must have been really hard
living like that.
Did you ever go out with anyone?
I spent half my life in love with a ghost.
And, before I knew it,
I'd spent 40 years without ever
really loving anyone at all.
What's the point of living like that?
[Ramiro] Hmm?
[Javi] Hey. How is the new apartment?
You haven't told me anything.
Good, good.
Patri says that it's all in order.
Didn't she send you a photo
or video or anything?
No, but, uh, I'll…
I'll be there in the morning.
Ah, really, such a lack of enthusiasm.
It's not like you buy
a new apartment every week.
-Wanna come over and see it tomorrow?
-Oh yes!
Yes, yes. And we can organize
a little housewarming.
What? No. There's no parties.
I don't want you
destroying my new apartment, all right?
Well, we'll destroy the old one
and do it before you move, then.
We have to celebrate this.
-Long live dyke couples!
-[door opens, bells jingle]
You have a customer.
[chuckles]
-Ramiro.
-Hello, Javier.
[Javi] Hmm.
I thought you were leaving Barcelona.
Me too, but, well, I didn't.
I wanted to come and tell you that
I settled everything with Rosa and Àlex.
Ah…
Well, that's good.
May I have a tequila?
-A tequila? [chuckles]
-Mm-hmm.
-You don't think it's too early?
-Maybe for drinking, yes.
But for… well, for the rest,
I'm actually terribly late.
I don't want to waste any more time.
[wistful music plays]
Neither do I.
[sighs]
[dance music plays]
[people chatter and cheer]
[ethereal music plays]
[keys clatter]
[swing version of "Silent Night"
plays faintly]
♪ And all is bright ♪
♪ Round yon Virgin
Mother and child… ♪
Hey. What's all this?
[chuckles] Well, don't get too excited.
It's just grilled chicken with broccoli.
Celebrating is one thing,
but ruining a diet is another.
Okay. But what are we celebrating tonight?
Álex. The Epiphany night.
Ah, well, in my house
we've always preferred Santa Claus.
I mean, shame on you,
just destroying a tradition like that.
It's not very Epiphany-like
to have grilled chicken for dinner
by candlelight, is it?
Àlex, don't do that.
[chuckles] Do what?
Pretend you're not excited about it.
It doesn't suit you.
It's just… no one's ever cooked me
a romantic dinner like this.
[chuckles] Well, I've never
done this before either.
-Well, come on. It's getting cold.
-Here.
-Have a seat.
-Oh…
I wanted to get a roscón for dessert,
but they were all massive.
So I told the pastry cook
to give me a smaller piece…
[Ibra's voice fades and echos]
I told her, I'm not trying to ruin a diet,
but I do want to have something
for the surprise.
Sorry, huh?
[echoing stops]
There's no roscón.
Ah, well, that's okay. I'm not really…
I don't have a sweet tooth, I mean.
Well, we'll think of
an alternative dessert.
[both chuckle]
Hand me your plate.
[Ibra chuckles]
-What's this?
-Your Epiphany gift.
But… I didn't get you a gift or anything.
You didn't have to.
Open it.
-A vacation?
-[Ibra chuckles softly]
-Ibra, this must have cost you--
-Almost nothing.
A stewardess friend of mine
helped me get the tickets.
I only had to pay taxes.
-We leave tomorrow.
-I'm working tomorrow. I won't be--
[Ibra] I talked to Vero. She said
we can go for ten days, no problem.
I was torn between Mykonos or Ibiza.
But this time of year
there's no parties, so I thought,
-"How about a little nice weather?"
-Yeah, I know, but… Senegal?
Well, listen, it's the best time
for us to visit.
Dry season. It won't rain.
We can spend the whole day at the beach.
Don't you like it?
Ibra, I love it. I really do.
Really, I'm… really looking forward to it.
I mean, I know that
Senegal isn't the best place for gays,
but we'll be fine.
And, besides,
it would mean a lot
if you could meet my parents.
-Uh, your parents?
-Mmm.
I know we've only been dating
for a little while,
and maybe it's too fast.
But I've never felt like this
for anyone else.
I've never been with someone
so… similar to me, you know?
[chuckles softly]
Yeah… No, me neither.
[both chuckle softly]
I don't want to miss this chance, Àlex.
I think I'm falling in love with you.
-[Vero] Hi.
-[door closes]
What are you still doing up?
What a night, love!
Half an hour before we closed,
this big group of people came in
and they just wouldn't leave.
I mean, they just… [scoffs]
Even when we killed the music,
they didn't get the hint.
Hey, are there any leftovers?
I'm really hungry.
Aren't you gonna ask about the apartment?
You said everything was in order, though.
Is it, then?
I spent the whole afternoon there.
[sniffles]
Thinking that…
that something wasn't there.
I went over the parquet,
the faucets, the tiles.
Everything's perfect.
Ready to be moved into.
Well,
then what's… Where's the problem?
It's not a home.
Hmm.
It will be once we're there.
You really think that'll be enough?
That it'll really be a home for us?
-It's not a redecoration?
-Of course not.
Then why aren't we happy about any of it?
-We are happy. Yeah.
-No, we aren't, Vero.
-[Vero] Yes.
-No, my love.
'Cause we just got the apartment
we've been wanting for years together.
We should be screaming.
Jumping on the bed, like we did
when we got approved for the mortgage.
We haven't even organized the move yet.
Well, because it's been
really tough lately
with the holidays and everything, but…
-But we can start planning it tomorrow.
-No. "We can"?
Or I can?
Uh, what are you saying?
You've put everything in my hands.
Uh, well, because you have more time, and…
And I don't know about
interior design much, Patri.
Or because we weren't doing it together.
-[Patri] Not really.
-That's not it.
That explains why you wanted
to go to Ibiza.
No.
Or your determination
to have an open relationship
-and everything else that's been going on.
-[Vero sniffling]
You probably didn't know how to tell me.
Or you didn't even see it all yourself,
really, but I don't know.
-[Vero sobs]
-But I can see it clearly.
Vero.
-[Vero crying]
-Look at me.
[sniffles]
You're not happy with me.
And, if you're not happy,
then I can't be either.
But, Patri, I do love you.
Yeah. And I love you too.
But that's not all it's about.
Love is just the seed.
What's important is the fruit
that it grows.
And what we do with it.
[stifled crying]
♪ I can't give you
Anything but love, baby… ♪
[chuckling]
♪ I can't give you anything but love ♪
[song ends]
[ethereal music plays]
[door creaks]
[wistful music plays]
[Ramiro and Rosa chattering]
[Rosa] Of course.
-[Ramiro] It was this one.
-[chuckles] No, no.
-Look right there.
-Come on. This was the day we saw--
[Rosa] It isn't! [chuckles]
[wistful music continues]
[kisses]
[music continues]
[wind blowing]
[wistful music intensifies]
[Christmas music
sung by children's choir plays]
[doorbell ringing]
-[Bruno] Hi.
-[Núria] Hey.
[Julia] Hurry! Come on, come on.
[children shriek]
Well, well. What do we have here?
[Bruno chuckles] Hello!
Love you. [kissing]
Look what I found at my house!
I found them at my house.
The Three Wise Men left gifts
for me to give to you.
-[Albert] He's doing great.
-[Bruno] This one says Artur.
-[Artur] Whoa!
-[Bruno] Why don't you open that?
[Bruno] And this one says… Julia.
-Wow! What is it?
-[Bruno] Let's see.
[chuckles] All right.
-[Julia gasps]
-Yeah? [chuckles]
[Julia] Oh!
LOW BATTERY 20%
CLOSE
Aw! Just like I asked.
-Yeah?
-[Albert chuckling]
Well, that's odd,
'cause you have been naughty this year.
[chuckles]
Thank you, Uncle Bruno.
Well, we have the Three Wise Men to thank.
Hmm?
-[Bruno] Come on. Let's play.
-[Julia] Let's go play.
[Julia] Wanna try mine too?
And this one is for… Ariel.
-[Albert] Look. For Ariel.
-Aw! Let's see.
-[Albert] They're just tired. Sleepy.
-Let's see what it is. [gasps] How cute!
Yeah? You like it?
Look, you can exchange it.
The Three Wise Men left the receipt.
-No, it's sweet, really.
-Yup.
-Huh, Albert?
-[chuckles] Yeah.
[Núria] Look!
[wistful music plays]
-Hello.
To the airport, please.
["Light in the Dark" by Ivana Lukic
plays on car stereo]
IBRA
ON MY WAY
I'M ALREADY HERE
BRUNO THE SNOB
[tense music plays]
CALLING
-[line ringing]
-[clears throat]
[Núria] Sweetie, careful.
[cell phone buzzing]
[Albert] Sleep tight, Ariel. Okay.
ÁLEX 2 GYMS
INCOMING CALL
[Núria] That's everything. Artur, come on.
[Albert] Hurry. It'll get cold.
We'll play after.
[voicemail beeps]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
[line beeps]
Hello, Bruno. It's Àlex.
Um…
You must be busy right now.
I'm actually headed to the airport.
I'm going on vacation to Senegal.
Uh…
And I didn't want to leave without, um…
Uh, thank you for the gift
that you brought me.
Because I watched it, and I loved it.
And, yeah, um…
Yeah, I just wanted to say that.
[breathing unsteadily]
[wistful music plays]
Well, no. No. In fact,
I wanted to apologize to you.
-[Bruno] Give me a sec.
-[Álex] Because I think I was wrong.
Because I shouldn't have let you go
the first night we slept together.
Or, at least, I should have called you
the next morning.
VOICEMAIL
ÁLEX 2 GYMS
And I shouldn't have offered you
an alcohol-free beer. I should have
offered you the one that you wanted.
But I didn't know
what that was gonna be yet.
I'm sorry I'm telling you all this now
because I know that you're with Ramón
and I'm with Ibra,
and that's all working fine.
And I suppose it's normal.
That you're with your great architect
and I'm with a gym guy,
I mean, cause that's
what others expect from us.
-I've spent my life stuck in this cycle.
-The number you've dialed isn't available.
Look. For years now,
I've gotten up in the morning
and done the exact same thing every day.
-I make my protein shake and…
-I'm sorry.
-I'll explain it later! See ya!
-…eat something, check Insta, work out.
-And after all that, I go distract myself.
-Taxi!
I'll hang out with a friend
until I have to go to work at the bar.
And, once I'm there,
I'll be cleaning things,
and I always, always, always
end up checking Grindr.
And I'll connect with a guy.
-And we'll meet up and fuck.
-Come on, come on.
And I always think, "Come on, Àlex."
"This time I'm sure it'll work.
This time I'm sure he's the one."
But I'm wrong. I mess it up,
and it all starts over again.
I've spent half of my life
doing the same thing.
I'm searching, trying to find a guy.
And, now that I've found one,
well, I don't know
if it's really what I want.
Because I feel nothing.
And because I know him already.
Because I don't feel the way
that I do with you.
And I know it doesn't make any sense
for me to say this now,
and I'm sure I already missed my chance.
But I couldn't just go to the other end
of the world without telling you.
I mean, even if it is too late.
And I wish you all the happiness, Bruno.
[chuckles, sobs]
[cell phone clicks]
[sobbing]
Thank you. Really.
You can stay here if you want to.
[wistful music plays]
[tires screech]
[Bruno] Thank you.
[driver] Hey! Are you kidding me?
-You need to pay.
-Sorry, sorry. I know.
Okay, uh, 15… Keep the change.
Here you go. Thank you.
[driver] Thank you.
["Al Final Abrazos" plays]
[announcer] This is a final boarding call
for flight A-298 to Dakar.
Come on, Álex. Come on, come on.
Please, come on.
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed is not available.
Ah…
ÁLEX 2 GYMS
[keys clicking]
[low battery chime sounds]
Fuck!
[song continues]
[song continues on car stereo]
[sniffles]
[song stops]
[whimsical music plays]
[sniffles] Thanks.
[blows nose]
[man] Bruno!
You didn't go.
I couldn't.
Not after everything I said.
It's over with Ramón.
I ended it with Ibra.
You're all I can think about,
and dating him was a mistake.
I feel the same way.
Well, that says something, doesn't it?
I mean, look. I know this is absurd.
And that whenever we're together we fight,
and that we couldn't be more different.
-You know, Katharine Hepburn, Cary Grant.
-[chuckles and sniffles]
But… But, if they tried,
well then, I don't see why we shouldn't.
And who knows
how our ending will turn out?
But we can have a new beginning.
["Al Final Abrazos" resumes]
If you want.
[Bruno] At the airport, I only had time
to write him one quick text message.
[horns honking]
[Álex] If I hadn't seen it,
I wouldn't have gone to his house
to find him that night.
[Bruno] It was a very simple message.
[Álex] An emoji.
[Bruno] Just a smile.
[Álex] A smiley.
[Bruno] There was no need
for anything more.
[Álex] It was probably
the best message I've ever been sent.
[song continues]
[song ends]
[wistful music plays]