A NETFLIX SERIES
[whimsical music plays]
[people chattering]
[Julia] Dear Three Wise Men of the Orient…
This year I have behaved very well.
I have gotten good grades,
and I have obeyed my parents
most of the time.
[Núria] I don't know, Albert.
You must have left them at the office!
[Albert shouting] I left them
in the kitchen. They were here yesterday.
[Núria] Why are you leaving
important documents in the kitchen
when you have your own office?
Don't you keep any copies?
[Albert] They were handmade plans
with corrections.
We don't have them on a computer!
-Did you ask Najat?
-Yes. She hasn't seen them either.
The council presentation's tomorrow, and…
-Are you an idiot? No!
-Albert.
How many times do I have to tell you
to not touch Daddy's stuff!
-[Ariel crying]
-[Núria] Don't ever talk to her like that.
It's not her fault that you keep
leaving things where they don't belong.
-[Núria grunts]
-[door slams]
[Ariel continues crying]
Is that a letter to the Three Wise Men?
Can you only ask the Three Wise Men
for your own presents,
or can it be for somebody?
I think you can ask for anyone you'd like.
Okay.
[whimsical music plays]
[Julia] Dear Three Wise Men of the Orient…
This year I actually don't want
anything for me.
What?
Look. Look, look, look.
-Look.
-[Bruno chuckles]
It's the first time
I've shouted at her, Bruno.
I'm the worst father in the world.
Well, just take her out
for ice cream later, and it's done.
-I don't know what happened to me.
-You're freaking out. That's normal.
-[sighs]
-It's our most important project.
Ramón and I have a lot at stake, but you?
I mean, you're
the new head of the studio soon.
-Shh. Shut up, shut up.
-All right, all right.
Crazy. All these years,
we thought Sunyer only put up with you
-'cause you were married to Núria.
-[chuckles]
This one's not working.
-Do you have an eraser?
-Yeah.
HAVE A GREAT DAY
R.
[chuckles softly]
-Wow, look at you.
-What?
-So… he's eating out of your palm.
-[chuckles]
Since he got back
he leaves Post-its all over the place.
Yeah, I don't know.
He's actually very romantic.
[chuckles]
-"But…"
-No, there's no "but."
-There's no "but"?
-There's no "but." You were right.
You were right.
Ramón is adorable.
We have good sex,
and we have a lot of things in common.
That's great, Bruno. That's great.
[both chuckle]
I got it. Not like with Àlex.
That… Can you imagine
what that would be like?
[scoffs]
Come on. A remake of an Iranian
Spider-Man is more plausible.
[Albert chuckles]
Take, for example,
something as easy as going to the movies.
Well, I'd choose All About Eve,
and what would he choose?
It'd be Frozen… a second time.
Because maybe he didn't get it the first.
And, besides, he's allergic to dogs.
What would I do with Puchusky? Huh?
Àlex would have to take an antihistamine
at my place. He'd get sick of that.
You know, because they say
it doesn't have side effects, but it does.
And then he'd make me choose
either him or Puchusky.
And there's no way.
I will not abandon Puchusky.
He's the only thing
that gives me joy in life.
-And we'd never go to any dinners.
-[both panting]
How could I?
We'd all be there talking about
the new urban plans in Tokyo,
and Àlex wouldn't have anything to say.
And you'd make fun of him,
and then make fun of me,
and in the end I would stop seeing you.
And we would fight.
We'd argue every day too.
Because I'd see him as a burden,
and he'd see me as a nuisance.
-And, before long, we would break up.
-[grunting]
And I'd have no boyfriend, no friends,
no vacations, and no Puchusky.
-[Ibra moans]
-Shh… [chuckles]
[amusing music plays]
Yeah.
[cell phone chimes]
-You up already?
-Your apartment isn't exactly quiet.
My bad. I'm really sorry.
No, no, no!
Don't you dare touch me with those.
-Yuck! [chuckles]
-No!
-You off?
-Yes.
There's a small problem at the bar.
We lost our caterer for New Year's Eve.
Wait. Shit. What happened?
A salmonella outbreak.
We have to find another one.
Two days before the party?
That's gonna cost a lot.
[Vero] Everyone's already paid.
We can't serve chips.
I've contacted a couple of restaurants
that might be willing
to give us a fair price.
-[Álex] Okay.
-Good morning.
Hey.
[door closes]
[whispers] I preferred
the architect, though.
No. Bruno was the last mistake of 2022.
-It's a new year and a new life.
-And what's new about Ibra?
He doesn't just want to fuck.
He's interested in who I am.
Mm-hmm.
And we also have a lot in common,
not like with Bruno.
I mean, can you imagine
my life with Bruno?
I mean, a concert where Rosalía
and… and Bertín Osborne sang together
would be more plausible.
Okay. Just try and be careful
is all I'm saying.
'Cause you get excited
and then you get yourself hurt.
[whispers] Ibra's different.
-[cell phone chimes]
-Sure…
PATRI:
MY PARENTS ARE LEAVING TONIGHT
Well, tomorrow you guys
can fuck in peace, I guess.
Oh.
-Thanks.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[chuckles]
[Rosa] All right, Diego.
Here is your order.
What about the squid?
When are they getting in?
They're in a box in the warehouse.
Come back this afternoon. I'll have them.
No, I'll send my grandson to pick them up.
Well, and if we don't see each other,
happy New Year to you.
[both] Happy New Year.
One minute, Diego.
We'd better go to the warehouse,
and I'll get them for you right now.
That way we don't have to bother
your grandson.
[Diego] All right.
Why don't you just leave?
You've hurt her enough. Don't you think?
[whimsical music plays]
[Julia] I have learned one thing.
When children want a gift,
we ask for it, but the grown-ups don't.
They never say what they really want.
If they said what they wanted,
everything would be easier, wouldn't it?
It happens to my mom.
She's always angry or sad or tired.
Please, bring her something
to make her laugh like she used to.
[Núria] Well, we can't offer you much
at this point.
Unless we were to finish
a few of the dishes here instead.
-Is there a kitchen?
-We only warm up the customers here.
-[Núria chuckles]
-I can bring my microwave if needed.
Well, then, let's opt for cold menus.
And just use the microwave
for sauces and such.
This menu is the basic option.
Three types of hummus, salads,
puff pastries, canapés…
And this menu has the smoked salmon,
plus the cod, caviar.
-[sighs]
-This one's better, right?
Sure, it's better, but it's twice as much.
Yeah…
It's, um… We're on
a really tight budget right now.
-[cell phone buzzes]
-Um…
[Núria] Would you excuse me a moment?
-[tense music plays]
-[Núria] Uh…
[Javi whispers] I mean, sure,
it's amazing, but the price is insane.
What is it?
Hello, Núria, sweetheart.
Um, my parents just called,
and, uh, they're staying in Sardinia
for New Year's Eve
and wanted us to come out.
-Uh…
-Núria?
[whispers] I have to cater.
Um, since when?
Yes, Albert. There was a new client
last minute, um, and we decided to accept.
But… But, I mean, you go with the kids.
And you guys spend the weekend
in the mountains.
-Yeah?
-No, no, no.
But I… I mean, I'm sad that
you're starting the year without us, um…
-Uh, we can stay here, right?
-No.
And make a toast
when you get off, at least.
[chuckles] No, no, no. Seriously.
Don't worry about me, all right?
I'll be fine, but I need to get back.
Ha-- Have a good night, okay?
-No, but, Núr… I… I'm…
-[cell phone clicks]
[Núria clears throat]
[Javi] I don't think we can swing it.
I have good news. That was my boss.
He mentioned we could give you
10% off on any of the menus.
And I'd be in charge of cooking.
So what do you think?
[music continues]
-Vero?
-[gasps]
Jesus, Patri. You really scared me.
I thought you had to work today.
No, I took the day off.
I spent the last day with my parents.
-Oh.
-Where are you taking that?
It's for the New Year's Eve party tonight.
Do you mind if I borrow it?
Mm-mmm.
Javi is preparing a show.
You'll love it. You'll see.
It's a… a tribute for the songs
of the '80s, I guess.
I don't think I'll come.
-You're joking.
-I just don't feel like going out tonight.
You're just gonna eat the grapes
alone here?
We'll see. I might say, "Fuck the grapes,"
and go to bed early. I don't know yet.
Patri, I want us
to bring in the new year together.
You know how important it is for me.
It was important for me to come out
to my parents when I was ready to,
but you didn't care about that--
-That's not true.
-For you, it meant nothing.
That's a lie.
-You only really care about yourself.
-Huh?
Vero wants to work in Ibiza.
Vero wants to see other girls.
-Vero wants a party and I have to say yes.
-No, both of us decided to do that.
Vero. And I wanted one thing,
just one thing, Vero.
You respect the most important decision
of my life.
And you couldn't have cared less.
You were accepted
by your parents, regardless.
-You don't need to hide now, all right?
-Ah! I get it.
-I should thank you, is that it?
-Yeah.
-Is that so?
-Yeah, actually.
-If it was up to you…
-Thank you.
…you'd have gotten married
to fucking Marco Antonio
and be expecting your third kid!
[somber music plays]
-Get out of here.
-Patri, I'm sorry.
Get out of here, Vero.
Right now.
[Rosa] Your grandmother used to say
that a boy and a girl couldn't be friends.
That what Ramiro and I were doing
wasn't normal.
Now I understand why she said that.
Okay, so… Dad was bisexual.
That isn't what matters.
I don't care if he liked men or women.
What matters is that they hid it.
How can I ever forgive that?
But, Mom, that was 30 years ago.
I mean, Dad stayed with you.
-You were happy together.
-Were we happy?
Did he choose me because
it was what he really wanted
or because he thought he should?
Well, he could have stayed with Ramiro,
and he didn't.
Oh, Álex, those were different times.
Two men couldn't
just build some life together.
Especially if one of them
was having a child with his wife.
That doesn't mean
he wasn't happy with you.
[sighs]
I don't know.
[whimsical music plays]
[Julia] Grown-ups are a real pain.
They always say that when they were little
everything was cooler,
and now everything sucks.
It's as if they lost something
the day they grew up.
I guess that's the reason
they complain all day long.
My parents always complain
that they don't have time.
We don't have the time to waste.
[Julia] Uncle Bruno always complains
that he can't find anyone to help him.
And my dad?
[knocking on door]
[Sunyer] Listen, you just need to tell me
what you need, and we'll get it done.
It isn't a problem.
-Is something wrong?
-No, no. Everything's all right.
I wanted to give you this.
TRM. THREE WISE MEN
[Albert sighs] Did you really come here
to give me this?
'Cause my heart nearly stopped
when I saw you here, Najat.
I know it's not serious, but,
well, the office was on the way.
I was worried it'd get lost
if it was laying around the house.
I'm in the middle of a meeting right now.
I need to go.
Look, it's important that you read this.
-All right, um, anything else?
-No.
[sarcastic] Well, thanks
for delivering the letter.
Lis, will you show her the way out?
[door slams]
We're ready, my love.
[sighs]
Well, are you sure you don't want us
to stay a little longer?
No, Mom. I'll be fine. I will.
-Well then, anem.
-That's it.
Isn't it "anem"?
Yes, Mom. That's it.
Well, anem. Anem!
[Patri chuckles]
-Thank you for coming.
-[man] I love you.
-[kisses]
Thanks, Mom.
-Oh, my love. Take care of yourself.
-I will.
-I love you.
-Oh.
-Now hurry. Let's go.
-You don't wanna miss your plane.
-Yeah, let's go.
-Yeah? Travel safe.
[melancholy music plays]
As soon as we get there,
we'll do a video call.
-[Patri] Yes, don't forget.
-[blows kiss]
Come on, sweetheart.
-I love you so much.
-[Patri] And I you!
-[blowing kisses]
-Have a safe flight.
[sighs]
-Kinda dead in here today, isn't it?
-Mmm.
Everyone's saving up for New Year's Eve.
It would've been smart
to have shows today and tomorrow.
Listen, honey. I need to rest too, huh?
This skin doesn't
just take care of itself.
[scoffs]
[woman] Can I have another one?
Elena.
Hi, love.
-I thought you were in Ibiza.
-Yeah, well,
I came here urgently to solve a problem.
What?
You.
Well, in the end I wasn't sure
if Sunyer would take me back.
-Well…
-Yes.
But then I told him I left
because I couldn't stand
working next to you. He understood.
-Hang on. You didn't say that.
-Yeah, sure.
Tell me you didn't say that.
-Ramón, please…
-[laughs]
You're a dead man.
I knew it… I mean, I knew it!
[laughing] I just said
that I couldn't take the workload.
That I didn't feel valued.
And not only was I rehired,
but I got a raise.
Wow…
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Uh, you want to go to that bar?
[Ramón] Yeah, have you been there?
I went there one time,
but, well, I didn't like it very much.
What are you saying? It's great.
Have you seen Keena Mandrah yet?
-Hey, let's go to La Federica.
-That's a bit far, isn't it?
Well, this way we walk a little,
get a little fresh air…
-Let's go to La Federica, all right?
-You're in a funny mood.
-[chuckles] That's right. Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Then he told you--
-Right. He said--
[man] Pikachu?
[Ramón] Oh, Charmander!
[Ramón and man laugh]
-What's up? How are you?
-[Ramón] Man…
-[Ramón sighs] It's been a long time.
-It has.
-It's been forever!
-How are you?
-Yeah. Since before the pandemic at least.
-No, I think longer. Even longer.
Oh yeah. Hey, who's this?
-[Ramón] Oh, sorry.
-[Ibra] How you doing?
Bruno, Ibra. Ibra, Bruno.
I met Ibra when it was still cool
to go catch Pokémon around the city.
-Okay.
-[Ramón] Remember?
-[Ibra] Good times!
-[Ramón] Yeah.
[Ibra] I got really hooked.
We would meet up with a group every
weekend and spend hours and hours playing.
-[chuckles]
-You going to Bar Bero?
-No…
-No. No, uh, La Federica. Right?
Why don't you join us?
That way we can catch up.
-Do you mind?
-No, of course.
No, I wish I could, but I gotta go…
[clicks tongue] …see my guy.
Wait, hold on. You're seeing a new guy?
Well, we haven't been together very long,
but it's going all right.
Why don't you guys come meet him?
-Great.
-No.
No, I guess…
If you guys are getting together, it's
likely a date. We don't wanna intrude.
It's not a problem.
We see each other every day.
-[chuckles]
-Besides, he can get us all free drinks.
-[Ramón] Oh, he works there?
-He does. I'm sure you know him.
-[Ramón] Who is it?
-He's very popular. His name is Àlex.
-[Ramón] I know him, not personally.
-Yeah, see?
-[Ibra] I bet you didn't expect that, huh?
-[chuckles] That's great.
[Ibra] He's a sweetheart.
I'm sure you'll love him.
-Come on.
-Okay.
[wistful music plays]
[Ramón] Bruno.
-Yes.
-[Ramón] You coming?
Yeah, of course.
[pop music plays on speakers]
Hey.
-Calm and quiet today, huh?
-Yeah, it's really dead today.
[bar sounds fade out]
[ethereal music plays]
[heart beating]
[heartbeat grows louder]
[Ibra] And this is Bruno.
-[heartbeat fades out]
-[bar sounds resume]
Uh, yeah. Yeah, we know each other.
-Oh yeah?
-Hmm?
Ah, that's right. We've met.
Àlex, with the two gyms.
Sure, sure, you looked familiar.
Sorry, I'm terrible with faces sometimes.
You good?
-I'm good, you?
-Great.
-Well, I'm glad.
-Yeah, me too.
Well, uh, want a drink?
-One gin and tonic.
-Make it two.
A beer.
And do you want it light, toasted, stout?
Alcohol-free?
I hate alcohol-free beer.
-I see. Mm.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
Just a normal.
Well, I'll go get those.
Perfect. [chuckles]
-[Elena] They like a girl from Berlin.
-Mm-hmm.
But I've asked them to wait a few weeks
to see if you come around.
I've already made my decision.
They're offering you 20% more
plus accommodations.
I'm really sorry.
It's Amnesia!
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know it's Amnesia.
And thank you truly
for your interest in me.
But I can't.
She won't let you, huh?
I saw your profile.
-[cell phone chimes]
-Hello. We are Vero and Patricia.
Mm-hmm. We've been together
for seven years.
She runs her own business,
and I work at a flower store.
And we're doing great…
-Yeah, we're great. Mm-hmm.
-Yeah, great.
Did it fuel or extinguish?
Huh?
Opening your relationship is like a gift.
You receive it with enthusiasm,
but you never know what you're gonna get.
Some people get gasoline,
others a fire extinguisher.
What did you get, Vero?
["Baby You Are a Star" plays]
According to this theory,
all of us are connected
to everybody on the planet
by just only six simple links.
In other words, I know someone
who knows someone who knows someone
and so on, until I get to, um…
Ah! Ariana Grande!
[Ramón and Ibra vocalize]
[all chuckle]
That's why it's called
the six degrees of separation.
Well, six degrees, with queers
in Barcelona is how many? One?
I have an ex that always says,
if you're over 30,
it's statistically impossible
to walk into a bar
and not have fucked someone there.
-Well…
-[Ibra] Is that so?
-[Ibra] Let's see, let's see, let's see…
-[Ramón chuckles]
Let's see… Uh…
-Ah! Your ex is right. Ah…
-[Álex chuckles] Mmm.
[Ibra chuckles]
♪ Film kiss and in my heart an explosion ♪
♪ Red lights recording
Every word that I say ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
-What was that for?
-I… just wanted to. [chuckles]
Well, that's good.
Do it again whenever you want.
[both chuckle]
♪ Baby, you're a star ♪
-Um, I'm sorry. I'll be right back.
-[Ibra] Sure…
[Ramiro] Hi, Àlex.
Why are you here?
-I think I owe you an explanation.
-You don't owe me anything. No.
I want you to know that it was
never my intention to hurt your mother.
A little late for that.
The last thing I intended
was to stir up the past,
but Rosa, she misunderstood me.
-I couldn't let her think that--
-I don't care.
Àlex. I need you to know what
really happened with me and your father.
I'm working, so I can't.
Then I'll wait until you're done.
I won't leave till you hear me out.
Do what you want,
but it's a waste of time.
[Javi] Everything okay?
[sighs]
Could I get a tequila?
Sure, honey.
[Javi] A triple for my sea dog,
coming right up.
-[door opens]
-[song continues in distance]
-[Elena] I think you need help.
-[door closes]
I think I've got it, thanks.
I didn't mean with the boxes.
[bottles rattle]
♪ Big screen showing
How I feel to the world ♪
♪ Bloodlines drifting through real life ♪
♪ Kiss me through the cinema screen ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
-[moaning]
[music intensifies]
♪ Kiss me through the cinema screen ♪
[moans]
-I can't.
-[boxes clatter]
[woman] Vero, Vero.
[woman gasps] Oh.
I thought I was in the wrong bar.
The name is spelled wrong
on the sign out front.
Yessenia, what are you doing here?
Well, we're on our way to the airport.
But I'm not leaving
until I talk to you first.
Listen to me, Vero.
I don't care if my daughter
is with men, women…
The only thing I need to know
before I leave,
is that my daughter is in good hands.
Do you love Patri?
-She is the love of my life.
-[Yessenia chuckles]
But how do I know that?
We've been together seven years.
Being together doesn't mean
you love each other.
Well, I know I wanna be with her forever.
That is just a wish, not a reality.
I don't know what else to say.
It's very easy.
What does love mean to you?
[breathes deeply]
[somber music plays]
When my parents found out that I was gay,
they beat me
and kicked me out of the house.
I know. I'm sorry.
I lost my family.
But I created a new one.
With Javi, with Àlex.
But, above all, with Patri.
[wistful music plays]
[Vero] I didn't know what a home was
until I met her.
Love is not a feeling.
It is a place.
A shelter capable of protecting you
from anything.
That's what Patri is for me.
[chuckles]
So did I answer your question, then?
Take good care of my Patri.
Please,
don't wait too long to apologize.
She just wants to… to forgive you, honey.
[kissing]
[blows kiss]
-Bye.
[melancholy music plays]
-[door opens]
-[bell rings]
[door closes]
[sniffles, chuckles softly]
[pop ballad plays on speakers]
Javi.
Do you mind if I leave early?
Go ahead, honey.
There's nothing happening here.
Okay, I'll go get my things.
-I love you.
-And I you.
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Wanting to believe ♪
♪ Oh ♪
-[glass clinking]
-[door opens]
[Patri] Vero.
What are you doing here?
I wasn't expecting you tonight.
Yeah. I know, me either.
But I couldn't wait, Patri.
Patri, I've come to apologize.
-Vero, I have to--
-And not just for Christmas.
You were right, my love.
I've been selfish, and I've dragged you
into decisions that you didn't want.
I say,
to hell with the other girls… my love.
-I just want to be with you.
-I'm…
-[clattering]
-[woman] Patri?
[floorboards creak]
Vero.
[fabric rustling]
[melancholy music plays]
No, Vero, wait. Babe.
Vero.
Look, I was down
and didn't wanna be alone.
Vero, try to understand, please. Okay?
Vero, wait. Just let me explain.
-[door opens, closes]
-[sighs]
That's why there are three balls.
[all laugh]
Well, another round, then?
-Oh, no, no, no.
-Oh… Ah.
-We better get going now.
-But it's very early.
Yes, but I'd rather get rest.
It's just we have a very important meeting
tomorrow with the city council, and…
To be honest,
we shouldn't have gotten drinks.
-[chuckles] Thanks for the drinks, huh?
-No, of course.
Well, uh, this was nice.
-[Ibra] It was.
-[Álex] Yeah, it was great.
[Álex] Great meeting you. See ya.
-You too. See ya.
-[Ibra] Pikachu!
-[Ramón] Ciao, handsome.
-[Bruno] Well…
-[Ibra] I'll see you later.
-Shall we, then?
-[Ramón] Uh, yes.
Oh, uh, give me a minute.
-Let me just use the bathroom quick.
-Oh. Me too. I'll come with.
Great, let's go.
["Dancing Through the Heartbreak"
plays on speakers]
[clears throat]
Your boyfriend's really nice.
-Yeah.
-[Bruno] Hmm.
Yeah, well, I mean,
we'll see what happens.
Ah, no, it'll be great.
He's your type, so…
My type?
Yeah, if I had to picture you
with someone,
he would be the first thing
that comes to mind.
It would be absurd otherwise.
How would you know?
You don't know what he's like.
-Well, I mean, you know what I--
-No.
I don't know what you're trying to say.
I just think that you're a good couple.
You both look like
a couple from an Ikea catalog.
Ah. Well, you can't complain either.
Was it Ramón?
Ramón. Yes, absolutely not.
Ramón's a great guy.
So humble, so intelligent. He--
How nice! This way you'll never be
short of conversation.
-[Bruno] No, no, not at all.
-[chuckles] Cool.
I always said I would never be
with an architect again.
-It's the best thing I did.
-Ibra's the same. Incredible.
The second I saw him, bam! Instantly.
Same for us! We met too and then, bam!
-That's how it is when you really connect.
-Right?
-Everything just flows, and it's all easy.
-It really is.
-You don't need those strategies.
-Yeah.
"Now I'll text, but now I won't."
-That--
-"Now I'll pretend I don't care."
-"Now I won't text for a few days."
-How boring.
-So boring, I don't like those loops.
-Me neither. Awful.
-[Álex] None of that. Phew!
-No, no, no.
[both chuckle]
[song continues]
[music intensifies]
[Ramón] Bruno.
-[Ramón] Let's go.
-[Bruno] Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Um, see you. Bye.
-[Álex] Have a good night. Bye.
-[Ibra] See you. Bye, guys.
[chuckles]
-So Bruno's a little weird, isn't he?
-Why do you say that?
I don't know.
He seemed a little awkward, I guess.
-You didn't notice?
-Mm-mmm.
How do you know him, again?
-I don't know. From the bar, I think.
-Hmm.
He seems familiar, but I don't know why.
-Hey. Should we get out of here?
-Don't you want to talk to him first?
No, not tonight.
-Javi, can you close the bar tonight?
-Yeah, no problem.
[Álex] See you.
Good night.
[door closes]
[Ramiro breathes shakily]
Can you tell me what's happening
between you two?
[sniffles]
Nothing.
Uh…
What's the damage? Close me out.
You're good. It's on me tonight.
Thanks.
-[Javi] Oh!
-[grunts]
Be careful!
-Oh fuck. Are you all right?
-Yeah.
-You okay? Come on. Get up.
-I'm okay.
[Javi] Here we go.
[grunts]
[panting]
I'm okay.
[sobs]
[whimpers] I am.
[cries, sniffles]
[sobs]
[melancholy music plays]
[crying]
Let it all out.
You cry as long as you need, all right?
[Sunyer] When the city council
entrusted us
with one of the most iconic theaters
on the Parallel,
we immediately understood
that it had to be top level.
At an aesthetic level with the legacy
of a unique city like Barcelona.
The New Arnau Theater will establish
a dialogue between past and future,
but above all between the stage
and the neighborhood that hosts it.
This will be explained further
by the director of the project,
let me introduce, the future director
of Sunyer Architects, Albert Costa.
[somber music plays]
[Julia] And Dad is always sad.
He wasn't like that before.
He was always happy.
But ever since Ariel was born, he's not.
I don't think he loves him.
And maybe he doesn't love us either.
He yells at us a lot.
I don't like living like this.
[Sunyer] Albert?
Whenever you're ready.
[whispers] Albert.
Hey.
-[music fades]
-[papers crinkle]
[door opens]
Where the hell are you going?
-Home.
-Now? Are you insane?
There's a presentation!
Fuck the presentation.
I don't want it. In fact…
Yeah, I'm done here.
I'm done.
[Julia] Please, let Daddy
go back to being how he used to be
when he always wanted to play
and didn't make Mom cry.
-[Julia] Dad's home.
-[Albert] Julia? Artur. Come here, kids!
Come here, my sweethearts!
Oh!
I love you so much.
I do.
[kissing]
[exhales deeply] Oh, I love you so much.
You hear? Forever.
[cell phone buzzing]
[Julia] And one more thing.
Since you have magic,
I'm also asking you to bring gifts
to all the people who are sad right now.
Make them believe in magic again.
And that way they will get what they want
and never be sad again.
[breathes deeply]
And if anything else comes up
let us know. You have my number. Thanks.
-Thank you. It was great.
-You're welcome.
Thanks. We'll get you those details.
Thank you very much. That was great.
We loved it. Thank you.
-[man] Congrats. Great presentation.
-[Ramón] Thank you.
-[Ramón] Thank you. Thank you very much.
-[Sunyer] I'll show you out.
[chuckles]
[cell phone chimes]
ÁLEX 2 GYMS:
HEY, WE'RE HOSTING A NEW YEAR'S EVE PARTY.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANY PLANS TOMORROW,
COME BY THE BAR!
["Dopamina" by Veintiuno plays]
[chuckles]