Dr. Cotter
He will die. She will
die, my mother will die
.I will die. Everyone will die
I couldn't get him to talk.
He doesn't say anything.
- This. - Yes
.Understood
Thank you, Dan.
She will die. My mother is going to
die. I am going to die. Everyone will die
It doesn't matter to
anyone. It doesn't matter
It doesn't matter. Mom doesn't matter
I don't matter. Everyone doesn't matter
He will die. She will die. I
will die. Everyone will die
It doesn't matter to anyone. It
doesn't matter, she doesn't matter
I'm going to die. Everyone's going to die.
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.
Mom doesn't matter
It doesn't matter to anyone. I don't matter
..me me
..hey..hey
everyone..me
It doesn't matter if it's me
Hello, Karl
How are you today?
I will die, you know?
.no
.I do not think so
I think you're having another panic attack.
..no
Don't argue!
You don't know
I feel like everyone around me is squeezing
.I am afraid
Carl, I know what you're
up against looks like...
.real
.but it can't hurt you.
.I promise you
He will die, she will
die, my mother will die
I'm going to die, everyone will die.
It doesn't matter what.
Hello, Wanda
I'll put Karl Rinken under
observation for a few days.
It's harmless
Just make sure he checks
it in. One every few hours
- That's it. - Thank you
Dr. Desai is looking for you
.Thanks
!No no! don't
You don't understand!
I don't want to go inside!
!no! no
.Please come in
.Welcome
Did you transfer a patient her name?
Sarah Marquette to the hall yesterday?
.Yes
She has a history of drug abuse and mania
She's in and out of our unit a few times.
.(Rose), she doesn't have insurance.
Well, but she needs treatment.
The board of directors pressures me not to make
a bed for anyone in need in the residency program
Perhaps the board of directors should try
to care about the purpose of our work here.
Listen, I don't doubt your judgment, okay?
I need you to come to me first so I
can see what to do next time, okay?
.Yes
Well, I'm sorry
You haven't been here since
your last shift last night, right?
Dr. Cotter
Laura Weaver, age 26, a graduate student
The police were called on her.
Because of breach of the public.
- EMS moved her here.
- Does she have a history of mental illness?
I didn't report anything.
But the police reported a different incident
in which they were involved in the past weeks.
What was that accident?
A teacher at her school beat
himself to death with a hammer
She was interrogated as the only witness
hammer?
.Welcome
(Lura)?)
My name is Dr. Cotter
I am a psychiatrist.
Would you like to sit down?
.Good
I know you're nervous.
.There is nothing wrong
I just want to have a conversation
I promise you this place is safe.
.not for me
Why do you say that?
Come on, let's sit down
.Help yourself
Well, I have to ask..you
have a few questions
Some of them might look stupid
What day of the week is this?
.Thursday
And a month?
October. I'm not crazy
No one says that
But I want you to understand that
I'm a doctoral student and I'm not crazy
- All right? - I just
Take a breath and I want
you to tell me what's going on
I see something.
.something that no one else can see but me.
I know how crazy this sounds.
..I know but this
This thing I can't explain.
What do you see?
He is embodied as a person.
He's not a person.
I'm not sure I understand
He looks like different people.
He looks like different people
Sometimes he pretends to be someone I know
And sometimes it seems like a stranger
..Sometimes
And sometimes he looks like my grandfather
Who died in front of me
when I was 7 years old
But it's always the same.
..it's a
..it looks like
Looks like he's wearing
people's faces like masks
.Good
Well, do you see him here now?
What happens when you see it?
.smiles at me
But it's not a friendly smile,
the worst smile I've ever seen
..and when i see her
I have a terrible feeling that something
really terrible is going to happen
I've never been scared
at all when I see him
Laura, have you or anyone in
your family ever had hallucinations?
It's not a hallucination. It's
real. you don't understand
He does things to me and
causes terrible things around me
It's taking over my whole life, my mind and
.tell me things
tell me that today
today is the day you will
.do not worry. There is nothing wrong
I know what you're
suffering from seems very real
Sometimes when we get
overwhelmed with feelings,
Or we suffer a severe shock
..that our minds
You're not listening to me! Oh my God!
I will die and no one will listen to me
Well, Laura, it's okay
.My God
Listen, it's okay
(Laura, would you look at me, please?)
.There is nothing wrong
.look at me
!My God! no
!he is here
- Go away. - It's okay, Laura
- It's just me! - No
- No one but me here! - No
!no
!My God
I have a patient in an emergency
situation. In Room No. 2
I need the crew to come here now. quickly
(Lura)?)
|| smile ||
Was Miss Weaver ever sick here?
.no
Was it typical of the
patients you see here?
It is an emergency psychiatric unit
Nothing is typical here
Well, she's a psychopath, right?
Excuse me, a psychopath?
We're just trying to get your
assessment of her mental state
..she was suffering
From acute post-traumatic psychosis
She was suffering from
delusions of persecution
What kind of illusions?
..was convinced that
That there is a spirit of a
demonic entity chasing her.
.nice
We'll contact Miss Weaver's family
to try to explain what happened.
So, we're looking for anything
that might make sense to all of this.
If there's anything else you
can tell us that might be helpful?
..Before
..you are death
..she was
.smiling
Yes, it looks crazy to me.
.(Day)
it's up to you
it is my fault. Did I hide you?
I didn't hear you come in. the curse
- Hello. - Hello
What is the matter?
.no thing. sorry
There is something wrong
She died sick today
.she was my patient
come close
.I'm sorry for hearing this
It happened in front of me.
It was terrible
I'm so sorry, is there
any help I can offer?
It's not a good start.
Maybe we cancel dinner tonight?
.It's not possible
Holly hired a babysitter
And you might get a big
headache if we don't go.
No way, Holly gets a headache?
Hey
Do you know how fatigue is?
Now when Jackson is in first grade
I get up at 6 o'clock every day
I make breakfast and prepare lunch box
And only God knows which foods
are served in the school cafeteria
Then take him to school
I hardly had time to get my stuff done
And I didn't even have time to do Pilates.
- My body is in bad shape.
- That's not right
Then I go back to school to pick it up
I take him to workouts, soccer and swimming
.. and Karate and theatre
Now he's starting to speak Spanish
Either days of the week
are really impossible
Are you coming on Saturday?
What?
Sorry, how about Saturday?
Are you kidding?
It's Jackson's 7th birthday party
I told you this 5 times.
.I can not come. I have work
what do you mean? It's Saturday?
I work on Saturday
I think it's exactly for this reason
You should leave that disgusting
hospital and work in a private clinic
- It's not disgusting.
- You should have a normal working day
Rose, there are surely a lot
of madmen who are actually
They will pay you for your time
Thank you very much for your opinion, Greg
.This kindness of you
Just saying why become
a doctor. If you can't be rich
you're kidding, right?
Rose loves being a doctor.
She serves for nothing.
While talking about
wasted earning potential
.Maybe we can sell the house
Can we not talk about this now, please?
I don't understand. abandoned house
We were brought up in that house.
It's about to fall. Why don't we
take advantage of the earth's money?
Can you shut up?
Wow
.Thanks
.Thank you so much
I was looking forward to this meal
"Activate the night system"
are you OK?
.Yes
Good morning, Doctor.
.good morning
.Welcome
Yesterday, sick (Laura Weaver)
The police sent a report...
about a different incident
.that she was involved in
Can you send this to me?
It's up to you, Doctor.
Also, I was supposed to
have a session with Jane Park
Yes, she pulled a lock of her
hair last night and swallowed it.
They took her to the emergency
room for gastric lavage
.the curse
.(Day)
..What do you do
I was just around the corner
on a errand and I thought maybe
You know, we didn't talk much last night
.about it all
I just want you to know.
When we received the report, I didn't know
It was up to you. So,
I'm sorry. it was weird
It's your job, I understand.
How are you?
(Jules, why are you here?)
You know, like I said I was... on a
mission around the corner and just thought
Coming to check on you
You know, everything that
happened yesterday wasn't easy.
Well, I appreciate it, but I
don't want you to check on me.
.Good
No, yeah, I mean... sorry.
I have to go back to work
.Yes
.I'll see you later
You know she's engaged, right?
.yes
.I'm single
Weaver says Muñoz approached her.
"Holding a Hammer"
"He hit himself"
"smile at her"
Holly is calling
- Hello. - Hello
Listen, I just wanted to
apologize for last night, okay?
I shouldn't have pressed you like that
..no Me
.who should i apologize
I've been going through
some tough things lately
My company wasn't good
Well, if you can't, come to Jackson's party
At least you can bring him a gift.
If you want ideas about it, he
likes the miniature railway game.
You look weird, are you okay?
Yes, no, I'm fine.
Patient Room 817
Hello, Karl.
How do you feel today?
.(Karl)
(Carl?)
.she will die
.I will die. Everyone will die
Carl, look at me.
You are going to die
.you will die
- You're going to die! - Help
Calm patient 5150!
Tied his limbs!
!no! no
!no
!no! no! no
!no! no
!no
.was aggressive
I think it's a psychotic episode
Karl Rinken was in and
out of here several times
He has never shown
any aggressive behaviour.
Do you mean I'm making this up?
Of course not, but yesterday was
one of your..patients you are caring for
She brutally killed herself in front of you
Is it possible that when I assumed
that Rinken... was a danger to himself
And your brain reacted to this?
I might assume I underestimated
the situation and overreacted
.Good
So, here's what happens
You will take a week off with pay
Morgan, it's not necessary.
You worked 80 hours a week for a month
I'm afraid you haven't had enough sleep.
We can't help these patients
unless our mental health is healthy
It is in the interest of loneliness for
you. Take a week off to clear your mind
Do whatever you have to do
to get your focus back, okay?
Children's model train shop
"Are you coming home soon?"
Trever: Sorry, I'm still stuck at work.
I hope you had a better day today.
.the curse
Welcome?
This security company "First Line".
May I have your name and passcode?
I'm Rose Cotter
"Acapulco"
The door alarm has been triggered.
Yes, the back door to my house is open.
Are you alone at home, ma'am?
.Yes
Are you sure?
What?
Are you sure you didn't
let anyone in, Rose?
Look behind you
Welcome?
This security company "First Line".
May I have your name and password?
We searched the house inside
and out. We didn't find anything
How about the back door?
Was it possibly left open the
last time you tried to close it?
.I do not know, maybe
Listen, you don't have to worry about
it. False alarms happen all the time
If something comes up, call us.
.Good
Good evening, sir
.Good evening
what happened?
Mustache?
".mustache"
So, is there a reason for
you to sound the alarm?
I don't really remember doing that
I must have fired it
unintentionally or something
unintentionally?
.sorry
My head was like this
Confused, turbulent and
distracted..mind all day long and
Then a strange incident occurred at work
..and then my boss asked me to take
.sorry
.everything is fine
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm fine. I was
expressing my feelings.
.Good
Can you search for herty "Mustache"?
I couldn't find it anywhere.
.yes
(Rose, did you break another glass?)
Mustache?
.Come
"mustache"
He looks like different people
Sometimes he pretends to be someone else.
And sometimes it looks weird, and sometimes
And sometimes he looks like my grandfather
Who died in front of me
when I was 7 years old
But it's all the same
.smiles at me
It's not a friendly smile, the
worst smile I've ever seen
And when I see her
I have a terrible feeling that
something terrible is going to happen
!My God. no
!no
No, he's here!
.I beg you
!step away! no
I have a patient in an emergency
situation. In Room No. 2
I need the crew to come
here right now. quickly
(Lura)?)
.(Day)
!(Day)
(Day)?)
!(Day)! (Day)
What the hell is this, Rose?
Rose, put the knife down!
!(Day)
.Welcome
(Day)?)
This is a surprise
It's not about her blood.
..it's about
. in her face
The look she was giving her
How did it make you feel?
Feeling clearly awful
.Weakness
.guilt
Guilt?
She was my patient
She was a troubled young woman
The one you only met for 10 minutes.
Yes, I'm just
I feel like it's stuck in my mind
I can't get it out of my head.
Have you ever thought about
why it's stuck in your mind?
Could it actually relate
to your mother's suicide?
Do you still blame yourself?
..listen
I really don't want to try to
discuss..this part of my life right now, so
What do you want to talk?
..I was hoping to
Get Risperdal's recipe
since that happened
..with the patient, me
I see things
And I hear things
I'm sure it's post-traumatic
stress disorder
Let's move away from self-diagnosis
What did you see and hear?
Memories of what happened with my patient
..she looks
Hallucinations about moments of tension
But when that happens, it seems
tangible and
.worrying
Rose, I guess it doesn't look
like I have delusions or ailments.
And definitely not delusional
My impression is that what
you encountered with your patient
Raised old anxiety with a
lot of stress and lack of sleep
You have wounds that have not fully healed
And maybe these wounds never heal
This is the nature of shock
But you can learn how to control it
Did you keep seeing patients
while you were dealing with all this?
.no
.I'm on vacation
.Good
If you want my advice, use this
time to get busy with different things
I do anything.
It distracts your mind from the
things that cause this tension
..I also think it will be useful
If we resume our regular sessions again
.naturally
What about Risperdal?
..i
Let's talk again next week,
before thinking about medication
Meanwhile, you can always call me.
.naturally
I ordered a white wine drink.
.My God
- God, you were able to come. - Hello
!Surprise
.Please come in
I thought you were at work
- I decided to take an evening vacation.
- I'll take this for you
Hey Greg, what are you doing?
I haven't asked for it yet.
.My God
I have to go get it sorted
out with my idiot husband.
Show my sister moisturizers. Adults, please
We have a cache in the kitchen. come
Hey, you're a psychotherapist, right?
.Yes
Fabulous! May I have some advice?
!happy Birthday to You
birthday
.amazing
Thanks, Harper. Thank
you, Harper, my mom's friend.
This is a gift from Aunt Rose.
Open it!
Come on, open it!
What did you get dear?
..no
- No! - Oh, my God!
“No, no.” Mustache
what is wrong with you?
It's not real.
"mustache"
.No no
.no. I swear, it wasn't me
.It was not me. I swear
Please believe me.
No one believes me
Who the hell are you?!
Leave me alone!
Do you see it?
You must see it
Holly, say you see someone.
.I beg you
pain assessment tool
Hello, Rose
.the curse
I heard you entered the emergency
room, I came to check on you, how are you?
.Fine
It was just an accident. Thanks
They said you had a panic attack
Rose, I'll be honest with
you. I'm worried about you
I mean this as a friend but I
really think you should see a doctor
Are you seeing a psychiatrist now?
Are you listening, Rose?
"no pain"
.wait
I want you to tell you something.
..I want you to know
I'm not crazy, okay?
.Good
..there is something
.happens to me
And it'd be hard for you to really believe.
.Maybe we should go in
No, listen to me
.sorry
Really sorry
..Good
There is something threatening me
..it's like
.evil spirit or force
I really don't know what it is
..but
But I think he killed my patient.
She described that she was suffering
from the same thing before her death
..and now somehow
He tied himself to me
..And
.afraid that something bad will happen
I really want you to say something.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to believe me
Now you're talking about a ghost.
No, it's not a ghost.
It's something else.
.Good
.Sorry
.I can not
I can't do this now
No. (Trever
Hey, Trevor. Do Not Enter
I want you.. that you
don't listen to what I say
- All right? - Well, (Rose .)
What am I supposed to reply now?
Do you listen to yourself?
You're talking crazy things.
I'm not crazy
.sorry
But it's hereditary, right?
What?
.mental occupation
It can be inherited from both parents
- You inquired about that.
- Why did you inquire about that?
..because I
I wanted to know what I might have been
associated with for the rest of my life
Is this unfair?
I'm going into the house
No, Trever, my life is in danger
..(Day)
Did you kill Mustache? - No
No, it wasn't me.
So, tell me what happened.
There was something
Trever, please.
.I beg you
Witness Laura Weaver's testimony document.
Professor (Gabriel Muñoz),
"Saint Agatha's College"
(Gabriel Muñoz)
A professor at Saint Agatha College
ends his life in front of a student
.(Day)
.Come here
Darling
.please help me
Your mom made a mistake
.no no no
.No no
!(Day)
!what is wrong with you? Are you crazy?
.sorry
Mrs. Muñoz?
I first noticed it .some changes
Then it all happened so quickly
He was nervous
.panicked
He would wake up in the
middle of the night and scream
I've never heard him
scream like that before.
Then he stopped sleeping completely.
I noticed him talking to himself
He was seeing things
He does weird things that
he doesn't seem to remember
Then one morning he disappeared
That night, the police called
And they told me he died
They asked me to identify his body
.face
Twenty-five years of marriage.
This is what I remember of him
.I am very sorry
Did Gabriel ever describe
the things he was seeing?
.I will show you
..I have to remove all of these
But I can't stand being here.
This is what Gabriel said he sees
He was always saying
this. He's trying to get into it
That's Gabriel's brother
He died in an accident 20 years ago.
Gabriel never recovered from this.
Since when did this happen?
Since returning from that conference,
which he participates in every year
Because he saw a terrible
woman commit suicide
But no one reported it.
Did he see someone commit suicide?
.yes
- I thought you knew that.
- What was her name?
I don't remember, I have to find it
have you ever
To mention why all this happened?
Did he find an explanation for all this?
Which correspondence are you?
Mrs. Muñoz, your husband wasn't crazy
The things he was seeing were real.
I see it
What, are you a psychopath?
What?
Obsessed with?
How dare you?
No, please. What happened
to your husband happens to me
Get out of the house! I want
you out of my house now!
Mrs. Muñoz, just give me the name, please
Get out of my house!
.the curse
yes?
.Welcome
.come in
You finally got rid of that yellow couch
So how are you?
Surely you didn't come
here..to share news based on
Rough show a few days ago
I want a favor
I want you to not ask questions about this.
.Fabulous. Yes. tell me what it is
Nine days ago
A man named (Gabriel
Muñoz) committed suicide
..I want to know if
Involved in other recent police reports
Can you find out from here for me?
Really, are you serious?
It's my only day off.
Go to the police station
Jules, please.
.Good
Yeah, damn it
What is his name again?
(Gabriel Muñoz)
Well, this is a report of his death.
Yes, another report..a week ago
From the state police station
What was it about?
It was a witness statement
He was staying in a hotel in
which a woman committed suicide
Well, what was that woman's name?
(Angela Powell)
She was a real estate agent
What is this?
.the curse
What is the matter?
It's a picture from the scene.
Let me see it
.no
- Let me see her. - No
You can't see this.
It's part of the evidence.
Or no, you can see it.
.fuck
I warned you, it's disgusting.
.Good
I want you to do the same search again
But this time about that woman, Angela
Could you tell me what all this is, please?
Jules, you promised not
to ask me any questions
No, it was you who asked
me to ask you any questions
Jules, I need your help.
Good?
.I beg you
There was a previous report
submitted. Four days before death.
It's a strange coincidence
She was also questioned
about a .suicide case
What is this? Is this a video file?
It's a CCTV video.
His job
He just endures.
What the hell?
My day was going well
Would you turn it back on? Really?
Play it back, Jules
What is this?
Is he smiling?
Rose, who are these people?
.I have to go
Where are you going?
(Rose, where are you going?)
what is going on? I'm confused now
Do me another favor.
Do you have a printer?
(Trever?)
Are you here, Trevor?
.Welcome
Hello, Rose
What is this?
What are you doing here? I
just wanted to make sure of you
I was talking to my fiancé
.I called her
Why?
..because of you
You were really acting crazy.
..no
I didn't know what to do
are you kidding me?
I turn to you because you are supposed
to be the most trusted person in the world
And I admitted that I was very scared.
And I needed you
Except you didn't listen to me
No, why do you think I called her?
All I'm trying to do is help you
No, all you're trying to do is
put the responsibility on others.
You have no problem as long as
everything is easy and acceptable
But, God forbid, if it was
anything serious or difficult
..and only you
You will think about how this will
destroy your whole ideal life plan
Hey, are you really serious now?
.Yes
If that's how you feel,
why are we even together?
.Maybe I do not know
..why not everyone take a breath and
Don't act like home is your home!
(Rose, are you really leaving now?)
- (Greg. - (Rose), what are you doing here?
Is Holly here? .I want to talk to her
I don't think it's a good idea
Greg, I want to talk to
my sister! (Okay? (Holly .)
You come here and talk to me like that?
Holly, can I talk to you for a moment?
- I don't think she should be here.
- Can I talk to you?
Honestly, it's not a good idea.
- It's okay. (- (Holly .)
- Go inside. - All right
.My God
.Well Well
how are you?
I realize it all now
I was cursed
.My God
Or somehow it ended up with me in a curse
I got it from my patient
It was announced
And when she died, she
passed the curse on me
and now that I'm facing a threat from
.entity
an entity?
He's the one who killed Mustache
And he was at the Christmas party
yesterday but you couldn't see him
No one can see it but me
.My God
No, Holly
I know it's hard to believe.
And I know it was hard for
me. I believe him from the start
Look at this
.My God
Why do you have these pictures?
Because this happened to other people.
- And then they all died. (- (Rose .)
Holly, I'll be next.
Curses aren't real.
..that you kind of suffer from
.nervous breakdown
What?
No, Holly.
You don't listen to me
- You don't listen to me. - (Rose
This is exactly what
happened to our mother.
This looks like it
How did you know this?
Sorry .. what?
You weren't there when my mom got sick
Where were you really when she died?
I don't know what you're talking about
Because I was the older sister, I
suffered worse than my mother's madness.
I had to leave home because it's
the only way to go on with my life
and sorry
Because I left you alone
That's your confusion
I know it wasn't fair. I wish I
could do something about it.
Because I tried so hard..to
move on with my life
And leave all this nonsense behind, okay?
..And you
You can't accept the fact that my mom
lost her mind and committed suicide.
And you let this take over your whole life. And
you blame me because I don't want that either.
Sorry I'm actually..I'm
trying to help people
Instead of being a grumbling
housewife stuck at home
She lives in her arrogant, selfish bubble
- Well. - I don't know why I said that
I won't go into this.
I'm not going to get into this with you.
You totally shocked Jackson, okay?
I can't fight anything with
you while you're like this
.the curse
(Holly?)
(Joule)?)
Why didn't you tell me there was a
connection between your illness and others?
.After you left, I inquired about it.
These cases have a pattern.
One is getting more and more
So far, 20 cases have been
found, including 19 suicide cases
It is a direct chain.
And the things these people
do to themselves, Rose, are ugly
Hey, you said 20 cases, but
only 19 of them are suicide
One of the cases did not follow the pattern
He's an accountant, Robert Talley
His co-worker committed
suicide in front of him
And after four days of
that..(I present (Tali .)
Suddenly killing a woman
he had never met in his life
And here it is, a week later
An eyewitness who witnessed a crime.
The murder committed suicide as well.
The pattern is repeating itself
Is he alive? - Yes
He is in Altoona prison
Jules, I have to talk to him.
- I want you to say something.
- Yes, I'll do that
..just... just
Give me a moment.. I mean, oh my God
I thought you'd say it's just
Suicide cult and blackmail conspiracy
..I mean that this
Hey, Jules
.Good
Just let's rule out the possibility
The presence of an evil
spirit or supernatural forces
What you are saying is that
there is..something is moving
From one person to another...
and make them kill themselves
Well, maybe it's not suicides.
What do you mean?
My patient, Laura, was terrified
But she didn't intend to commit suicide.
And then at the end,
everything about her changed
as if it's
The person I was talking to has disappeared
..and there is one more thing
.have it
He's like that guy
.Yes
- On the surveillance camera that...
- Yeah, exactly like that
Oh my God, what the hell is this?
..in the cases I found
How long was the time
between each victim and another?
No one survived for more than a week
Some of them did not even exceed four days
Today is my fourth day
Whatever happened to these
people, it won't happen to you
.I promise you
"Translation by Dr. Ali Talal"
"correctional prison"
Let the guard go to Gate 3
.Thanks
Open the door, they have a pass.
"No talking in the hallway"
I'll owe you this, Doug
You two are fortunate that he refuses
to even meet his assigned lawyer.
You know what this guy did, right?
Dr. Kotter specializes in
psychological profiling in cases like this
Well, Tally is totally insane.
So, good luck
I'll give you 10 minutes with him, okay?
Longer than this period.
Requires a court order
.I appreciate that
No contact during the visit.
Sir. Tully. My name is Rose Cotter
..me, you know
I hope you know the
answer to a few questions
.لا تسأليني أيّ أسئلة .لقد اعترفت
في الواقع لست مهتمة .بما اتهمت به
..ما أريد معرفته هو
ما الذي واجهته في الأيام
.التي سبقت ارتكابك الجريمة
..كان لديّ مريضة
.امرأة شابة
..قبل أربعة أيام ثمة رجل
.أنتحر أمامها
..منذ ذلك الحين، إنها بدأت
.ترى شيء ما
شيء يتجسد بهيئة .أشخاص آخرين
..والرجل الذي رأته ينتحر
.كان يدعي أنه يرى ذات الشيء
ما الذي تريدينه مني بحق الجحيم؟
ـ ما هو؟ .ـ لا اعرف
.لا أعرف
لمَ الجميع الذين رأوا الشيء
ماتوا وأنت لا زلت حيًا؟
.لماذا؟ أرجوك
سيّد (تالي)، يمكنك مساعدتها، حسنًا؟
.أرجوك
.اطلبي من الشرطي المغادرة
.هذا لن يحدث
اطلبي منه المغادرة .وسأخبركِ بما اعرفه
.(جول)، ارجوك)
.سأنتظر في الخارج
حاولت جاهدًا البحث عن
كل .شيء يتعلق بذلك الشيء
كانت هناك سلسلة آخرى .في الماضي
"وجدت واحدة في" البرازيل .قبل بضعة أعوام
ثمة رجل هناك تخطى ..تلك السلسلة
من خلال قتل جاره وانتقل
.ذلك الشيء إلى زوجة جاره
..ستموت مريضتكِ
.ما لم تقتل شخصًا
إنها الطريقة الوحيدة .للتخلص من ذلك
.the only way
You have to make sure that
there is a witness to move him
Because this thing spreads through shock.
This is what gives him strength. By shock
And your patient must make it work
Tell her to use a weapon
and make it the biggest mess
I can't kill anyone.
You?
Do you have this?
.no no no
Why did you come here?
I won't let this come back to me.
- Go away! - Sorry!
Get out of here!
Get her away from me!
Hey
.Wait
What happened? - Nothing
What did he say?
.no thing
no thing?
He's totally crazy
Dr. Madeleine Northcott is calling.
Trevor: Where are you?
We should talk. Are you home?
.the curse
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry if we surprised
you yesterday. It was wrong.
.sorry
.Yes, you should go.
()Day)
We both know that I have a
responsibility..to report to the authorities
If you pose a danger to yourself or others
And I want you to convince
me that you're not a danger.
He reminded Trevor of a ghost
I didn't use the word 'ghost'
.evil soul. Paranormal
I confessed to him that I see things
The same things I told you
But I don't see her anymore, okay?
It was stress and lack of sleep.
I wished him so. Seems like a mistake
But that's it, okay?
Are we in agreement?
How do you feel today?
..let me think
I'm pretty sure my fiancé thinks me crazy
And my sister kept me
out of her life completely
..and now
My previous treatment is
conducting an unannounced home visit
To make sure I'm not a danger.
..so
Otherwise, I'm really fine.
Won't you answer the phone?
What?
(Rose), it's Madeleine.
I've been trying to reach you all morning
I'm so worried about
what happened yesterday.
(Rose)? - No
Do you still hear me?
Welcome?
- No. - (Rose)?
.No no
Time is running out for you, Rose
Who the hell are you?
.no
.No no
.no no no
.no
Hello, Dr. Cotter
Aren't you supposed to be on vacation?
I came to get something from my office
(Karl). Welcome)
- No, no. - It's okay
.no no no
- It's okay. - Oh my God
- Calm down. - No, no
!silent
calm down, okay?
.(Day)
What are you doing here?
.I do not know
Rose, you can't get close to the sick.
Damn it, Rose!
!the curse
(Rose, what are you doing here?)
.no thing
..I don't know
..I don't know why me
Why don't we go in together and talk?
!no
It's not safe
Rose, I don't think you should.
You should be alone now.
I want you to be alone
I have to be alone.
Sorry, I have to go.
Listen, Rose, I don't think
you should go anywhere, okay?
Just calm down. I'll make a call
Rose, don't go anywhere!
Rose, please, don't go anywhere. Wait
Rose, wait! (Rose)
Jules is calling
.(joules)
There is a circular to all police
patrols about being a danger.
What the hell happened?
I know what I'm doing
This thing he wants from all his victims
To pass it on to someone else
But if no one sees it, you
won't pass on to anyone
As long as I'm on my own,
I'll prevent this from happening
.it does not make sense
Do you intend to avoid people forever?
I'm not going to run away yet, okay?
I have to face him
Well, Rose, I'm coming
to you..just tell me.
Jules is calling
.(Day)
..Darling
.please help me
Your mother made a mistake
.that phone
.Call for help
!(Day)
.(Day)
It's okay dear
come close
.I'm so sorry
I wasn't a good mother
I wanted to be too
I really tried to be.
..but sometimes
.everything is burdened
There is something horrible inside of me.
- I hate myself. - Stop it
stop. stop
Do you feel ashamed of me?
.no
Why did you let me die?
Why didn't you save me?
It's not my fault.
You could have asked for help
stop. stop
- But you didn't call. - Stop it
.and i wish i was dead
Because I was afraid of you.
I was 10 years old
.You were wild
And I know it wasn't fair
That you needed help.
But I couldn't.
You took the guilt
all my life
I have to get rid of this
It's not real.
(But oh (Rose .)
Your brain makes it real
What are you?
Why do you do this to me?
..because your mind
.Very attractive
You can't escape your mind, Rose.
It's a
.it's my mind
And you can't escape from it either
.the curse
are you OK?
May I come in for a moment?
.Yes Yes
where have you been?
.I'm sorry
..sorry because I
I pushed you into all my mess
for most of my life
..I was afraid
to get people close to me
..because I was afraid
What would they see if they looked closely?
So, I put barriers around me
.and keep people away from me
and then
your ability and
And it felt like those
barriers were collapsing
And it scared me so much.
, so
I was selfish
And he wasn't fair to you
.and I'm so sorry
And I'm being selfish again,
..when I ask this but do you think
..May I stay here
just sleep?
Can you
Stay with me while I sleep?
.I beg you
Yes, of course, I'll stay with you.
.I will stay with you forever
.no
.no no no
!(Day)
Rose, open the door.
.open the door
!(Day)
!no
.the curse
Rose, I'm coming!
!no
.(Day)
(Day)?)