A NETFLIX SERIES
-[clock ticking]
-[birds chirping]
[baby coos]
[Julia] Merry Christmas!
-[screaming]
-[Núria] Oh.
[Julia] It's Christmas!
-[Núria shushes]
-[Albert] Christmas? What do you mean?
-[Albert] The Tió!
-[kids yell]
[Albert] The Tió's not fat enough yet.
Huh?
Last night it grew so big!
-Big, big, big, big!
-Oh really?
-Ariel, it's okay, honey.
-[Albert] All right, let's go see.
-[children cheer]
-[Albert] Oh my God.
-[mellow swing music playing]
-♪ Hark! The herald angels sing ♪
♪ Glory to the newborn king ♪
♪ Peace on earth and mercy mild ♪
HAPPY HOLIDAYS!
♪ God and sinners reconciled ♪
♪ Joyful all ye nations rise ♪
♪ Join the triumph of the skies… ♪
[Dolo] Well, done.
These are pretty, huh? These napkins.
-I bought them from Mercedes. Yesterday.
-They're beautiful.
♪ Hark! The herald angels sing… ♪
This should be fine. Here.
-[doorbell rings]
-[Patri] Ahh!
-Oh…
-[sighs]
-Just hurry up. Come inside.
-Merry Christmas, pigeon.
[doorbell rings]
Eli's here! Merry Christmas.
[both] Mwah!
-Come on. Now everyone's here!
-[Vero] Hell yes!
[Bruno] Hey! Oh, you're so cute.
Oh, with your little ears, huh?
-Here, Puchusky. Puchusky!
-[shutter clicking]
That's it. Look, buddy.
Look! Who is this?
Who is this, huh?
You couldn't be more handsome. [kisses]
[doorbell rings]
[woman] Hi, beautiful.
-Merry Christmas.
-Merry Christmas. Hi, sweetheart.
-[woman] Hey!
-[Sunyer] Hi!
♪ Christ is born in Bethlehem ♪
♪ Hark! The herald angels sing ♪
♪ Glory to the newborn king ♪
♪ To the newborn king ♪
♪ The angels swing ♪
♪ With the newborn king ♪
[song ends]
[cell phone chimes]
[holiday music plays]
-Here you go, Mom. The nougat.
-[chuckles]
And Ramiro you already know.
Sorry about the other day.
I didn't know how to bring it up.
No worries. My mother explained.
-Merry Christmas.
-Hey, thank you.
You only brought three?
Jijona, chocolate,
and egg yolk, like always.
Yeah, but there are more of us today.
We might be short.
Did you get the polvorones?
Relax, there's always too much food.
Come on. Sit down.
I'll take care of the soup.
Mom, did you put the galets in?
[Rosa] Wait. What's the rush?
We're not all here yet.
Would you like a vermouth?
Who isn't here?
-[doorbell rings]
-[amusing music plays]
[sighs] Don't be angry, please?
Hmm.
-[chuckles] Merry Christmas, Ms. Rosa!
-Ibra, you made it! Come in.
[Rosa] We were waiting for you.
-Oh. You didn't need to bring anything.
-[both chuckle]
-Merry Christmas, Àlex.
-Mm-hmm.
[Rosa sighs, chuckles]
Mom, wait. Mom, no. Come back.
What's happening right now?
Why is Ibra here?
Why didn't you tell me
he had no family in Barcelona?
He was going to spend Christmas
all alone, the poor thing.
I was too sad about it.
And, besides, if there's room for four
then what's five, right?
You couldn't have asked me first,
at least?
[chuckles]
When you organize Christmas at your house,
invite whoever you'd like.
-[Dolo] Absolutely.
-[Ibra] I appreciate it.
Ibra, honey, do you like zarzuela?
[Ibra] Well, I'm not a big opera fan, but…
-[Dolo laughs]
-[Rosa chuckles] Oh, you are too funny.
[clock ticking]
[Julia] Artur. Hey, stop it.
[Artur] Yeah!
[both chuckle]
-[Artur] Give it to me, okay?
-[Julia] No.
-[Artur] Yes!
-[Julia] No, Artur…
And why don't you spend Christmas
with your parents, Bruno?
Uh, uh… Well, it's complicated.
We don't have the best relationship.
-[Sunyer] Ah, I see.
-Ah.
[Albert] Anyone want a salmon snack?
[both] Yeah!
[Albert] Okay, come on.
Go wash your hands.
[woman and Sunyer chuckle]
-[chuckles]
-Has Lis told you about the next meeting?
Salvador, we agreed no work talk.
-I know, but it's getting urgent.
-[sighs]
We're presenting the Arnau Theater
to the council next week already and…
-With Ramón being, well, gone, it's--
-Will he still be on leave?
No, no, no. He's not on leave.
He's left the studio.
[somber music plays]
-He what?
The day after we had the Christmas party,
he told me he didn't belong there.
I don't know what happened,
but he sounded very upset.
We've lost one of our
very best architects.
And I found her… asleep on the street
in the middle of the winter.
You serious?
-Of course not!
-[all chuckle]
Do you have to tell it as if
it were a Victorian novel or what?
-Let her tell it, then!
-But she never tells it the right way.
My parents couldn't stand that
I was a lesbian, so I disappeared.
But I didn't end up being homeless.
I had some friends
that would let me crash for a night.
She used to sleep
in highway service stations.
-Take it easy. It was only one night.
-[Javi] Sure…
-They left me stranded, all right?
-And on Christmas Eve?
-Mmm.
-[Vero] Yes, girl, yes.
And, ever since that night,
Javi and I spend Christmas together.
Well, Christmas
and the whole year, really.
This one and I have been trotting together
longer than the Three Wise Men's camels.
-[laughs]
-Yeah. I've regretted it every day since.
Look at her playing tough on Christmas.
That's Vero.
-Anyone want more wine?
-I'm in.
[Patri] I'll get the stew.
[doorbell rings]
Are you waiting for another lover?
-Mmm.
-[Javi chuckles]
-Surprise! Oh!
-Surprise!
-[man] Honey, this is the wrong floor.
-No, she said 3-2.
See, I told you.
-Double check before you ring the bell.
-You wrote it down. 3-2. Look.
Call your daughter
and ask her to sort this out.
If I do that, honey,
we'll ruin the surprise.
Well, honey, if you don't call her,
it won't be a surprise either,
since we have the wrong address, and we'll
spend all day lost in this place.
-[man] Sorry.
-[woman] Go on. Call her.
-[Patri] Mom!
-Oh! My darling!
-[Patri] Dad!
-[woman] Oh! My little girl!
Oh, honey. Oh, my sweet girl.
-Oh! [kisses]
-You're here!
Oh, you're so beautiful.
Oh, I wanted to see you, my angel.
-Let me hold you.
-[Patri] Yeah…
-Hi, Dad.
-I love you, my dear!
You know that two months ago
we bought these tickets,
and we were supposed to get in last night,
but the airport was chaos.
We were delayed.
I wanted to tell you we were coming,
but he wouldn't let me.
The surprise was all her idea.
I swear. I was dying every time we talked
and I couldn't tell you. I was suffering.
I was lying to my own daughter. Oh my God.
-But, anyway…
-[Patri chuckles]
Now we'll spend Christmas together
just like we did when you were little.
-Oh, my darling.
-[Patri] Uh, um…
-[woman] Oh, my girl! Oh!
-It's okay, no.
And where do our things go?
Huh?
Our suitcases, our bags.
You're gonna stay here?
-[woman] Of course, my love, where else?
-[man] Yes.
Yeah, sure.
-Uh, there's only one room, though.
-[Patri] Mm-hmm.
-And who are you?
-[Patri] This is, uh…
This is a… a friend… of mine.
[chuckles nervously]
-[Patri] We're all friends here.
-[woman] Ah.
Um, this is Vero. [chuckles]
-[woman] Nice to meet you.
-Uh, Eli and Javi.
-We're all celebrating Christmas.
Oh, how beautiful.
But hold on. No!
[woman gasps] Is this… But this is… Oh!
This is the stew we make back home.
-Did you make it? Oh my goodness.
-Mm-hmm.
Make room for another one then, honey.
Oh, thank you so much. That's wonderful.
-Well then, when do we start lunch?
-Yes! Uh, I'll get an extra chair.
Excuse me.
[lively music plays]
-[chuckles]
-[music stops]
[Rosa] And how long have you lived here?
I was born in the Canary Islands,
but I've lived in Barcelona for years.
[Rosa] Oh.
My mother was pregnant
when she arrived on a cayuco.
-She almost died.
-Coming from where?
-Nouadhibou in Mauritania.
-[Ramiro blows air]
-But they came from Senegal.
-That's hundreds of miles.
[Dolo] Oh my! Poor dear.
What about your father?
He was deported.
My mother didn't want to leave him,
but… they decided she should stay
so I could have a future in Spain.
They were apart for 15 years.
My mother always said
that seeing him again
was what made her get up every morning,
and that, eventually,
that day would be here.
Because there was an invisible,
unbreakable thread tying them together.
-[Rosa] How beautiful!
-[Dolo] That's lovely.
It's an ancient Japanese story
that says there's an invisible red thread
that binds people
who are destined for each other.
[wistful music plays]
-[Ramiro] Where are they now?
-[Ibra] In Dakar.
They saved money to buy a house
and went back.
I go see them when I can,
but, it's true,
the gay issue in Senegal is…
It's clear I belong here.
It's important to find
where your place is in the world.
[plate clinks]
I'll check on that zarzuela.
I HEARD YOU LEFT THE FIRM. ARE YOU OKAY?
[woman] We saw this one last night.
It's on every Christmas Eve.
There's a man that wishes
he had never been born. Uh…
It's a Wonderful Life, Frank Capra.
-Ah, that's it.
-[Bruno] Yeah.
It's beautiful.
Kids, kids.
Did you know that, when a bell rings,
it means that an angel
has just earned its wings? [chuckles]
Mom, don't talk about religion
to the kids.
-We're discussing cinema.
-[Bruno] Uh-huh.
[Núria] Well…
They don't make Christmas movies
like they did.
Uh, well, true.
They're no longer as fashionable
as they were in the golden age.
What's fashionable… are Christmas values.
-At least not the way they used to be?
-[chuckles]
-Dad, stop.
-Hey, it's all right.
I'm not talking about religion, honey.
I'm talking about generosity,
and family, and love.
But real love, the kind that lasted
a lifetime… and solved all problems.
Not like nowadays, when young people are…
-[cell phone buzzes]
-…too quick to quit
or get caught up
looking for something better.
DON'T WORRY. HAPPY HOLIDAYS.
Well, no, I don't agree at all,
to be honest.
Love Actually, for example.
Right, Bruno? Love Actually.
-Huh? Bruno!
-Hmm?
[Albert] Love Actually,
a modern, very good movie.
[woman] It's beautiful.
There are stories about
all the types of love that there are.
Well, all types… except homosexual ones,
which are nowhere to be seen.
Well, I mean,
there are other movies for that.
-[Núria] Mom.
-Ehh…
-What did I say now? [chuckles]
-[breathes deeply]
What's your favorite
Christmas movie, then?
Uh…
I don't have one.
I don't really like romantic comedies.
[sighs]
[Vero] A friend?
A friend? Are you fucking kidding?
Fuck. Look.
They just walked through the door.
I can't let them find out like this.
That's perfect. Except, what do we do now?
'Cause they wanna stay here.
That's right. Shit, the photos!
-[Patri panting]
-[Vero] You're not…
Are you fucking kidding me?
-Patri. Listen to me, for fuck's sake.
-Give it to me.
You and I aren't the ones
who have to hide. Don't you see?
It'll just be a couple of days.
Just a few days and they're gone.
And what do I do until then? Huh?
Just cease to exist magically, now, huh?
I don't know. Stay in the new apartment.
That works, right?
Wait, you want me to spend Christmas
with no heat and alone?
[Patri muffled] I'm not kicking you out.
The only thing I'm asking you is--
[Vero muffled] To what? Leave!
-[Patri] That doesn't matter.
-[Vero] It does!
Look, stay with Àlex,
or-- or go to Javi's. I don't know.
I don't believe this. My girlfriend
is kicking me out of my own house?
-No.
-On Christmas?
-[Patri] It isn't that I don't…
-Here.
[Vero] But I left because I wanted to…
Hey! Why don't we play
some Christmas music, yeah?
[Patri] I just need…
Ah, this one. This one is very moving.
-Ah! Yeah.
-[speaker beeps] Connected.
["Dime, Niño, ¿De Quién Eres?" plays]
-[lip-synching]
-[in Spanish] ♪ Tell me, child ♪
[lip-synching]
♪ Whose are you ♪
♪ All dressed in white ♪
♪ Tell me, child ♪
♪ Whose are you? ♪
♪ All dressed in white ♪
♪ I am the Virgin Mary's son ♪
-Stop.
-What are you afraid of?
Your parents aren't just
gonna stop loving you if they know.
You don't know them.
No. They're the ones who don't know you.
They haven't even been
part of your life for years.
If they turn their back on you
for being who you are, then fuck them.
I can't do that, okay?
Stop it, Vero! And just leave me alone!
[song continues faintly]
When we decided to be open,
do you remember what the first rule was?
Stop lying to each other.
And you proposed it.
Well, you'd better stop
lying to yourself, then,
because, if not,
what the fuck are we doing here?
[Álex] Mmm. That smells good.
It should. Caught fresh yesterday.
-Mmm, you don't say.
-[chuckles]
[Ramiro talking indistinctly]
You're not happy that he's here, are you?
-Your boyfriend?
-[scoffs] No, he's not my boyfriend.
That's a shame.
He's so nice and has been through a lot.
No, I meant Ramiro.
What happened, huh?
Ask your mother.
Mom said they were good friends,
and that one day he left
without an explanation.
Well, if that's what she told you,
that's what happened.
Oh, come on.
Just tell me what it is,
because you've been dying to for days.
[Dolo huffs]
[Dolo] Ramiro didn't leave just any day.
He left right after you were born.
Why'd he do that?
He never admitted it, but he was always
in love with your mother.
Since they were kids.
-Ah, so they were sweethearts.
-No.
She always saw him as a friend,
but… they were inseparable.
They did everything together.
To the point that she was never interested
in any other guys.
She said Ramiro gave her
everything she needed, but then
she met your father.
-[somber music plays]
-Now one of you two. [chuckles]
-Hold still… Smile.
-[shutter clicks]
[Dolo] Your mother always says that
those were the happiest years of her life.
People in the neighborhood
used to ask me if she had two boyfriends.
Can you imagine?
[Rosa] Oh!
[all exclaim]
[laughs]
-Ah.
-Ah!
[Dolo] But when he realized
that she really loved your father,
everything changed.
Love can build many things.
But it destroys much more
when it's not reciprocated.
That's why he left.
What's the matter with trying again?
'Cause Mom looks really happy to me.
Ramiro hurt her badly,
disappearing like that.
He wasn't there for her
when your father passed away.
And now he's back and wants us
to pretend none of it ever happened?
I'm sorry, but it doesn't seem right.
And are you more into the Three Wise Men
or… or maybe Santa Claus?
I'm more into Tió de Nadal.
Mmm. What's that?
-You don't know?
-[woman] No.
-It's a delicious Catalan tradition.
-[woman] Mmm.
During the entire month of December,
little kids adopt a log.
-A log?
-A log. Mm-hmm.
-They feed it tangerines to fatten it up.
-Mm.
And on Christmas Day
they hit it with sticks
to make it shit out their gifts.
[whispers] From its asshole.
[both chuckle]
[doorbell rings]
I'll get it. I'll go.
[chuckles]
-[gasps] Flor.
-Merry Christmas!
Come in. Come in.
-[Patri] No!
-[chair scrapes]
Patri! You're gonna give me
a heart attack.
Sorry. It's just
I didn't think we'd see Flor today.
What a surprise! She's here!
[chuckles nervously]
-Oh, hey.
-Well, Flor, what a beautiful name!
I'm Patricia's mother.
Are you a friend of hers?
Yes of Patri's and Vero's.
-In fact, we are--
-You're Javier's girlfriend!
[laughing loudly]
[stops laughing]
Um…
Flor! Hi, honey!
Thank goodness you were able to come.
I thought I wouldn't see you.
-Give me a kiss. It's so good to see you.
-Aw.
[Javi] I'm happy you're here.
Sit down, dear. Are you hungry? Huh?
Our good friend Patri will go
make something for you to eat now.
How's your dad?
[Vero swallows loudly]
I think that Ramón resigned because of me.
The day of the party, he kissed me.
But I was a little rude.
-You're an idiot.
-What should I have done?
What do you mean?
Look, Ramón is perfect for you, Bruno.
-You have everything in common.
-So you've said.
Is he a little nerdy? Yeah.
But so are you, man.
Don't fuck with me.
You're like a fucking walking IMDb.
Don't be crazy. We're not that similar.
But, what? You and Mr. Two Gyms are?
[wistful music plays]
He's a paleontologist, very intelligent.
She's a brat, really annoying.
Yeah, but I saw it when I was a kid.
There was this lion?
-No, a leopard.
-Oh, well, close enough.
To calm him down,
they sang the song. Oh, what was it?
Uh… Uh…
-♪ I can't give you an… ♪
-Uh… Um…
-♪ Anything but… but love, baby ♪
-♪ Anything but love, baby ♪
Yeah, that's right, yeah.
[both chuckle]
[Albert sighs]
You might not like Ramón
because the two of you are so alike.
And, if you don't like yourself,
how can you like him? Huh?
What are you channeling RuPaul or what?
[chuckles] Hey, wait.
I'm sorry. No, I didn't…
I didn't mean that.
No, it's just…
That's what Àlex said
the night that we met.
[glass clinking]
[Sunyer] Family!
Gather around.
We have an announcement to make.
Come on. It's fitting for the occasion.
The occasion? [chuckles]
We wanted everything to be organized, but…
-[woman chuckles]
-Your mother and I are tying the knot.
-Again?
-[Sunyer] Mm-hmm.
He means that we are renewing our vows.
-Ah!
-[woman] Yes.
Afterwards we'll take a trip.
To where? To Paris, Cancun, or… Where to?
Around the world, for one year.
-Or… maybe two. [chuckles]
-[woman] Or maybe two.
Are you kidding?
You don't need us any longer.
Before we get too old--
-[woman] Well…
-Well, we want to make the most of it.
-[woman] Mmm.
-[kisses]
And, if you reach our age together,
then you'll understand.
I'm sorry, but… [chuckles nervously]
What about the company?
Mmm.
I think…
I'll leave it in good hands.
-[woman] Well, shall we toast? [chuckles]
-[Sunyer] Well…
-They're getting married again!
-That's right, honey. Indeed, they are.
-[woman] Cheers!
-Here's to us!
Here's to us. My dear, here's to you.
["El Noi de la Mare" plays]
[all chattering]
Oh, it's perfect. I love it.
Wow, Mom. Get over here.
[singing "Caga Tió"]
[Albert] What is it? Look at that!
["El Noi de la Mare" continues]
[dialogue imperceptible]
And he was cold
until he felt the sunshine!
Oh my. Bravo. Bravo, my love.
Amazing! That's great.
[song fades out]
Hi. Uh, merry Christmas.
Well, I suppose that you're
with your family, or…
Well, I don't know. Um…
I'm sure I'm the last one
you'd expect to hear from, but…
It's just I'm, uh… Uh…
I would like to see you.
[cell phone beeps]
[song resumes]
[song ends]
Are you partying too, Ariel?
He is so handsome, really. [chuckles]
No, it's "they."
What's that?
-[Albert] We--
-Mom, ignore it.
Albert, can you stop it?
[Sunyer] We'd better get going.
-Salvador.
-Yeah?
-You've forgotten their gift. [chuckles]
-Oh, you're right.
-If my head wasn't attached…
-Mom, we said we didn't need anything.
That's ridiculous.
-Happy holiday, kids. [chuckles]
-[Núria] Wow!
-Jesus!
-[Núria] That's huge.
-Sure is.
-[Albert] It's…
-[Núria] What is it?
-Whoa, look.
[Albert] Jesus!
-[Núria] Oh!
-[Albert] Wow.
[Núria chuckles]
-It's by Gartín Camarassa.
-[groans awkwardly]
-And he's very popular.
-[Albert] Sure…
Its force is incredible.
I mean, it's amazing. Right, Albert?
-Huh?
-[Núria] It's beautiful.
Oh, yes, it is.
We, um, appreciate it. So thanks.
We need to figure out where
we're gonna hang it, 'cause it's so… big.
Well, you can take that one down.
-I did that one.
-There you go.
It's been there for ages.
You must be sick of looking at it.
And, sorry, but if I had to choose
between yours
and an exclusive Gartín Camarassa,
it's an easy choice. Right?
Uh, sure.
Well, I mean, no, no, no.
It… We can try and hang it tomorrow,
'cause with Ariel, it's just--
-She's right. We have a lot--
-It'll only take a minute.
-Let's make sure it fits.
-[woman] Salvador.
No, but, Salvador, we need
to drill new holes--
-We'll place it, and then we'll see.
-[Ariel crying]
It'll be quick.
-[woman] Come on--
-Take Artur over there.
-[Sunyer] Come on. It'll be fine.
-[Albert] Just wait.
[Sunyer] Everyone over there.
Careful. We need room.
It's our home. Let us be the ones--
Mom, just tell him, please.
Everyone, calm down.
Just wait. You'll see.
No, Salvador, it won't--
-[all exclaim]
-[gasps, whimpers]
-[Bruno] Ah…
-[Artur gasps]
-[Sunyer] I…
-Oh…
I just…
Maybe it's not so bad, huh?
Now you have the space.
[Ariel coos]
[woman] Look at her body
when she was 12 years old.
She was already a little woman.
-[Javi] Look at you. You little model.
-[Flor] Oh, so cute!
-Poor thing, it was so hard on her.
-[Javi] I bet.
She was even teased at school.
But I told her that,
"The boobs that make you cry today
will be a gift tomorrow."
-[Javi] Amen!
-[Flor] That's right.
-[woman] And I was right.
-[Flor] Amazing.
She had a queue of suitors waiting
in front of the house, down the block.
-[slurring] She did? I didn't know that.
-[Patri] No.
So did you have a lot of boyfriends?
No, the usual amount.
The usu… Oh, the usual!
Well, she had many men after her, but only
one real boyfriend. Isn't that right?
-[Javi] Prince Charming?
-Marco Antonio.
[woman] Marco Antonio.
Marco Antonio was so cute.
They loved each other so much.
They made such a beautiful couple.
I was convinced they would get married.
But, when he proposed,
she said no and came to Barcelona.
-[Patri] I did. That's right.
-[gasps] Why, Patri?
Hmm?
Why didn't you marry
that nice guy in the end?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
And that boy hasn't stopped
thinking about her
for a single second since they broke up.
-You don't know that, my love.
-[Patri chuckles]
Well, my love, he tried.
He went and got married to another woman,
to try and forget her.
But he couldn't, and it ended.
But now… he's coming to Barcelona!
-[Javi] Oh, okay.
-[Flor] Mm.
And I'll tell you something.
The moment that boy sets foot here,
he'll be over here in a second.
-Because he wants another chance.
-[Patri chuckles] No way.
-Love is knocking on Patri's door!
-[Patri] No.
How romantic! Ohh!
-That's the most romantic thing, isn't it?
-[woman] Yes!
Let's toast. Come on. Oh…
-[Patri] No… Don't, Vero.
-[Javi] Easy.
-For Patricia!
-[Patri] Uh…
-And for Marco Antonio!
-[Patri] No.
[all] Cheers.
-[Patri] That's right.
-If it's what you've wanted all along.
-To wear a white dress.
-[chuckles nervously]
-[woman] That's right.
-Marry a nice guy.
And, of course, in church.
Hey. Why don't we sing
some carols together, huh?
-[Vero] That's her dream.
-Well, yeah!
[Javi] Come on, then.
And then buy an apartment.
[Javi]
♪ Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer-- ♪
And then have a few kids, huh?
Just like the Lord wanted!
-Yes. You said it!
-That's what we're hoping.
-[Vero] Sure, huh.
-[chuckling]
And I'm sure your parents
will be delighted, right?
Right?
Well, if that's what she wants then, yes.
[Vero laughing loudly]
[chuckling nervously]
-[Vero laughs loudly, gasps]
-Okay, Vero.
[Vero continues laughing loudly]
[Patri chuckling nervously]
The problem is
she doesn't want that at all. [laughs]
Vero. Vero, that's enough. Okay? Please.
-What's wrong, huh?
-[Javi] Come on.
It's not like I'm saying
anything wrong, okay! Calm down.
It's not my fault your parents hate you.
Stop.
[somber music plays]
[woman] Sweetheart.
Why do your parents hate you?
What is it?
[exhales]
Because I'm a lesbian, actually.
Just like all of us here.
Like Eli, like Flor.
And like your daughter.
Who also happens to be my girlfriend,
and lives here with me.
[Vero sniffles]
[gasps] Oh, one little thing,
just to clarify, hmm?
I am not a lesbian. Just gay.
[melancholy music plays]
I don't know why I'm giving you a scarf
when you run around bare-chested.
-Relax, I'm gonna wear it.
-Oh, wear it now so I can see it.
And don't just put it in the closet.
I know you.
-Bye.
-Thank you for the invitation, Ms. Rosa.
Hmm. Thank you.
-Everything was delicious.
-Mmm. And enough with the "Ms."
-Want to come tomorrow for cannelloni?
-Actually--
I think he's had enough celebrating
with our family.
-[chuckles]
-[chuckles] Thanks again.
Are you sure I can't help clean up?
-No.
-Okay.
-It's fine.
-See you tomorrow.
[Rosa chuckles]
-[Álex blows kiss]
-[Rosa sighs]
[sighs]
Leave that. I'll get it tomorrow.
No. It's no problem, Rosa, really.
I insist. You've already done the dishes,
and you're not doing any more.
-One minute. I have something for you.
-No, no more food, Rosa. I'm done.
[sighs] I'm about to burst.
Did you really think
that I wouldn't get you a gift?
[chuckles]
-[Rosa chuckling]
-[Ramiro sighs]
[chuckles] I guess
this wasn't meant for me.
-Ah, Àlex wasn't going to wear it.
-[chuckles]
Let's see how it fits.
I mean, with your big head,
it might be too small.
[chuckles]
-[Rosa sighs]
-[chuckles]
-Well, look. No.
-No?
-How do I look?
-You look… very handsome.
Hmm?
But make no mistake.
It's because you're wearing that hat.
[chuckles]
[wistful music plays]
[Rosa moans softly]
-I'm sorry.
-No, no, no, no. It's all right, Rosa.
It's all right.
[sighs]
Well, you can stay here tonight,
if you'd like.
[melancholy music plays]
[sighs]
[sighs] Rosa…
You don't know how much I appreciate
everything you're doing for me,
but this isn't what I wanted.
Oh?
Rosa, I've always loved you.
You know that.
Only, not in the way that you needed it.
And I never did.
Then why did you just leave?
Why?
[somber music plays]
[Ramiro] Because I couldn't bear to watch.
To see you live the life
that I wanted to live.
But…
with Juan.
[music intensifies]
[Rosa] You loved him?
All this time you loved him?
I loved you both,
but that doesn't matter now.
No, it does. What are you even saying?
Quit lying for once in your life.
It was just once.
Did Juan cheat on me with you?
It meant nothing to him,
and we were really drunk.
[Rosa] Ohh…
Just leave.
-Rosa, please. Listen to me.
-Get out of here.
-He always loved you.
-I don't want to hear anything you say.
I don't want to hear it. Get out!
[melancholy arrangement
of "O Come, All Ye Faithful" plays]
No, it's okay, my love.
Don't you worry.
Everything's all right, Patri.
Yeah? [sniffles]
[sniffles] It's okay. Don't worry.
It's all right, my love.
Well, I'm going this way.
How about you?
I'll take the subway.
I had a great time tonight.
Me too.
Though it was bold of you
just showing up like that.
-[chuckles] It was suicidal, I guess, huh?
-[chuckles]
But the way you looked at me
when you saw me at the door…
It was worth it.
Merry Christmas.
[wistful music plays]
Merry Christmas, Àlex.
[bells ringing]
Hey!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for sending you that message.
I didn't know.
If I had the right to send that message
and on Christmas, but, uh…
It's just… that I've been
thinking about you all day.
For a few days, in fact.
And I think that you deserve an apology.
I owe you an apology.
-[Álex] For what?
-An apology for what?
[Ibra and Bruno] Yes, for the way
I treated you.
[Ramón] There's no need though.
You can't help how you feel.
And, if you don't like me, then…
-It's not that, Àlex.
-I do like you.
I really like you.
But I guess I didn't want to admit it.
I didn't tell you this,
but… I haven't stopped thinking about you.
I've been thinking about
this other guy, a lot.
And I thought you might say something.
I thought he might call.
-That you'd call, like other guys.
-But he didn't.
But… no, you didn't. And I'm glad.
And now I realize
that this guy wasn't… wasn't special.
He was just different than
the guys I was used to dating, and…
That makes you different from
guys who call me when they're horny.
I didn't realize that what I was really
looking for maybe is right in front of me.
That doesn't happen often.
And when it does,
you can't let it get away.
Well,
I wanted to see…
-if you want to see a movie.
-[Bruno chuckles]
Maybe we could get a drink right now?
[Ramón] Uh-huh.
["O Christmas Tree" performed by
Stuart Roslyn and Matthew Foundling plays]
♪ O Christmas tree
O Christmas tree ♪
♪ Thy leaves are so unchanging ♪
♪ O Christmas tree
O Christmas tree ♪
♪ Thy leaves are so unchanging ♪
♪ Not only green when summer's here ♪
♪ But also when 'tis cold and drear ♪
♪ O Christmas tree
O Christmas tree ♪
♪ Thy leaves are so unchanging ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ O Christmas tree
O Christmas tree ♪
♪ Thy candles shine so brightly ♪
♪ O Christmas tree
O Christmas tree ♪
♪ Thy candles shine so brightly ♪
[song ends]
[wistful music plays]