[telephone line ringing]
[ethereal music plays]
A NETFLIX SERIES
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
[line beeps]
[man] You see?
In the end I decided to call you.
[alarm chimes]
09:45
STOP
["Contemporary Love" plays]
All this time spent
debating whether to call you or not,
-only to get your voicemail.
-[cell phone chiming]
I haven't heard from you for two weeks,
and I thought, "You should call him."
"He must not have seen my Insta messages
or my Grindr messages."
I know you're really busy with work,
and you're not paying attention.
And sometimes I forget
that not everyone is like me,
'cause I can't stand having
a red notification on my screen,
that's why they make them red,
the bastards, so you can't ignore them.
You know, tell me
what your inbox looks like,
and I'll tell you
what kind of person you are.
And you're one of those people
who has 340 unread messages
and who doesn't even bother
to filter your spam.
I know you're one of those people
who doesn't answer right away,
that's why I sent
you the WhatsApp messages.
And I know you've read them,
because they all have
the double check mark on them.
All 23 of them.
But you haven't said a thing.
And it's strange,
because the last few weeks
were quite different, weren't they?
-You're not calling that bastard Lolo?
-[whispers] No. No way!
[man] I loved it when
you would send me a picture
and make me guess where you were.
-I cooked up some lentils.
-Mom, I'm on a diet.
[chuckles] You might be on a diet,
but you always ask for seconds.
-[phone chimes]
-[woman chuckles]
[man] You could send me the photo
at any time of the day or night,
and the game was on.
LOLO:
WHERE AM I?
I would ask you questions,
and you could only answer
with "yes" or "no."
-IN A PUBLIC RESTROOM?
-YES
-IN THE CITY CENTER?
And we could spend hours with the game.
-THE FNAC RESTROOM?
-YES
And I adored it.
Especially when you asked
the last question.
You always had the same answer.
-SHALL I COME?
-YOU'RE ALREADY LATE
-Hey!
-Wait, Mom. What are you doing?
You're always tapping away, you look
like a hamster with a bag of seeds.
I remember the day you sent me
the photo of the bricks.
It was just a wall. That's it.
There were no clues. Nothing special.
[cell phone chimes]
LOLO:
WHERE AM I?
[man] And I responded
without a second thought.
I got it right on the first guess.
I had recognized
it was the wall in your room.
And you responded with, "This is magic."
And it was.
It was. For a few days it was.
And the next day you made me breakfast
and I ate those muffins you made with jam.
Me! I don't eat anything with sugar,
and I'm more of a toast person.
But, you know what?
I didn't want to destroy
the magic that was still there between us.
And, as soon as I left,
I sent you a message.
A very simple message.
Just a smile.
A smiley.
And with a smiley,
I was saying
that I wanted to do it again tomorrow.
That I already missed you,
that I finally had found someone who fit.
That I had found someone
I felt sexy with, funny, witty…
Someone who would laugh at
the same things that I do.
[wistful music plays]
Someone that I didn't
have to pretend with.
Who loved me for who I really am.
Someone that I could look at pictures with
of me when I was four years old,
and who would laugh and say, "Wow,
how I've gotten more handsome with time."
And I'd think, "He'll be saying
the same thing in five years,
in ten years, in twenty years."
[kissing]
[man] What are you doing?
Someone that I could dream up
the cheesiest things in the world with,
and deep down have us both hope
that someday they might actually happen.
[wistful music continues]
[rain pattering on windows]
All of that was said with that smiley.
And you could have responded
in so many ways.
The keyboard of your cell phone offers you
an infinite combination of characters
that you could have used
to just say one thing,
"Yes, I feel the same way."
But you never did.
[sniffles]
You know what the worst thing is?
That one day we'll bump into one another
out somewhere
and I'll smile at you
so as to not seem spiteful,
and you'll say,
"No, I think we should just be friends
and not ruin everything that we have,"
and all of that bullshit.
All that bullshit you say
so you can fuck one guy,
and then another and another
before complaining and saying,
"Oh, it's just no one can find
their ideal guy."
Well, I don't know If I was ideal,
but you had a guy
who could have loved you.
And you treated him like shit in the end,
and I was an idiot for thinking
it might actually have been real.
And that what we had actually was magic.
So why don't you just go fuck yourself.
You… fuck your cell phone, your magic,
and your fucking muffins with jam
that no one can swallow, you asshole.
[handset rattles in cradle]
SUNYER ARCHITECTS
[whimsical music plays]
That's a long message. Who was that?
I have no idea.
[man] Wasn't it for you?
I don't know, it was some hysterical guy
yelling at his boyfriend
about… an industrial pastries thing
I don't really get, to be honest.
If you were anyone else then I'd think
you had hurt a guy and didn't remember it.
-I've broken many hearts.
-[laughs]
Only, I'm kind enough
to remember them all.
-Yeah. You have… never.
-What're you laughing at?
[both chuckle]
-I think it was crossed lines, wasn't it?
-No way.
That only happens
in movies by Howard Hawks.
You know? "Operator, operator."
"This woman is calling from Seattle.
She lost her dog."
-Yeah.
-Nothing like that happens.
But it's weird
that he'd call the wrong number.
Well, he called from a landline.
Maybe he misdialed one of the numbers
or something.
-Would anyone do that?
-Sunyer is waiting for you in his office.
-I don't think he's in a very good mood.
-[sighs] You don't say.
Lis. Lis, Lis. Uh, Have you ever called
a boyfriend from a landline
so he wouldn't know it was you?
I did. Just once.
I was 15. Typical girlish reaction.
-Why?
-No, forget it. Thank you.
-Thank you for that, Lis.
-Anytime.
Your stranger is very mature, huh? I mean…
So is it really, really freaky
if I call him?
-[groans] Why would you?
-I don't know…
I mean, what if he regrets
the things he said to his boyfriend
and this way I could give him
the chance to act like it never happened?
It would be like going back in time.
Yeah. What is it you always
say about time travel movies?
If you change the past
you screw everything up.
-Exactly.
-But, no… But, no, listen.
I'd wanna be called back
to know it was the wrong number.
Didn't you say this guy was hysterical?
When he wasn't screaming he seemed nice.
Plus, he said he believed in love.
-Bruno, don't project.
-I'm not projecting--
-Yes, you're projecting.
-No, I'm not.
-That's why you're overthinking it.
-No.
It would be easier…
[whispers] …to hook up with Ramón.
Fuck that. No way.
-Yeah? Why not?
-Just no.
-He's our best architect.
-And?
He's been crazy about you
since you started.
Albert, I'm not hooking up
with a co-worker.
Especially one who's 35
and still collecting Pokémon.
Oh, that's great.
Hey. Maybe your mystery man
collects dead bodies in the basement.
You're so dramatic.
-I'm dramatic?
-Incredibly.
Look, delete the message
and forget the guy.
[Bruno scoffs]
Oh, by the way. There's a costume theme
for the dinner tonight.
-I don't think I'll be able to make it.
-No, no, no, no. Don't bail on me.
Bruno, we have… Bayona,
Sauquillo, Oyarzabal is coming.
-Even Oyarzabal, Bruno.
-Listen…
And yet we haven't seen
our college classmates in over ten years.
Don't you think there's a reason?
Yeah, and I haven't been out
for ten months, not even for a water.
Great. You can go by yourself, okay?
Nobody there will miss me.
-I will miss you, Bruno.
-But you see me every single day.
Yeah, but we don't party like we used to.
-[sighs]
-You remember the old days.
Fuck, remember how much fun it was?
And you don't want to feel that again?
Just for one night? Just one night.
-I wanna enjoy my day…
-Please, Bruno? Please, Bruno. Come on.
Just the dinner.
-That's it.
-That's all.
The theme for dinner is famous architects.
-And whose idea was that?
-Mine.
-Yeah.
-Don't pick Gaudi, okay?
-I'm going as him.
[Albert] Good morning.
Maybe it is for you.
You're so nice, and you always
get involved with the biggest pricks.
-I have bad luck. That's all.
-Sure, bad luck. Always the same story.
It's my fault?
Just look at the last few guys
you went out with.
Look. Let's just be friends.
A relationship would end
and would ruin what we have.
But you get that, right?
Couples always break up,
but friendship is forever.
Look, monogamy's for repressed guys.
It's joyless.
Seriously?
You wanna be stuck with someone?
[scoffs]
-And we'll get bored in bed, then what?
-Let's just be friends.
[both] Let's just be friends.
Let's just be friends.
But we could… keep fucking, if you want.
I have a really great time with you.
[chuckles]
-Don't you see the pattern?
-Sure. They're all assholes.
-Sure. Assholes with perfect figures.
-And?
[dog barking in distance]
Listen. If you want different results,
you can't do the same thing as before.
According to Einstein.
[door groans]
-Patri, it's just us!
-[Patri] Close your eyes!
Patri, look. Cut it out.
I'm here with Àlex.
[Patri] I don't care!
Close your eyes or I won't let you in.
[sighs]
-[Patri] Are you ready?
-Yes. Come on, already.
[Patri] One, two, three!
Don't you love the parquet in here?
I need to install it in the small room,
but then it's done.
-It's amazing.
-Isn't it?
So does it smell a little funny,
or is that just me?
No, it's 'cause I burned
a little white sage and incense
to cleanse the energy of the apartment.
Ah, well, yes. It is really clean, yeah.
But this isn't the flooring we picked out.
-You loved it the most.
-Yes, but it was the most expensive.
We can't just go over budget, Patri.
Ah… Oh, my love. Don't ruin it, huh?
It's gonna be fine.
We'll figure it all out!
When's the move-in date?
[Patri] The construction manager says
in January.
And hopefully at that point
your friend will be happier.
I am happy about this.
I know what will cheer you up. Follow me.
-Ah, this is here too.
-Mm-hmm.
A plant is the first thing
to go into a new apartment.
And you made it a plaque.
VERO AND PATRICIA
SEVEN YEARS GROWING TOGETHER
Welcome to our new life together, my love.
[ethereal music plays]
[cell phone buzzing]
Yes?
-[whispers] Now's a bad time.
-[Patri] Do you like it?
I know you're gonna be
happy here together.
And now it's your turn.
I could never get a loan for a house.
That's not what I mean.
I'm with her now.
Tonight?
Why don't you swing by the bar?
Sounds great. Yeah, me too.
I'll see you later. I'll see you then.
[sighs]
-[latch clicks]
-[door opens]
-Puchi?
-[dog barks]
Hey! Who's this little guy?
Have you been taking a nap
in Daddy's bed, huh?
-[Puchi whimpers]
-Let me see, huh?
Oh, you're so tired, aren't you?
Oh, my pretty boy, I could eat you up.
[kissing]
[soft jazz plays]
[Puchi barks]
SWEETIE, 250 M AWAY
HEY
JUST ME 34, 160 M AWAY
[man] Hi.
Hi, how are you?
[dance music plays]
-[man] Hi, honey.
-Hey.
Hello, hello, hello!
-[Álex] Hey.
-How are my little pigeons doing?
Your little pigeons are sick of you
always getting here late.
-Okay.
-I'm sorry.
I had to attend to
a matter of critical importance.
Hold on to your wigs, girls!
♪ Oh… jingle bells, jingle bells
Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh what fun it is to ride… ♪
-No, Javi. We agreed no decorations.
-Oh, what a sacrilege, honey!
I told you.
Decorations are tacky, all right?
Come on. Show a little Christmas spirit.
Don't try too hard, honey.
She doesn't have that.
Lesbians lose it
when they eat their first pussy.
But not to fear,
Javi is here to save Christmas! [chuckles]
Javi, it cost a lot already
to get the bar looking like this,
and you're gonna ruin it
with cheap decorations.
Um, I'm sorry. It cost me a lot of money.
You hardly contributed.
-[Vero] That's a lie.
-[exclaims] She says it's a lie.
But, if it were up to her,
this would be Maleficent's castle.
I really think she has
the vision of a dog.
Everything she sees is in black and white.
Come on, let's stop arguing. Votes for?
Attention, s'il vous plait.
Espumillón, dix points.
-I'm picking up the tree tomorrow.
-No. No, no, no.
-No trees. No!
-Sorry, sweetheart.
Welcome to the dictatorship
of the gayarchy.
No, Javi, no.
Besides, Àlex's vote doesn't count.
He's not a partner.
What do you mean, it doesn't count?
The next time,
I expect you to take my side.
[door closes]
[Àlex chuckles]
Hey. Cover me quick. I'll be right back.
Do you know who that is?
-No idea.
-Hmm…
Forgive me for being so persistent.
I know what I want.
And I'm flattered by that, really.
Okay. So then, what's the problem?
Look. She's gonna support it.
She'll see it as a betrayal.
Hmm. And wouldn't it be worse
to betray yourself?
-[sighs]
-Look.
How about this, huh?
I'll leave you the contract.
Read it over carefully,
and tomorrow you give me an answer.
-Just let me have a few days.
-There's no more time.
We need this sorted before Christmas.
Don't let me down.
This chance comes once in a lifetime.
[sighs]
[cheering]
Hey, so that bastard Lolo hasn't shown
any signs of life yet?
After my message,
he must have blocked me even on LinkedIn.
Well, don't worry.
There are plenty of other fish
for you in the sea.
And you won't have any problem catching
a tuna with a good belly. [chuckles]
-It's not that simple.
-Don't be ridiculous.
Most of the customers in this bar would
give an arm and a leg to be with you.
To fuck. Not to be with me.
Oh yes, poor little thing,
you are so right.
How awful! It must be so difficult.
You know what I'm talking about.
Look, kid. Don't complain about
being full on cake
when there are those of us who don't even
have any bread to put in our mouths, huh?
Or, rather, a good baguette.
[both chuckle]
[narrator] Those two rocks are linked
by Akai Ito, the red string of fate,
to remind us that even rocks
without a heart are capable of loving.
[cell phone chimes, buzzes]
[pan flute playing melancholy tune on TV]
[sniffles]
STOP SAYING HEY, YOU BORE.
I WOULDN'T HOOK UP WITH YOU
EVEN IF I WAS ON GHB.
[pan flute continues]
DELETE GRINDR?
DELETE
[cell phone clatters on table]
[Puchi barks, whimpers]
[sighs]
VOICE MAIL
DECEMBER 9, 2022, 11:05
[playful suspenseful music plays]
[phone ringing]
[Àlex] Everything was easier before.
You'd meet a guy, you'd fuck,
meet again a few times,
and if you understood each other,
you'd just decide you were together.
Straight people do it.
If straight people do it,
we should be able to do it too.
I have a lot of friends who've been
together for many years, all right?
-They're in an open relationship.
-Not all of them.
-[phone continues ringing]
-Lesbians don't count.
They don't? Well then, yes, all of them.
[phone continues ringing]
Bar Bero?
You there?
Uh, hi.
Hi, yes. I'm sorry, but, uh…
You don't really know me 'cause…
Well… Well, I was calling
because I heard your message.
Uh, about muffins?
-Oh…
-Yeah.
At first I wasn't gonna call you back
because you seemed so upset.
But, after what you said,
then I thought that,
you know, it was important
that I tell you something.
You dialed the wrong number.
[music ends]
No. You're wrong, Bruno.
It's true. I don't know
why you ask for my opinion
if you always follow your knob.
[kids chanting] Knob, knob…
Kids!
Albert!
It's a part of a door.
They can say "knob."
Really. [groans]
All right, hold on.
So you called a guy that you've never met
before and haven't seen or anything?
Mm-hmm.
And in the end
he turned out to be really kind.
Bruno.
Nice meeting you. Well, I'm Àlex.
-[sighs]
-Well, listen, Àlex.
Things with that guy didn't end well,
but there will be others.
Yeah, I still can't fucking believe it.
-What was that?
-[sighs]
No, no. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just, that before this guy,
I knew this other amazing guy.
He had a really great body, was nice.
I thought I had won the lottery
with him, honestly.
And what happened then?
He asked me if I would strangle him.
I mean, when he was about to cum.
And he tried to get me
to choke him like a murderer.
[chuckles] Well, to each their own,
I guess, right?
Yeah. Well, that's what I thought.
But, after that, he didn't want to cum
any other way, said it's not gonna happen.
I didn't wanna have to do that every day.
Especially not at the beginning
of a relationship.
Think about it. What about later on
when you really do want
to kill him though? [chuckles]
[chuckles] Man! And when I told
that guy that it was over,
he said that I was a bigot
and a homophobe.
Yeah, I mean,
the same thing happened to me
with a guy who wanted me to pee on him.
I don't think I've ever drank
so much beer in my life.
-And that's why you ended it?
-No, not me. He ended it.
Because he said
it was too small, in the end.
-Your penis?
-No, bladder!
-Said my stream didn't last long enough.
-[chuckles]
[children chanting] Penis, penis…
-Bruno!
-Sorry.
-[woman] Seriously?
-I'm sorry.
They don't even know what it means.
[woman chuckles] Here.
Look, take Ariel for a second.
Julia, you need
to go brush your teeth now. Move it.
No. I want to know
how Uncle Bruno's story ends, Mom.
-[woman] Really?
-It ends badly, as always.
Hey.
Sorry. But it ends badly, right?
Look, almost all the guys I hook up with
either don't want to commit
or are in an open relationship
or cheat on their boyfriend.
And I don't want that.
You're a bit of a romantic, then.
-Right?
-[chuckles] No, no.
I just want to be happy, I guess.
[pan flute continues on TV]
[exhales]
[crowd chattering]
Do you know the legend
of the red thread of destiny?
No.
Well, it's an ancient Japanese story
that says there's an invisible red thread
that binds people
who are destined for each other.
It says that we all have one tied
around our little finger,
and that it can never break.
-But how do you know it's red?
-What's that?
I mean, if it's invisible,
nobody would know what color it is, right?
-It's absurd.
-Yes, sure, but it's a legend.
It isn't meant
to be taken literally like that.
Yeah, well, but you did.
-Yup. Well, okay… [chuckles] …yeah.
-Ah…
All right, I mean, isn't it
a beautiful metaphor though?
That right now
there's a stranger out there who is
going to be the most important person
in my life.
I feel like I trust the future.
It seems like
you're the romantic one here.
[Bruno chuckles]
-Don't you think that's beautiful?
-Hmm.
Hey. Are you on Instagram?
-No.
-[Javi] Hang up now. I'm alone.
-Um, Twitter?
-No, I'm not on Twitter.
-Facebook? Grindr? Anything?
-Nothing like that for me, no.
All deleted.
I deleted them. Why do you ask?
Well… to meet, I guess.
I'd be open to meeting up.
Yeah. Yeah, but I don't know
what you look like.
Yeah, I'm not sure
what you look like either. [chuckles]
Yeah, that's fair.
[Àlex] Hmm.
-Do you know Bar Bero?
-What barber?
No, the Bero. It used to be a barbershop,
and now it's a bar. Bar Bero.
Ah, yeah, I saw it once.
Um…
Well, I work there.
[chuckles]
-You're going on a blind date?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah.
-Great. When is it?
This evening. And I'll bring a book
so he'll recognize me.
Wait. What do you mean, this evening?
What about the reunion dinner?
You're so annoying.
I won't be late. Don't worry about it.
Okay. What if he's insane though?
Isn't it risky?
Great, you too?
Look, I have a good feeling about it.
I'll go, we'll have a beer, and that's it.
What's the worst that can happen? Huh?
-[Ariel retches]
-Okay.
[whimsical music plays]
[coos]
[sniffs] Oof.
[laughing]
Fuck. What do you feed this baby?
Plutonium?
-Don't laugh.
-[laughing] Hey! Okay, okay…
I'd better give you one of mine.
-No, no. You're crazy. It'll be too large.
-What are you saying? We're the same size.
We were once, Albert.
The verb tense is important
in this case. We were.
Yeah. I'd like to see you
take my place with three kids. Hmm?
Come on. I wish.
What are you talking about, Bruno?
Don't be ridiculous. Come on.
Look. The most action that I get
is jerking off in the bathroom
while the kids watch
Dora the Explorer, all right?
Lately I've been cumming
more with her than with Núria.
-Seriously?
-It's true though.
Now when I hear her voice,
I get a hard-on. Like Pavlov's dogs.
Well, now with the new sitter
you should have more time for yourselves.
Sure, if she's Mary Poppins.
[chuckles, sniffs]
Okay. Look, I'm going home to change.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
-Oh. You better be at the restaurant.
-Yes, you pest.
-9:00 p.m. Don't forget the costume.
-[Bruno] Bye, Núria.
-[Núria] Oh, are you leaving?
-[Bruno] Yeah, I'm going home to change.
[Núria] Kids, say goodbye to Uncle Bruno.
-[Bruno] Bye, kids. I'll see you later.
-[kids] Bye.
-[Bruno] Be good.
-[inhales]
[Núria] I hope your date goes great.
Let us know, okay?
[Bruno] Yes, I will. Have a good night.
I'll see you later. Come on, kids, let go.
I'll wait and buy the sea bass tomorrow
and freeze it.
The Christmas prices are ridiculous.
Well, it's what the market sells us.
It's not our fault.
-You want some sardines?
-No. I'll check out now.
-[vendor chuckles]
-[POS beeps]
And have you heard about Ramiro?
Montse's daughter says she saw him
the other day in the neighborhood.
Are you sure?
He hasn't stopped by to see you?
Well, I'll leave you in good company.
-And save me a good sea bass, okay?
-See you later.
Don't worry.
I'll save you the best one we get.
-Need anything else right now?
-What? You're leaving? Stay a little.
No, I can't tonight. I have a date.
-[woman] Oh.
-And I wanna stop home first.
You have a date? And what do I tell Ibra?
Who's Ibra?
He's the new guy
who works in Mercedes' shop.
He has dark hair. He's really fit.
Looks like a model, with great eyes.
-Mom, what'd you do?
-Me? Nothing!
Come here.
I might have shown him a photo of you
the other day, but it was an accident.
I was just looking at it with Mercedes,
the thing on the phone.
That Insta… What's it called?
-You have Instagram?
-I saw your profile.
And, since he was there, I told him.
-"Look what a beautiful son I have."
-Don't show my photos.
Ibra is very hardworking, and he's cute.
I know you'll hit it off.
Look. Ibra!
-Come here. [chuckles]
-No, Mom. Please don't…
Good afternoon, Ms. Rosa.
Ibra, this is my son, Àlex.
-Hello. Hey.
-How are you?
I'm Ibra.
-Your mother talks about you a lot.
-Yes, she does. Too much though.
-Why don't you go and have a drink?
-Mom, stop.
-And chat about how your day is going.
-Ignore her. No problem.
-I have to work anyway.
-Well, that's a pity.
Look. Let me give you his number
so you can see each other.
-What do you think?
-Sure.
-That works.
-Right?
-See you later, Àlex.
-Yeah, see you.
[upbeat music plays]
Yeah.
Don't I have a good eye?
I know your type.
Your aunt says he has a girlfriend,
but I think it's a lie.
Whoa…
He's straight though?
He's too handsome to be straight.
If anything, he's bilateral, you know.
[chuckles] "Bilateral." Okay.
I'll call you tomorrow, huh?
Oh…
-[Àlex] Bye, Aunt Dolo.
-Bye, have a good day.
[sighs]
["Got Me Looking at You" plays]
♪ You know I got it ♪
♪ Dancin' in the sun ♪
♪ Fancy life like a superstar ♪
♪ Turn up the music
Show me what you got ♪
♪ Watch me now
I've just begun ♪
[singer vocalizes]
♪ Rock it loud
Make it hot ♪
[singer vocalizes]
♪ Turn it up
Another notch ♪
[Àlex blows]
[Bruno sighs]
I don't get you, Vero!
And it doesn't matter how you spin it.
I still don't get you.
Well, maybe you would get it
if you'd just let me talk.
You guys can't still be arguing
about decorating.
That's not what we're fighting about.
She's leaving the bar.
She's leaving Bar Bero!
Don't listen to him. It's not true.
It is. She's gonna go
be a big VIP manager in Amnesia.
-You're moving to Ibiza?
-[Vero] No. I haven't accepted it yet.
But she'll obviously take it.
You see the look on her face?
That treacherous bitch face
she has going on.
Javi, stop it!
It's only a few months this summer.
And, besides, just think of the publicity
for the bar I can do there.
You see? She's already imagining it!
She can already see herself there.
If I knew you'd be like this,
I wouldn't have told you.
And what exactly
do you expect from me, Vero?
'Cause it was you who told me
not to sell my father's barbershop
and to instead turn it into a bar.
And now we're swimming in debt
as a result of it all.
And you decide to leave me high and dry.
The bar has consistent business,
and it's turning a profit.
It's no big deal
if I leave it for a few months.
But you do know this isn't
just a business, don't you, Vero?
It was our dream.
It was yours, and it was mine.
But you want something else
'cause you don't care about that.
[somber music plays]
Javi…
You gonna yell at me now?
Is this what you want?
My whole life,
I've wanted a job like this.
I promised I'd pick your side, didn't I?
What's Patri think about it?
Well, I haven't told her yet,
and I'm worried what she'll think.
Hmm.
Yeah. Yep.
Does Dad look handsome? Look. Puchi.
Be good, Puchi. I love you.
-[exclaims]
-Why don't you answer your phone?
-[Puchi barks]
-It's the weekend, Ramón.
-I can't find the project.
-Uh, which project?
Our project. The Arnau Theater.
Sunyer wants to send it to City Council.
I can't find the final.
-It's gotta be on the server.
-It is not on the server.
Here. I only could find
version 4, 4 final,
version 4 final approved,
and 4 final approved definite.
-And version 4 final approved def-def?
-It's not there anymore.
There's no def-def.
I think I might have erased it.
Check the recycle bin.
[sighs]
Ramón, tell me you didn't empty
the server's recycle bin again.
I do it to save memory.
No, Ramón. It's because you have OCD,
and when you see the full trash icon,
we end up here.
-Tell me you saved a local copy, please.
-Uh… Yeah, I'll send it tomorrow, I guess.
-Would you double-check?
-No, I'm on my way out.
-Please, Bruno. It'll only take 5 minutes.
-No…
Bruno…
[sighs]
Five minutes. Hurry. Let's go.
["Eres" by Massiel plays]
[singing along to stereo in Spanish]
-[doorbell rings]
-Mm.
[continues singing]
Hello, Rosa.
Don't tell me you've forgotten my name.
Ramiro…
[Vero] But who is this mystery man?
I barely know anything about him.
He didn't say much.
But his voice gave me confidence.
-You haven't sent each other a photo?
-No.
-So you can recognize each other?
-I decided to take a lesson from Newton.
-Einstein.
-Ah, whatever.
-[crowd chanting] Keena, Keena, Keena…
-What's taking her so long?
-I'll go check.
-[chanting continues] Keena…
Pardon me. Excuse me. Excuse me. Sorry.
Keena! Your audience is getting impatient.
[Javi] I'm coming. Turn on the music.
-[chanting] Keena, Keena…
-Excuse me.
[chanting continues]
-[feedback]
-[theatrical music plays]
Ladies and gentlemen… and others.
I now give you all
the one and only… Keena Mandrah!
[crowd cheering and whistling]
-[crowd chanting] Keena, Keena, Keena…
-[man] You are gorgeous!
-Thank you, thank you, thank you.
-[chanting continues]
Thank you. Okay, now.
Okay, okay, enough. You're gonna
wear my name out like that. Huh?
-[chanting stops]
-Yes. Keena Mandrah, that's me.
Welcome, everyone, to Bar Bero.
As you may know,
we don't do haircuts here anymore,
but if you can't control yourself,
you might end up bald.
So now… I'm looking at you.
I know you get carried away in here.
-[Javi chuckles]
-[chuckles]
[Javi] Oh, so many new faces.
Oh! Honey, what's your name, huh?
-Mine?
-[Javi] Yes, you.
-Modesto.
-What is it?
-Ah, Modesto.
[doorbells jingle]
[Javi] Do you always speak so softly,
or are you living up to your name today?
[women chatter and laugh]
-You're just too far away.
-"Far away"!
Not as far as you, honey.
From reaching your dreams.
[Javi and spectators laugh]
Oh! My girls, there you are.
The women's section. You're late, girls.
My short-haired girls are here.
-They've all been to the same hairdresser.
-[Vero] Hello, my love.
[Javi] It must be
a copy-paste job for their stylist.
So, beers for everybody?
-I would love a cocktail.
-That's a strong way to start.
Let's just say
we're toasting to your new floor.
-Any excuse is good enough for you.
-Uh-huh.
So then? Four gin and tonics?
-Well…
-[both] Yes.
[Javi laughs]
And where was the kennel
that you escaped from, honey?
In Cala Calobra.
[laughs] And what's that?
A spell in Harry Potter?
[all laugh]
No, it's a village in Ibiza.
Ah, Ib… Ibiza! Yes, Ibiza.
Of course it had to come out.
Ibiza, Ibiza!
-Pearl of the Mediterranean!
-[doorbell jingles]
[Javi] The club of Europe.
What are you doing here when you can be
in Es Cavallet, surrounded by hot guys?
Who fooled you into coming here?
I would rather be here with you!
-Oh, how cute!
-[crowd cheers]
-This is a surprise.
-[Javi] Round of applause.
-Your mother told me you work here.
-Oh yeah? Did she?
What'll you have?
A beer for now, thanks.
After that, we'll see.
Oh, I wish everyone had
the same opinion as you, honey.
I say this because my friend has decided
to do the opposite of what you've done.
She's going to work in Ibiza.
And she's going to leave poor Keena
lost in the city.
Alone, completely abandoned.
-Evicted like a stray bitch on the road.
-Aww. [chuckles]
-[spectators] Aww.
-Alone!
[spectators] Aww!
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't hold it against her.
Well, at first I was angry too,
because, well, I'm a bit…
-Because I'm very stupid.
-[spectators laugh]
And because I love her dearly.
Truly.
More than she could ever imagine.
It's because of this
that I decided I can't ever be the one
to stand in the way of her happiness
like that.
-Please excuse me for making a scene.
-[Vero mouths] No, no…
[Javi] I'm really sorry.
And I wish you the best
in your new life, Vero.
I wish you the best.
Now please help me
give a round of applause
for the brand-new VIP Manager
of Amnesia in Ibiza, my Vero!
Of course, honey! And congratulations.
My dear, may you be very happy.
["Ya no te hago falta" plays]
Patri. Patri, wait.
Patri. Fuck!
Patri!
Don't be Bruno. Don't be Bruno.
[Àlex sighs]
[chuckles]
Shit.
[song continues]
[song ends]
[wistful music plays]