A MEMENTO TO KEEP WHEN WE FAR APART
RAPIN
Hey, Yoi!
It's me Mahesuan!
Fai sent me here.
Come on out here and talk.
Yoi!
If you don't come out,
I'm coming in. Hey!
Mahesuan, if you want to eat
some lead, just come on up!
Wait!
DID YOU CATCH THAT?
IF NOT, WE'LL PLAY IT AGAIN…
Yoi!
Fai sent me to deliver your reward
for singing to the police.
Dum! Hang on!
Wait for me!
Hey, Dum!
-Where the hell are you going?
-I need to see someone.
What is it with him?
Don't cry now, my little one.
Oh, nurse,
he never came.
He broke his promise.
Oh, my poor dear.
Don't be sad.
Come take a bath now
and change out of these clothes.
Look,
you're all soaked through.
And tomorrow's your big day…
Tomorrow…
what shall I do?
Tomorrow you'll be engaged.
There's no other way now.
Now you two are one.
For Kumjorn and Rumpoey,
I hope you live together in harmony
and be faithful to each other.
I wish you, my dear children,
a beautiful couple
and prosperity in your life.
This is my law.
If you betray Fai,
you will die.
Yoi didn't learn it
until he was in his grave.
Dum, my right-hand man,
had to teach him.
You see, Somjit? I told you.
Dum's not like any other person.
He never misses.
Right, boss.
I've never seen anyone like him
in my entire life.
He's the best gunslinger on earth!
I mean, along with you, Mahesuan.
What do you think, Mahesuan?
You have met your match!
Hey!
Where the hell is Dum anyway?
Go and fetch him for me.
I'll get him myself, boss.
Oh, this is a laugh!
Who'd have thought
the great "Black Tiger,"
said to kill men without even blinking,
crack shot, the fastest man in the land,
was also master of the harmonica!
What?
Don't stop! Go on!
I was just starting
to get all carried away.
You know,
although I don't know much about music,
but it sounds like
your song
was about something sad and lonely.
Like someone's got a broken heart.
Hey!
Now, I'm sure!
This is a woman's handkerchief!
The big Black Tiger
has fallen in love, then?
Mahesuan! Give that back!
Hey! What's wrong with you?
I'm just kidding.
What are you so riled about?
Come on.
Give it back to me
or I'll kick your ass!
Then bring it on!
Come on!
I want to know how good you are, Dum.
You think you're tight with Fai, do you?
Bring it on!
Let's make it clear now.
Between the Black Tiger and Mahesuan
who's the best gunslinger?
Draw!
I saw it up in the branches,
getting ready to bite you.
Dum,
you saved my life!
A MEMENTO TO KEEP WHEN WE FAR APART
RAPIN
TEN YEARS AGO
BANG PLA MA JUNCTION
Dum, I saw a swamp full of lotus blossoms.
Take me there
to pick up some lotus, would you?
Dum!
Take me rowing. Now!
The city has so many fun things.
There are cinemas and theaters everywhere!
And on weekends,
my father takes me to Bang Pu Beach.
Have you ever been to Bang Pu?
I've heard of it.
I heard it's very beautiful.
But my whole life
I've never seen the sea.
Really?
You've never seen the sea?
That's a shame.
The sea is where the water meets the sky.
So huge and wide
that it makes you feel tiny.
It has a beautiful blue color
lovely cool breezes,
and waves that break
on the shore all day and night.
I wish I could see it just once.
Well, when you come
to visit me in Bangkok,
I'll ask my father to take us there.
But first,
you must be good to me,
do everything I say. Understand?
Very good! Now…
take me over there.
How beautiful!
Who built such a beautiful pavilion
in the marsh?
This pavilion is called
"Awaiting the Maiden" pavilion.
Why is it called that?
My father has told me a story.
Long ago,
a poor young woodcutter
lived in this forest.
One day, he met a rich man's daughter
who come from the city
to rest in the forest.
They fell deeply in love
and swore
they'd run away together
when the wildflowers fell
from the trees.
So the woodcutter gathered
the very best wood,
from the very best trees,
to build her a beautiful pavilion.
Then, every year
when the wildflowers fell,
he'd wait for her here in the pavilion
but she never came.
But why did she break her promise?
Her father caught her leaving the house
and locked her in her room.
When she knew she'd never meet her lover,
she hung herself.
The pavilion has been called
"Awaiting the Maiden" ever since.
Why are you crying?
It's just a story.
We don't even know if it's true.
I feel sorry for the girl
and the woodcutter.
Come on now. Let's go home.
It's getting dark. I'll get in trouble.
Come on!
What's with your rowing, idiot?
Can't you watch where you're going?
Look who it is! It's Dum. Dua's son.
Where are you rushing to, Dum?
Koh! Let it go.
No! You got a problem?
He said let go. We're hurrying home.
Man! Dum, you've got a brave
girlfriend here.
You're crazy! I'm not his girlfriend.
Oh, yeah? So why are you two
out alone in a boat, then?
Right, guys?
Hey, baby, why don't you be my girl?
Let go of me!
Koh, leave her alone!
Dum! You to dare hit me?
You're dead! Get him!
Don't fight!
That's enough, Dum!
Don't! That's enough!
Dum! Look out!
Dum. Are you all right?
Dum.
Dum, don't!
Dum! Enough! Stop fighting!
Dum's gone mental! Help me!
Dum, please stop it!
Enough!
Come on. Let's go!
Before he hits me again.
Have you found them yet, Dua?
Not yet, sir.
The servants say.
Dum took the little miss out rowing, sir.
They're probably caught in the rain.
I've already sent some men to look.
Dua, how the hell did you raise your son?
You let him keep my girl out
until dark like this?
What if something happened to her?
She's my only daughter, Dua.
When Dum gets back,
he'll get the whipping of his life, sir.
They're back!
What's wrong with my daughter?
Bring her here. Help her!
Dum, how could you do this?
What if she's hurt?
Come here.
I'm going to whip you until you're raw!
You ungrateful child! Take this to heart!
After today you'll never do this again!
Never do it again!
Never again!
Remember! Never again!
FRAGRANCE'S GONE
BY THE END OF THE NIGHT
BRING FRESHNESS WITH IT
LOVE AND YEARNING ON MY SIDE
HAVE ALWAYS LEFT IN THIS MOONLIT
With your permission, sir…
Sure. Kumjorn. Seat yourself.
There's an urgent concern
and I need your advice, sir.
Since I've been stationed in Suphan Buri,
I haven't proved myself.
Just sat and slept and hung around.
I don't feel I'm earning my salary.
Just as I thought.
The young city-trained man,
transferred upcountry,
loaded with energy…
You're anxious to show
what you've got. It's natural.
No, sir.
I just want to help
and protect the people.
That's the reason
I trained to be a policeman.
Also, I came here to see
with my own eyes the "city of bandits"
I've been hearing about.
I think you've already seen
what it's like.
This morning,
I investigated a murder
committed by Fai's gang.
Nine members of a rich family
were cruelly robbed and killed.
I'm outraged.
They can mock us like this
and still be at large.
-Do you plan to take on?
-Yes, sir.
I'm willing to lead the troop.
What do you think, sir?
I admire your bravery
and determination, Kumjorn.
You're a very fine young man.
That's why I'm giving you
my daughter's hand in marriage.
But I have to warn you,
as a governor
and as someone born here in Suphan Buri.
This province is plagued
with thieves and killers
and suppressing them is very difficult.
Especially Fai.
We have no leads on him.
No one will even open their mouths.
Because Fai kills everyone
who informs on him.
You need not worry sir.
Luck is on our side.
One of Fai's henchmen came to repent
and became our informant.
He'll lead us straight to Fai's lair.
Sergeant Yam, did you say goodbye
to your wife yet?
Sir! Every one of them, sir!
What? How many do you have?
Sir! Seven wives, sir!
This is heavy, indeed.
After today's mission,
I'm afraid they'll all be widowed.
Sir! I told them if I don't make it
they can find new husbands, sir!
Ms. Rumpoey, I've come to say goodbye.
It's official business
and I must leave immediately.
But I wanted to see your face first.
I'll be gone for many days.
Sorry to bother you so early.
No bother.
Captain is my fiance now.
Won't you wish me luck?
I wish you good luck
and safe return.
I'll be always thinking of you.
I'll beg the days and nights to rush by
until I see you once more.
Captain, you had best go.
Your men are waiting.
Farewell, my dear Rumpoey.
May I
take your photo with me?
It could be my good-luck charm.
-Help yourself.
-Thank you.
I'll guard it with my life
and keep it by my heart at all times.
By everything sacred in this world,
I, Mahesuan,
swear, with Buddha as my witness,
I'll always be true
and loyal to my blood brother
Dum, the Black Tiger,
who saved my life.
If I break this oath,
may his gun
end my own.
THE POLICE ARE IN TROUBLE
FAI'S GANG ROBBED UNDER THEIR NOSE
FAI SHOTS HIS HENCHMAN
THEN ROBBED THE POLICE STATION
THE GOVERNOR ORDERED
TROOPS TO ATTACK FAI'S GANG
Attack!
Tigers! Fight to the death!
-Where are you going?
-My job's done, Captain.
I've already led you here.
-If Fai sees me, I'm dead.
-Not yet.
You must identify the real Fai first.
Sergeant, restrain him!
-Sergeant Yam, show them your bomb throw!
-Yes, sir!
Good shot, Yam!
But why is there no explosion?
Damn!
I forgot to pull the pin!
Request permission to throw again, sir!
Yod, bring me some ammo.
We're running out of bullets, boss.
Just rifles and pistols left.
-What should we do?
-Damn it! Give it to me!
Fight to the last bullet.
Yod, give me a pistol.
Shit! The police are attacking!
Dum! Quick!
Dum and Mahesuan are here!
Now it's my turn!
Stop! Arrest him!
No!
Please spare me, boss!
I made a mistake! Boss!
Forgive me.
Boss, please!
You're right! You made a mistake
when you betrayed me!
You know what?
Now your whole life's only worth one cent.
See this?
The coin has a hole in it.
Somjit, I'll give you a chance.
If my bullet can't get through it,
you live.
But if it can,
you die!
My law is simple.
Whoever betrays Fai dies!
Dum!
This is your duty now.
That filthy captain
has been locked up in the cabin.
He's the last living person
who knows where our hideout is.
Go finish him.
Captain, forgive me.
So, this is the end of me.
Black Tiger, since I'm about to die,
let me die with dignity.
Untie me.
Thank you. Black Tiger.
If I ask a final favor
will you do it?
If I can, I will.
After I die,
there's someone
I'd ask you to inform.
I'm afraid
she'll be waiting for me anxiously.
Your wife?
My fiancee.
We're about to get married.
But now all hope's gone.
-Here…
-Captain!
-No tricks!
-Of course not.
I was only showing you her photo.
Slowly!
If you try anything, I'll shoot.
Her name's Rumpoey Rajasena.
We were engaged only last month.
If you will,
please let her know of my fate.
Tell her that I,
Captain Kumjorn, her fiance,
have died.
But I loved her
and thought of her until the very end.
Dum, will you do this?
Dum, I'm begging you.
Help me!
Please.
If you must kill me after that, go ahead.
Go ahead and do it.
Everything in order Dum?
Dum! What happened?
He's gone.
What the hell?
How could you let him get away?
Dum!
Hey.
Dum's been stabbed. Go get help!
Quick! Goddamn it!
Dum!
Dum! Stay with me, friend.
Rumpoey…
BANGKOK, ONE YEAR AGO
Dum.
It's you, isn't it?
It's me, Rumpoey. Do you remember me?
I'm sorry, madam.
You have the wrong person.
Wait, Dum!
Do you really not know me?
I've never met you before.
Besides,
my name is not Dum.
What is your name, then?
My name is Rapin.
This harmonica is proof!
I gave you this ten years ago.
Remember, Dum?
Anyone could have a harmonica like this.
You're mistaken.
This harmonica belongs to me.
I'm not someone important enough
for you to know.
Not now
and not ten years ago.
Please leave me be, madam.
You're lying, Dum!
You're lying and you know it.
Look!
I engraved my name on it.
Rumpoey Rajasena.
You see it every time you play.
But why deny it?
Do you want to forget me, Dum?
You hate me, right?
That's why you pretend not to know me.
You're still angry with me
because I have caused you
to be punished at that time.
Is that right, Dum?
Please give me back my harmonica.
Yes. I already gave it to you.
It's definitely yours.
But I want to tell you
that these whole ten years,
I've thought of you every day and night.
And every time I pictured you,
I saw the scar on your face.
It was my fault.
That scar…
You got it because
you tried to protect me.
Every day for ten years,
I prayed
that I would see you again.
No matter how long,
I'm happy to have a chance
to tell you
what I should have said long ago.
I'm very sorry.
If you're finished speaking now,
I'll be going.
Hey there, Rumpoey!
Jedsada! You scared me to death!
What are you doing around here?
Don't you know
this is no place for a lady
to go strolling!
I'm going home.
How about a ride?
I'll take you for a spin in my MG.
No. I have my own ride.
Get out of my way.
Come on, Rumpoey.
I'm your old pal.
No need to be so cold.
Rumpoey,
let me keep you
for ten minutes,
then I'll let you go.
Otherwise…
-What will you do?
-Me?
I'll steal a kiss from you.
Don't you dare! You bastard!
How dare you slap me!
Well, then.
If you disrespect me…
I'll disrespect you!
-Don't! Let me go!
-Stay still!
-Help!
-I just want a little kiss!
-Help me!
-You two! Grab her!
-Help! Help!
-Stay still!
Dum!
Koh! Let her go now!
Well, well. Look who's here!
Dum. Dua's son himself.
Hey!
You know her too, Dum?
How the hell could a peasant
know a girl from a rich family?
Are you going to play the goddamned hero?
Come on.
Don't you even remember
who gave that scar…
on your face?
Hey, Scarface?
Stop it! Don't fight!
Dum! Watch out!
Stop it!
We can't win. Let's get out of here!
Dum, are you all right?
Does it hurt?
Dum!
Dum. Come back.
Dum! Dum! Hold on.
Dum…
What happened to you? Tell me.
They kicked me out of college.
Oh, dear.
Why?
You didn't start it.
They're the one
who deserves the punishment.
I'll ask my father to help.
Don't take the trouble, Ms. Rumpoey.
I'm just a peasant.
I don't want to stain
your father's reputation.
What are you talking about?
You're in trouble because
you tried to protect my honor.
Am I right?
I'm grateful for that.
You're in trouble again because of me.
You're going home now, aren't you?
Let me take you there.
I don't have a house.
I stay at a temple.
Get in the car, then. I'll take you there.
Please get in, Dum.
What are you planning to do now?
Tomorrow I'll go back to Suphan Buri
and help my father on his farm.
So we'll never
see each other again, right?
Dum,
when we were children,
I made you a promise.
If you come to Bangkok,
I'd take you to Bang Pu. Remember?
Mr. Mun! Drive to Bang Pu.
-Ms. Rumpoey!
-Pardon me, miss?
I said, "Go to Bang Pu."
-You mean right now, miss?
-Yes.
But the master…
Do you want to go to Bang Pu
or quit your job?
LOVE IS LIKE A RAGING BULL
YOU CAN'T PULL IT
AND LOVE CAN ROAM FREE
NO NEED TO GET A PERMIT
So this is the beautiful ocean.
No wonder people long for it.
It's like the edge of heaven itself.
When I was a child,
each time my father brought me here,
I was surrounded
by happiness, complete and boundless.
So much happiness
I couldn't hold it all at once.
I remembered
praying that it would last forever,
just like that,
every day and every night.
But when I grew up.
I found out
time never stands still.
Especially, happy times
as it goes by fast.
It comes like a fresh sweet breeze.
Pauses for a moment, then passes on by.
Dum,
why must we grow up to be adults?
Growing older just brings sorrow.
It seems life
is just a long and terrible sadness.
And so we must hunger
and chase after happiness,
the smallest hope of reprieve,
until the very end of our days.
Ms. Rumpoey,
tomorrow I must leave you
though my heart rebels
because I want to be with you.
For the past ten years,
you alone
have dwelt in my heart.
And each time I play the harmonica,
I see no other image
but your face before me.
If this is so,
why did you try to push me away
when we met?
Because when we met,
my heart was wounded.
I knew I'd never be worthy
of someone high-born as yourself.
It was impossible
to even think about it.
That's not true, Dum.
I…
I love you. Do you hear me?
I love you…
-More than anything in life.
-Rumpoey…
Rumpoey…
Can you promise me you'll wait for me?
I promise.
No matter how long,
I'll wait for you.
What if your father won't permit it?
Then I'll run away with you.
Dum. Do you remember
the "Awaiting the Maiden" pavilion?
The day my father
rejects our marriage…
is the day I'll be there.
Remember it, Dum.
Father!
Who did this to you?
Kong, the village headman…
Kong? Why?
Why would he do this?
He wants to replace me
as a district chief.
He came as a bandit…
Kong!
I'll kill your whole clan!
Father!
Look at me!
Come on!
Hey! He's in the tree. Shoot him!
Little brother,
how are you related to Dua?
Dua saved my life once.
I gave him this gun!
This gun is powerful armor!
No outlaw gang would dare oppose it.
Kong, you bastard.
You dared to rob and kill my friend Dua.
Today
you'll taste the same pain.
Ms. Rumpoey, you've troubled
to visit me! I'm so happy!
Don't worry.
I'll get better for our wedding.
You may not believe it,
but I survived
because of you.
Remember your photo that I brought
as my good-luck charm?
It really did save my life.
After Fai captured me,
he sent the Black Tiger to kill me.
When I knew I'd die soon,
I asked him as my last request
to inform you.
Then I showed him your photograph.
When he saw it,
he had a sudden change of heart,
and spared me.
It was truly a miracle.
Rumpoey,
don't forget our wedding day.
I'll pray the nights
and days rush by until then.
Die! He has to die.
Nobody
walks over me
and gets away with it.
Not even the police.
I'll follow him and kill him.
Mahesuan, tell Dum our plan.
Two days ago,
I sent a man
to spy on Captain Kumjorn in the city.
He said that
this Sunday,
the captain's to marry
the Governor's daughter.
The wedding
will be at the Governor's palace.
When the wedding day comes,
I'll ambush them
just as they did me.
Fai, I don't agree with the plan.
Why?
The wedding will be packed
with police from all over the province.
Good!
I'll kill them all at once.
-It's too dangerous.
-Danger?
I love danger!
Besides, they won't expect us
to attack them in their own lair.
They'll be totally unprepared.
I'm dying to see the look on their faces.
-But, Fai…
-Enough, Dum!
No more opinions.
I've made up my mind.
You two go to see Guronsan.
Buy as many weapons as you can.
On Sunday night,
we'll level the place.
My darling Dum,
from here
to the ends of the universe,
happiness calls
but once in every life.
Let mountains tumble into seas,
let bodies turn to ash,
my love for you remains
until I breathe no more.
Oh, my god! Miss…
Miss! My little miss!
Miss! Why are you doing this?
Let me go, nurse.
Just let me die.
Let's try this coffee. I made it myself.
You'll be glad to have it.
How was it?
This tastes like dirt!
Typical for a stolen one, right?
No, you can't have that.
Hey!
Where the hell is Dum?
Dum!
Help me!
Help me! Dum!
Dum!
-Mahesuan!
-Dum! Look out!
What are you doing?
Drop the gun or your pal's dead.
They've betrayed us!
Dum, get out of here!
Don't worry about me.
I said drop the gun.
I never thought the great "Black Tiger"
would fall for a trick like this.
Mahesuan you cunning fox!
You robbed the tiger of his teeth!
Mahesuan! What does this mean?
It means
Fai ordered me
to set you up.
Fai?
Yes.
He doesn't trust you anymore,
he thinks you're a spy
since you let Kumjorn get away.
How did he know about it?
I told him myself.
I opened his eyes.
Fai lost his way
the day he started trusting you.
You know?
I used to be his right-hand man.
But after you came along,
I was treated like a dog.
I've waited patiently
for this day.
It's payback time!
Mahesuan, you're traitor!
Remember your oath
in front of the Buddha?
-You treacherous dog!
-And you?
You betrayed us all!
Don't you remember Fai's law?
Whoever betrays Fai
must die!
But before you die,
I'll tell you something
to make it sting.
When I'm done
with Captain Kumjorn this Sunday,
the Governor's daughter,
the one you "love,"
I'm going to make her my wife!
You're just a nameless corpse, Dum.
You filthy animal!
RUMPOEY RAJASENA
Let me wish you great happiness
and the brightest future.
May love flourish until you're old,
gray, and walking with sticks.
I wish you both
a happy life.
-Dum!
-Black Tiger!
Captain,
Fai plans to ambush your wedding tonight.
Be warned!
Wait! That's the Black Tiger.
-Arrest him! Quick! Halt!
-Don't…
-Arrest him! Help me!
-Quick! Follow me!
Why aren't the bride and groom
taking the first dance, huh?
Why are you just standing here?
Go!
Don't be shy. Just go.
I never imagined
the Governor's daughter…
would consort with
a scum like the Black Tiger.
Rumpoey, you still haven't told me
when have you befriended him!
Or…
is there something more intimate?
Why did you protect him?
Rumpoey! Answer me!
Captain, when will you
believe me?
I didn't know he was the Black Tiger.
You didn't?
But you called him like a close friend.
You never knew, huh?
I…
Can see it in your eyes.
They say exactly how you feel about him.
If you won't believe me,
I can't do anything.
-Everyone got envy.
-I agree with you.
Hey! Lucky guy! Take it easy!
You'll get drunk.
I want to get drunk!
Oh, nurse.
I feel so sorry for him.
It must have hurt him
to see me changed.
I broke my promise to him.
It's fate.
You can't prevail against it.
And he's an outlaw!
What kind of life could you have with him?
In this life,
I'll never love another.
Only him, always.
So that's the reason.
I get it now
why Dum released me.
He did it for your sake.
How stupid am I?
The Black Tiger.
That robber is luckier than me.
He has your heart to himself.
Rumpoey,
do you know
what I hate most?
I hate…
I hate being a loser.
And now I've lost.
I know now I will never own your heart.
But…
I can still own…
-your body!
-Captain, don't!
RUMPOEY RAJASENA
-I heard you got promoted.
-The news spread fast, doesn't it?
Then let me salute you, sir!
Hey! That was gunfire!
Tigers, attack!
Take positions!
What happened Kumjorn?
Fai's attacking, sir.
It's safer if you stay up here.
I'm going down to fight them.
No way! I'm coming with you.
They dare to attack me here.
I'll show them who I am. Go!
Sakon, how many of them?
No less than 50.
Call the barracks for reinforcements!
Okay.
Sakon!
Don't move!
Well, what a peach!
-No wonder Dum's obsessed.
-Don't you touch her.
-You beast! What are you doing?
-Get out, you old hag!
Or die.
Move!
-Don't do it!
-Come here!
-Don't! Help!
-You old hag!
-Help!
-No one's going to help you.
Dum's gone to hell already.
Well, Captain…
-It's all over now.
-Fai.
You won't get away.
All the police in Suphan Buri
are on their way.
I know.
But before that,
you'll be a ghost by then.
Get ready to meet your death.
Don't you recognize an old hoodlum?
Dum!
-So you're still not dead!
-Mahesuan.
Let Rumpoey go!
Let's settle this
man to man.
Sure!
I want to know
who's faster.
You or me?
Freeze, Black Tiger.
Put Rumpoey down slowly.
Don't try anything!
Dum.
Don't!
Dum!
It seems that life
is just a long and terrible sadness.
And so we must hunger
and chase after happiness,
the smallest hope of reprieve,
until the very end of our days.
THE END