What's wrong with you?
Where did you even get that?
Johnny, what are you doing?
9-1-1, what is your emergency?
Hello? 9-1-1.
Do you have an emergency?
Sir, can you speak?
If you can't speak,
press any button on your phone.
Once for yes, twice for no.
Are you still there?
Sir,
I want you to stay on the line
for me, okay?
I'm gonna track your location.
Are you still with me?
Hello?
Are you still there?
Okay.
129, Peterson Drive,
Miles County Morgue.
Sir, are you still with me?
Just sit tight and remain calm.
Police and paramedics
are on their way...
♪ You're not alone ♪
Ma'am, I understand.
But I can't give you
that information.
Your husband's the only one
listed on the policy.
Bitch!
No, ma'am, not you. Not you.
Mom, don't we have
a tape measure?
I don't know.
Check the drawer
by the microwave.
Yes, ma'am!
I understand that,
but in the future,
your husband's going
to have to call the policy.
All I can tell you
is that it's still active.
Yes.
Mm hmm.
Can you wait five minutes,
and go get your brother, please?
Yes, ma'am.
My manager
is just gonna tell you
the same thing.
So, did you figure out
what you're dressing up
as tomorrow?
The Miles County clown.
- Don't do that.
- Why not?
Because that's beyond
disrespectful.
What are we talking about?
He wants to dress up
as a real guy
who murdered nine people
last year.
Do you have any idea
how insensitive that is?
Not to mention, sick.
- Oh, you're not doing that.
- It's just a costume.
How would you feel
if God forbid,
he attacked someone
in our family,
and people celebrated him?
That's basically
what you're doing.
You don't see people
dressing up as Jeffrey Dahmer
or Charles Manson.
I think
you're both overreacting.
Do you?
Charles Manson technically
never killed anyone.
All right, all right. Enough.
I said, "No," and that's it.
Did you know that Nazis used
to inject children's eyeballs
to see
if they would change color?
Jonathan!
Thank you.
So, what are your plans
tomorrow?
Megan Melanie's throwing
a Halloween party.
That's nice.
Who are you going with, Allie?
And Brooke.
She's not driving, is she?
I'm gonna take an Uber.
Why, so you can get shitfaced?
Who do you think I am,
stupid, Sienna?
Do we have to do this
every time I go out?
You know I don't drink.
So you say.
Your brother never closes
these goddamn boxes.
Give me that. I got it.
Mom, do you ever...
wonder about Jonathan?
What do you mean?
You know, he's...
- He's an oddball.
- So, what?
He was looking up serial killers
when I went in his room before.
Now, he's... he's talking
about Nazis and the Holocaust.
- I mean...
- It's just a phase, Sienna.
It'll pass.
You said that a year ago.
Yeah, well, he lost his father.
And I didn't?
You don't see me
crying out for attention.
Yeah, well, I wish you would
from time to time.
You keep everything bottled up.
It's not healthy.
All right.
Just don't be surprised if you
find a dead animal in his room.
You know what?
Watch your mouth, huh?
And what about you?
When Daddy took you fishing
for those midos or macos.
Minnows.
Whatever they're called.
And he found you
cutting the heads off.
Didn't think I'd remember that,
did you?
I was a lot younger
than Jonathan.
Well, you were old enough
to know the difference
between right and wrong.
Your brother's fine.
Do you have any Super Glue?
A little.
- Why, what happened?
- The string came off.
I thought you weren't gonna wear
this tomorrow.
I won't paint my face then.
- Jonathan.
- Come on.
It's too late
to get another costume.
Give me.
Jesus. What, did you grow
another foot since dinner?
Tallest kid in my class.
Yeah, well, I can still kick
your ass.
Not for long.
That is sick.
- How much do you have left?
- Just finishing up the skull.
It looks
just like Daddy's character.
You know?
You draw almost as good
as him now.
Thanks.
Is this a part
of your costume, too?
No. I could not walk out
in the streets with that thing.
I'd get arrested
in like two seconds.
Yeah. But nobody
would mess with you.
- That's for sure.
- Right.
Just be careful, please.
That blade's like razor sharp.
There. Should be good now.
Awesome.
You think
that guy's still out there?
Who?
The Miles County clown.
What's up with you
and this clown all of a sudden?
You're like obsessed.
They never found his body.
What if he decides
to come back here?
Is that why you wanna dress up
like him?
You think if he sees you
wearing his costume,
he'll be all cordial with you?
Cordial?
Friendly.
No.
I wouldn't worry about it.
On the off chance
that he is still alive,
I'm sure he's gone far away
from here.
- Thanks again for the hat.
- You're welcome.
Tap lower down.
Owen, I saw it again.
Hmm?
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ The club
is downright gruesome ♪
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny,
food's a little funny ♪
♪ Food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Drop on by the clown café,
your favorite meals on wheels ♪
♪ The menu is disgusting
and it's full of special deals ♪
♪ Nothing here is good for you,
so grab yourself a tray ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ Double up your order quick
before it runs away ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Why not visit after school
and have yourselves a bite? ♪
♪ An appetizing appetizer
certain to delight ♪
♪ We haven't done a ride
♪ And thus,
it makes your tooth decay ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ The grub
is downright gruesome ♪
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
Food's a little funny ♪
♪ Food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
Will you help this man?
You, over there!
Yeah! Feed this man.
How about you? He's hungry.
Will you feed this man?
He's not invisible. Feed him!
New Art
Crispies from Sugar Plum.
Fun, little surprises
in every bite.
Glass, insects, and razor blade.
There's no telling
what you may find!
Special prize included
in every box.
Wow! I wonder what I got!
Speaking of surprises, kids,
we have a very special guest
with us today.
Now, for a guy
who doesn't speak,
he sure makes a lot of noise.
All the way from Miles County,
please welcome Art the Clown.
Whoo! Whoo! Yeah!
Yeah!
Stop everything
you're doing now!
I see you feeding your faces.
Feed him! He's so hungry.
Feed this man!
Special
prize included in every box.
Shit.
What's going on?
- Mom!
- Get downstairs!
Jesus Christ!
Mom,
what are you doing? Come on!
Really, Sienna?
You left burning candles
on your dresser all night?
What are you, fucking stupid?
I didn't do anything.
They weren't lit.
Then please explain to me
how your goddamn room
caught on fire.
- I have no idea.
- You have no idea.
So, it just spontaneously
combusted out of thin air?
- I guess so.
- Sienna...
Get back to bed.
You have school in the morning.
- You mean I still have to go?
- What did I say?
You know what, Sienna?
You are going to kill us
one of these days,
between your chemicals
and your heat guns,
and staying up until 4:00
in the fucking morning
doing God only knows what!
Oh, my God.
For the hundredth time,
I was not using chemicals
and I did not leave
burning candles on my dresser!
- Why can't you just believe me?
- Because...
Stay in my room tonight,
and I'll sleep on the couch.
I don't mind sleeping
on the couch.
Go to bed.
I kept whatever
was in the bottom drawer.
Most of it's ruined.
Make sure you park
in the garage when you get home.
Those animals next door
are always throwing eggs
and shaving cream.
I don't want the car
getting scratched up.
You know the sword Daddy got me?
What about it?
It was on top of my dresser
last night.
Well, maybe it can be restored.
Is it bad?
It's fine.
There's not a mark on it.
That's good.
Can't say the same
for your clothes.
Jonathan, hurry up.
You have five minutes.
Welcome back to the program.
If you're just tuning in,
I'm sitting here live
with the sole survivor
of the Miles County massacre,
which occurred
exactly one year ago today.
I've worked on the show
for many years,
and I've never sat across
from someone
who has a story to tell
quite like yours.
Thank you again
for taking the time to sit down
- and speak with me.
- It's my pleasure.
Now, when we left off,
we were talking about the moment
you woke up from the coma.
Do you remember
your initial reaction
when you first saw your face?
Yes.
Would you like
to share that with us?
I wished I was dead.
Do you still feel that way?
People are frightened
by the way that I look,
especially children.
And it's really difficult for me
to deal with that,
so isolation is ideal.
Now, what about your attacker?
The man only identified
as Art the Clown.
Well, there's a lot
of controversy
surrounding his supposed death.
The authorities issued
a statement,
claiming that his body
disappeared
from the county coroner's office
the morning after the attack.
He's dead.
I saw it happen.
- What are you guys doing?
- Dude, look what Sean found.
It's the new mascot.
Oh, man.
Right up your alley, huh, J man?
I wonder how it died.
Probably
had the school meatloaf.
I think
you should leave it alone.
What for? He doesn't mind.
It's so gross.
Dude, you should have been here.
Couple of birds
were eating his asshole.
Yeah.
Watch this. Stephanie!
Stephanie!
Come here for a minute.
Sean, come on.
It's gonna be awesome.
- What's up?
- Check it out.
Some cat just gave birth
behind the dumpster.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Go look at all the kittens.
Oh, my God!
What's wrong?
Maggots need love, too!
Stephanie!
Can you?
What's going on?
Oh, shit. Ms. Principe.
What are you boys doing
back here?
Oh, Christ. Mr. Henderson.
- Nothing.
- Really?
You go find
Mr. Curtis right now,
and you have him move that.
And you two, get to class.
Move it!
Jonathan.
Keep your eyes
on your own paper.
Mr. Whalen.
May I be excused?
Wait. I think
I forgot my shorts.
I think I have an extra pair.
- Do you have an extra shirt?
- I might.
We can go to the bathroom...
Hey! No running in the hallways!
Jonathan, get back here!
Oh, my God.
Happy Halloween, my pretty.
- Little early for chocolate, no?
- Mm.
You're talking to someone
who eats Count Chocula
on a regular basis.
Can we not talk about cereal?
Please?
Okay.
Someone's in a mood
this morning.
Sorry.
Barely slept last night.
Let me guess.
You were up until 4:00
in the morning,
working
on that Halloween costume again.
Actually, it was more like 6:00.
Did you guys hear
about Monica Brown this morning?
Ugh! That bitchy talk show host?
Yeah, that bitchy talk show host
totally got her face torn off.
What?
Okay, get this.
So, she had that Miles County
survivor on.
Do you remember the one
who was in the coma
and her face was all mutilated?
What's her name?
It was like, I don't know,
Victoria or something.
- Victoria Heyes?
- Yes.
She had a meltdown
on the show, right?
And then backstage,
she went full-on psycho,
and mauled Monica Brown
with her bare hands.
- No way.
- Oh, my God.
Is she dead?
I mean, if she's lucky.
What? You ever see photos
of those transplant faces,
looking like Mr. Potato Head?
- Fuck that shit.
- God, is it really that bad?
Well, I haven't seen photos.
But from what I hear,
she kinda looks like
the inside of my cookie.
Her eyes are all gouged out.
And her nose was like
falling off of her face.
Oh, my God.
And I heard that her cheek
like a little bit, was found
at the bottom
of Victoria Heyes' shoe.
You okay?
Sienna?
Hey, you all right?
I really didn't mean
to freak you out
with that Monica Brown shit.
- I'm so sorry.
- No.
- You okay?
- I'm okay, I'm okay. I'm fine.
I just...
I just need a second I think.
Hi. Excuse me.
Can you mind your own business,
please?
Thank you.
My God.
Sienna, talk to me.
What's going on?
We had... we had a fire
last night.
- What? Where?
- My room.
I must've fallen asleep
with the candles burning.
- It was pretty bad.
- Okay. How bad is "pretty bad"?
Like flames touching
the ceiling,
entire house
could have burned down bad.
- Jesus. Is everyone okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
No, my mom
put the flames out in time.
Wow. Fucking Barbara
to the rescue.
I swear
that woman's a superhero.
- Was she pissed?
- Livid.
Berated me for a good hour
and a half this morning.
I mean, that's not so bad.
I mean, you did almost torch
the whole family
in their sleep.
Look. The important thing
is that nobody got hurt. Right?
Seriously, in a few weeks,
you'll be laughing
- about the whole thing.
- More like months.
- Okay. A couple months.
- Probably a year.
It wasn't just the fire.
It...
Something really strange
happened last night.
What?
Nothing. Nothing. I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, no, come on. Um...
Let's... let's go back.
Now, that my food
is probably ice cold.
You want a piece
of my Monica Brown cookie?
- Brooke.
- Sorry.
I hate you.
Thank you, Officer.
I'm so sorry
to cause you trouble.
No problem.
Have a nice day, ma'am.
You, too.
- Get to your room.
- But mom, I...
Go to your room.
I don't wanna hear
another word out of you
until I say so.
I can't believe I'm reduced
to a pair
of cheap store-bought wings.
You think these are too small?
How big do you want 'em?
You're gonna be knocking
over people's drinks
and shit all night.
I think they're cute.
Well, they're not terrible.
You don't really have a choice.
Ugh, it's my mom.
Where did you tell your mother
we were going tonight?
Megan Melanie's Halloween party.
Okay. I'll catch you out front.
Okay.
Hey, Mom.
Good.
No, I'm just in town
with Sienna.
What time are you gonna be home?
Because...
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Nice.
Nothing. I just ran into a man
wearing terrifying
clown costume.
Can I help you find anything?
Need any help?
Uh, find everything okay?
Yeah. Mm hmm.
I'm gonna need to scan those.
Oh. Um, right. Sorry.
It's all good.
Okay. That'll be 32.25.
Yeah, um...
I think
I left my bag downstairs.
Sir.
If you're gonna put that
in your mouth,
you gotta pay for it.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You know what?
I'm gonna go get you a big bag.
Oh, no, no. I... I really...
- I don't... I don't need it.
- No, no, it's fine.
I got 'em right back here.
Okay.
Please don't.
Stop. Please stop! Please!
Hey, buddy?
You wanna quit causin' trouble?
- Thank you.
- Happy Halloween.
- You, too.
Yo, we closin' up, man.
Can I help you find something?
8.99.
Are you serious right now?
Yo, can you pay for that or not?
Sir, what are you doing?
All right. Sir, you know what?
I'm gonna call the police.
Hey! Did you hear what I said?
Get the hell outta here
before I fuck you up.
That's fucking crazy.
I'm telling you
it was him, Allie.
Right down
to the little black dot
on the tip of his nose.
Sienna, you said it yourself.
I mean,
there are gonna be hundreds
of douche bags dressed up
as that psycho tonight.
Even your brother
was talking about going as him.
Not that I'm calling
your brother a douche bag.
It's just a coincidence.
Then how do you explain
the fire?
I dreamt it and it happened.
Did you change medications
recently?
Jesus Christ. I'm not crazy!
Take a breath.
I... I'm just saying,
did you ever consider
the logical explanation
that maybe the fire
caused your nightmare,
not the other way around?
What?
I think that the fire
started while you were sleeping.
And it worked its way
into your nightmare.
I mean, your body must've felt
the flames.
You know shit like that
happens all the time.
Look, are you getting candy
or what?
I mean, what are...
What are we doing here?
Even if that is the case,
it doesn't explain
how the fire started.
Come on, honey.
Oh, my. They're closed.
- Wow.
- Oh.
Look at that, Mom.
Yeah, that's wonderful, honey.
Cool.
All right. Let's go. Let's go.
You're just gonna stay here
the whole time.
Come on.
We don't go direct
with our insurers.
Okay, but let me get
your zip code.
I'm gonna find a broker
in your area.
What are you doing home?
He's here, Sienna.
Who?
The Miles County clown.
What are you talking about?
I saw him today in my school.
Just like in the police photos.
Slow down.
It was him.
Something really bad
is gonna happen tonight.
Is that Daddy's sketchbook?
Look here.
How long have you had this?
Jonathan, answer me.
You know how long
we've been looking for this.
Read this.
I saw her today.
This exact girl.
Only she didn't look human.
There's some kinda connection
between her, the old carnival,
and the Miles County clown.
Something really
bad's gonna happen tonight.
I know it.
Did you put these in here?
No.
But look at this.
It's him!
Daddy drew this?
That's not all.
What if you're connected, too?
What?
Jonathan, you're acting crazy.
You're acting crazy. Okay?
He created
this character for you.
He gave you that sword
right before he died.
It's like he saw this coming.
Daddy drew a lot of things
for me.
He bought me tons of shit.
Seriously,
what's wrong with you?
- Do you even hear yourself?
- What's going on in here?
Did he show you this?
She doesn't care.
She's just pissed,
'cause I might get suspended.
Suspended. For what?
Oh, you didn't tell her?
Your brother brought
a dead animal to school
this morning.
- What?
- Yeah.
A dead animal.
Can you believe it?
He vandalized the halls.
I almost
had a fucking heart attack
when they told me.
It wasn't me.
It was the clown.
The little girl brought it in.
I don't wanna hear another word
about this goddamn clown.
He was covered in blood
on his shirt and his hands
when he got here.
The principal literally
caught you red-handed.
That's 'cause he threw it at me.
I should've listened to you.
You have been telling me
over and over again
about this kid.
I'm calling Dr. Schiffrin
on Monday.
I'm putting a stop to this now.
And put your goddamn bowl
in the sink.
I'm not telling you again.
It was him.
You gotta believe me.
Jonathan.
It was...
It was probably just some kids
at school, messing around.
It's the one-year anniversary.
I mean, I already saw some...
jerk wearing that same costume
in Abracadabra an hour ago.
What about these drawings
and these articles then?
We both know what happened
to Daddy.
Okay, none of this
was his fault.
And all of these ugly things
in here,
that's not who he was.
He loved you...
very much.
It's gonna be okay.
- Stay home tonight.
- Jonathan.
Please. I'm begging you.
- Nothing's gonna happen.
- Fine.
Just don't act surprised
when a bunch of people
get killed tonight.
Have you ever...
I believe him.
About what?
I don't think he vandalized
the school.
Oh, now, you believe him?
Yesterday,
he was the Zodiac Killer.
What's changed?
Get the door.
Restaurants on the East Coast
have recalled romaine lettuce
due to a recent
E. Coli outbreak.
At least 12 people
have been hospitalized
and two
are in critical condition.
- Hi.
- Trick or treat!
Happy Halloween.
Oh, I love your makeup.
Oh, she did it all herself.
Wow! Great job.
What do you say?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Bye.
Ah, aren't you a little old
to be trick or treating?
Wait a minute.
Aren't you that guy
from the costume shop?
You are?
What are you doing here? Oh.
Seriously, do you live
around here or something?
Hmm.
You're really weird,
you know that?
Yeah. Look, I get it, dude.
The whole creepy, silent
mime gimmick.
I mean, it's very effective.
And the blood
is a nice touch also.
Yeah.
I can't give you anything.
No, I'm sorry. Really.
No... no candy for grownups.
Come on.
Go away.
Seriously, asshole,
go bother somebody else.
Are you kidding me right now?
I said, get out of here.
I mean it.
Wait. So, if I give you candy,
you'll leave?
Fine.
Here. Happy Halloween.
In other news,
talk show provocateur,
Monica Brown
is still in critical condition
this evening,
following a violent attack
which took place
at KLA Studios earlier today.
The TV host
was violently assaulted
in her dressing room
after a live broadcast
with guest Victoria Heyes.
Heyes is the sole survivor
of the Miles County massacre
of 2017, which left
eight people dead
and Heyes in critical condition.
The 20-year-old was arrested
at the crime scene,
and taken into custody
by authorities.
The interview sparked
controversy
upon its announcement
given Brown's
exploitative tendencies.
Heyes was released
from St. Michael's Hospital
yesterday evening
after months of rehabilitation
and psychoanalysis.
Like you, Sienna.
Halloween is officially here,
and thousands are lining up
for the parade
in New York City's East Village.
Weather conditions are expected
to be cold and rainy,
so dress warm
if you're planning to attend.
No! No!
No!
No, no!
Johnny!
You're still afraid.
Stop it now. I mean it.
They're coming
to get you, Barbara.
Well?
Stop it! You're ignorant.
They're coming for you, Barbara.
It's revealing.
Stop it.
Three months' worth of work,
and all you can say
is it's revealing?
Your tits are practically
popping out.
They are not!
They are! Turn around.
Here he comes now.
Johnny!
You know what I was making?
It's Daddy's character.
Yes, but seeing it on paper
and seeing it on your daughter
are two different things.
You look like you're going
to a strip club.
Mom, this is how people dress
on Halloween these days.
Do you have any idea
how much work
I put into this?
You did an excellent job.
But when did Halloween
become synonymous with sex?
You're such a prude.
Okay. That's my ride. Later.
Sienna.
Dad would have loved it.
Bye.
Allie!
Have you been handing out candy?
That bowl is still filled
to the brim.
Allie!
Oh, my God.
Allie?
Allie? Allie, answer me.
Where are you?
Allie?
Oh, no! No, no! No! No!
Mom.
What'd I tell you?
I never doubted you
for a second.
Come on. Let's go get fucked up.
What can I get you guys?
Uh, vodka and coke, please.
What do you want?
Off your phone.
Uh, rum and coke. Mixed.
Also, can we have two shots
of whiskey, please? Thank you.
Has Allie texted you back yet?
No.
Well, can you check?
Negative.
You know this isn't like her.
It's fine.
Just relax.
And have a good time
for once in your life, okay?
Maybe if I just text her mom,
she will get back to me.
No. Off your phone.
- Phone down.
- Okay!
- Look, we're gonna have fun.
- Mm hmm.
- Stress-free environment.
- Yep.
- Take this.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- All right. Thank you.
Will you excuse me? Sorry.
Oops!
- Let's go.
- Okay. Yep.
Okay.
To a great night with my girls.
- To a great night.
- Happy Halloween.
Oh, God.
Oh, you're such an amateur.
I do not know
how you drink that shit.
Well, chase it.
Oh, you asshole!
Happy Halloween, baby.
You look hot.
Oh, yeah? You like my hair?
I do.
How long did that take?
You don't wanna know.
Ooh!
Yeah, nice shirt.
Wishful thinking.
I bet!
Oh, Jeff.
This is my best friend Sienna.
Hi.
Wow. That is a badass outfit.
Thank you.
This girl
is unbelievably talented.
You have no idea.
She made this whole thing
herself, head to toe.
What did it take you,
like five months?
No. It didn't take that long.
Yes, it did.
You have no idea.
It took forever.
You are unbelievable.
You know, honestly,
I feel upstaged.
Okay.
Could you guys please stop?
You're making me feel
a little self-conscious, so...
Oh. Well, a couple
of shots will help that.
- Oh! Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots!
- Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots!
No. No, no, no.
I cannot drink anymore tonight.
My mom will get so pissed
if I get fucked up.
No, she won't!
Your mom's gonna be asleep
in two hours.
I can't do it.
Okay, fine.
Take a picture of us.
Okay.
Ooh, let's dance!
- Trick or treat!
Kids, look how cool!
Oh my God!
So cool.
Ew. Why is mine so sticky?
Don't
worry. It's just fake blood.
Just put it in the bag.
Ooh, I like it.
Ew.
All right, thank you!
- Thank you!
Let's go. Happy Halloween!
- Happy Halloween!
What are you doing in here?
You wanna watch a movie?
There is a lot of candy
leftover downstairs.
Come on.
I'll let you stay up late.
Go away.
Jonathan.
I am sorry that your plans
were ruined tonight.
I really am.
But you should've thought
about this
before you pulled that shit
in school today.
I mean, enough's enough.
I told you the truth.
- I'm not doing this again.
- It wasn't me!
Well, if it wasn't you,
then I sincerely apologize.
But I just don't believe you
anymore.
What about this?
Again with this fucking book!
Why was Daddy collecting
these news articles?
"Slain girl found at carnival."
And this?
Look at these drawings!
This isn't like Daddy!
He was sick.
Why can't you understand?
He didn't know who he was,
or what he was doing
half the time.
And this.
This bullshit is nothing
but a fucking reminder.
No!
I want this out of my house.
You're such a bitch!
Don't you ever say that
to me again!
Jonathan.
Jonathan, you get back here.
Jonathan!
I'll be right back.
Wait. Where are you going?
I'm gonna grab a drink.
- Yo, can I get a selfie?
- Sure.
Fuck, yeah, girl!
What?
Oh, my God.
Sienna!
- Hey!
- Hi!
I missed you, girl.
Hi.
No, wait.
- Feel this.
- Oh.
Oh.
- Oh, my God.
- No, no. Wait.
You don't understand.
I want it.
- I know.
- I wanna like...
live in it, you know?
- How are you feeling?
- Good.
Yeah?
- So good actually!
- Okay.
I feel like...
that shot's really starting
to hit me.
Well, whiskey will do that
to you.
- I needed this.
- Yeah.
You were right.
- You were so right.
- Yeah.
I needed to just, like get out,
and stop thinking,
worrying about every little
thing in my life.
Like... like this costume.
Yeah.
I mean,
it should be a happy thing.
- Yeah.
- You know?
It reminds me of my Dad.
He used to...
He used to draw this character
for me when I was a little girl.
He used to tell me
I was gonna grow up
to be like her one day.
And I really believed it.
Well, look at you now!
You are her.
I am nothing like her.
I'm not courageous.
I'm not brave.
I mean, I literally
had a panic attack today
in school in front of everybody.
I put molly in your drink.
What?
I did. I put a half a tablet
in your drink,
the other half in mine.
Not even really,
it was kind of nothing.
But it's fine,
'cause I'm also on it.
So, we're totally fine.
You and me.
And that is why you feel
like you're on molly.
'Cause you are.
Right now.
You fuckin' bitch!
What the...
- That is so messed up!
- I did it.
I made you feel better,
didn't I?
I'm fucking pissed.
No, don't be pissed.
You're smiling.
You can't be pissed.
No, bitch. I'm not smiling.
You're totally smiling.
So, we gotta go back out,
and we gotta dance.
Jonathan.
Jonathan, please get back.
Jonathan!
Oh, shit.
What?
My mom called me like six times.
- Ooh. Do not call her back.
- I'm gonna see...
- Don't call her back!
- Shh, shh, shh!
Sienna. Sienna.
- Sienna.
- Hey!
- Stop it.
- He's dead, Sienna!
Wait. What?
Cut the call.
Wait, mom.
Mom, I can't hear you.
Just...
Um, sorry.
Um, what'd you say?
He covered the entire
fucking car with shaving cream!
What?
Yeah! The whole fucking thing.
Shaving cream, toilet paper,
eggs. He's dead!
He...
Jonathan wouldn't do that.
Yeah. He didn't do this.
Just like he didn't vandalize
the school this morning!
Look at this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This... this is crazy now.
He's going to that psychiatrist
immediately.
I cannot deal with him anymore.
Really, mom?
You're gonna send him
to a shrink
because what, he put like
a little bit of shaving cream
on your car?
I'm glad you think
this is funny, Sienna.
It's just shaving cream.
It's not like he took
a baseball bat
to your windshield.
It's Halloween. I mean...
Are you drunk?
- No.
- Yes, you are.
I can hear it in your voice.
How many drinks have you had?
I... I thought we were talking
about Jonathan.
Sienna, so help me,
if you come home plastered
on top of everything else
- I'm dealing with tonight...
- No.
I swear to God, I'm not drunk.
I'll even take a breathalyzer.
You're killing me.
You know that?
You and your brother both,
I have had it.
I love you.
Yeah, Sienna, I am warning you.
No. Really, mom.
I... I love you. I...
I don't say it enough.
I love you, too.
Go and enjoy your party.
I'm... I'm sorry to bother you.
And listen.
Everything will be okay
with Jonathan.
I promise.
Just remember what I said.
Be careful getting home,
all right?
I will. Bye.
Happy Halloween, motherfuckers!
- How'd it go?
- Fine.
All right.
Let me give you a little
molly etiquette here.
Rule number one, you never
ever call your mother
when you're rolling on molly.
Okay? Your mother, never.
All right?
Rule number two,
you don't fucking let it go
to waste. Come on.
Look at this.
Did he really think
he was gonna get away with this?
He is in for a rude awakening.
Things are gonna change.
♪ Pain, always pain ♪
♪ Pain makes the rhythm,
makes the rhythm ♪
♪ Makes the rhythm ♪
♪ Pain, pain makes the rhythm,
makes the rhythm ♪
♪ Makes the rhythm, pain ♪
Do you see that?
There. There.
That little girl.
What is she saying?
What are you talking about?
I... I... I swear to God.
She was right there.
I... I saw her.
She was...
She was... she was right there.
Okay. Come on.
It's bathroom time.
Sienna? Sienna?
Okay. Sienna, look at me.
It's okay. Shh, shh, shh.
Sienna, breathe. Breathe.
Breathe. You're gonna be okay.
Sienna?
Mom!
Help me!
I'm sorry you had to leave.
It's no problem.
You okay?
Sienna, what the fuck was that
back there?
I'm fine.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No! You're not fine.
You are so completely far
from fine right now.
You're just totally freaked out.
Gee, Brooke. I wonder why.
Oh! Don't blame this on me.
I'm on the same shit as you
right now, okay?
- I'm not freaking out.
- Whoa!
What are we talking
about here? What shit?
I put a pinch of molly
in her drink.
It was nothing.
- Plus Xanax.
- What?
I did not give you Xanax.
No, she was already on Xanax,
which I didn't know about, okay?
Let's make that perfectly
fucking clear.
You could've fucking killed me.
I was trying to do
something nice for you.
Jesus Christ!
You're like Ms. Morbid
all the time.
Thanks.
Just take me home.
Sienna, whatever happened
back there was not normal.
Okay?
You could have had like
a brain aneurysm,
or seizure, or something.
What if it happens again?
Wanna take her
to the emergency room?
I... I just...
I just wanna go home.
Just take me home.
If that's your mother,
do not answer it.
Hello.
Sienna, I'm in trouble.
Oh, you think?
Mommy told me
what you did to her car,
you little asshole.
I mean, really?
No.
I need your help.
You have to come get me.
What do you mean?
What's wrong?
Where are you?
I'm at the old carnival.
Eric and Sean left me here.
I'm all alone.
What's wrong with you?
Please.
I'm really scared.
I don't know what else to do.
I can't call mommy.
Okay. Um, all right. Calm down.
I'll come get you, okay?
Hurry, my phone is dying.
All right. Just wait
by the main entrance, okay?
Jonathan? Jonathan? J...
Goddammit.
He's bullshitting you.
No, he's not.
Yes, he is.
It's Halloween.
Are you really telling me
right now
that it's beneath your brother
to do something twisted
like this?
Come on. The old carnival.
No. I... I know
when Jonathan's lying. Okay?
I... I could hear it
in his voice.
Something's... something's wrong.
Sienna! Like, dude...
It's only a few miles from here.
This is so stupid.
Great. Fine. Whatever.
I don't care.
It's not like this night
can get any worse.
Well, where is he?
I told him to wait in front.
- How old's your brother?
- 12.
Even the fact that
he's out here right now
should be telling you something.
Didn't like a little girl
get murdered out here
a couple years ago?
I'm gonna go look for him.
What?
Sienna? Get back in the car.
Sienna!
She's crazy.
Jonathan!
Maybe we should go with her.
Fuck that.
I guarantee you,
her brother's just gonna scare
the shit out of her.
He's turned
into a complete psycho
ever since his father
killed himself.
Ever since what?
No joke.
He had like
this giant brain tumor
that I don't know,
it just made him do
all this fucked-up shit.
And he was like seeing things.
And he got really abusive
towards the end.
Especially towards Sienna.
And then one day,
he drank a whole bottle of Jack,
and he got in his car,
and he drove straight
into one of those
transformer things.
And the car caught fire,
and he got trapped in the wreck.
And he burned to death.
You could hear him screaming
from a mile away.
Well, I've only known
your friend for a few hours,
but that explains a lot.
Yeah.
All things considered,
I think she's doing pretty well.
Come on, answer me.
Where are you?
I'm searching
all over the place.
Help.
Jonathan, can you hear me?
I can't...
Listen.
I'm gonna wait for you
by the merry-go-round, okay?
Did you hear what I said?
Meet me at the merry-go-round.
Hello?
Text me back.
What is that?
A little pick-me-up.
Wow, Jeff. Okay.
Don't let Sienna see that shit.
Well, we'll just have to do it
before she comes back.
I'm not doing that.
You ever try it?
Yeah. Once. I didn't like it.
Oh sure, impossible. Come on.
This will put us
right back in the club.
Fuck.
Trust me.
Okay.
All right. Fuck it.
Um...
okay.
Ugh!
That tastes weird.
Jonathan?
What's wrong?
Where the hell is she?
Who cares?
Wait.
All right.
Look, but, like, seriously,
what time did she leave?
- Well, who cares?
- Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna call her
really fast, okay?
Just really quick.
Where are you going?
I have to go pee-pee.
You wanna hold it?
Ew. Leave.
Hi. It's Sienna.
Leave a message,
and I'll get back to you.
The mailbox is full...
Unbelievable.
...and cannot accept
any messages at this time.
Goodbye...
Asshole!
That's twice!
Oh, it's so funny.
Yeah, you're so funny.
You know
what's actually really funny?
- Mm.
Let me see here. Oh.
Oh, hey. Don't fuck her up.
- Come on.
- Oh.
- Oh, you better say sorry.
- I'm sorry.
And I don't really know
if you can snort this
out of an ashtray.
It'd be kinda hard to snort
out of.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I won't do it again, I promise.
Are you actually sorry?
Hey.
Okay, fine.
But you're a jerk.
Jeff?
Oh, my God!
No! No, no!
Sienna!
Oh, God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Jonathan!
Can you hear me?
Somebody, please!
Help me!
Sienna!
Help!
Brooke!
Oh, my God! No, please! No!
Stay back. Stop. Please stop.
Stay away from me!
Don't, please!
Wait, wait.
No! Please, please stop! No!
No, no, no, no!
Stop it. Stop. No. Please!
No. Stay back.
Don't... don't come near me.
Please don't.
No, no, no!
Brooke!
Brooke.
Jonathan?
Jonathan, run!
Come on.
This way.
Sienna.
You're hurt bad.
I'm all right. I'm all right.
Let me... let me see you.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
You were right.
You were right about everything.
I was right about you, too.
About what?
They used me to get you here.
They need you in this place
for a reason.
What are you saying that?
It's what Daddy saw.
I think you're the only one
who can stop him.
Why?
I don't know.
Well, we gotta find a way
out of here.
Okay, come on.
Wait here.
Jonathan.
Sucker!
Jonathan...
Sienna!
Sienna. Sienna, wake up.
Stay with me. Stay with me!
Please don't go.
Sienna.
Please don't leave me.
Sienna. Baby, wake up.
Mom?
Sweetie, it's okay.
You're safe.
Mom.
Oh, shh, shh, shh.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I thought
I was never gonna see you again.
Oh.
Jonathan told you...
didn't he?
What?
Sienna!
Get away from her!
That's not Mommy!
Jonathan!
No! No!
No! No, you tucker!
Fuck you.
Speaking of some prizes, kids,
we have a very special guest
with us today.
Let me out!
- ♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
♪ The club
is downright gruesome ♪
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
food's a little funny ♪
♪ Food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
Sienna!
Sienna.
You got him.
It's over now. Okay?
Okay.
Please tell me
this is pumpkin spice.
Not a chance in hell.
What is this?
Zombie platter.
My wife made it.
That's disgusting.
Creative, but disgusting.
I wouldn't say
that before you try it.
It's pretty tasty.
Mm. No, thanks.
As appealing
as that brain looks,
I don't really have the stomach
for it right now.
Everything okay?
I've been tending to our
celebrity patient all day.
Is that bad?
Let's just say her face
doesn't stimulate
one's appetite.
- What's she like?
- Tame.
Pretty cooperative actually.
It's kind of hard to imagine
she ripped that woman to pieces.
Pass me one of those eyeballs.
Huh?
And, uh, put some
of that brain jelly on it, too.
And, Lola, don't be stingy.
Oh. There it is. There you go.
Little more.
Thank you.
Diet starts tomorrow, so...
Mm!
Mm.
- What is that?
- Hmm?
That song
you're singing, what is it?
Oh.
I have no idea actually.
Victoria's been singing it
all day.
I can't get it out of my head.
Huh.
♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
You fucking cunt!
Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt!
Oh, God.
♪ Drop on by the clown café
your favorite meals on wheels ♪
♪ The menu is disgusting
and it's full of special deals ♪
♪ Nothing here is good for you
so grab yourself a tray ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ Double up your order quick
before it runs away ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪