How long have we been walking this road?
Has it been fifty years already?
And you've never said a word.
Sorry, miss.
I've gotten old.
What have you brought today?
A bunch of old wire.
Don't worry about the cops.
Nobody's seen the old lady in a few weeks.
In a moment,
they'll drag a corpse out of there.
Wait and see. We'll get a good show.
Is this from a motorbike?
That's my grandpa's era.
I've only seen them in photos
taken back in the day.
Let's do it like this.
For all this, I'll give you… 400,000.
I can strip the copper from the wire,
but the rest has gone to shit. Okay?
I'll take it, 400,000.
Good. Not a haggler.
Less of a headache.
Damn. Vintage.
You've got the old government issue chip?
Fucking ancient.
Ancient technology, ancient man.
Nobody's used
that shit for a thousand years.
Did it even go through?
Yeah, all right.
Go on. Get out of here.
You'll be safe here.
And you won't be alone.
Mom! Whose graves are these?
I don't know. They probably belonged to
a family that lived here a long time ago.
I don't think spirits are lingering here.
Their souls must have
moved on a long time ago.
I like coming here.
It's peaceful.
Come help me up.
Help me with these.
That will do. You better get home.
Your father will want you
back sooner than later.
Go home before he gets angry.
Go on.
Please don't leave me alone here.
All the farm work I do
and it's barely enough to eat.
I sent the boy home to help you.
Where were you all day, boy?
He can't hardly do anything yet.
In the end,
I just have to do everything myself.
I've grown as much as I can.
And we can't rely on
the little bit you sell.
There's a foreign company
in town offering help to farmers.
What kind of help?
How much are these?
Two for 5,000.
Too expensive. Can you give me a deal?
I really can't…
How about three for 5,000?
I can't make any profit
at three for 5,000.
Your vegetables are wilted.
Just sell them at cost.
I lose money at that price.
I'll only pay three for 5,000.
Please add some extra for me.
Hello.
Can we talk, brother?
Is this your mother?
No.
Was she your wife?
Here's the deal.
The woman that runs
the noodle shop went missing.
Nobody knows where she is.
We contacted her daughter in Vientiane.
And why are you here?
Didn't she have a damn microchip?
Isn't that how you usually find people?
We found her microchip inside her shop.
EVIDENCE
That woman.
She had dementia.
She's wandered off before.
She disappears for three
or four days at a time.
Don't worry. She'll come back on her own.
We know that she's dead.
She was all on her own.
Somebody needed to help her.
She could hardly feed herself.
She was skinny as a cat.
She couldn't even run her little shop,
much less take care of herself.
And her daughter? Where was she?
Why wasn't she here to help?
We want you to take us to the body.
Everybody in the village
has heard about you,
that you can talk with spirits.
If you could contact her
spirit and ask her
where her body is…
No.
We just want to recover her body
before her daughter comes back.
If you could help us…
I can't help you.
Here.
Do you see?
You're all right now.
Are you working or what?
When I was your age,
I'd have finished the whole row by now.
Are you going to work today?
Or are you just going to daydream?
Go on. Get out of here.
Check if your mother sold anything.
Enough that we can eat tonight.
Perfect. You came right on time.
I'm getting ready to go home.
Come on. Help me pack up.
Hey! Slow down!
You'll destroy the vegetables.
What's wrong?
I haven't seen you sleep in weeks.
Is something the matter?
That's my mother.
I remember
when you first started following me.
It was before she got sick.
When I was a boy…
was there an old man sitting behind you?
And what happened to him?
Did he ask you that, too?
If you'd sold this bike to me all at once,
I'd have given you a million kip.
Piece by piece…
I've probably paid you twice that by now.
Come on. Try to find something
I can sell to the tourists.
I don't want this shit.
If your mother wandered off
and disappeared into the jungle,
her chances of survival would be low.
Let's go.
Fine. Then stay.
Why are you still here?
Thank you.
We can walk together if you want.
Where are you from?
Can't you talk?
It's all right.
I don't like talking much either, I guess.
There's my mom.
Come on, I'll introduce you to her.
It's okay.
Come on.
I'll get you a beer.
The cops told me that they asked you
to contact my mother's spirit.
Is that something you do?
No.
When I was growing up,
my mom used to tell me
that people would see you walking
down the road with ghosts.
I just want to ask her a question.
They don't answer questions.
I need to tell her that I'm sorry.
How much do I owe you?
Nothing. There's no charge.
I don't really know how to run this place.
And the lease ends next week.
I just need to get rid of what's left
before I go back to the capital.
When I was a boy
my father left us
and went to work in the capital.
My mother was terminally ill.
Her lungs filled up
and she drowned in her own blood.
She died right in front of my eyes.
I was there with her.
Do you think that feeling sorry
changes anything for your dead mother?
I could pay you.
Who are you?
What are you doing in my house?
Leave it there!
Were you eating our food?
I'm sorry, brother.
I'm in the wrong house.
-What's happening?
-Stay inside!
Lock the door. Don't come out.
What are you staring at?
Get the hell out!
If I catch you here again…
I'll drag you to the village chief.
I'm warning you.
Next time, I'll call the authorities.
I thought we knew everybody here,
at least their faces.
But I didn't recognize
that old guy at all.
I shouldn't have chased
him with the machete, the old bastard.
He seemed more confused than anything.
He was probably just hungry, right?
Yeah. You're right.
Oh! There's a piece missing.
Hold it together, okay?
Careful! Be careful!
It's just the fumes from the glue.
Put the kettle on for your mom.
Hello?
He's asking if it's okay to look around.
Yeah, okay.
There's more land behind the house
with good soil for crops.
It's a lot of space.
Something like two hectares.
It's good land. Beautiful land.
Everything grows well.
But I don't have the right equipment--
Don't worry. They know what they're doing.
Yeah, okay.
They'll be back to install your
solar panels sometime next week, okay?
Solar panels?
Yeah.
But we don't need electricity.
These instructions are
for you to read, brother.
I really just need a tractor.
Well, our organization doesn't
really do that.
He asked if you understood everything?
Hello!
Sorry for the mess. I'm moving out.
You said you'd pay me.
Of course.
Not the microchip. I want cash.
I need a pen and paper.
And something personal
that belonged to her.
She wore this for ten years,
before I bought her a new one.
This comb still has some
of her hair in it.
This will do.
You needed a pen, right?
Is she here?
Who?
My mother.
The lights never flicker like that.
She didn't die here, did she?
No. I don't think so.
Will I be able to see her?
It doesn't work like that.
But I'll be able to talk to her?
Let it be.
Don't read it now.
That's it?
Did you want more?
Was that not enough
of a show for your money?
"Your mother isn't here."
What does that mean?
Here's your money.
Go back to the capital.
What can I do with 400,000 kip?
My mother was missing for a month.
I didn't even know she was gone.
I quit my job.
I sold everything I owned.
Whatever I have left is
packed in a few bags.
I knew my mother was crazy.
I knew she was wandering off.
I don't even know where to go next.
Your mother died alone.
How would you even know that?
Do you want a cup of tea?
What?
I'm making tea. Come join me.
If you need a place to live, stay here.
Come on! Don't just stand there.
Get down. If my dad sees me,
he'll make me work.
I want to show you something.
You know… my mom was pregnant
once when I was little.
Just like you were.
I saw your suitcase in the jungle.
You packed baby clothes.
I think you ran away from home.
My baby sister died in mom's belly.
I guess the baby was too sick.
After the baby died,
my parents never talked about her again.
It doesn't matter.
It was a long time ago.
I was really young then.
This is my mom's favorite place.
Do you like it?
Don't worry. Nobody comes here.
Just me and my mom.
This place is nice.
It's sunny, but it's also got shade.
It's peaceful.
I think it would be a good place
to bury your body.
What do you think?
That is called lettuce in Lao.
Organic vegetables
Fresh from the garden
You have to take me back.
Back to see my mother.
I know you made it happen.
Please.
I know it was you.
I need to go back
to take care of something…
Who are you talking to?
Come on. Let's go home.
Here, sister…
Let me help you.
Thank you, but I can manage.
No worry. I can help.
It's not so heavy.
Let me help.
I might be old,
but I can still carry a basket.
Thank you.
The other night,
I wandered into the wrong house
and I accidentally broke
something of yours.
I wanted to return it to you.
Here. Have some tea.
It's bitter.
It's an old family recipe.
It's dried wildflowers and honey.
It will help your cough.
Thank you.
Will you stay and keep me company?
Just until my son comes.
Of course.
I might rest my eyes.
Take a rest.
I'll watch things for you here.
I'm sorry if I somehow offended you.
It's okay.
I can see her, too.
Perhaps she wanted the two of us to meet.
I gave your mother something
to help her sleep.
Are you a doctor?
No, I'm not a doctor.
But the girl and I can help your mother.
I was there when she died.
Of course, you were.
Just like I was there
with her fifty years ago.
Your mother won't get better.
There's no treatment.
How do you know?
Maybe, I don't.
Take the money you have
and buy medicine for your mom.
Hide the rest of it from your father.
And if you decide that you need help…
The girl knows where to find me.
Let's go.
Who's the girl in the photo
you keep in the cabinet?
I found it in the jungle.
She was pretty, so I kept it.
I think I've seen her before.
No.
You haven't seen her.
How long has this been cracked?
Does it matter?
It does.
It's always been broken.
Did I tell ever you how my mother died?
You said she was sick.
Did I say how she was sick?
Something with her lungs.
You said she was coughing up blood.
Really?
That's how I said she died?
Don't you remember?
Of course, I remember.
But the cabinet's cracked now.
Everything has changed.
What's my name?
Why would I need to know your name?
Come on. Get up.
I'm going to bed.
Why is your bag so heavy?
Is it rocks?
You play all day. Just being useless,
while I slave under the hot sun,
and your mother works on the roadside.
And you're out collecting
shit in the jungle?
Here. Your mother is staying in bed today.
I already packed her basket.
You'll have to go sell in her place.
The old man said…
that you died fifty years ago.
But when I met you,
you were still alive.
If my mom died…
She wouldn't be sick anymore.
Just like you, right?
You died and you're still here.
Careful. Don't mess with their equipment.
They'll be back to check
on it at some point.
We need to keep it nice for them.
We hardly have enough money to eat.
Where will we find more
to pay for this electricity?
Whatever.
At the very least,
we'll have enough light
to watch each other
while we starve to death.
Go check on your mother.
I'll go see about dinner.
Your father says you worked for me today.
Where did you get this, son?
You didn't steal it, did you?
I found it inside an old suitcase
out in the jungle.
You just happened to find
a suitcase full of money?
Okay, then. I'll put it some place safe.
You lied to me.
You said you could communicate
with my mother's spirit.
I only told you
that your mother's spirit
wasn't in your house.
Then where is she?
Is she here?
No.
Where do you go all day?
Your house is filled with dried flowers,
and bones from God knows where.
Is this some sort of occult shit?
Or is it witchcraft?
My mother's necklace…
You asked me to talk to your mother.
And I have.
And she gave this to you?
I found her body.
It just took me a while.
It's already late.
Her body's a distance away.
I'll take you to her in the morning.
Go rest.
Do you want a cup of tea?
When my mother died,
the villagers cremated
her body in the temple.
The monks told me
that my mother had moved on.
But moved on to what, I don't know.
Was she reborn?
Whatever happens next for you…
I don't know.
I'm so sorry.
Her arm had stitches.
Doesn't that feel strange?
She's been out here for three months.
We should let her daughter take the body.
She can give her mother a proper
funeral and let her move on.
People don't change when they die.
They don't get less crazy
or start thinking clearly.
Your mother couldn't have
answered your questions.
Hello?
…and there are other women
that have gone missing.
I looked it up.
Seven years ago, another woman--
Seven years ago? Come on.
I believe him.
He found her body.
I'm going back to Vientiane soon.
It's all over now.
Is your mother out of bed, dear?
Good. We were all a little worried.
Your family lives so far out of town.
Here you are, dear.
Especially with that nasty
cough that's been going around.
Take care of yourselves.
Do you need anything else?
The old man said that if I needed help,
you'd take me to him.
I'm not saying I need help.
But why would I need you to take me?
Why couldn't I go myself?
Where the hell have you been?
Did you know?
Did you know that your bitch mother
was hiding money from me?
Why don't you ever talk?
Are you drunk, Dad?
You little bastard, am I drunk?
I'm so sorry, son…
I didn't hide it well enough.
Come on.
Fill this hole before I throw my back out.
Here, help me.
You know this place, don't you?
Do you see them out there?
I'm responsible for these souls.
I put them to sleep
and then I wake them here.
They were all sick and in pain.
And I helped them die at peace.
But…
Why don't they move on?
No.
They're at peace here.
When our mother dies,
I want you to bury her here.
I want to teach you something.
My father never hit me or my mother.
And he never broke the cabinet.
He found the money in my bag.
I explained where I'd found it.
He and my mother discussed it
and my father went to work in the city.
And your father?
Where did he go?
I just know that he left.
That's different.
Doesn't matter. It still happened.
Our father left us both.
You don't look like you have
the money for medicine.
This tea…
Will help your mother's cough.
This medicine,
half of a pill will stop the pain.
A whole pill will make her sleep.
But take absolute care…
No more than two pills a day.
Understood?
One day, when you're old…
And a boy comes to ask you for help,
you teach him this, as well.
So that he can help his mother.
Do you understand?
And what about you?
Who taught you?
I heard voices. You were talking to a boy.
Was the girl
from the photograph there, too?
Why does she visit you?
I was there when she died.
Hello, little boy.
I think you might be the boy
I've been looking for.
Sorry… Here, let me show you.
The villagers have seen you walking
with a young woman.
But whenever they get close,
she disappears.
This was my daughter.
Have you seen her?
She ran away from home months ago.
I just want to find her.
I want to give her a proper funeral,
so that her spirit can move on.
Please. Can you help us?
That's enough, isn't it?
This is a waste of time.
I didn't know you had a dog.
I'm sorry.
Here, dear.
Is this your mother's ring?
People saw your father leave
for the city on the bus.
If you and your mother need to eat,
just take the rice.
We've arrived.
Well, this is it.
It's cool.
It's been comfortable enough.
I promised you dinner.
Let me make something.
She told me that you helped her
find her mother's body.
Thank you.
I liked that one shop
where we used to get coffee.
I remember.
Give me your hand.
Yeah, right there.
It vibrates and it's like
the music is inside my head.
That's awesome.
They put the chip against the bone.
And it's good surgical work. No scars.
I'm going to get my eyes done next.
You should come back with me.
I want to.
I don't have a job anymore.
Don't worry… I'll take care of you.
I should probably go. It's late already.
Just stay.
It's late. You can sleep here.
The weather's cool. I'll sleep outside.
I guess that if I forgot anything…
You can throw it out.
Or you can try to sell it.
If you want it,
I left dinner for you.
It's not much, but…
Thank you.
Goodbye, Uncle.
I'm thirsty.
How long did the seizure last?
Can she still speak?
It scared me that first time.
And it scared me every time after that.
The seizures will get worse every time.
She'll have difficulty breathing.
She'll be in constant pain.
And then she'll slowly die.
You told me no more than two pills a day.
As you grow up, you're going to
meet people who need our help.
People that don't deserve to suffer.
This is how we help them.
Do you understand?
No.
You will soon.
Let me help you up.
The seizure frightened your boy.
He asked me to come help you.
Thank you.
Wake her up.
Mom?
You were supposed to help her.
Bury her in the clearing
beside the grave pillars.
She always liked the flowers there.
Don't let them cremate her.
Get out!
Get out! Both of you!
Mom?
Are you there, mom?
I'm hungry.
Please. I'm begging you.
Keep up.
You should bathe.
Don't you want me to undress for you?
Of course not.
You usually take my clothes
to keep me from running away.
Is that something you do?
Once.
Are you going to run off again?
Take a bath.
Come back up when you're done.
I'll find you something to wear.
Does this belong to one of you?
I didn't do this to you.
You're not one of mine.
Hello?
I see you're looking better.
Here. Go put these groceries
in the kitchen.
Go on. Move.
How are you? Are you feeling better?
Please don't take her.
If we don't do the proper
ceremony for your mother,
she won't realize that she's passed away.
She needs to see us prepare her body,
so she can accept death.
Tomorrow we'll take her
to the temple for the cremation
so her spirit can be reborn
and she can move on.
Understand?
I don't want her to move on.
Darling, don't say things like that.
Put your hands together
and focus on praying, okay?
How did the candle go out?
We don't want her spirit getting lost.
There. Concentrate on your prayers.
Hey, where are you going?
This is where you'll sleep.
Focus on your studies and your new life
until your father comes back for you.
He won't come.
You don't know that.
Have faith that he'll return.
Hello, sister.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Are you well?
I'd like to make
a take away order, please.
Two servings of caramelized pork stew.
Thank you.
No.
No, no.
Cannot.
-You can't. No.
-Sister.
-No, no, no. You can't. Cannot.
-It's okay, sister. Calm down.
Just sit down. I have cash.
I don't need any change.
Lina.
Lina? Where did Lina go?
Where are you, dear?
Why would it be you?
Why did I take you?
Sit down.
Finish eating.
I'm not hungry.
Stop that.
I'm used to it now.
You have a girlfriend in the city.
That girl with tattooed hands.
I know you don't want to fuck an old man.
I'll put your dinner away.
You can eat it tomorrow morning.
Mom?
I brought you dinner.
A boy came to the house today.
He talked to me through the door.
Who is he?
He's the reason why you're here.
No.
You're the reason I'm here.
I'm going to fix this.
It will be like you were never here.
For who?
For me or for you?
Satu.
Don't walk away from me!
Where are you going?
Come back here!
Did I die?
You told me the dead don't feel pain.
There was a girl locked inside your house.
There was.
She left already.
She told me that you hurt her.
I didn't hurt her.
Then who did?
My mother died because she was sick.
-But your mother--
-You killed my mother.
I didn't think I could change
things so much.
I was wrong.
I haven't hurt anybody.
Not yet, perhaps.
But you will.
You'll hurt that girl.
And a dozen others.
Why would I do that?
I don't know.
You have to help me.
My leg is injured.
I've lost too much blood.
I can barely walk.
I can't help you.
I don't want to be like this.
Help!
Are they all gone?
In the end…
I never helped any of those women.
They suffered more for it.
I watched you grow up.
Grow old.
And then die.
Circling around a thousand times.
And what about the boy?
He only died once.
You held my hand while I was dying.
And I loved you for that.
I did.
But you only helped yourself.
You never helped me.
Back then…
I couldn't have kept you from dying.
But you could have let me move on.
You never did.
Will we be together?
Walking up and down
that road for eternity?
I don't know where you go.
Will you stay with me?
Just until I die.
No.
Hey, lady!