Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
The life of a small-town boy
is so carefree that
I sometimes wish I could stop time.
I don’t want to grow up
just to see…
Suppalo is an all-boys secondary school
with a long-standing prestigious reputation
because we believe that…
With rules comes honor.
Just because the rules are long-established doesn’t mean they should continue.
The school has no right to dehumanize us.
[School uniforms won’t make us smarter.]
We have full rights to our bodies.
No school uniform.
Suppalo’s reputation is on your hand, Akk.
Take care of it.
Yes, sir.
(They say as the solar eclipse approaches)
(the curse becomes stronger.)
No school uniform.
Hey!
Look out!
Shit! No driver.
How did that truck get here with no driver?
Is it the curse again?
Ouch!
It hurts.
Wat, Kan, take care of things here.
Where are you going?
Excuse me.
Move!
Sorry.
You, newbie.
This restroom is for teachers.
Students have no business using it.
Why are you here then?
I’m a prefect.
So?
Why are you not wearing Suppalo’s school uniform?
I don’t want to.
But you must.
It's the rule.
I will when I want to.
Okay?
I’m a prefect.
My duty is to make everyone follow the rules.
Why don’t you deal with that accident instead of picking on me?
Students under your care almost got hit by a car.
Not your concern.
We will take care of that.
How rigid.
My first day here is already amusing.
I'm curious what more this school has in store for me.
There was no one in the car.
How did it drive itself?
The Suppalo curse.
It was the flower pot last time.
This time, a ghost car.
What next?
Here he comes.
Look at him.
Hey.
Why a long face?
Did you take care of it?
Yes. Where have you been?
I followed the new kid.
He was acting so shady.
An old issue remains unsolved.
A new issue arises.
Kan, you're the biggest fan of the Suppalo curse in our school.
Consider what’s been happening lately.
Honestly, this is too much to handle for Mr. Kan.
Mr. Kan, can I just kick you in the face?
Wat, you’re talking like a bastard.
Are you kicking me?
I must get him.
The newbie?
Do you know which class he’s in?
Where will you get him?
Hi, guys.
Today we get to welcome a new friend.
Please come in.
Introduce yourself to your friends.
My name is Ayan.
You can call me Aye.
Ayan, have a seat next to Thuaphu.
Thuaphu, please help guide him.
Of course, Teacher.
He can sit with me.
Kanlong will sit with Thuaphu.
I’m a prefect.
I will take care of him.
Is that okay?
Sure.
You, come sit here.
Thanks, Akk.
Please.
Whatever you’re here for,
I’ll be watching you.
Keep that in mind.
Catch me if you can.
[Ayan Sukkhapisit]
That new kid is really from Parot School.
That’s our rival.
Why did he transfer three weeks after school started?
It’s totally unusual.
Maybe
he came to ruin our school’s reputation.
Hey.
In every movie I watch,
each character has a goal and motive to do something.
That means
we must find his motive, right?
Right.
Shameless,
what’s your goal?
But the only goal I have here
is to know when you guys will start eating.
It’s all burnt, jackasses.
Okay. Let’s eat.
And why are you eating BBQ pork in my room?
You’re making my room smelly.
Are you eating it or not?
I am!
No!
[Mom]
Yes, Mom.
How is it going?
Do you need anything from here?
I’ll get it for you after the meeting is done.
No.
You can focus on your work.
You got a flight to catch, don’t you?
How is school?
Good.
Pretty fun.
I think you should transfer back to your old school.
Parot School?
No.
The one you’d always gone to.
You don’t need to follow…
No.
I will go here.
I’ve made up my mind.
Talk to you later.
I’m going to school.
Hold on, Aye!
Why are you here?
Why aren’t you in class?
Is it against the rules to just hang out?
Take that back!
You punch me once.
I kiss you once.
The rules there are really strict.
Make one tiny mistake and you will be closely monitored.
Why are you still not wearing the school uniform?
I will wear it when I want to.
Do you wear it because you want to or someone made you to?
I’m willing to.
Nobody made me.
You’re tame.
No surprise you've been selected as The Prefect Club president
in this age when people don't believe in archaic and foolish rules.
Take that back!
Suppalo rules are not foolish.
Is the rule keeper breaking the rule by using violence against me now?
But I’m telling you.
You punch me once.
I kiss you once.
Want it?
(All student prefects, please proceed to the Student Welfare Department immediately.)
You get away this time.
If I didn’t get called, you’d get hurt.
What a shame.
You just missed a kiss from me.
What a jackass!
You’ll have to deal with me one day.
Bring it on.
Right here. Right now.
Shut up.
Don’t you think I wouldn’t hit you.
I just love
people who are cocky.
Hey!
Mr. Sit,
can you please confirm if you did or did not put on the handbrake when parking the car?
I’m not sure.
I usually do it every time.
Then you can’t confirm if you did.
Teacher.
Mr. Sit has been the school driver for over 10 years.
Do you really think he forgot to put on the handbrake?
That’s right.
That’s possible.
So it might be an accident.
Wait a minute, Teacher.
Isn’t it too fast to jump to that conclusion?
Why don't you investigate thoroughly?
Someone wants to hurt your students.
No one is hurting anyone.
How do you know that?
This isn’t the first something like this happens to us.
It’s the curse.
You guys were causing trouble.
That’s why the curse is back.
Did you forget?
Every time the solar eclipse is near,
a curse falls upon Suppalo students who violate the rules.
You’re a science program student.
How could you believe in such nonsense?
Teacher,
this isn’t an accident.
Someone is behind this.
You must catch the one who is responsible.
Right.
You can’t let the issue go away.
Someone is behind it.
It’s an accident.
There’s no way our school members would hurt each other.
Don’t ever let me hear that accusation again.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
Did you see?
‘The World Remembers’ group is now affected by the curse.
You’re right.
The other day,
a flower pot fell from the English teacher’s room, right next to them.
Luckily, they didn’t get hit.
And yesterday, a car with no driver almost hit them.
They say as the solar eclipse approaches, the curse becomes stronger.
Teacher Chadok,
did we really make a good judgment?
Why?
If the students aren’t satisfied and digging into it themselves,
what’s going to happen?
Why don’t we…
You’re an assistant to a student welfare teacher.
You still lack experience.
Just do your job.
Do not question.
Understood?
Yes.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
Teacher Waree,
since I’m new here, may I ask you a question?
Yes.
Is the school curse real?
I’m dealing with the accident yesterday.
The students don’t believe it was an accident.
So I think…
What did your boss say?
Teacher Chadok said we leave it as is.
Trust him then.
If you want to work here for long,
don’t get involved in anything that isn't your business.
Will you please excuse me?
[So this is how the rule breakers are punished.]
If we break the rules,
what will they do to us?
Hey, newbie.
Why are you here?
Why aren’t you in class?
Just hanging out.
Is it against the rules to just hang out?
He’s a real pain like you said.
Believe me now?
He’s such an ass.
Give it back.
Give me that.
I need to use it.
Just follow the rules.
Who sent you to mess with this school?
What are you doing?
Your pin tilts.
It is not you at all.
Why are you here?
Why aren’t you in class?
Give it back.
Give me that.
Give it.
Don’t you know it’s against the school rule to use a phone?
It’s mine. Give it back.
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
Or what?
I’m a student prefect.
But what you’re doing is like a thief.
Not a prefect.
Give it back.
Give it to me.
Akk.
Kan , Wat.
You can collect it later at the student welfare department.
But I need to use it now.
If you can’t follow the rules, you don’t deserve to be in this school.
Go back to class.
You can’t pretend to be a prefect.
That.
Where did you get that?
I want to be a prefect.
Accept me in your Prefect Club, please.
Please.
You registered but were not qualified.
Try to understand.
But I can improve.
I’m trying to up my GPA to 3.
And I’m working out hard.
Please include me.
You can’t be.
Come on.
Hey!
Guys!
All right.
That’s all for today.
Don’t forget the assigned group report.
Yes, ma’am.
Students, say thank you.
Thank you, Teacher.
What a long day.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
I’m fine.
You don’t need to get so close to me.
I know.
Don’t forget to gather the info.
I’ll call and let you know when we’re doing it.
My mom is here.
Yes.
You’re so bossy.
Just go.
Don’t forget to search for the info.
Yes.
Well, well.
Aren’t you going with your boyfriend?
Boyfriend, my ass.
Do not tease me about that, Wat.
People will misunderstand.
But I’m wondering…
Okay.
Easy, man.
Akk.
Want to go for a beach walk?
Akk!
[Just because the rules are long-established doesn’t mean they should continue.]
[Christmas Board Activity]
What do you think you’re doing?
Just looking at these leaflets.
They’re interesting.
The World Remembers gang is so cool.
The next Hyde Park is going to be so much fun.
Don’t you even think about joining them.
Why not?
Are you worried about me?
Are you afraid I’d be cursed like them?
You already know about that.
That’s all the more reason not to join.
Unless you’re the one behind them, stirring things up.
It’s so outdated to think the protesters have someone backing them up.
Why don’t you think everyone has their brain and can think for themselves?
They have the right to question what’s not right.
If they can think, why don’t they think they should abide by the rules?
So that everyone is happy and peaceful.
Chaos wouldn’t be happening.
Who is happy in this case?
If they are truly happy with your rules, why would they protest?
I’m wondering.
Rules are there to follow.
Why can’t you do such an easy thing?
It’s not that we can’t.
The question shouldn’t be about why we can’t do it.
It should be why we must do it.
Who sent you to mess with this school?
Your old school?
What are you doing?
Your pin tilts.
It is not you at all.
Here.
Let me fix it for you.
And you look like The Prefect Club president again.
Don’t.
Give that back.
What are you doing?
Your pin tilts.
It is not you at all.
Let me fix it for you.
And you look like The Prefect Club president again.
Don’t.
Akk, focus!
Ouch!
Thua, did you just prank me?
No.
Here. Read this and summarize it for me.
Then we’re done.
You should’ve just said it nicely.
You wouldn’t listen.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Read this page.
This page too.
From there to…this page.
And summarize it.
You hate me that much?
No.
Let’s get to work.
I’m meeting a girl at the night school.
Nian, what should we write?
Let’s see.
Rules are there to break.
Oops!
Oopsy-daisy!
Come on.
Faster.
These guys never learn their lesson.
The curse will get to them again.
Do you think so?
Hey!
What are you doing here?
You’ve been following me everywhere.
Are you into me, prefect?
That’s nice.
Beautiful.
We go hard this time. The school board will be so surprised.
I hope that’s true.
They never care about us.
Don’t worry.
They will pay attention to us now.
This is grand.
Not just one of us.
But all three of us.
Who’s there?
Is that…
The protest against the school uniform has gone bigger.
Yeah?
I think someone is behind this.
Someone behind the protesters?
Yes.
The protesters always backed off after the curse fell upon them.
They were not as stubborn as they are now.
Who do you think is behind them?
The new kid from Parot School named Ayan.
Ayan?
A student in your class?
Yes, sir.
I’m afraid if he keeps inciting them, my Prefect Club won’t be able to handle them.
And I’m afraid…
The curse will be back.
Right?
Right, sir.
You must stop them.
It’s your duty.
Do you get it, Akk?
Yes, sir.
I’ll do my best.
Keep an eye on Ayan.
Find out what he really wants.
We might be able to fix it in time.
Yes, sir.
Perhaps,
what we’ve been keeping,
the regulations and the reputation for over 100 years
is ruined just because of an outsider who doesn’t have faith like that boy.
I got it.
So?
Have you found it?
One second, Uncle.
Hold on.
Almost get it.
Found it.
‘Equality’ is a noun meaning the state of being equal.
Fairness.
That’s right.
When you learn a new word, you must know its part of speech, its role, and its true meaning.
So that you can use it correctly.
Its true meaning?
Right.
The true meaning.
[Suppalo’s English Department Building]
Hey!
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
You’ve been following me everywhere.
Do you like me, prefectly?
I’m not a friend you can play with.
Do you think of me as more than a friend then?
If you don’t shut that foul mouth,
it will get punched by me.
You’re small but trashtalker.
I’m small and what?
What can a big guy like you do to me?
I can do more than you think.
Do you even know what I’m thinking?
What are you doing in a teacher’s room this hour?
I came to seek advice from an English teacher.
Have you forgotten I started three weeks later than you?
I don’t believe you.
We all know it's too early for anyone to come.
You came.
You’re as early as me.
It’s not unusual.
The flower pot that fell from here,
does it have anything to do with the school curse?
Nian and Nong,
I can’t stand the student welfare department anymore.
I think we should upgrade our protest.
How about in front of the department?
Nian!
Nice idea.
That sounds nice but…
Aren’t you afraid of the Suppalo curse?
Come on!
The curse isn’t real!
Shit!
How did this happen?
I told you.
The curse is getting us.
It’s scary.
How did you know about that?
It happened before you joined this school.
#SuppaloScaryStories is pretty well-known.
But I don’t believe it’s the curse.
Why?
A plant doesn’t have hands. it can't move itself.
Someone did it for sure.
Your school sucks.
If you hate it here, why did you join?
You get mad so easily.
Seriously, what did the school members ever do to you?
What did we do to you?
Why are you ruining our reputation?
Mr. Sit.
Hey.
Can I help you?
Did you know Mr. Dika, an English teacher who used to teach here?
I just transferred from Parot.
Yes.
What a shame.
He’s a good teacher.
He shouldn’t have been bought somewhere else.
Why do you think he's bought?
I heard the rumor.
He’s a great teacher.
A great employee.
When he was an assistant in the student welfare department,
Teacher Chadok was so harsh on him,
After that, they were on good terms for a while.
Then he suddenly quit.
Teacher Dika was an assistant in the student welfare department?
If you hate it here, why did you join?
You’ve been following me everywhere.
Do you like me, prefectly?
Directed by Tanwarin Sukkhapisit
I know you came to mess with my school.
But your method isn’t working on me.
What’s wrong, Big Foot?
You’re tense.
What can be a problem if you’re close to me?
You want it now, Shortstop?
Sure, Big Foot.
I can go to your room right now.
Next time, you don’t have to protect me.
I don’t want to see you get hurt like that again.
Do you want to be my boyfriend?