Kham!
What are you doing?
Easy, dude.
Put the knife down.
Just tell me what you want.
I did, Sergeant.
You ignored me.
Back off!
I won't, until you drop the knife.
It's too late, Sergeant.
I have no choice.
Kham! No!
I'll teach you "The Elephant",
Muay Thai's first technique.
-What's this?
-The elephant's tusks.
What about this?
-The trunk.
-The elephant's shaking it off.
What is this called?
-The ears.
-The elephant's flapping his ears
five times at once.
One, two, three, four, five.
Kham, you teach me only the dance moves.
What if we've been hit?
Mud, come here.
You're curious, right? Come here.
Want to know how?
Check this out.
Which part of Khon that is
the strongest and most lethal?
His tusks.
Exactly. If so,
the key of "The Elephant" technique
is using our body's strongest part.
Our elbow.
To defend and attack.
Hit me.
Right here.
Then, it's like twisting the trunk.
Mud! Get home now!
How many times have I told you
not to learn this nonsense?
Why don't you go to school?
How is this bullshit
any better than my stick?
Kham! I've said too many times
that your elephant
is not allowed at the market.
Look at the mess he's made.
If you want to keep that elephant,
live in the jungle.
Mud! You go home now.
Quick.
Khon, come on.
Khon, move.
Come here.
Kham.
I have something to show you.
Come on. This way, come here.
I want you to see this.
If you keep pulling pranks on me,
I'll tell the monk about this
and then you're out of here.
Please don't tell him.
The Lord Buddha said that
making an experiment
requires a hypothesis,
trials and errors,
here and there,
then we can be successful.
Wait! Kham!
My ass.
Ouch!
Come on.
Kham.
-Come on.
-Kham.
Stay hungry and foolish, Kham.
Stay hungry and foolish.
Keep that in mind.
I can guarantee that
you'll love that elephant, sir.
Sir, he's here.
Please.
What do you think, sir?
He has excellent features
of the finest breed.
-His species--
-Enough. Too much information.
You'd better get the papers
for this gentleman.
Come on.
You touch him. I kick you.
No need to make a scene.
Just name your price.
Only a fool
-thinks money can buy anything.
-Hey.
You talk like that bitch
I fucked last night.
"You can't buy me." So what?
She was in the shower when I left.
Hey.
Suchart's interested.
It can be your best shot, man.
Your elephant
would have a better living
than in this wasted land.
-You can't even make a living.
-Pride has its price.
I'll ask you one more time
how much does this elephant cost?
Same price as your mom and dad's.
Hey!
Kham!
Dad has some coconuts for you
but you have to go and get them.
I'm talking business here.
I don't want to threaten or hurt you.
Even I can do it.
Give him my contact information.
Damn you. Only a fool loves his elephant
more than money.
That's a lot of money.
What a fool!
Hey! Kham.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm glad you're here.
Please watch Khon for me.
I'll be back. Come on.
Back when?
Take these for me.
A male elephant, aged 40 years old,
weighing around two tons
was found dead in crouching position
with his face down.
All four legs were bent backwards
and there was a long cut on his face
from his eyes to his mouth.
The most notable point was
that his tusks were sliced off,
as well as the tip of his tail.
-In the middle of the forest...
-What the hell?
There was also a gunshot wound
about one centimeter wide
at the right side of his mouth.
Look.
I've just read the previous case
in the paper.
Another dead elephant?
...before he was injured
and died at that spot.
Officials have prepared...
ONE SHOT DEAD
WILD ELEPHANT POACHER
...near the elephant's body.
Piak, Pon. Thanks.
Job!
Kham! They're...
taking Khon.
SUCHART WILAWANDET
Pinit, sir.
Is this line secured?
Are you alone?
Go on, sir.
You delivered that elephant?
I did.
Just wondering,
we've plenty of elephants,
why do they need this one?
Or you could ask
what do they want to do with him?
You don't want to know that.
Our job is done.
All I need to say is
we no longer know each other.
I think you should lay low for a while.
-That's it.
-Sir.
Where's Suchart?
Second floor.
Uncle!
Uncle! Uncle!
You!
Stop!
I didn't kill him.
Follow him! Quick!
Ping.
Hands up!
Sergeant Mark.
Kham.
Sergeant, you all right?
I'm bleeding. Can't you see?
-Sergeant.
-Call the medic now.
Was it him?
I'm not sure.
It's too fast.
Ouch! It hurts.
There's no camera in this room.
-But we've got enough evidence.
-Yeah?
You see that?
Of course. I'm not blind.
He was hit three times with a hard object.
A hard object?
-What kind of hard object?
-I think it's a man's fist.
You mean he was beaten to death?
The killer must be a pro, Sergeant.
He knows martial arts.
That's why he almost cracked your skull.
Lucky that you survived.
We're really grateful, Sergeant Mark,
for tipping us off with the leads
from Interpol.
You even chased after the suspect.
Are you kidding me?
You guys run like cripples.
So lame.
-I couldn't stand it.
-Take it easy, Sergeant.
It's great that you helped us.
I want to fight with No.2.
What is this?
"Rank 31 wants to fight No.2?"
"That's a fucking suicide."
"Let me see him handle her first,
all right? Then we'll talk."
What? Her? Stronger than me?
Stop!
-Sergeant, what're you doing here?
-I should be the one asking you.
Why were you there?
-In Suchart's house.
-I was looking for Khon.
Looking for Khon?
You've lost your elephant again?
Is he that small?
He disappears all the time.
Sergeant, listen.
Suchart and his men went to my place
to buy Khon.
I said no.
When he left, Khon was missing.
So, you killed him?
You talk like you don't know me.
That's because I know you.
I know your madness.
Lucky you,
I still believe that you're naive.
That's why I didn't turn you in.
Kham!
You can't go anywhere.
Sergeant, if you're not gonna help me,
stay out of my way.
You might think that
Khon is just an elephant.
But for me,
he is my little brother.
Your dad fucked an elephant?
You!
Hands off!
Get off me.
I don't want this
and I have something to tell you.
Tomorrow, the leader of Katana
will visit Thailand.
There will be a terrorist attack.
That's why I'm here.
Then I met you
unexpectedly.
Kham.
I can help you if you trust me.
Tell me the truth.
What truth?
I know nothing.
Take it easy, girls. Easy!
Asshole!
Get him!
Fuck you!
Move.
Cars!
Hold it!
MEET ME AT THE SHIPYARD,
MARK
SENDING
Let me go! Let me go!
Who are you people?
-Let's go!
-Hey!
I can't breathe, asshole!
Let me go!
...please leave a message.
Stop it.
Wait.
Stop!
I didn't kill him.
Do we need to babysit him?
Hey! He told me to get rid of him.
Let me eat this first.
Shit. It's me again?
Damn you.
You ruin my lunchtime.
Should I cut your ears off?
Make it quick.
Just stab him in the neck.
What the hell?
Hey!
Why did you guys kill my uncle?
Easy, girl. Calm down.
Why did you do that? Why?
You don't look like one of them.
Call Lieutenant Kong for me.
Lieutenant Kong.
I told you he'll be here.
Who's that? Is she with you?
The victim's family.
Can I go now?
I'm feeling so stiff.
As you can see,
he was killed
by the lethal attack
at three vital spots
almost at once.
His xiphoid process was cracked
so he couldn't breathe.
He bent down
but he was hit by the second blow
at his neck
so his windpipe got ruptured.
The victim lowered his head by reflex
to get the final blow
at the top of his head.
That's the nerve center of our body.
In short,
the one who did this
must be a professional killer.
I'm sleepy. I'm go to bed now.
Turn off the lights, okay?
Yeah.
She's not the injured one.
Take good care of Khon, my boy.
Keep in mind that he is
a divine elephant
from Akkanipong's family.
Promise me
that you will take care of him
the best you can.
Don't worry about Khon, Dad.
I'll protect him
with my life.
Finally we meet you.
I'm a big fan of you.
Especially what you did in Sydney.
Superb.
For the past five years,
I've been quite disappointed.
You live like a country boy
eating sugarcane.
That's not a life
for a man with your skills.
I decided to give you a job
in my organization.
You get a lot of money...
...a lot of pussy...
...and all the coconut you can eat.
What do you say, Kham?
You said no?
You need to be persuaded
by something else, perhaps.
Kham!
Job!
Join us, or your friend dies.
He'll count to three.
One.
Two.
Wait! Wait! Stop!
Too late, too late indeed.
A fighter should be fast.
That's okay.
One more chance.
One more surprise.
Khon!
Untie me!
Kham.
Stay hungry and foolish.
You're killing your elephant.
If you do it again, your elephant is dead.
Wait.
What's happening?
Kham!
What are you doing?
Drop your knife!
Kham.
Trust me.
Put it down.
What do you want?
-Just tell me.
-I did, Sergeant.
You ignored me.
Step back!
I won't
until you drop the knife.
It's too late, Sergeant.
I have no choice.
Kham! Don't! Kham!
Ouch! Wait!
Damn it.
You're not gonna ask me, are you?
What do you know? Tell me.
Okay. I will. Easy, dude.
Well,
Boss says you won't make it.
They will be here to kill you.
I just came to check
that you're dead for sure.
That's all I know, okay?
You guys are not going to
give my elephant back, right?
Where's my elephant?
What else? Tell me everything!
Tell me everything.
Okay. I will.
They're gone. Come out.
Sergeant,
will you help me?
What happened to you?
I've lost a lot of my men.
-It's not worth it.
-Take it or leave it.
Let's go.
You're such a troublemaker.
Are you my lost brother or what?
I have to protect you
and help you over and over.
Easy.
Here.
Wipe your blood with this.
I knew it.
-You didn't do it.
-Why do you want to help me?
You finished your job?
My job is over,
as much as my life.
Darn it.
I'll help you get your elephant back.
Perhaps my life is worthy.
The guy that you beat him up,
what did he say?
He said Khon will be delivered
to Phuket tonight.
-Phuket...
-Tonight General Dutafi,
the leader of newly established
West Katana,
will make a visit to Thailand.
After more than ten years of negotiation
between Katana's government
and the separatists.
Finally, the war between them
is coming to the end.
East Katana requires Thailand's government
to prepare a banquet in Phuket
and a native elephant
as a special gift for West Katana.
To where?
My job hasn't finished yet.
The problem is
you're on a run.
Now you get on a flight.
Step back.
You are such a dick
for that stupid elephant.
Who'd have thought that
an elephant could be a bomb?
Attack as fast as you can
hit him both high and low...
Shut my ass up.
Shut my blind ass up.
Sergeant, there is a bomb with Khon.
Holy Shit.
There's a bomb. A bomb!
The elephant! Run!
Run! Quick!
Move! Quick!
Sergeant!
Let's go.
-Job!
-Hey! Kham!
-What the hell are you doing?
-I don't know.
-No idea. I didn't do it.
-It's you!
-People could die.
-How can we remove it?
-How?
-I can't at this point.
If the tusks are off, the bomb goes off.
Don't be scared, Khon.
Hey! Put it back.
What should we do, Sergeant?
I've seen how they deactivate a bomb.
Today is the real deal.
Calm down, Khon.
Come here.
-What now, Sergeant?
-Back off.
-Now, Khon. Go back.
-Khon, turn around.
Kham, you hold his tusks.
I'll take care of this.
Sergeant,
would you help me?
Kham.
I'm exhausted in this scene.
Exhausted.
Your skirt didn't get ripped.
Sergeant!
I don't want this, Khon.
-Cut!
-Kham!
What's wrong with you?
You have ringworm?
You need an ointment, man.
Action!
-Sorry.
-I'm all right.
Don't cry. Be a man.
Don't show your pain.
You can run.
Camera's up.
Stand by.
Tony Jaa is leaving.
Ready, pull.
Keep pulling.
Hands off!
I'll take you to a theme park.
Can't get my gun.
I don't want this, Kham.
You need to...
-The shoes...
-Want to take them off?
-You can take them off.
-Just take them off.
Tell me the truth.
I can't focus.
What's this?
This is a comedy movie though.
Subtitle translation by Chutarat Banthakit