Go!
6 DAYS EARLIER…
Why are the pool lights on?
Those are automatic lights.
Art team!
Yes.
You're an art guy?
We've met before…
Good. Go check the underwater light
that keeps going on and off.
Fix it quickly.
You have to finish tonight.
-They will close the pool tomorrow.
-All right.
Day, here's Lucky.
Babe.
I'd like to dive, can I?
Naughty girl.
Just once, please.
Please, please, please?
No, you can't.
Here you are.
Are you tired?
I'm sorry, I haven't taken you anywhere.
It's all right, I understand.
Bad boy.
Worried that we'll get caught?
Lucky is here.
I have something for you.
Waste of money.
It's cute, you're grumpy.
Here.
Isn't it cute?
You don't like it?
Have you named the baby?
Come on,
don't say that.
Just kidding.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not pregnant. Don't be so serious.
Lucky.
Lucky, come out.
-Mayom.
Hey, if you stayed silent,
you'd have had a free show.
You just missed it.
Hey, Day.
The director is looking for your dog.
Go to the set.
I'm coming.
You work on set
and bring your dog in for extra money.
Saving up for a wedding?
Day? Keep it up.
-Bro.
-Yes.
When he gives the word,
have the dog jump over
and cross the camera frame.
-Do you hear, Lucky?
-Okay?
Make me proud.
Need a rehearsal?
No, I trained him myself.
Come on. Get ready.
Sound, ready?
Yes.
Let him finish playing with his dog.
Then we'll start shooting
He's ready.
This is the last cut.
One, two, three!
It's a wrap!
Lucky! Lucky, come here.
Come here. Come.
Come on, quick.
Come on, Lucky.
Fetch the ball.
FLOODING CRISIS. OFFICERS IN SEARCH
OF ESCAPED CROCODILE
Damn it, Day! You leave stuff everywhere.
So comfortable, huh?
Get out.
I've just released the water, come.
Hey, why did you chain him?
You're lucky I haven't chained you.
He could have run around
and fallen into the water.
Day, your insulin shot.
Better keep them in a safe place.
KOY
You aren't coming back, are you?
Of course not.
See you in three months.
Clean up everything for me
and leave anything you don't need here.
This pool is no longer used.
Bribe me 300 for leaving work early.
I'm gonna miss my flight.
Order pizza for me then.
Come on.
Want pizza?
-Pizza!
-Hey.
I gotta go.
Nepal is waiting.
Good luck, man.
CAUTION - POOL DEPTH 6 METERS
Ridiculous.
Calm down, Lucky. It's gonna be all right.
It's gonna be all right.
It's going to be all right.
Help!
KOY
Get up, Lucky. Up!
Pizza delivery!
Hello. Hi.
What's up?
I don't see anyone here.
There's only a dog.
I just called out. Nobody is here.
Yes.
Help.
Help!
Can anyone hear me? Help!
Don't jump, Koy!
Help!
Help, anybody! Help!
Can you hear me, Koy?
Things can't get any worse.
Go on, keep barking.
Make yourself useful.
Lucky. Shut up.
Lucky, quiet.
No!
Lucky! Let it go, Lucky.
Don't bark at it. Let it go.
No. No. Lucky.
Lucky, you stupid dog!
Do you know what you've just done?
Don't be afraid, Koy.
It's going to be all right.
Someone will come to help us.
Lucky, shut up.
Shut up.
Koy, be patient.
Bastard!
Help!
Can anyone hear me?
Help me!
Help!
You are burning.
Help, please!
Help!
Does anyone hear me?
Day.
Koy.
I'm here.
Are you all right?
What happened?
We are stuck in a swimming pool.
And what is that?
I thought he'd take the baby out of you.
Who…
Who'd take the baby out?
Damn.
How come she picked someone like you?
I'm handsome.
You are insulting her.
I'm serious.
What do I have against
those rich guys who were after her?
Seriously,
I heard that she is pregnant.
I'd tell her to have an abortion.
How will she feel if she hears that?
I can't support her.
The baby will grow up struggling.
I haven't slept for how many nights now?
How can I be a father?
Aren't you a bit selfish?
She is not pregnant.
What if she is?
Abortion is illegal.
Don't do it.
It's also a sin.
Baby…
Day.
You knew that?
Don't give up.
Day, you can help me and the baby.
I know it.
How are you doing?
Hungry.
Poor Lucky.
He is hungry like us.
Lucky.
Open your mouth. Open it.
Open your mouth. Lucky.
Come on.
Open it. Share with us.
You…
Son of a bitch!
You are ungrateful.
When we make it up there,
you're staying outside the house!
Don't dream of sleeping on our bed.
Eat up.
It's still fresh.
And you?
I'm not hungry.
It'll go off anyway.
The baby would want his father to eat.
I love you, Koy.
Liar.
You can't even take me to eat pizza.
I have to work.
Always about work.
Beg me, please.
Why are you crying?
I'm having my pizza now, Day.
Do you want to order more?
HELP
Day.
I'm tired because of the heat.
Hey,
did he do anything to you?
It's not a "he."
Is it a female crocodile?
Come on. Come on.
Have you done this before?
At home,
I didn't have a match.
No lighter.
No stove.
I lived in a cave.
This was how I started a fire.
Funny.
So not true.
I saw it in Castaway.
Take it easy.
You have to eat.
Let's share.
We can't stay here any longer.
We have to find a way out.
Day, a little higher.
Day. I can't do it!
Okay, Koy. It's all right.
Get down.
We can never get out this way.
We have to let the crocodile up.
And you go into the tunnel.
There will be a place you can hide.
If I'm not around…
she will come after you for sure.
Don't be stubborn.
The doll is gone.
Might have fallen off up there.
Hey.
You didn't take it out, did you?
You've never wanted me
to have an abortion, have you?
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Why?
Why, Day?
Why are you so cruel?
Think about it.
If the baby is born,
and I'm still like this,
how disappointed would the baby be
that his father is struggling so bad?
No, Day. That's not true.
Look around you, Day.
How could you be worse than this?
Listen to me.
If you want to do something
the baby will be proud of,
you have to do it now.
Make it up there.
You have to make it!
The music box?
You go ahead.
I'll be right behind you. Hurry up.
Are you all right?
How many days
haven't you had insulin shots?
I've lost count.
You have to be all right.
I…
I remember…
There is one shot up there.
Baby.
Our baby…
Baby…
Baby.
-Day.
-Baby.
Damn it, Day!
You leave stuff everywhere!
I'm okay, Koy.
I'm okay.
I am okay.
An addict, you are.
Help!
Help! We are stuck in here!
Koy. Wait for me here.
There must be some way.
Come here.
Cover the hole with this barrel.
So nothing can come through.
It's safer in here.
Help!
Just a kid's toy?
Does anyone hear me?
Help!
Anybody, help!
Does anyone hear me?
Help!
Go!
Koy, stay with me.
I will
go to the other end of the tunnel.
Let's see where it leads me to.
Wait for me here, Koy.
No!
I told you.
Enough, just go home.
It's raining.
Look.
Come on, it should be
somewhere around here.
Will my motorbike get stolen?
Hey.
What's that? Looks creepy.
There it is, our glider.
You go get it.
Hey. Let's go together.
How?
Should we jump?
Look.
So deep.
You can't wait now? Genius.
Come on.
Pick it up.
Did someone die here?
What the hell?
Let's go. It's gonna rain.
Who did that?
Could have been a commercial production.
It's none of our business. Let's go.
Stop wasting time.
Come on.
They must have left it.
It's soaking wet.
What's your problem?
Come on.
-Ready?
-Wait.
Ready?
Yeah.
Where is the step?
Hold it tight. Let me go up.
Hey, moron! I might fall off.
I'm going up now.
-Ready?
-Wait.
Help…
Help.
Help… Help us…
Help…
No. Lucky! No!
Wake up, Koy!
Koy, can you hear me?
Wake up, Koy. Wake up.
I've come back to you.
You hear me, Koy?
Wake up, Koy!
Wake up!
Wake up! Can you hear me?
Koy! Wake up!
Wake up…
Wake up. Koy…
Wake up, Koy!
Koy! Wake--
Come here.