NETFLIX PRESENTS
SOBRIETY CHECKPOINT
You okay?
Sort of.
You can tell me.
ALARM
Hey, Paula, be careful,
looks like something's there.
All right, let's go.
Simón.
Simón!
Hello.
You okay?
No.
-Wait, wait, wait!
-Hey, wait, hey!
Look out!
Slow down! Stop! Stop!
-Move, move, move!
-Stop, stop!
-You hurt?
-No.
Are you all right?
-I'll call an ambulance.
-There's no time.
It's serious.
-I should've called an ambulance.
-Quite the contrary.
Your quick action saved her.
It looked like the motorcycle
didn't even hit her.
That's not the problem.
She was already very sick.
What's wrong with her?
We're running tests.
-And her parents?
-We're trying to find them.
But there are
no missing girls in the area.
When you found her, did she say anything?
Did she speak?
-She didn't.
-No, nothing.
If she's not talking,
how did you find out her name?
One of the nurses is named Clara,
and she reacted very strongly to the name.
-Anything else?
-Nothing.
-How come?
-We're not sure.
Mutism is very broad.
There are many things that can cause it.
Well, how did she get so sick?
I mean, do you have any idea?
There are lots of unanswered questions.
The main thing is that the doctors
are saying she's handling
the treatment extremely well.
And soon we'll be able
to say she's a normal healthy girl.
Hey, what's wrong?
What happened?
Did something happen with one of the kids?
Hey, hey!
Okay, okay. Calm down.
Do you want us to stay?
Clara?
Is your name Clara?
I'll stay with her here.
How do they know her age?
They did an X-ray on one of her hands.
-And her parents?
-They can't find them.
-Did they say more?
-No.
They don't know much.
So they can't tell us much.
Oh my God, that poor girl.
It's awful.
Was she abused at all?
No.
Is she staying at the hospital?
Mm. She's very sick.
Her kidneys barely work.
They don't know
if it's genetic or--
Terrible.
That's why
they need to find her parents.
They should cut their balls off.
Leave it there.
Excuse me.
Is she not feeling well?
We have her sedated right now.
Why is she tied up?
It's for safety.
Simón.
Can't untie this girl.
-Clara.
-I'm sorry.
You can't be here. Excuse us.
NO ONE CLAIMS GIRL FROM THE ROAD
POLICE STILL INVESTIGATING
WHERE SHE CAME FROM TWO WEEKS LATER
Come on, I'm in a hurry.
Paula, I'll be late.
I'm coming!
Shall I pick you up to see Clara?
Huh?
Simón, should I get you?
Yes.
Weren't you in a hurry?
Want some?
Thank you.
What?
I can't stop thinking about her.
Her kidneys
are finally responding,
and thanks to you, she's improved a lot.
And her parents? Any news?
We can't find anything.
Think of the chalk square like this table.
Inside, everything is fine.
But if we force her to come out…
for Clara,
it's like falling into the void.
In the hospital, she's not doing well.
In order to help her,
we need to establish some connection
so she feels safe.
It's a huge responsibility, but she has
started to form a bond with you,
and we wanna take advantage
of that to help her find her family.
This isn't like fostering.
It's more complicated than that.
When parents foster, there's usually
a learning period. We don't have time.
She is our priority, especially since
we don't know where she comes from.
-And she doesn't have a home.
-We understand.
I've been completely honest with you.
I've explained everything.
So it's up to you.
Think it through and if you agree,
we'll start on the paperwork.
Hey, uh, Paula,
did the doctors approve this?
Yes.
Well, I think that little girl
should be in a hospital,
cared for by professionals.
Yeah, but she's not doing well there,
and this was a good option.
We'll see how it goes
for a few days and go from there.
Have you thought this through?
Yes, we both discussed it.
So it's decided, yeah?
She'll get here tonight.
Tonight? Well,
we should leave you to get set up, then.
Simón.
She saw the chalk square.
Good morning, Clara.
Want some?
-You want some?
-Yes.
-Mmm!
-Is it good?
Mmm! Really good.
Mmm. Delicious.
Yogurt is a good choice.
-Mm. Yeah.
-It's always good.
Good night.
Clara, you wanna come with me?
It's in all her drawings.
She's probably
done it her whole life.
Clara, will you come and play outside?
You want to?
Clara, I'll erase it.
Gloria, don't.
Wait in the kitchen.
-Don't do that.
-We have to try it.
Come on.
Look at me. At me.
I'll count to three,
and then we'll erase the chalk line.
One.
Two.
Don't be afraid.
And… and three.
Are you hurt?
Come on, wait. Let her do her job.
Breathe.
Clara!
-Buma! Buma!
-Stop it!
Shh!
Clara, I know you understand.
I know you can speak.
Earlier you said "buma."
What is "buma"?
No, I can't talk.
Please.
What is that? I can't hear you.
Where is your house?
House. Kreide.
"Kreide?" What is "kreide"?
-Kreide.
Where's your home? Is it near here?
Is it far away?
Who do you live with?
Mama.
You live with your mama.
Anyone else? Do you live with your papa?
Clara, who do you live with?
If you don't wanna talk to me,
I'll have to erase the chalk.
Clara!
Hello.
I won't force you to speak to me.
I know you're afraid
of crossing the chalk,
but…
you don't have to force yourself.
Clara, while you're living here,
Simón and I will make sure
nothing bad happens to you.
I promise.
We'll stay here.
What's this?
Is it for me?
It's beautiful.
I love your gift.
-Hey, you brought lots of things--
-Don't step on the chalk line.
We thought she couldn't talk.
-Yeah, we thought that too.
-It's been a surprise to everyone.
What does she say?
It's random words.
Nothing understandable.
The psychologist thinks
she'll start talking a little.
She said "mama."
She probably lived with her.
-And her dad?
-Nothing about him.
You gonna teach her to speak?
We're wondering if it's just
a matter of her gaining confidence.
You need a glass.
-Oh, yes.
-No, no, no. I'll go. I'll go.
Thank you.
Sorry, I don't know what I'm doing.
It does sound like you're making progress.
-Hmm.
-Thanks to Paula.
The girl adores her.
Ainhoa is dying to meet Clara.
Yeah?
It might be good for her.
To play with some other kids.
We can come over tomorrow morning
and have breakfast together.
Okay.
That might've been
a little too intense, honey.
Go on, go play with her.
It's good we came over before her game.
-I can't believe how big she is.
-Neither can I.
You're looking better.
I'm happy for you, Paula.
-Do you want some more toast?
-No, I think I might explode.
Girls!
Come have breakfast.
Girls.
What's wrong?
How is she?
Fine, I just helped her back home.
Come here.
Look at what I found.
These were in the jam.
Plus the one Claudia had in her mouth.
Look at the jar there.
-But it looks normal.
-Exactly.
-Simón--
-Someone put the glass in it.
Oh, yeah?
No.
Do you not understand
what's going on here?
That there was a piece
of broken glass in the jar?
Come on.
Should we call Gloria
and tell her about this?
Mm, no, we can tell her tomorrow.
What a mess.
I'll be back.
Remember to buy some more chalk for us.
What's wrong?
Look.
"Kreide?"
What is "kreide"?
-Please.
-Shh.
What is that? I can't hear you
Please.
Shh.
SPANISH - GERMAN
DID YOU MEAN: BESTRAFEN
PUNISHMENT
Where's your home?
Is it near here? Is it far away?
FEAR
And "buma"?
NO MATCHES FOR: BUMA
I'm going to tell the police.
If Clara is German, I'm sure
they can help them find her parents.
I'll call you as soon as I know something.
Thank you.
Why don't you wanna
tell her about the glass?
I don't want her to misinterpret it.
'Cause I did?
In my hand.
So you speak German.
Is your mama German? Or your papa?
Have you lived in Germany?
Hey, come on, talk to me, please.
I'll be right back.
Clara.
Clara?
María! Did you see a girl
come out of my house?
Blonde, about six years old? You seen her?
Don't worry…
What are you doing? Drawing?
Do you want some water or juice?
What's wrong?
Hey, the washing machine broke.
Everything's fine!
Hey.
Were you hiding from me?
Hmm?
What are you afraid of?
Is it "buma"?
Is it something?
Is-- Is it a person?
Talk to me, Clara.
Is it a place?
What if we drew it?
Let's draw it together. Here you go.
Okay.
We won't. It's okay.
Can you please talk to me?
Clara.
Clara, what do you prefer,
talking or erasing the chalk?
You know how to both of those things.
I'll do it.
Hey!
Listen to me, hey!
Clara, I won't erase it!
I'm sorry.
Did Clara hit you?
-No.
-She didn't attack you?
Well, I tried to force her to talk to me,
but I couldn't.
And the glass? A pregnant
woman ended up in the hospital.
We were gonna tell you tomorrow.
Yes, it was a real shock.
She understands when I speak German,
but she won't say anything.
Clara, why won't you talk anymore?
Has something made you angry?
Or maybe you're sad?
She's done
this lovely drawing.
Can I see it?
I think
she drew it for Paula.
Can I take a look?
Is that your house?
That's grass. Do you live in the country?
That's the sky, isn't it?
Why is it green?
Hmm?
I don't know, honey, why don't you--
-We'll talk in a couple of days.
-We're doing fine, really.
She's starting to trust me.
This isn't working out. I'm sorry.
Oh, please, no.
It's not your fault.
We'll get the paperwork started.
When were you gonna tell me Clara hit you?
No, Simón, she didn't hit me.
She's six years old.
-You're leaving?
-I'll be back.
-Paula, we're talking right now. Paula!
-Just watch Clara please.
Watch your step.
You told everyone about it.
Now they're taking her away.
-Yes, because it was--
-Mind your own fucking business.
Are you coming to bed?
Yes, I'll be right there.
TRANSLATE: VUMA
Clara… I know you understand.
I know you can speak.
-I'm going.
-Ciao.
Earlier you said "buma."
What is "buma"?
No, I can't talk.
Shh.
What is that? I can't hear you.
Where is your house?
House. Kreide.
"Kreide?" What is "kreide"?
-Kreide.
Where's your home?
Is it near here? Is it far away?
Who do you live with?
-You live with your mama.
-Mama.
Anyone else?
Do you live with your papa?
BU MAN
Clara, who do you live with?
BOOGEYMAN
If you don't wanna talk to me,
I'll have to erase the chalk.
Clara!
They found her jacket.
Where was it?
In the swamp.
The divers are looking.
-What happened after?
-She-- she was holding me.
And I locked her in to go to the bathroom.
-You locked her in?
-Yes, I mean, with the chalk.
How long were you in the bathroom?
Less than five minutes.
When I came back…
…the door was open and--
And Clara wasn't there.
Were you alone in the house?
Yes, I was at work.
Wasn't there a previous incident
with the glass?
Yes, it didn't feel important.
Your neighbor went to the ER.
These kinds of accidents
should be reported.
I was aware of it,
and deciding how to deal with it.
I believe the girl ran away on her own.
No, that's impossible.
-Because the girl won't cross the chalk?
-Exactly.
But we've been informed that
this isn't the first time she disappeared,
and you ran outside
to go and look for her.
No,
I don't think she went outside.
I think that… she was hiding.
Yeah, you dealt with that as well?
Look, I've spent a lot of time with Clara,
and I know she was good with us.
So while you're looking in that swamp,
I ask you,
don't exclude any other options.
All right.
Don't move from here. She might come back.
-You need to talk to Paula.
-Yeah, I know.
I've never seen her like this.
The most important thing is
for her to get back to normal.
-Do you think someone took the girl?
-No. Well, I don't know.
I hope she's not in that swamp.
Don't say that. Paula.
How are you?
Fine. Is there any news?
You only slept for two hours.
You had time to clean.
Are you okay?
Come back to the office.
If you don't,
they'll take your projects away.
It's always nice
to get back to normal, Paula.
Well, do you know
they're moving my due date up?
Really?
-It'll be born on the same day as Beltrán.
-They told us on the way here.
What a coincidence.
What?
I don't know, Paula.
What do you think?
What do I think?
I'm really happy for you, Beltrán.
-Paula, they're just cheering you up.
-Just shut up.
-Paula, relax.
-Hey!
-Can you get out of my house, please?
-Paula.
Can you all go?
I'll see you out.
I'm sorry.
Simón, I'm so nervous.
-Where is she?
-I don't know.
Well, I can't sit around waiting.
Can you stay here, please?
I don't want
her back in our house.
-What?
-She wasn't doing well.
Yes, you said that.
It's one thing for the others to say it,
but you?
-You think Clara opened the door and ran?
-You've been injecting yourself.
-What?
-How many cycles have you done?
You went to the clinic alone.
I thought we were planning
on being parents together.
Were you gonna tell me?
I didn't go to the clinic.
The shots were in the bathroom.
Hidden, but they were there.
It's what I had left over from before.
So just one cycle?
-I wanted to do one.
-How many?
I wanted to do one, but it didn't work.
-And I thought I could do another one.
-So you won't answer.
Okay, hang on, Simón.
You're right. I should have told you
I did, but I didn't want you to worry.
-How could you do that?
-I couldn't take it.
But we talked about it. We agreed
that we would take a break for a year.
I'm sorry, I couldn't.
We've gone through six years
of treatments and doctors.
Don't you remember how it was for us?
Yes, we were tired.
No, we were bad.
All right, so,
you think you're on your own with this?
No, I've never thought that.
You just said a moment ago
you didn't wanna worry me.
It's not about that.
I wish I could have done more.
Taken on more.
This is for us, my love, I promise.
All right then, so?
I wanted to sit you down and tell you.
"Hey, guess what, we're pregnant."
No.
Yes, it's as simple
and as difficult as that.
But you decided all on your own.
-I felt strong enough, Simón.
-How can you be strong enough if I'm not?
We're different.
Yes.
Yes, you took
that thing you said was ours,
and you made it yours alone.
It's the same with the girl.
What? I'm confused.
This has nothing to do with Clara.
You didn't include me, Paula.
You became obsessed.
-Locked yourself up.
-I don't see it like that.
-You don't?
-No.
We've been sleeping apart for weeks.
You've been hiding things
and attack people who disagree.
-I'm not hiding anything.
-She hit you.
No, she didn't hit me.
She's six years old, Simón.
-She ran away.
-She was hiding!
-You don't care what I say.
-I forced her to speak to me.
You're always going to
have an explanation.
Do you know what my explanation
is right now?
What?
-That I devoted myself to that girl.
-I didn't?
I accepted the responsibility
we had to that girl.
That's different from an obsession.
No, you insisted
on keeping that girl here in this house
when they should have taken
her away weeks ago.
-That's what's going on.
-That's your idea of being a father?
I am not her father.
I'm not her mother.
I don't understand why you
wanted to bring her home, then.
-The truth?
-Yes, please.
Because I thought it would
be good for us, good for you.
But you're saying you were neglected?
Can you explain this to me?
Explain it.
Take a bath, eat something.
Yes.
Hello.
Mama?
Clara?
Clara, where are you?
Mama.
Are you okay?
Ho-- honey, what's wrong?
Fine. All right. See ya.
You have any news?
We're studying cases from all over Europe.
We're leaving no stone unturned.
Have you traced the phone call?
We know the number
from which the call was made.
Have you had your phone stolen recently?
-No.
-Then it was you who made the call.
Of course I didn't.
Is that your number?
Yes, that's my cellphone number.
Simón, I know she called me.
Please, help me explain.
You were there too.
No, Paula, I had left.
They are going to give
you a psychological exam.
I don't need a psychologist. No.
Then go ahead
and tell us everything you know.
The worst thing that can happen
to that girl is to let more time go by.
All right,
I explained this already.
I heard her perfectly calling me "Mama."
Full name?
Paula Ejea Guzmán.
-Age?
-Forty-two years old.
You have to
leave your phone with us.
You can go now.
Stay reachable in the area.
Let's go home.
I need to go for a walk.
-I'll go with you.
-I need time to think about this.
Well, let's think together. Paula--
We'll talk about it tonight. I promise.
MISSING GIRLS
CRIMES AGAINST CHILDREN
MINOR'S FILE
AUTOPSY REPORT
FULL BODY IMAGE
…IN THE MOUTH OR THROAT
DESCRIPTION OF INJURIES
…ABDUCTION AND RAPE
TRAUMA
…SIGNS OF SEXUAL ASSAULT
UNIDENTIFIED
PERSONAL RECORD
I'm sorry, I don't understand you. Please.
And Dr. Carrére, s'il vous plaît.
Yes, the doctor is in,
uh, forensic, um, anatomy
in another, uh, bigger town.
Where?
If you're not a police officer,
she can't help you.
Uh, she says she's sorry.
S'il vous plaît, madame.
S'il vous plaît.
I need you to tell me everything
you know about this little girl.
She's very sorry.
She can't help you.
Are you a mother?
Please translate that.
Then you must help me.
S'il vous plaît.
It was two years ago.
She doesn't remember much more.
The organs were very damaged.
Her kidneys were no longer functioning.
Various marks
from repeated injuries to the neck.
She suffered greatly.
These two letters here.
Can you tell me what they mean?
Amblyopie fonctionnelle.
I'm not sure how to translate it.
What is it?
A lazy eye.
NO NEW LEADS IN CASE OF GIRL
WHO WENT MISSING FROM A BEACH IN MÁLAGA
A YEAR HAS PASSED SINCE THE DISAPPEARANCE
OF THE SWISS GIRL IN PEDRALEJO BEACH
12 YEARS OLD
SHE'S OUR ONLY CHILD
I BEG YOU
CIVIL GUARD HASN'T REVEALED WHETHER
THE PARENTS ARE SUSPECTS OF CHILD ABUSE
It happened on a beach in Málaga
on the fifth of June in 2011.
Ingrid Morand disappeared without a trace.
A year later, her parents haven't
given up hope of finding her.
She's very kind-hearted
and has a great imagination.
I'm sure she really misses her bedroom.
So please, bring our Ingrid back.
She's our only daughter.
She's always making little crafts
that she gives to us and her friends.
She says they are guardian angels
and that they protect us from bad things.
…guardian angels and that
they protect us from bad things.
Simón.
I'M AT THE POLICE STATION. CALL ME
-Emergency.
-My name is Paula Ejea.
My neighbor Eduardo Olivares
may have something to do
with a missing little girl.
Please, you have to come here.
-Is your daughter missing?
-No, no, no. She's not my daughter.
But my neighbor Eduardo Olivares may have
something to do with her disappearance,
and also Ingrid Morand's.
Please, you have to hurry. My address is--
I can see your address on my monitor.
My colleagues are on their way.
We ask that
you wait inside your house, please.
No, stand up. Stand up.
You can walk.
Go that way, toward those lights.
You can't talk.
Let me see you go.
I'll come back for you, but you're sick.
Look.
See? Follow the chalk line.
Follow the chalk line.
Have the doctors agreed to this?
That girl should be in a hospital,
looked after by professional doctors.
Have the doctors agreed to this?
What did she say?
It's random words,
nothing understandable.
A psychologist thinks
she'll start talking little by little.
She said "mama."
She probably lived with her.
-And her dad?
-Nothing about him.
Are you gonna
teach her to speak, then?
We're wondering if it's
a matter of her gaining confidence.
You need a glass.
-Oh, yes.
-I'll go. I'll go.
Thank you.
Clara?
What are you doing in here alone?
Do you want some water or juice?
What are you doing? Drawing?
Hey, the washing machine broke.
Good morning.
Everything's fine!
-Is there more?
-No, but I can make you something else.
It's okay.
Get the leftovers from the fridge.
It's no trouble.
How would you like an omelet?
Just take out the leftovers in the fridge.
Maite.
What?
I had put those beans aside for tomorrow.
What for?
Don't you remember?
You're on your own tomorrow.
I won't be here.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Barcelona to see the boys.
I told you,
they've finished all their exams.
You didn't tell me.
Did you forget?
You told me I could go.
You gave me permission.
No.
You even told me where to have lunch,
where you went that time.
-When you went with your co-workers.
-Well, as you wish.
But tomorrow we agreed
to meet Paula and Simón.
But you can go without me, right?
Why don't you call the boys, hmm?
And you can tell them to come here.
It's been so long.
I think they're busy.
I thought you said
they finished their exams.
They might have started their classes
for the second term.
They work hard.
I think they could come home
for a couple days if they wanted, hmm?
You're right.
Paula and Simón are not well.
I can go some other time.
Are you sure?
Yes.
-Do you have to work?
-Yes.
And the police?
They are stumped.
-What are they saying?
-They thought she ran away.
But there's a detective
who believes Paula,
so they're investigating more.
The most important thing is
for her to get back to normal.
Do you think
someone took the girl?
No. Well, I don't know.
I hope she's not in that swamp.
Don't say that. Paula.
How are you?
Fine.
Is there any news?
You only slept for two hours.
You had time to clean.
Are you okay?
Come back to the office.
If you don't,
they'll take your projects away.
It's always nice
to get back to normal, Paula.
Tell her, she'll be happy.
Well, do you know
they're moving my due date up?
Really?
It'll be born
on the same day as Beltrán.
They told us on the way here.
What a coincidence.
What?
I don't know, Paula.
What do you think?
What do I think?
I'm really happy for you, Beltrán.
-Paula, they're just cheering you up.
-Just shut up.
-Paula, relax.
-Hey!
-Can you get out of my house, please?
-Paula.
Can you all go?
-Let's go.
-I'll see you out.
Hello.
You okay?
Yes.
Are you alone?
Yeah.
Why?
Maite told me to come over
and pick something up.
What?
Some maps.
She said I could borrow them.
Oh, she didn't tell me.
Well, come in.
I'll find them.
Let's see if they're here.
Why do you need maps?
I'm going to keep looking.
For the girl?
Yes.
Have you heard anything?
Nothing.
That Maite.
Wait a second. They might be in here.
-Yes.
-Are you Eduardo Olivares?
Yes, that's me.
We received a call.
We would like to ask you
some questions if possible.
Paula Ejea called you,
didn't she?
Ah, don't stay out there. Come in.
I told the police.
They're gone now.
They'll find me.
Tell me, Paula, how did you know?
I found Ingrid.
You found Ingrid?
Ingrid's autopsy.
Where?
Where, Paula?
It's in-- I left it in my car.
Are you lying right now?
-Are you lying to me?
-No.
Paula?
Clara, listen to me, please.
This is very important.
I need you to help me.
Will you do that?
Watch very carefully. Look here.
Clara, take this.
Too far.
I have it!
Try please and if you want, we can stop.
-No, don't-- don't want to.
-Clara, listen to me.
You don't have to be afraid, please.
I know it's difficult, honey,
but you can do it.
Do you know why?
Because you're the bravest girl I know.
I haven't met anyone in this world
who is as brave of a person
as you are, my dear.
So please, Clara.
Do it for both of us.
Clara, are you in the closet?
I don't want
Mama's punishment here.
Was your mama here?
Yeah.
Your mama's name was Ingrid?
Where is she?
Clara.
Honey.
Where is she?
Tell me now! Where is she?
Clara!
Clara! Clara! Clara!
Simón!
Yes, I just got home.
She's not here.
Simón!
How can she contact me
if they took her phone?
-Simón!
-Hello.
What are you doing here?
Are you Clara?
Are you all right?
Where's Paula?
Calm down.
Calm down, relax.
It's all fine.
Relax, come here. Come here.
Everything's fine.
It's over. Calm down.
Simón!
What do you mean stay at home?
No, no, no, no, no, you listen to me.
This is how things will work.
I'll go to see the boys whenever I want.
You'll give me money
for the tickets and for food.
I'll go, and then I'll come home.
I'll be here as usual.
But you'll never ask about them again,
and they never have to come back here.
And the basement?
Thank you.
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it for my sons.
And now?
Now I'll make some coffee.
I'm going out to the garden for a while.
Police!
Hands in the air! Don't move!
Where are they?
Did you hear me? Where are they?
Hey, there!
-How are you?
-Great!
Great! Oh, my love.
I'm so happy to see you.
You look great.
How's your grandmother?
Oma?
Pass the phone to her later.
I wanna say hello.
It looks beautiful in Hamburg.
Sunny!
Look here.
It's cloudy today, see?
How's your ankle doing?
Can you walk on it? A bit?
That's amazing!
Simón.
Look who just got home. Hang on a moment.
Simón, come here. I'm talking to Clara.