(CLOCK TICKING)
(CLOCK TOLLING)
JONATHAN: Dear Lewis,
enclosed please find
one bus ticket and
two silver dollars
for your trip to Michigan.
I'm really sorry about
the loss of your parents.
Your mom was my sister,
so, that makes you family.
And I'll do my best to make
you feel right at home.
As Einstein said,
"Life is like a bicycle.
"To stay balanced,
you gotta keep moving forward."
And so will we.
I look forward to meeting ya.
Your uncle, Jonathan.
PS, sorry for the stain on the letter,
that's chocolate.
(SNORING)
(SIGHS)
Mom, Dad,
are you there?
Am I gonna be okay?
"Cannot say."
(SIGHS)
MAN 1: Gonna buy Charlie
a bike for his birthday.
MAN 2: He's gonna love it!
MAN 3: Emma Jean! Bus is here!
(HORN HONKS)
Last stop, New Zebedee.
(SNORING)
TRAVELER 1: Are you coming?
TRAVELER 2: Oh, golly.
I'm a little nervous.
TRAVELER 3: You want me to get that for you?
TRAVELER 4: If you don't mind.
- TRAVELER 3: No problem, ma'am.
- (LEWIS GRUNTING)
TRAVELER 4: Thank you so much.
TRAVELER 3: There you go.
Have a great night.
(GRUNTS)
JONATHAN: Oh, come on. Don't kill yourself
before I've had a chance to meet ya.
Lewis, I'm your uncle,
Jonathan.
Are you wearing a robe?
It's a kimono.
Oh.
Here, let me
help you with that.
Oh! Good Lord, what do you got
in this thing? Encyclopedias?
LEWIS: Dictionaries.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, you're serious.
I like new words. I think
they're very pulchritudinous.
Well, welcome
to New Zebedee.
Or should I say "salutations"?
You can look that one up.
I know what
"salutations" means.
Well, smart kid.
Uh, do you think that
we're gonna be home soon?
Because the Captain
Midnight show's almost on.
Uh... You don't have to worry about that,
I don't have a TV.
But, I do have a big poker game tonight,
if you wanna join. Do you play?
Uh, no, I'm 10.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Duly noted.
- (BELL TOLLING)
- (GASPS)
(TOLLING SOUND DISTORTING)
(TOLLING STOPS)
(CAR HORN HONKS)
Huh. Here we are.
Excuse me.
The Muggin Samoon.
Temperamental
door handle. Hop in.
Here you go.
Watch your tootsies.
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
All right, here we are.
You can get out here.
Here we go.
(CAR DOOR CREAKING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Home sweet home.
(OWL HOOTING)
- Do you like Halloween?
- Hmm?
Oh, no. I keep those up
year round. (CHUCKLES)
- MRS. HANCHETT: Mr. Barnavelt!
- (DOG YAPPING)
Come, darling.
Yes, good puppy.
Mr. Barnavelt!
Ah, Mrs. Hanchett.
Marmalade.
- (MARMALADE GROWLING)
- Is that a robe?
It's a kimono.
You've been playing
your saxophone again.
Madame, not everyone
can appreciate the intricacies
of a free-form jazz odyssey.
I don't care what you play.
You're playing at 3:00
in the morning.
So, I'm begging you!
Who's this?
Oh, this is Lewis, my nephew.
He'll be living with me.
You're responsible for
keeping a human child alive?
That's right.
Good evening.
This way, Lewis.
I'll try to keep it down
around 3:00 a.m.
But, uh, them's my
best jamming hours.
(DOOR OPENS)
And, here we are.
(CLOCKS TICKING)
LEWIS: Wow, you've...
That's a lot of clocks.
Well, what constitutes a lot is
really a matter of personal taste.
For me, it's a perfect
amount of clocks.
- (RATTLING)
- (CLOCK CHIMING)
Oh, sorry.
There's a deranged cuckoo in there.
Your ratchet wheel's shot,
and the click spring's not far behind.
Hello. You're Lewis, I presume?
How was your trip?
This old hag is my next-door neighbor,
Mrs. Florence Zimmerman.
I'm relieved to see you didn't inherit
your uncle's freakishly oversized head.
Huh. Says the woman who
literally looks like a Q-tip.
Oh, look.
The giant head is angry.
My God,
did that withered purple skeleton just speak?
It's nice to meet you.
- Lewis, are you hungry?
- Yes, please.
Florence, I'm gonna
show Lewis to his room.
For once in your life,
could you make yourself useful
and whip up a batch of those chocolate
chip cookies? (CLICKS TONGUE)
And how would you
like them, sir?
Stuffed down your throat,
one by one?
Or crumbled up
and shoved into your pants?
Ignore her, Lewis.
She thinks she's smarter than me
because she's got more college degrees.
No, I think I'm smarter than you
because I'm smarter than you.
(ORGAN PLAYS NOTE)
- Shh!
- (ORGAN STOPS PLAYING)
- LEWIS: But, Uncle Jonathan?
- Mmm.
Don't I have to have dinner before
I'm allowed to have cookies?
Well, why not just eat cookies for dinner?
They're far more delicious.
I know. It's just,
we had these house rules.
Well, not in this house.
There's no bedtime,
bath time or meal time.
You can eat cookies till you
throw up for all I care.
You'll see. Things are
quite different here.
All mine?
All yours.
Although, why this is yours
I have no idea.
You know it's about the complete
opposite of real magic.
Um...
It's the last thing my parents
gave to me before the...
(STIFLES SOB)
The car crash.
(LEWIS CRYING QUIETLY)
I'm sorry.
Uh, here, yeah,
take that back.
Um, I have a tissue
around here somewhere.
Ah.
(CONTINUES CRYING)
Here you go.
No, hold on. Sorry.
I didn't mean to, to...
I didn't realize the ball was
of emotional significance.
Almost there.
(GROANS)
Feel free to grab any color
tissue, they're all the same.
FLORENCE: Hey, gorilla groin, are we
playing poker, or am I playing solitaire?
Hold your horses,
you scarecrow!
- (CHAIR SQUEAKS)
- Right?
Calling that a poker face
is an insult to faces.
(JONATHAN CHUCKLES)
(JONATHAN INHALES SHARPLY)
Sore loser, frumpy.
(EXHALES)
Well, beat that.
(SIGHS)
(GROANS) He wins. Again.
You're hustling me.
You've played before.
I haven't. I swear.
Beginner's luck, I guess?
Well, I'm gonna drown my sorrows
in some hot cocoa. You want some?
- Yes, please.
- Florence?
- Delighted.
- Get your own.
Choke and die.
So, how long have you lived
next door to Uncle Jonathan?
Oh, we've been friends forever.
Ever since I came here.
Ran here, actually.
From Paris.
After the war.
And, no. To answer
that look you're giving me,
- your uncle and I aren't anything kissy faced.
- (CHUCKLES)
- JONATHAN: Gross!
- Ugh!
The word's "platonic."
That's right.
Look, your uncle drives me nuts.
And he doesn't always smell so terrific,
but he's gotten me out of more tough
scrapes than I care to mention.
You know, I've found that all
one really needs in this world
is one good friend.
Oh, but I'm sure
you've got lots.
Yeah. Tons.
All my friends
are really great.
Hmm.
(SOFTLY) Good night, Mom.
Good night, Dad.
I really miss you guys.
Love you.
(KISSES)
(METALLIC CREAKING, CLANGS)
(GASPS)
(DISTORTED NOISES)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
- (CLOCK CACKLING)
- (GASPING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PANTING)
- (CLOCKS TICKING)
- (MECHANICAL RATTLING)
Uh, Uncle Jonathan?
FLORENCE: (SOFTLY) You've got to go
into the wall.
JONATHAN: (WHISPERS)
What do you mean I have to...
- FLORENCE: Will you...
- I am going in the wall!
- You did not go into the wall yesterday.
- Yes, I did.
- FLORENCE: I saw you. You did not go...
- You...
- Hello?
- (GASPS)
Lewis!
Didn't see you there.
Big day. First day of school.
How'd you sleep?
I...
Fine. How did you sleep?
Peachy. Like a baby.
Like a big peachy baby.
Okay, off you go.
Knock 'em dead.
(LOCK CLICKS)
JONATHAN: I played it perfect,
he suspects nothing.
MAN: (ON RADIO) Forty-third,
New Zebedee Blue Ribbon Bake-Off...
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
- STUDENT: Hold the door!
Clark,
let's make a decision.
(SIGHS) Herman.
(SIGHS)
- (THUDDING)
- (CRUTCHES CREAKING)
Good hustle, Herman.
HERMAN: Thanks, Coach.
Woody.
We're even teams now.
Let's play ball.
Maybe next time,
ankle-biter.
Coach.
Come on, just pick him.
(WHISPERS) No, just pick him.
WOODY: (WHISPERS) No.
Come on.
Fine. All right. You're with us.
You can play, right?
Sure.
I'm open! I'm...
COACH: Goggles, get up! Come on, guys!
Down the court! Down the court!
You all right?
COACH: Bring it on!
You good?
COACH: All right, open your space up.
Come on, guys, open the space!
Now, again. Let's go,
let's go, let's go!
- BOY: Pass the ball!
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
COACH: Goggles,
what's going on?
Come on, let's go. Defense!
Look alive. Look alive, guys.
Goggles, make the shot!
Come on!
Make the shot!
BOY: Goggles!
Not at me! The basket!
You gotta pass
the ball, Goggles!
Goggles, Goggles,
I'm open! (GROANS)
I'm sorry!
COACH: Come on, give it back to Owen!
Give it back to Lewis!
Hey, guard your guys,
guard your guys! Let's go!
Shoot! Shoot!
BOY: Shoot! Shoot!
(BOYS CHEERING)
- Nice shot, Speedy.
- Thanks, Coach.
- (BELL RINGING)
- WOMAN: (ON PA) Attention, students.
The honor class club is meeting in
the library today, after school.
There he is. Star forward
for the Minneapolis Lakers.
- How you doin', buddy?
- I'm good.
A vote for Tarby Corrigan is a vote
for pop in the drinking fountains.
- Thank you.
- Hey! A vote for Tarby Corrigan
is a vote for pop in
the drinking fountains!
Please. How is he gonna carbonate
the drinking fountains?
Whoa.
- (SIGHS)
- STUDENT: Come on! Hit it!
Don't just stand there.
Can you pitch?
Uh, no, not very well.
I'll take what I can get.
Come toss me one.
Come on.
What are you doing here?
Where are all your friends?
Football practice.
Can't play.
Can't do anything.
My butt is just
warming the bench.
So, you're new in town.
Where do you live?
Kind of this big, old place
on the end of High Street.
Wait.
You live in
the slaughter house?
I'm sorry. The what?
Some old guy died there.
Now it's haunted.
Well, everyone says so.
Have you seen
anything creepy?
No. Well...
Last night I thought I heard something,
but it wasn't anything.
- It was just my uncle.
- What was he doing?
I don't know,
just sort of wandering around.
I think he was
looking for something.
Maybe he was looking
for an ax?
It's his house.
Why wouldn't he know
where his own ax is?
Maybe he hid it from the police
after the last murder.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Look, I'm just trying
to help us both out.
You can't vote for me
if you don't have arms.
Come on.
(RAT SQUEAKING)
LEWIS' MOM: Lewis.
Lewis?
Lewis.
Sweetheart.
(SIGHS) Hey, kiddo.
I missed you so much.
I miss you too, Mom. A lot.
Your dad and I, we'd give
anything to be with you again.
You know that, right?
(SIGHS) So?
How are you making out?
How do you like
Uncle Jonathan?
He seems nice. Just...
What?
Hey! It's okay.
You can tell me.
This house is scary, and old, and scary.
And there's all these clocks.
And I see weird stuff out
of the corner of my eye and...
I feel like...
I almost feel like that Uncle
Jonathan's hiding something.
That's because he is.
Hiding something.
From you.
I'm sorry, sweetheart,
but you're in danger.
Danger? (STAMMERS)
What danger?
What do you mean?
(WHISPERS) You're gonna
have to be brave.
But I... Mom, this is me.
I'm not brave.
(SHUSHING)
(KISSES)
First you get the book,
then you get the key.
Book? Key? What are
you talking about?
(CLOCK TICKING)
Do you hear the ticking?
(GASPING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
- (DOOR SHUTS)
- (FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(WHISPERS) Brave.
Brave. Brave.
(CREAKING)
(FAINT SCREAMING)
(FAINT HOWLING)
(CREAKING)
JONATHAN: Come out,
come out, wherever you are.
You can't hide forever.
- (JONATHAN GRUNTING)
- (CRASHING)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
- LEWIS: (SCREAMS) Help!
- (PANTING)
(SCRATCHING)
(GASPS)
(GASPING)
(GASPING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(CLOCKS CUCKOOING)
(ORGAN PLAYING
FOREBODING TUNE)
(CHAIR WHIMPERING)
(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
Help! Let me out!
Help! Please!
Help me! Let me out!
(SCREAMS)
- It's me.
- (SCREAMS)
- (CHAIR SQUEAKING)
- Down boy! I said, down.
Go. Go on. Go to
your room. Go on. Get.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- (SIGHS)
I'm sorry
you had to see that.
No. No. No.
Houses don't attack you.
And if they do attack,
you're definitely not supposed to say,
"Sorry you had
to see that."
Is this place haunted?
Are you gonna ax murder me?
What? No.
You're gonna ax murder me,
aren't you?
(LAUGHS) I'm not gonna
ax murder you.
Then what is going on?
(SIGHS) Well, one thing's for sure.
The house likes you.
Houses don't like anything.
They're houses.
- (ORGAN PLAYS NOTE)
- (METAL SQUEAKING)
(CHAIR SQUEAKS)
Do you know what
a warlock is, Lewis?
LEWIS: It's...
A boy witch.
Well... (CHUCKLES)
I think they're a little
more than boy witches.
"Warlock. Noun.
A man who practices magic."
A boy witch.
Are you saying that...
You're a warlock?
Would it scare you
if I was?
Well, are you a good
warlock or a bad one?
Ah. Depends on what
you mean by "bad."
I'm nice,
but not that good.
Just a parlor
magician, really.
But, uh,
Mrs. Zimmerman...
Now, she's nice
and good. Damn good.
Got a doctor of magic quorum degree
from the University of Göttingen.
LEWIS: Why are you always
wandering around at night?
What's that ticking
in the walls?
You've heard that?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
This house used to be owned
by another warlock.
Isaac Izard
and his wife, Selena.
He, uh...
Passed away.
And left a magic clock
in the walls.
Why?
Because he's a terrible...
Joker.
Practical joker.
Put a clock in the walls
to drive me nuts.
I try to drown it out
with all those other clocks,
but it doesn't
really work.
So, at night I go around the house
and search for the damn thing.
With an ax?
Sometimes I get over-enthused.
I'll admit that.
Do you have to be
born a boy wi...
A warlock?
No. Anyone can learn. They study.
Practice hard enough.
- Can I learn?
- No.
But you just said anyone.
Grown-up anyone.
There's charts, and hieroglyphs,
and stuff that would stump
a Harvard professor.
- And I don't have time to teach a...
- Please?
Please. Please teach me.
Please. Please.
Please. Please. Please.
Okay! Have it your way.
(JONATHAN SIGHS, BURBLES)
Oh.
(BLOWS)
(JONATHAN CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
Let me know when
you've read all those.
Just for a start.
- Jack-o'- lanterns.
- They scare away evil.
And iron does too.
Well, it repels evil, like bug spray.
And that is why
we have iron horseshoes.
And that's why cemetery gates
are made of iron.
JONATHAN: Mmm-hmm,
mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm.
- (GROWLS)
- And how does one become a full-fledged warlock?
You have to defeat an evil
spirit by using your own magic.
That is absolutely right.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SNIFFING)
What smells
of rancid sulfur?
(CREATURE FARTS)
Bad kitty!
(CREATURE GROWLS)
Am I gonna have to defeat
an evil spirit one day?
Oh, don't worry. Not for a long, long time.
You're perfectly safe.
(BOTH GASP)
(CREATURE GROWLS)
That's safe?
(CREATURE SCREECHES)
- As long as it's fed.
- (CREATURE BURPS)
Used to be Florence's
pet garter snake, William Snakespeare.
She tried to turn it purple,
the spell backfired.
And, between you and me,
most of her spells backfire these days.
LEWIS: Why?
JONATHAN: Ah, you'll have
to ask her that one yourself.
What's all that?
Charms, hexes,
wards, spells.
Evil can't come within 20 feet of
that cabinet, much less open it.
What's in it?
You know how I said
there were no rules?
Actually, there's one rule.
Don't open that cabinet.
Ever.
Or I'll toss you out on your
ear, you understand?
(SIGHS)
This is pretty much the only
thing I'm serious about,
so I need to hear you say it.
I understand.
JONATHAN: Isaac!
FLORENCE: Isaac!
Isaac, don't do this!
- JONATHAN: Please! Isaac!
- (CHANTS INDISTINCTLY)
Isaac! Please!
(BOTH GROAN)
Isaac.
(GASPS)
ISAAC: It's the beginning...
And the end.
The alpha...
And the omega.
Do you hear the ticking?
(CLOCK TICKING)
(EXHALES)
FLORENCE: Well, I have scoured
the crawl space.
I found a dead mouse,
but no clock.
You think reading that for the millionth
time will turn up something new?
No, not really.
So, you've told Lewis
everything?
Well, not everything.
I think you should.
Isaac may be dead,
but he is still dangerous.
If Lewis knew the truth...
Well, we don't know the truth.
We don't know where the clock is,
or what it does,
except something horrible.
No, we gotta do
the responsible thing.
Lie to the kid.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I can't believe
you did that.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
- (BELL RINGS)
- (CHUCKLES QUIETLY)
- Hey, Lewis.
- Hmm?
Why do you wear
those goggles?
Captain Midnight wears
a pair just like these.
You ever seen his show?
He's indomitable.
He's what?
Indomitable. Adjective.
Impossible to defeat.
That's what they call him.
The indomitable Captain Midnight.
I just think it might be easier for you,
if you lost the goggles.
Acted a little more,
you know,
normal.
Oh.
You think?
I'm just telling you
as a friend.
Right. Friends.
We're friends.
- (MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR RADIO)
- GIRL 1: That'd be swell.
Lewis!
GIRL 1: We could play jacks.
GIRL 2: I love jacks, yeah.
- Lewis!
- (CAR HORN BEEPING)
- (SIGHS)
- Can't you see me? Over here, right here!
Lewis! It's your uncle,
Johnny!
I should go.
Probably.
Come on, let's go! Get in.
Where's your goggles?
What are you
doing here?
Oh, we gotta
get some supplies.
Got a harvest moon tonight,
it's perfect.
Perfect for what?
For your first big-time,
serious spell.
Should I punch it?
You won't believe what this thing can do.
- (LAUGHS)
- Can we just go, please?
MAN: (ON RADIO) Well, doggone,
that moon'll be gone next week
with the lunar eclipse comin'.
Till then, let's
keep on rocking.
LEWIS: (SLOWLY) "From Saturn to the sun,
from the beast to noble one,
"like the alchemists of old,
"turn this dross lead
into gold!"
Wow. That was
really, really...
- Terrible. I mean, just awful.
- Hey!
You're reading it
like it's a Buick manual.
It's not what
you say, Lewis,
it's how you say it.
You're the only you
in the whole universe.
JONATHAN: That makes your style
of magic just crazy unique.
One in a hundred million
kajillion.
So, I can give you the right books,
teach you the right spells,
but that last 1%,
that's up to you.
So, how do I find my magic
style? Or whatever it is.
It's in there somewhere.
You just have to quiet down and listen.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Now it looks like
you're pooping.
Well, I don't know!
This all feels weird.
What's wrong with weird?
Weird's like the nuts
in my cookies,
it's the nuts that
make things interesting.
Let me show you
what a little weird can do.
(PLAYING MELODY OFF-KEY)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
You be a dear? Fetch a knife
and stab me in the ears.
(CONTINUES PLAYING)
- (YAPPING)
- (SIGHS)
(CREATURE GROANS)
(CREATURE GROWLS)
Well, for a boy who loves words,
you're sure at a loss for them.
Uncle Jonathan,
you're way more than just a parlor magician.
Have a look around.
(FAINT RUMBLING)
(TRICKLING)
(GROWLS)
Finally. A smile.
I was starting to think you were incapable.
(CHUCKLES)
- (LEWIS GRUNTS)
- (GASPS)
(GAGS)
Bad kitty!
You use the litter box!
(CREATURE GROWLS)
All right.
I'm going to bed.
You're welcome to stay up as
long as you like, of course.
- Uncle Jonathan?
- Hmm?
Tonight, that was
the most splendor...
Splendortast...
Splendorific.
I don't know the word yet,
but thank you.
I just wish that I met you
a long time ago.
Yeah, me, too.
Good night.
Why didn't I?
How come you left home?
(SIGHS) Well...
Truth is, my father,
your grandpa,
didn't like magic.
And he sure didn't like
me messing around with it.
We fought about it and...
And we fought some more,
until finally I just took off.
I was the black swan
of the family.
It's a black sheep.
Mmm, pretty sure
it's "swan."
(GULPS) Is that why you didn't go
to Mom and Dad's funeral?
(SIGHS)
I don't really think
she would've wanted me there.
I don't know.
She missed you.
She talked about you
all the time.
(SIGHS)
Good night.
Uncle Jonathan.
I think...
I think that I might be
a black swan, too.
Well, then I guess
we're a flock of swans.
A bevy.
It's called a bevy of swans.
Right.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CHAIR CREAKS)
- (CAT MEWS)
(CHAIR SQUEAKS)
- (CAT MEOWING)
- (CHAIR GROANS)
(CHAIR WHINES)
(JONATHAN YELPING)
Guys! I'm floating!
- Wait, wait.
- Oh. Uh, just...
I don't know!
JONATHAN: Levitaius dominungus!
Put me? Chair! Chair! Guys!
FLORENCE: Just. No, I...
(JONATHAN GROANS)
(CHAIR WHIMPERING)
- No, no, that's not the right...
- Fiddlesticks.
Just get the...
- Just one. Just...
- (CHAIR SQUEAKS)
- (KIDS GROANING)
- KID 1: Come on!
KID 2: The bell's gonna ring.
KID 3: Hurry up!
KID 4: Hurry up.
KID 5: Move it.
WOODY: Mmm... Mmm!
KID 1: Seriously, are you almost done?
KID 2: Please, hurry up!
(SOFTLY) Water to the face
at a very high-speed pace.
(GASPS AND CHOKES)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Shut up! Shut up!
Stop laughing! It's not funny!
(LEWIS CLEAR THROAT)
You can control the energy
if you focus and channel it.
- Won't it kill me?
- Not if you focus.
Then you are
the conductor. Watch.
- (SHOUTS)
- (CHAIR SQUEAKS)
Show me what you got.
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
- (CHAIR GRUNTING)
- Oh, Chair!
- Sorry, Chair!
- (OBJECTS SHATTER)
Ooh... (EXHALES)
Not bad.
(TABLE SEARING)
(SOFTLY) Oh...
- (CLOCK GONGING THRICE)
- (METALLIC CREAKING)
(OBJECTS RATTLING)
(GRUNTS, GASPS)
(MUFFLED TICKING)
JONATHAN: Three gongs, Florence.
Last time it was four, now it's three.
What happens when
it gets down to one?
We'll hide in the basement
like sensible people.
Okay, this is no time for jokes.
Things have changed.
I know.
Lewis.
What happens if he's here
when it goes off?
He won't be. Because we are
going to find it.
We just have to
hold it together.
(SIGHS) Okay.
(GRUNTS)
I'm sorry.
Let me get some butter.
(CORN CONTINUES POPPING)
(EXHALES)
Plaid button-down, please.
NARRATOR: (ON TV SHOW) And will
the indomitable Captain Midnight
defeat the dastardly
Comrade Ivan?
Maybe later, okay?
- (CHAIR WHIMPERING)
- Come on! I'm gonna be late!
See ya!
JONATHAN: Toodles.
WOMAN: (ON TV SHOW)
I'm getting out of here.
MAN: No, stop!
You ain't going anywhere.
WOMAN: I foolishly
walked into a trap.
- MAN: Why, you double-crossing...
- Stay.
- (CHAIR GRUMBLES)
- MAN: I'll have your life for this.
(LOCK TURNING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(SNAPS FINGERS) Yes!
Oop. Chair.
MAN: (ON PA) And the winner of the fourth
grade class president election is...
Tarby Corrigan!
(ALL CHEERING)
Thank you.
(BELL RINGS)
LEWIS: Tarby. Excuse me.
Tarby! Congratulations, Tarby.
Thanks, Lewis.
If you want, I can bring some
cookies tomorrow and celebrate.
Yeah, Tarby. Go have a cookie
picnic here with the little runt.
TARBY: Woody!
Just...
I'll catch up later.
Hey, you got your cast off.
Do you wanna go hit some balls?
Sorry. The boys and me...
We're gonna explore
Wilder Creek.
Maybe another time.
I've got something
way better than that.
Oh, yeah?
My house.
Everyone's wrong, you know.
It's not haunted.
It's magic.
Magic?
Magic's not real.
It is real.
My uncle.
He's a warlock.
That's a boy witch, and...
I can teach you spells
to throw a curveball,
or hit a home run,
or throw a touchdown every single time.
Cross my heart.
You can see for yourself.
(MUFFLED CLOCK TICKING)
So where is it already,
you evil, old coot?
The arm.
(CLICKS)
(CREAKING)
(GASPS)
Blasted pigeons.
Got you.
I'll find you that curveball
spell. Just give me a sec.
Whoa, what's in there?
LEWIS: Oh, um...
We're not allowed
to open it.
Oh, yeah? Why not?
I don't know, but
it's my uncle's only rule.
Besides, it's locked.
No. It's not.
(LOCK TURNING)
Tarby, I mean it. We can't.
TARBY: Don't be
such a scaredy-cat.
Maybe it's the spell
you're looking for.
LEWIS: No!
What's "necromancy"?
Noun. The practice of communicating
with the dead or raising them to life!
Let's put it back.
Raising the dead?
Now, that would
be a trick.
(MUFFLED CLANGING)
Put it back!
- We have to put it back right now!
- Stop! Ow.
TARBY: Fine!
None of it's real anyways.
It's all just weird.
You're just weird.
Was that the Corrigan boy?
- He was just leaving.
- What were you two doing?
Nothing.
Uncle Jonathan, do you
wanna play ball with me?
I can't right now.
There's something I need to look into.
Later, okay?
- Okay.
- (DOOR CLOSES, LOCK CLICKS)
(SIGHS)
JONATHAN: Isaac hid the room with
a hex so no one would find these,
but I can't make
heads or tails of this.
FLORENCE: I know about
every magic language there is.
The Alberti Cipher, the Enochian Glyphs,
but this... (SIGHING)
Really?
Well, at least I lived to see the
purple pachyderm get stumped.
I don't know how much longer any
of us will be living, weird beard.
- Cranky old crone.
- Mush brush.
- Hag face.
- Oh, go braid your back hair.
I'd give you a nasty look,
but you've already got one.
(SCOFFS) Okay, okay,
you old yeti. Now, look.
What does this
mean to you?
JONATHAN: The omega.
Isaac talked about it
when he died.
The last letter
of the Greek alphabet.
And in early Christianity...
It means Judgment Day.
LEWIS' MOM:
You all right, kiddo?
I'm okay.
You always were
a lousy liar.
(SIGHS)
You're lonely, huh?
I just wish Jonathan
wasn't so busy.
I wish he could spend
more time with you.
It's okay.
What about Tarby?
- Tarby hates me.
- Oh.
You can fix that. Easy.
Just show him
some real magic.
I can't do any real magic.
Yes, you can.
With the book, silly.
The one I told you to find.
Well, you found it,
didn't you?
Book?
You mean the necromancy book
in the library?
Uncle Jonathan told me
never to even touch it.
Oh, he won't mind.
He's too busy, anyways.
Take the book.
Show Tarby a real trick.
He's gonna be your friend again.
I know it.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(KIDS CHEERING)
ROSE RITA:
Tarby's a jerk, you know?
He runs for president every year and
he's always nice until the election.
After that,
he goes back to being, him.
You don't need him.
We could go look for spiders.
- If you want.
- (BELL RINGS)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Just leave me alone, okay?
Tarby!
Okay. You wanna see
some real magic?
I'll show you.
Yeah? You gonna
saw a lady in half?
I'm gonna raise the dead.
You're a liar. No one
can raise the dead.
Watch me.
Unless...
Unless you're scared.
You need a babysitter? Fine.
But this whole thing is just
gonna be a big waste of time.
When?
(FAINT CREAKING)
(MUFFLED TICKING)
LEWIS: Tarby!
Tarby?
(BIRDS CAWING IN DISTANCE)
- (OWL HOOTING)
- (INSECTS CHIRPING)
- Boo!
- (YELPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Tarby, that's not funny!
It is from here.
Well, come on,
smart guy.
Who are we
gonna wake up?
How about this one?
The lamb means that it's a kid's grave,
and I don't wanna raise up a kid.
It's creepy
that you know that.
This way, I think.
TARBY: Nice trick with the book, Lewis.
I know that's you.
LEWIS: No, it's not.
Is that it?
Yeah, I think so.
Well, come on.
(OWL HOOTING)
(LEWIS GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
"For thou who sleeps
in stone and clay,
"heed this call,
rise up and obey.
"Trek on through the mortal door,
assemble flesh and walk once more."
(WIND BLOWING)
TARBY: So, what now?
That's it.
That's all it says.
See, told you
all this was a huge...
(BREATH TREMBLING)
Tarby?
Tarby!
(BONES CRACKING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(CLOCK GONGS TWICE)
(YAWNING)
Could you put
those back, please?
(NOISY MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
(PUPPETS CHATTERING)
He's coming home.
He's free. He's back!
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING
AND RATTLING)
PUPPETS: He's coming home. He's awake.
He's back! He's coming home.
He's coming home.
He's awake! He's back!
(WHISTLES)
That's not creepy.
JONATHAN: Who'd be crazy enough
to bring Isaac Izard back?
Someone suicidal.
- (CLOCKS TICKING RAPIDLY)
- (CREAKING)
The house knows he's back.
Can you feel that?
Like a dog with rabies.
Knows his master's coming home.
I'm gonna need your help
on this one, Florence.
My magic won't be enough.
I'm barely qualified as it is.
I can't.
I'll just mess it up.
- I can't do this alone.
- We won't have to. Lewis.
- What about Lewis?
- He's stronger than you know.
And one and a half warlocks is better
than nothing. Just tell him the truth.
No. He's just a boy.
You're the smartest witch I've ever known.
You can cast spells
I can't even pronounce.
I said I can't.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Look, Isaac is coming back and
we can't let him get inside.
(SIGHS) Well, if your magic is off-limits,
then what's the plan?
I can still swing a hammer.
- (MARMALADE BARKING)
- (HAMMERING CONTINUES)
These are crazy people,
Marmalade. Crazy people.
Do you think these are enough
to keep Isaac out?
Oh, yes. Maybe.
I'm gonna get some more.
(WHISTLING JAUNTY TUNE)
(MECHANICAL RATTLING)
(STOPS WHISTLING)
LEWIS: Uncle Jonathan?
Don't come up! I'm...
I'm coming down.
(SIGHS)
Listen, I need
to talk to you.
Not a great time, Lewis.
I'm working on a heavy-duty spell.
I want you to stay
at Mrs. Z's for a few days.
Come on. I see the horseshoes.
I know something's wrong.
What are you talking about?
Everything's fine.
FLORENCE: No. It's not.
You're right, Lewis.
Something is wrong. Something is very wrong.
- Florence...
- He's got eyes, Jonathan.
(SIGHS)
It's our friend, Isaac Izard.
Except he's not our friend.
He's very wicked,
very powerful.
And I'm afraid he's back
from the great beyond.
Yeah. That's what
I wanted to talk to...
And when we find out who's
raised him from the dead,
they are going to
be sorry. Very sorry.
Oh.
Mmm, yeah, they...
They sure will.
Look, the truth is,
it's not safe for you here.
At least, not now.
So, go next door with Florence, okay?
Everything's gonna be fine.
WOMAN: Maybe just once more
around the block...
MAN: Sure, no problem.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
- Come on.
- (CRACKLES)
Mrs. Zimmerman?
Uh, I'm sorry, dear?
What are you doing?
I'm just trying...
- (SIGHS)
- (MUSIC DISTORTS, FADES OFF)
Nothing.
LEWIS: Wait.
Isaac and Uncle Jonathan
used to perform together?
They did everything together.
They were best friends.
LEWIS: They were?
Once.
Isaac was an orphan.
And Jonathan, a runaway.
Neither of them had family.
All they had was magic.
And each other.
Then, Isaac went away to war.
He was fighting in Germany
when he went MIA.
Months passed.
Then, suddenly,
Isaac came back home.
But it wasn't the same Isaac.
He was different.
And angry.
And more powerful than any
warlock had the right to be.
How? What happened to him?
We don't know. All he said was,
he was lost in the Black Forest.
Now, that is a very old place
with very old magic.
It's where the Brothers Grimm
wrote their histories.
You mean their fairy-tales?
Now, we think that Isaac met
a dark warlock in those woods.
A teacher who gave him some
terrifying, forbidden books.
One of which
is so dangerous
that your uncle keeps it
locked up in his cabinet.
Then, Isaac abandoned
poor Jonathan.
No explanation. And he found
himself a witch. Selena.
So spiteful and mean,
he married her.
And they locked themselves
away in the house.
Until one night last year,
Isaac performed a blood magic
ritual that killed him.
LEWIS: What was
the ritual for?
To make a key.
A clock key of human bone.
We think his wife's bones.
We think Isaac killed
Selena to make it.
Uncle Jonathan said that you were a
really good witch. Even better than him.
I was.
Once.
My magic was
the toast of Paris.
You should've seen me
before the war.
I melted Salvador Dali's watch
one time, right off his wrist.
Then why can't
you help us?
You know how magic
comes from the inside?
Well, I got hurt one time.
Pretty badly.
And even though my outsides got better,
my insides never did.
And so, now, every time I try
to work any real magic,
it just comes out broken.
(SIGHS) Now,
there's very few problems in the
world that can't, at least, be helped
by a good chocolate
chip cookie.
- (BELL RINGING)
- Tarby. Tarby!
Not now, Lewis,
I'm late for gym.
- No, now. We gotta talk now!
- What?
BOY 1: Let go!
WOODY: Where do you think you're going, huh?
The other night, what we did
in the cemetery...
We did something awful.
My uncle's in trouble. We all are, and...
See, there's this clock...
Lewis! Just stop. Nothing
happened in that cemetery.
Look, I get it, you're scared.
I am, too. We're the...
- (GASPING)
- Woody!
LEWIS: Tarby, get off me!
BOY 2: Come on, let's get out of here.
BOY 1: Let's go!
(GRUNTS)
- Good morning, Miss Fisher.
- Woody.
- I'm not scared.
- (PANTING)
And if you tell anyone I was there,
I'll break both your arms.
(LEWIS GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
TARBY: You're just a weirdo.
(LEWIS COUGHING)
(WOODY CHUCKLES)
LEWIS: "Indomitable."
(GASPING AND PANTING)
(CLOCKS TICKING)
Uncle Jonathan?
You in here?
No way.
(DOOR SHUTS)
(WINGS FLUTTERING)
(RATTLING)
(BIRD CAWING)
(SCREAMING)
Help me! Help, please! Help!
Uncle Jonathan! Uncle Jonathan!
Help! Help me, please!
JONATHAN: Come on. Come on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Get those papers!
(GRUNTING)
- You all right?
- (PANTING)
What are you doing here?
I told you it's not safe!
I was being indomitable.
(JONATHAN SIGHS)
I suppose you were,
weren't you?
You can't do this alone.
You need help, and I can help you!
No, you can't.
Actually, I can. 'Cause
I know how to read this.
But I'm gonna need
some Ovaltine.
Wait. I don't understand.
You've seen this code before?
Yes. Comrade Ivan uses one just like it
to send commands to his Red Brigade.
JONATHAN: "Comrade" who?
LEWIS: Comrade Ivan
from the TV show.
But Captain Midnight always
stops him and decodes it
with, uh...
This! The Captain Midnight
secret decoder pin.
I don't believe it.
I don't believe it!
Three Ovaltine shakes,
please.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
"With this clock, Selena and I shall
wipe this filthy world clean."
(LEWIS SLURPING)
It's a doomsday clock.
In a way,
it destroys everything.
But not by ending the world,
but sending it back to the beginning.
If the planet is one giant clock, then this
damn thing is the winder. (SNAPS FINGERS)
- (GASPS)
- He's winding it back to the very beginning of time!
So, everything goes in reverse.
We grow younger and younger
until we vanish.
Until there's no one left.
(JONATHAN WHISTLES)
I knew Isaac
was strong, but
this goes beyond anything I ever
thought he was capable of.
When's it happen?
"When night's
at its blackest."
The total lunar eclipse. Tonight!
All those moons painted in my bedroom.
What if Isaac was studying them
and waiting for the right moment?
That's what the gongs
are counting down to.
(PEOPLE GASP)
We'll take
the gumballs, too.
JONATHAN: Isaac's been here.
(BIRDS CAWING)
Isaac pulled
all the horseshoes off?
Burned 'em off.
One by one.
FLORENCE: Like ants
with a magnifying glass.
(SIGHS) Just how
powerful is he now?
Death's been good to him.
Wait here.
- (CREAKING)
- (CHAIR MOANS)
Chair! It's okay. It's okay.
I'm here. I'm here to help.
Here, it's okay. It's okay.
You're okay.
He's torn the place
to pieces.
He must have been
looking for something.
And I think I know what.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's get rid of it.
Uh, shouldn't this be
melting right now?
Too much John
the Conqueror root.
No. Not enough Goofer Dust.
(GASPS) Oh.
JONATHAN: (CHUCKLES)
Grains of paradise.
FLORENCE: We don't have
any Grains of Paradise.
JONATHAN: You know what?
Maybe a pinch of motherwort.
Uncle Jonathan.
FLORENCE: What about some Lotus root?
JONATHAN: Yeah, yeah.
More Lotus root.
- LEWIS: Uncle Jonathan.
- Hmm?
This is my fault.
Lewis, you helped us.
You're the one who decoded the blueprints.
LEWIS: No.
I mean, I'm the one
who brought Isaac back.
Lewis?
What are you
talking about?
(GULPS)
I opened the cabinet.
I used your book.
(STUTTERS)
I'm so, so, so sorry.
You couldn't have. You don't know enough
magic to pull off a spell like that.
I just followed
the directions.
I bled onto the book.
Oh, Lewis.
Blood magic?
That was my one rule.
I know. I'm sorry.
- And you broke it?
- I didn't mean to.
So, you opened
a forbidden cabinet,
and performed an unholy ritual,
on accident?
- Jonathan...
- I didn't know Isaac was evil.
You never told me.
Oh, so this is my fault?
I didn't say that.
- Then, what are you saying?
- (WHIMPERS)
What the hell
were you thinking?
I just wanted Tarby
to be my friend again!
And I want my parents back!
(SOBBING)
And I figured
if it worked here,
I could go home
and try it on them.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
I just want my mom!
(LEWIS CRYING QUIETLY)
I'm sorry.
It was a mistake.
You coming here.
FLORENCE:
Now, hold on, Jonathan.
No! No, please!
Please. I'll make it up to you. Please.
No. This is no place
for a kid.
It's not safe for you here.
I was wrong to ever think that it was.
But we're a bevy of swans!
JONATHAN: I'm sorry.
(CRYING)
You stay here.
Let me talk to him.
I know I've got a Malleus Maleficarum
around here somewhere.
Should help with the key.
(SIGHS) Go ahead,
yell at me, call me some names.
No names.
Not this time.
Jonathan,
that little boy needs you.
But what he did...
He's a child.
Children make mistakes.
They get in trouble.
That's why they're children.
No, this is not swiping a comic book,
Florence. This is...
(STAMMERS)
I don't have a choice here.
FLORENCE: Of course you do.
You could stick it out!
No, no, when the going gets tough,
you get going, right for the exit.
Like how you ran away
from your family.
Ran away?
My dad threw me out!
And what about
your little sister?
She'd looked up to you.
She needed you, and now she's gone.
And you're going to abandon
her only child.
Look, I don't know
how to take care of a kid.
How to talk to him, how to keep him safe.
Especially now! I'm just...
You're scared.
Yes, all right? I'm scared for Lewis!
Scared he'll get hurt!
FLORENCE: Well,
guess what, genius?
That is the whole point.
You having a child means
being scared for them 24/7
and doing it anyway.
It's the whole damn
job description.
And I would give everything
to have that job again.
To have my little
girl back, to...
You know what?
I do have a name for you.
Jonathan Barnavelt,
you're a coward!
(MARMALADE BARKING)
Mrs. Hanchett! Mrs. Hanchett!
- Lewis.
- He's free! We gotta go now!
Well, who, what are
we talking about?
There is someone
in your house.
- Please. Hurry!
- Who?
- Come on.
- Take Marmalade. Wait.
Come on. Hurry, please!
We don't care about the door.
What? Lewis, it's cold.
- LEWIS: He's upstairs. I saw him!
- Oh, my God, it's a step.
He's in your house
right now!
Lewis! Lewis!
LEWIS: Please! Hurry.
- Lewis, wait! Hold on. It's slippery.
- Hurry. Come on.
Please hurry,
Mrs. Hanchett! Please!
Lewis, it's slippery.
Lewis, stop!
You're not making any sense.
What bad man?
His name is Isaac.
Isaac Izard.
Isaac Izard?
Lewis, he's dead. He died last year.
Stay here.
Uncle Jonathan!
Mrs. Zimmerman!
- It's locked.
- (DOOR RATTLING)
It must be Isaac.
Out of the way.
(GRUNTS)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Mrs. Hanchett,
get away from the door.
Don't be ridiculous.
No!
(LAUGHS)
Hello, Lewis.
(PANTING)
- (COUGHS) Hmm.
- (MARMALADE YAPPING)
- Mmm.
- (GASPS)
Stay away from her.
(BONES CRACKING)
Why should I stay away
from my beautiful wife?
(MOANING)
You're Selena Izard?
- (BURBLING)
- (BONES CRACKING)
(BARKING, SQUEAKING)
(YELPING)
(SQUEAKING)
(SIGHS) In the flesh.
Uncle Jonathan!
Lewis!
But, you died.
Whoever said I died?
FLORENCE: Isaac!
JONATHAN: Isaac!
Isaac!
- (RUMBLING)
- (ISAAC CHANTING INDISTINCTLY)
JONATHAN: Isaac!
SELENA: Isaac!
FLORENCE: No!
(GRUNTS)
Is that bone?
FLORENCE: Human.
He killed her to make
some sort of key.
I thought it was made from...
Not my bone, no.
That was a chunk
from the real Mrs. Hanchett.
Lovely woman.
That is, before I killed her
and took her place.
(GASPS)
Mmm, my wife,
she has a talent
for disguises.
(GIGGLES)
I learn from the best.
- Aw.
- (BONES CRACKING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(GIGGLES)
Come give
your mommy a kiss.
LEWIS: You.
It was you in my dreams.
I couldn't get near that locked cabinet.
The charms were too strong.
But you, you could get
that nasty, old book for me.
Raise Isaac for me.
You could do everything I wanted.
And now,
you are going to get us
that clock key.
(GASPS)
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
No, no, not that,
not there. (LAUGHS)
Whoa, whoa! (SCREAMING)
- (THUDS)
- (CAT YOWLS)
Whew!
Hmm.
- (JONATHAN GROANING)
- Well, come on.
Now you're just showing off.
FLORENCE: Lewis!
- Lewis!
- Lewis, where are you?
- Isaac took him.
- Yes, but where?
I think I know.
(CRACKLES)
- LEWIS: Uncle Jonathan!
- Lewis!
LEWIS: Mrs. Zimmerman, I'm over here.
FLORENCE: We're coming.
LEWIS: I'm over here!
LEWIS: Uncle Jonathan,
over here!
No, here! No,
over here! Help me.
(FLORENCE
AND JONATHAN GRUNTING)
(APPLAUSE)
ISAAC: Barnavelt and Izard,
masters of prestidigitation,
beloved by the crowned
heads of Europe, together again.
I'm sure you'll remember
my next trick.
(GASPS)
No!
FLORENCE: No.
- Uncle Jonathan!
- Isaac, don't do this!
ISAAC: I like the boy.
An orphan with a love
for Captain Midnight?
Mmm, warms my dead heart.
Please don't
make me butcher him.
Give me the key.
You don't have to
hurt anyone. Just tell us, where is the clock
The clock is under
a witch's hex.
You'll never find it.
This is over.
JONATHAN: Isaac, please.
There must be some part of you
that doesn't want this,
that isn't completely dead.
I was dead
long before I died.
We know you went through
something awful during the war, we all did!
Oh, on the contrary.
It's where
I met my teacher.
My unit had been
caught in an ambush.
Everyone slaughtered.
I'd been left for dead.
I stumbled through
the Black Forest for days.
I chanted every spell I knew,
with one thought only.
"Make me powerful enough
to end this!"
To erase the horrors
I had witnessed.
When I opened my eyes,
I saw him.
He offered me
something to drink.
(WHEEZING)
For a small price, of course.
Suddenly, I had it.
The blueprints
for the clock...
(MECHANICAL RATTLING)
...in my mind.
Clear as day.
That wasn't a warlock.
It wasn't even a human.
It was a demon, you reckless idiot!
- You summoned a demon!
- (ISAAC LAUGHS)
Yes! Yes.
"Azazel," to be exact.
The fourth prince of Hell.
Oh, he gave me
a wonderful gift.
(MARMALADE SQUEAKING)
The greatest magic trick ever.
I'm going to make
people disappear.
Spin the world back,
until the dawn of time.
All that will be left...
Selena and I.
But if you go back
to the beginning,
history, humans, it will all
just start over again.
ISAAC: No.
I'll make sure people
are never born this time,
with the help of a friend.
Lewis' parents won't die
in that awful crash.
Your husband and sweet little
girl won't be killed.
ISAAC: They'll never
have existed.
No people, no war.
Now, Jonathan,
the key.
Florence,
now would be a good time
for a little magic.
ISAAC: Of all people, Florence,
I thought you'd want this.
I know what losing
your family did to you.
You're too sad and broken
to work any real magic.
Maybe I was.
But now,
I'm indomitable.
(JONATHAN GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Ha-ha!
Marmalade! Now!
(SQUEAKING)
(SCREAMING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
- (YELLS IN PAIN)
- (SIZZLING)
(GROANING)
(CREAKING)
JONATHAN: Where are they?
FLORENCE: They're gone.
Mind your step.
There's a tongue.
There's a big tongue.
JONATHAN: I've got it.
(LEWIS GULPS)
So
creepy.
(JONATHAN GASPING)
- (MECHANICAL SQUEAKING)
- PUPPET: Time for this little boy to go.
Uncle Jonathan!
- (SCREAMING)
- JONATHAN: Be careful!
- Lewis! Don't freak them out!
- (PUPPET 1 LAUGHING)
Unhand me! Let me go! Oh, no!
Put me down! Stop! Put me down!
PUPPET 2: Mommy. Mommy.
(PUPPET 2 CACKLING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
PUPPET 3: Why won't you talk to me?
Why won't you talk to me?
(SCREAMS)
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
(SCREAMING)
Wait, wait. Jonathan!
LEWIS: Mrs. Zimmerman!
Let me go! Let go of me!
Jonathan!
- (GROANS)
- JONATHAN: Son of a...
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
JONATHAN: Lewis. You okay?
LEWIS: I'm okay.
Would you look at that?
JONATHAN: Okay,
let's get back in there.
FLORENCE: What?
With those creepy, metal monsters inside?
They'll tear us to shreds!
JONATHAN: Florence,
we have to find Isaac and Selena.
FLORENCE: We don't know
where in the house they are.
JONATHAN: No. But if we wait around,
we know something bad will happen.
FLORENCE: You heard Isaac.
He's using the witch's hex!
I understand that. So, should we just sit around
and try to figure out the hex?
- We don't have time!
- No. We need a plan!
Guys!
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
(PUMPKINS SCREECHING)
(ALL GROWLING)
Oh, my giddy aunt.
Don't worry, their teeth
are made of pumpkin,
they can't really hurt us.
(GASPS)
(GROANING)
Okay, I made that up.
(ALL GASPING)
It's some kind of
ungodly adhesive!
LEWIS: I'm stuck!
Me, too!
You know, I didn't think
this is how I was gonna die.
(GROWLS)
Look! Mrs. Zimmerman,
grab my shirt!
I've got you!
Just chop. Chop, chop!
FLORENCE: Lewis! Hurry!
(GROWLS)
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS) God,
I hate pumpkins.
JONATHAN:
Did you see that, Florence?
I exploded it with a psychic
energy blast! It worked!
FLORENCE: Yes, Jonathan,
we're all very proud of you!
JONATHAN: Did you see
that I now have the power?
FLORENCE: Yes,
I understand. Gold star.
Ha-ha!
(YELLS, GROANS)
LEWIS: Uncle Jonathan.
Uncle Jonathan, it's me, please wake up!
- FLORENCE: Jonathan. Jonathan, you've got to get up!
- Uncle Jonathan.
You've got to get up
right now!
(GROANS)
What are you looking at,
you shriveled old prune?
I'm looking at you,
you dumb baby orangutan.
(CHUCKLES) Aw, Lewis.
Oh, Florence,
you missed a spot.
Lewis. I'm sorry, Lewis.
I'm sorry about everything.
It's okay. Me, too.
FLORENCE: Don't get me wrong,
uh, this is lovely,
but there's only
18 minutes to the eclipse.
And they've got the key.
How do we find the clock?
We can't.
It's got a witch's
hex on it.
And that means it's hidden
from every witch or warlock,
no matter how powerful.
Not even Florence
could find it.
(SIGHS) There must be something
we're not thinking of.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Maybe I could find it.
I'm not a witch
or warlock.
Well, not yet anyways, but
maybe if I tried
some magic?
Would that work?
(EXHALES) Okay. I'm ready.
Lewis, I don't know
about that eight ball.
Hey, this is my magic.
Not yours.
(LEWIS SIGHS)
Let's go.
Locate. Verb.
To discover the exact place
and position of.
Secret! Adjective!
Something that is kept unknown or unseen!
Clock! Noun.
A mechanical device, used for measuring time!
A time-piece! A horologe!
Wow. He is weird.
Isn't he, though?
LEWIS:
Locate the secret clock.
Locate the secret clock!
(SOFTLY) Please,
Mom and Dad.
Tell me where
the clock is. Please.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(LIQUID SLOSHING)
"Under the boiler."
- (GASPS)
- Lewis, you genius!
(PUMPKINS GROWLING
AND SCREECHING)
Shall we?
(PUMPKINS SCREECHING)
(PUMPKINS GROWLING
AND SCREECHING)
- JONATHAN: Trick or treat!
- (PUMPKIN SCREECHES)
(GROWLING)
Mrs. Zimmerman?
FLORENCE: Hmm?
What is that?
(CREATURE GROWLING)
Jonathan. Open the door.
Working on it.
- FLORENCE: Jonathan?
- (FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
- Jonathan!
- (LEWIS SCREAMS)
That's not helping!
(GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMING)
- (GROWLING)
(FLORENCE SIGHS)
- (PUPPETS CACKLING)
- (DOOR BANGING)
Lewis. Crack it open.
- (MECHANICAL WHIRRING)
- (MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
JONATHAN:
Even in death, so creepy.
(PUPPET SQUEAKS)
(PUPPETS POWERING DOWN)
(GASPS)
JONATHAN: Florence,
I really have to pee.
FLORENCE:
Not the time, Jonathan.
(EXHALES)
(GROWLING)
Snakespeare!
- Mrs. Zimmerman!
- Florence!
Go! Go!
It's okay, she knows how to handle Snakespeare.
Come here. Quickly.
Isaac!
Stop! (GRUNTS)
(BOTH GROAN)
ISAAC: Please. I taught you
everything you know, Jonathan.
I didn't teach you
everything I know.
(BELL TOLLS)
(BLOWS)
ISAAC: My darling.
No!
(GASPS)
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
- (GRUNTS) Wait there, Lewis!
- No, I have to come with you.
No! There may be traps.
I have protection.
(GRUNTING)
I feel something.
I've got it!
- (CRACKLING)
- (GROANING)
Uncle Jonathan!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Uncle Jonathan?
Uncle Jonathan!
(WAILING)
(SHUSHING) It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's me. Lewis, your nephew.
(CONTINUES WAILING)
Lewis! Come with us to the turret.
It's a special turret. It'll protect us.
I like you, Lewis.
I like being your mom.
ISAAC: Forget about your uncle.
Soon he'll be gone...
- (GASPS)
- ...like everyone else.
Uncle Jonathan?
Uncle Jonathan!
(LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Hey! I got you.
(GRUNTS, EXHALES)
(LEWIS GROANS)
(ISAAC GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
- (LEWIS PANTING)
- (COOING)
(JONATHAN BABBLING)
(GEARS CREAKING)
(GASPS)
(JONATHAN LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
What?
(JONATHAN GURGLING)
Mom. Dad.
What should I do?
"Say goodbye"?
Say goodbye? I don't get it.
What do you mean?
(GASPS)
(CRACKLING)
Okay. Goodbye, guys.
(SHUDDERING) I love you.
(GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
Look, my darling.
It's beginning.
(MECHANICAL GROANING)
The sands of time
are shifting. (LAUGHS)
- (THUNDERCLAP)
- (PEOPLE GROANING)
(LAUGHING)
(GASPING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (GEARS SCREECH)
- (GRUNTS)
(CREAKING)
ISAAC: Quickly!
Something is wrong!
SELENA: What is it?
Help me! (GRUNTING)
(GEARS CREAK)
(CRACKLING)
(GRUNTING)
(ISAAC GRUNTING)
I want to show you
what a little weird can do.
(GRUNTS)
- (GASPS)
- (SELENA YELPS)
(YELLING)
(GEARS CREAK)
(PANTING)
- (JONATHAN GRUNTS)
- What?
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(BOTH EXHALE)
Uncle Jonathan.
I'm back.
You did it. (LAUGHS)
You stopped the clock!
Do not tell Florence
about the baby body.
She'll never
let me live it down.
- I won't.
- You promise?
I swear. No baby body.
- Warlock secret?
- Never happened.
(CHUCKLES)
- You're the best. You did it. Toss me my trousers.
- (CHUCKLES)
Not a word to Florence.
I'm serious.
Well, well, well.
Look what the cat threw up.
(BOTH LAUGH)
- (JONATHAN LAUGHS)
- Whew!
Oh, you fixed Snakespeare!
Well, you stopped
the clock.
Nah, I just wet my pants.
Literally. Lewis stopped the clock.
FLORENCE: Lewis.
You are indomitable.
Mrs. Zimmerman,
I'm sorry you lost your family.
I'm sorry you lost yours.
But maybe would you wanna be
a black swan with us?
Can I be a purple one?
Deal.
I would like that
very much.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
I don't want
the creepy little runt.
Think I want him?
LEWIS:
You know what, fellas?
I don't really
wanna play anyways.
(WHISPERS) Ball to the face
at a very high-speed pace.
(GRUNTS)
(KIDS EXCLAIM)
Lucky shot.
We want Lewis on our team.
No. We want him!
ALL: No, Lewis, come on!
Come on! Lewis, come on!
(ALL CONTINUE SHOUTING)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
- Rose Rita, right?
- Mmm-hmm.
Can I see your bug book?
I've seen you with your dictionary.
You know the word is "insect."
But sure.
Wow. You drew these?
These are really good.
You look like an insect.
I mean that
as the highest compliment.
That's how I take it.
- (BELL RINGS)
- LEWIS: I'm so excited. Like it's so...
- (HORN BEEPS)
- Oh, yeah.
- Bye!
- Bye.
Who was that?
Rose Rita Pottinger.
She's a friend.
She is?
Is it kissy-faced?
No, platonic.
Look at him playing it cool.
James Dean,
all of a sudden. (LAUGHS)
Uncle Jonathan,
punch it.
Let's see
what this baby can do.
(JONATHAN AND FLORENCE LAUGH)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
- Hi. We're home. Hello.
- Aw.
(CHAIR SQUEAKS)
You ready?
LEWIS: Oh, yeah.
- (CHAIR WHIMPERING)
- Stay.
FLORENCE: You know, Jonathan,
you drive like an old grandma.
JONATHAN: Oh, that's funny,
you look like one.
LEWIS: Guys, stop!
You're both super-old.
JONATHAN:
Ha-ha! Nice one, Lewis.
FLORENCE: Gold star.
(CHAIR SQUEAKS)
(CHAIR WHINES)
JONATHAN: Bad kitty!
Use the litter box!
- (CREATURE GROANS)
- (CHAIR SQUEAKS)
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
- (CREATURE GROWLS)
- (CHAINSAW CONTINUES WHIRRING)