(WAVES SLOSHING)
(RHYTHMIC CLINKING)
(CLINKING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
(WAVES SLOSHING)
- Colored HI and improvements by StreamFlex
NEWSCASTER: ...spread of this,
happening outside the walls.
- (NEWS THEME PLAYING)
- Tonight's storm is causing
all kinds of problems
around the Bay.
Pete Giddings will have
the forecast.
And we'll show you
what would happen to the Bay
if some scientists' predictions
come true.
All on 7 at 11:00.
♪ ♪
TV ANNOUNCER: What has 12 million eyes,
192 million teeth
and stretches from
the Golden Gate Bridge
all the way to the Twin Towers?
It's Hands Across America.
A 4,000-mile-long chain
of Good Samaritans
standing hand in hand,
through fields of grain,
past purple mountains,
and across fruited plains,
from sea to shining sea.
That's right.
This summer, six million people
will tether themselves together
to fight hunger
in the United States.
Visit your local record shop
to find out
how you can be a part
of Hands Across America.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTTLES CLATTERING)
Put some heat on that one.
RUSSEL: Yeah, I guess
I missed my chance to go pro.
(CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- Oh!
- (RUSSEL EXHALES SHARPLY)
Tell you what.
Right now, you could walk away
with a prize
from the second level,
or you could keep going for
a prize from the third level.
Okay.
What do you think, Addy?
Should we stop or keep going?
(ROLLER COASTER RUMBLING,
RIDERS SCREAMING)
Don't look at me.
It's your birthday.
I want number 11.
- Yeah?
- That one?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Uh, yeah, uh, that one.
- RUSSEL: Thanks, man.
- Of course.
Yeah.
RAYNE: That shirt better not
give her nightmares.
RUSSEL: In trouble for winning
my daughter a T-shirt.
(CHUCKLES)
That's a new one.
RAYNE: She was terrified
when it came on TV.
You'd know that
if you were around, right?
RUSSEL: Who let her watch it?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
You know...
you know, they're filming
something by the carousel.
You should see if
they're looking for extras.
RUSSEL: Uh... I need another beer.
(ROLLER COASTER CLANKING)
(RIDERS SCREAMING)
(RAYNE SCOFFS)
RUSSEL: I can't have a beer now?
Hey. How about the Big Dipper?
Addy, you want to try it?
RAYNE: Russel, you know she's
not big enough to do that.
And I sure as hell
am not doing it, so...
- (CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
- (BELL RINGING)
RUSSEL: Whac-A-Mole!
Yeah, Whac-A-Mole, guy.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- How many tickets?
- Two tickets.
- Two tickets!
Two tickets!
RAYNE: Hey, Addy,
come to the bathroom.
I don't have to go.
(ELECTRONIC GAME MUSIC PLAYING)
- (BELL RINGING)
- Russel?
Russel! Can you watch
your daughter, please?
I'm watching.
Baby, stay close, okay?
(ELECTRONIC GAME MUSIC
CONTINUES)
(THUNDER CRASHES,
ELECTRONIC GAME MUSIC FADES)
(AUDIO CONTINUES
FAINT AND DISTORTED)
- NANCY: Glen.
- GLEN: What?
- Stop it.
- (LAUGHS): I'm not doing anything.
NANCY: You keep doing scissors.
GLEN: Ah, I'm just cruising.
- (NANCY LAUGHS)
- Come on.
- GLEN: Um, what?
- (RIDERS SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
- NANCY: This is ridiculous.
- GLEN: It's too rad.
Two knots. Come on, now.
(LAUGHS): What?
- This is... this is impossible.
- Oh, my God.
(WAVES SLOSHING)
(PLAYFUL SCREAMING, CHATTER)
(RIDE WHIRRING, LAUGHTER)
(PLAYFUL CHATTER AND SHOUTING
IN DISTANCE)
(THUNDER BOOMING)
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER
IN DISTANCE)
MAN: (LAUGHS) Don't do it. Don't do it.
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
NARRATOR: (OVER SPEAKERS) These, the earth and water,
he divided into places
from which life could spring.
The mountains and the valleys
and the waters
were all where they should be.
(MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
Then Sotuknang went to Taiowa
and said,
"I want you to see
what I have done.
And I have done well."
And Taiowa looked and said,
"It is very good.
"But you are not done with it.
"Now you must create life
of all kinds
and set it in motion
according to my plan."
(HOOTING)
- (GASPS, EXHALES)
- (NARRATOR CONTINUES)
(OVER SPEAKERS): ...and went
into the endless space
and gathered substance
to create his helper,
the Spider Woman.
"Look all about you,
Spider Woman," said Sotuknang.
"Here now is endless space,
"but in the world,
there is no joyful movement.
The world needs..."
(NARRATION STOPS,
ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(RAIN PATTERING OUTSIDE)
(THUMPING, ADDY GASPS)
(DISTANT CLATTERING)
(WHISTLING "ITSY BITSY SPIDER")
(SOMEONE ELSE
WHISTLING A TUNE NEARBY)
(ADDY STOPS WHISTLING)
(WHISTLING STOPS)
♪ ♪
(CHOIR CHANTING OMINOUS MUSIC
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
♪ ♪
("I LIKE THAT"
BY JANELLE MONÁE PLAYING)
♪ ♪
♪ Sometimes a mystery ♪
♪ Sometimes I'm free ♪
♪ Depending on my mood
or my attitude ♪
♪ Sometimes I wanna roll
or stay at home ♪
♪ Walking contradiction,
guess I'm factual and fiction ♪
♪ I'm always left of center ♪
♪ And that's right
where I belong ♪
- ♪ I'm the random... ♪
- (MUSIC STOPS)
We made it!
- Why?! Why?!
- No, Dad!
- 'Cause y'all sleep too much.
- ADDY: All right.
- Come on. Let's go.
- (GABE LAUGHING)
- Careful. Hey, hey, hey!
- (KIDS SHOUTING)
- Ah, whatever.
- Bags in the house first.
Look, look, look, look, look.
- Ew.
- Come on.
You're too old.
- ADDY: You know the drill.
- Don't judge me.
Don't judge me.
- Little dude.
- The Wi-Fi's not working.
You don't need the Internet.
You got the Outernet.
ZORA: Good one.
GABE: Okay, okay, okay.
GABE: Knock-knock.
- JASON: Who's there?
- GABE: You.
ZORA: You who?
GABE: (SINGSONGY) Yoo-hoo.
Open up the door.
(GABE CHUCKLES)
ZORA: My God, what's wrong with you?
- JASON: Can we get a dog?
- ADDY: No, we can't.
GABE: You should run
while you're here.
ADDY: Jason, eat something.
- Something.
- ZORA: What?
- GABE: What's with all the attitude?
- For me.
I'm sorry.
Yay, track and field.
Whoa. You don't want
to run anymore?
GABE: You love track and field.
- Well, what's the point?
- The Olympics.
I'm not gonna make it
to the Olympics, guys.
You could do anything
you set your mind to.
Can I drive
while we're up here?
- No.
Well, that's what
I set my mind to.
- You know...
- Where you going, Jason?
- Jason?
- Well, Cara and Haley...
JASON: Yeah, I'm gonna get something.
You need to come
and finish your food.
Cara and Haley drove
with parent supervision.
GABE: Yeah, well,
you don't need to know
how to drive when you're
an Olympic-caliber athlete.
- Oh, my God.
- You run.
- You run on the sand.
- ZORA: Why?
Because it's harder, okay?
- No traction.
- Mm.
Practice on the beach,
you get on dry land,
- you take off.
- (SNAPS FINGERS)
We're going to the beach?
GABE: Yeah. Well, later.
Once we get settled.
- What beach?
- Santa Cruz.
Josh, Kitty and the girls
are gonna be there.
(SLURPS)
(QUIET CLICKING)
What are you doing?
It's a magic trick.
I left it here last year.
Okay. Let's see it.
(CLICKING CONTINUES)
This thing's kind of bullshit.
Hey. What, are we cursing
at the table now?
When you point a finger
at someone else,
you have three pointing
back at you.
GABE: What is that supposed to mean?
It's four fingers
pointing back at you.
JASON: (MUFFLED) What are you talking...?
ZORA: (MUFFLED) Look. See?
One's a thumb,
and it's not pointing at you.
RAYNE: So, what is it?
(THUNDER RUMBLING SOFTLY)
DR. FOSTER: I think she has
post-traumatic stress disorder.
RUSSEL: She wasn't in 'Nam.
Okay? She got lost.
For 15 minutes. That's...
DR. FOSTER: That can be very scary.
No, you don't know
what happened to her.
Anything could've
happened to her.
Okay, so... so how-how do we
get her to talk?
DR. FOSTER: Look, I think
we need to encourage her
to draw, to write, to dance.
Anything to help her
tell us her story.
(RUSSEL CHUCKLES)
I just want
my little girl back.
It's gonna be okay.
- RAYNE: Um...
- RUSSEL: I'm sorry.
- Is...
- I'm... I'm gonna...
I need to have a smoke.
♪ ♪
GABE: (DISTANTLY) I don't get
why we have a summer home
(NORMAL): by the beach
and don't go to the beach.
What about the beach
right here?
- What beach?
- There's a beach right there.
That is not a beach.
That is a bay.
That is a shore.
I'm talking about a real beach,
with people and sand,
amusement park.
There's, like...
It's crowded there.
- Oh, come...
- And, like, there's weirdos
at that beach and...
I-I'm not going to that beach.
- We're not going.
- Okay.
I guess I'll just cancel, then.
Okay.
It just sucks, is all.
I mean...
I know Jason really was
looking forward to it.
This is the first summer
we've been back here
since Grandma died.
I know it's been
pretty hard on him.
(SIGHS)
We leave before dark.
Yeah.
Yes. Yes.
It's gonna be great.
- And you're gonna enjoy it.
- Mm-hmm.
GABE: (MOCKING) Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Are you really not
gonna kiss me?
Mm-mm.
You're not gonna kiss me?
Hmm? Mm...
(CELL PHONE CHIRPS)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY
OVER EARBUDS)
Where's your brother?
Your brother... where is he?
I don't know.
Really?
Jason?
(KNOB SQUEAKS, WATER RUNNING)
(ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
(WATER RUNNING)
♪ ♪
(JASON YELLS, ZORA SCREAMS)
(JASON PANTING,
FRUSTRATED GROAN)
♪ ♪
(BANGING, JASON SCREAMS)
(BANGING, JASON SHUDDERING)
Baby, that's why
you can't play in here.
- Didn't this happen last year?
- Zora, please.
(HORN HONKING REPEATEDLY
IN DISTANCE)
- (HORN HONKING)
- GABE: Yeah!
That's right.
What do you think?!
Daddy is home, baby!
(HORN HONKS)
Craw Daddy!
(LAUGHS)
- He's kidding, right?
- He is not kidding.
Got a cassette player
and everything.
Leather seats!
Glove compartment!
- Wow.
- That's right.
It's even got
one of these, baby!
(ENGINE SPUTTERS, SHUTS OFF)
Oh, I got it, I got it.
Guy taught me how to do this.
It veers a little to the left,
so you got to hold on to it.
Least I got it really cheap.
- Will we all fit, though?
- GABE: You know what?
Y'all are spoiled.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(CHUCKLING)
(GABE LAUGHS)
GABE: Spoiled.
(JASON'S TOY
CLICKING REPEATEDLY)
Did you know that there's
fluoride in the water
that the government uses
to control our minds?
I forgot. Nobody cares about
the end of the world.
Maybe you could just tell us
what's supposed to happen,
and then we can picture it.
Maybe you can
kiss my anus, Zora.
- Ew!
- Whoa, whoa! - What?
"Anus" isn't a cuss word.
Why are we even talking
about anuses?
- ADDY: Why would you say that?
- GABE: I would have
actually preferred you use
a curse word in this case.
JASON: Mom, I can see you laughing.
- I am not laughing.
- Where'd you even learn that?
Okay, we don't always
have to be talking.
(CLICKING CONTINUES)
(RADIO CLICKS ON,
"I GOT 5 ON IT" PLAYING)
♪ I got more growing pains
than Maggie ♪
♪ 'Cause homeys nag me to take
the dank out of the baggie ♪
- ♪ I got five on it ♪
- ♪ Five on it ♪
- ♪ Got it good ♪
- ♪ Grab your 4-0... ♪
That's a classic right there.
- ♪ I got five on it ♪
- ♪ Five on it ♪
♪ Messin' with that
Indo weed... ♪
What does
"I got five on it" mean?
- It's about drugs.
- It's not about drugs.
It's a dope song.
Don't do drugs.
(CHUCKLING)
- ADDY: Jason, come on.
- Hmm?
Get in rhythm.
(GRUNTS RHYTHMICALLY)
♪ Don't need no crutch,
I'm so keyed up... ♪
There you go. There you go.
♪ Next time I'll roll it
in a Hampa to burn slow ♪
♪ So the ashes won't be
burning up my hand, brah ♪
- (CHUCKLING)
- ♪ Hoochies can hit ♪
♪ But they know
they got to pitch in ♪
♪ Then I roll a joint that's
longer than your extension ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll be damned if
you get high off me for free ♪
♪ Hell no... ♪
GABE: Oh, yeah.
Welcome to Santa Cruz.
♪ 'Cause you know
you got asthma ♪
- ♪ Crack a 40 open, homey, and guzzle it ♪
- Huh?
♪ 'Cause I know the weed in
my system is gettin' lonely ♪
- (CHUCKLES)
- ♪ I gotta take a whiz test to my P.O. ♪
♪ I know I failed 'cause I done
smoked major weed, bro... ♪
- (CHANTING): Santa Cruz!
- (MUSIC FADING)
Santa Cruz!
- Santa Cruz!
- JASON: Okay, we get it!
(LAUGHING): Santa Cruz! Santa Cruz!
(FADING, ECHOING): Santa Cruz!
- RUSSEL: She did...
- RAYNE: Five minutes.
- You can't even talk.
- Look, I don't want to
- talk about who can't talk.
- Russ...
- What's gonna happen?
- If something happened to her...
RUSSEL: What's gonna happen,
okay? She left!
(SIREN WAILING)
ZORA: Oh, my God.
- Don't look. Don't look.
- Is he dead?
You got to be kidding me.
♪ ♪
(DISTORTED SIREN,
RADIO CHATTER)
(CHOIR CHANTING OMINOUS MUSIC
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
♪ ♪
- GABE: Hey.
- Hey! What's up? - Hey.
Thought you guys said 2:30.
Where's the efficiency, man?
- Us Wilsons, you know, we take our time.
- Hey.
- Hey. Look at you.
- Oh, my God, look at you.
- Yes.
- Welcome to paradise.
- Of course, man. - Hey.
- You look so pretty!
- Hi. How are you?
- Thank you.
Oh, the girls are gonna be
so happy to see you.
Uh, what do you want?
I can get some beer for you.
- Becca! Lindsey! Look who's here!
- No.
- No?
- The answer is no.
- Please.
- He's old enough.
- In a couple more years.
- Don't hawk her.
- All right, all right.
- (CHUCKLES): Hi.
- No shit. You got the boat?
- Yep, I got the boat.
- Good for you, dude.
- Boom.
That's fucking awesome.
What'd you get?
- A dinghy? You get, like...
- Oh, shut up.
You got to make sure
you have the essentials.
- You got the life preservers?
- Got that.
- You got a fire extinguisher?
Do you have a flare gun?
(IMITATES BUZZER)
- I knew you'd fucking forget the flare gun.
- (LAUGHS)
JOSH: We got to get out there
and do a double excursion.
We're right across the bay
from you guys, for fuck's sake.
Sure you don't want
anything to drink?
- No, I'm good. Thanks.
- This rosé is delicious.
Mm-hmm. I'm sure, yeah.
Did you guys have
a good summer so far?
Yeah, it's been great.
GABE: No, a little bit small,
but a classic design, you know?
You good?
Yeah.
What?
I have a hard time just...
you know, talking.
Oh, I get that.
Yeah, no, I totally get that.
You guys, uh, want something?
Got a full bar here.
No. All good. Water.
You want thirds, huh?
- Thank you.
- Okay.
I'm gonna get my wife
her medicine.
That's beautiful, isn't it?
JOSH: Here you go.
- Just... - Mm, yeah.
- JOSH: Ah, ah.
What do we say?
I hate you?
- That works.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Good.
- Never stops.
- (CHUCKLES QUIETLY)
I think about
murdering him sometimes.
- So nothing's changed, huh?
- Nope.
Oh, actually,
a little something has changed.
Oh, my God.
Did you get something done?
Just, like, an itsy-bitsy,
little... a little thing.
- (CHUCKLES): Oh, fuck off.
- Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
Well, you look just like
you did last year.
Aw, thank you.
I mean, that's the idea,
you know.
- Just, like, a little bit can go a long way.
- Mm.
Not that you need
anything, whore.
(KITTY CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHTER, PLAYFUL CHATTER)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER EARBUDS)
- JASON: Oh, man.
- LINDSEY: Oops.
BECCA: What was it?
JASON: Just a stupid tunnel.
That's all.
BECCA: Ugh.
Beach toys are such baby shit.
Your brother's so weird.
He just has
a hard time focusing.
Are you going in the water?
- No.
- Why not?
LINDSEY: Yeah, why not?
- Hey, where are you going?
- To the bathroom.
BECCA and LINDSEY: Why don't you pee in the ocean?
Jinx. Double jinx.
Triple jinx. Blackout.
- BECCA: Shut up.
- LINDSEY: You shut up.
Do you ever wish
you kept dancing?
Sometimes, yeah.
'Cause you were, like,
you were really good, right?
Yeah, well...
(CHUCKLES): I peaked at 14.
Oh, I mean, didn't we all?
(BOTH LAUGH)
(RIDE WHIRRING)
(RIDERS SCREAMING PLAYFULLY
IN DISTANCE)
(GULL SQUAWKS)
I think I could have been
a movie star
if the girls hadn't been born
at exactly the wrong time.
- (PLAYFUL SCREAMING NEARBY)
- I went to Stella Adler,
and I booked two commercials
before I met Josh.
- (MAN SHOUTING)
- It's just, I stopped auditioning
when I got pregnant.
Then the move to San Francisco
- was a career killer, and...
- (GULLS SCREECHING)
I was supposed to keep flying
back to L.A.
(VOICE FADES)
- It's just...
- (BOTH GASP)
Jesus. Watch it.
KITTY: Ugh. That's crazy.
Been having so many
crazy coincidences lately.
(DISTANT CHATTER,
PLAYFUL SCREAMING)
(GULL SCREECHING)
(ROLLER COASTER RUMBLING,
RIDERS SCREAMING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
WOMAN: Yeah, that's what he said.
♪ ♪
- Anyways, we should go back to our place.
- Sure.
- I think it's vodka o'clock.
- Oh, yeah. Definitely.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay, good. Let's pack up.
KITTY: Okay.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING PLAYFULLY)
Where's Jason?
KITTY: Mm...
Jason. Where's Jason?
Gabe.
Where's Jason?
Jason?
♪ ♪
- Jason?
- Jason!
- Where were you?
- I was in the bath...
No! You don't do that.
You don't run off
without telling me.
- Ow.
- (PANTING): I'm sorry.
GABE: Okay, okay, okay,
okay, we're good.
- We're good. All right.
- You don't do that to me.
- Understand?
- JASON: Sorry.
GABE: I'm gonna get ready to go.
- Okay?
- I think we're gonna head out.
- JOSH: Yeah.
- GABE: Okay?
- No worries.
- Yeah, we're...
SPORTSCASTER: The Houston
Astros were essentially short
one everyday player
heading into the season.
No incumbent...
You saw their new car, right?
He had to do it.
He just had to get that thing
to fuck with me, too.
I guess mission accomplished.
Don't run inside.
(TOILET FLUSHES, DOOR OPENS)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER EARBUDS)
Way to freak Mom out.
SPORTSCASTER: And here's something you don't
see every day: extra innings in Minnesota.
I'm gonna go say good night.
SPORTSCASTER: 11-11,
tied in the seventh inning.
Yeah, you see, Hollister, known
for his late-inning fastball,
comes in at a cool...
GABE: You good?
I'm just gonna watch
the Giants highlights, okay?
(QUIETLY): I'll see you later
in the magic room.
- Night-night.
- (MUSIC PLAYING OVER EARBUDS)
- Good night.
- Phone off.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(MUSIC RESUMES,
CELL PHONE CLICKING)
Mask off.
You thought I was dead?
Um, no. Uh, I just...
I just didn't know
if you were lost or...
taken or...
By terrorists and perverts?
(ADDY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Stick with me,
and I'll keep you safe, okay?
Look.
ADDY: 11:11.
Bedtime.
♪ ♪
- Who's this?
- (TOY CLICKING)
(GRUNTS "I DON'T KNOW")
GABE: You know, I was thinking about
getting some fishing gear
tomorrow.
Four rods, we can all
go fish off the dock.
You know?
Of course,
there's the boat, too.
I'm just saying, if we could
get out there in open water...
(SPUTTERS LIPS)
I'm not trying to force anyone.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
Gabe, I want to go.
Where you trying to go?
I can't be here. I...
(STAMMERS)
It's too much.
You serious?
Being here, it, um...
Hmm.
(SHUDDERING): It feels like...
there's this, um...
...black cloud
just hanging over me,
and, uh...
I don't feel like myself.
I think you look like yourself.
Okay. Yeah.
(ADDY TAKES A DEEP BREATH)
♪ ♪
When I was a kid,
I went to that boardwalk
with my parents.
I wandered off.
I don't know why. I just did.
I ended up
in that hall of mirrors.
There was another girl
in there.
She looked like me.
Exactly like me.
But you were in
the hall of mirrors...
She wasn't a reflection.
She was real.
(SHUDDERING): She was real.
She...
♪ ♪
I ran as fast as I could.
My whole life, I've...
(CRYING): I've felt like
she's still coming for me.
Okay, well, whatever happened,
happened a-a long time ago,
right?
You know how sometimes
things line up?
- Yeah.
- You know, like coincidences.
Since we've been here,
they've been happening
more and more.
I think...
I feel like it means,
like, she's getting closer.
Who? The mirror girl?
You don't believe me.
I-I... I-I do.
I do.
I'm-I'm processing. Okay?
I just...
can't believe you kept
all this inside for so long.
(SIGHS) Come on.
You know I'm here, right?
I'm pretty sure
I could kick your ass,
so if she looks like you,
then...
(GABE POPS LIPS, CHUCKLES)
Okay. Bad joke.
All right.
I'm sorry. My bad.
I'm just trying
to lighten the mood.
(ADDY YELPS, SHUDDERS)
GABE: Oh, shit.
We lost power.
Perfect timing.
See, this is why Josh has
a backup generator.
(SCOFFS)
- God! Hell!
- (ADDY SCREAMS)
Jesus!
Okay, we lost power.
Go back to bed.
There's a family
in our driveway.
What? There is not a family
♪ ♪
Huh. Who is that?
Uh-uh.
GABE: Oh, it is a family.
What, y'all scared of a family?
A bogeyman's family.
Okay, all right.
Enough... enough of that.
No. Uh-uh.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Uh-uh.
What?
Zora, give me your phone.
- I'm not on it.
- Zora!
Sorry.
- (PHONE CLICKING)
- Is there someone outside?
It's just a family
standing outside.
It's probably the neighbors.
ZORA: You're kidding me, right?
- ADDY: Hello.
- JASON: I'm scared.
My name is Adelaide Wilson.
Are you seriously
calling 911 right now?
We're at 2311 Seagull Way. Shh!
Everything's good.
We lost power.
There are four trespassers
on our property.
- All right, sure, okay.
- Yes.
- You know what?
- What?
- I'm gonna fix this.
- No, we don't.
- I'm gonna find out who they are...
- What?
No, they haven't,
but I know they will.
...find out what they want,
and everything's gonna be fine.
- Gabe.
- Calm down, okay?
15 minutes?
No, no, no, that's too long.
Oh, boy.
No, you don't,
you don't understand. We...
How about we all just try
to keep calm...
- ADDY: Gabe. - ZORA: Dad.
- ...keep our heads,
and everything's gonna
be all right.
ADDY: (SHUDDERING) No, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Just one sec... Gabe.
♪ ♪
(QUIETLY): Trying to have a vacation,
and my whole family lost
they goddamn minds.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Hi.
Can I help you?
Okay.
If y'all are out here
trying to scare people,
I think you picked
the wrong house for that.
Zora...
put your shoes on.
I... I asked you nice.
Now I need y'all
to get off my property.
♪ ♪
(QUIETLY): Okay.
Okay, let's call the cops.
I did.
They're 14 minutes away.
What? 14 minutes?
Okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
- Jason, give me the bat.
- What bat?
The baseball bat. The bat.
- There's one in the cl...
- ZORA: Here, here.
- GABE: Thank you.
- ADDY: Gabe?
All right, hold on.
I got this.
Let's try this again.
- Gabe?
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All right.
- Gabe!
- I got this. I got this.
Now, I thought
I already done told y'all
to get off my property.
Okay? So, if y'all want to
get crazy, we can get crazy.
Now, the cops are
already on they way.
(TAPPING)
Hey. Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
- (LOUD BANG)
- ADDY: Oh!
Sh...
(LOUD BANG)
- They're going around.
- (ADDY WHIMPERS)
- Is the back door locked?
- (LOUD BANG)
- My window's open.
- Gabe... Zora, no!
Gabe, Jason!
(LOUD BANG)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMS)
- (LOUD BANG)
- Yo, I'm serious, man!
I will break your head!
If I were you...
- (SNARLS)
- (ADDY GASPS, GRUNTS)
(LOUD BANG, ALL PANTING)
Gabe.
(SOMEONE WHISTLING
"ITSY BITSY SPIDER")
(WHISTLING CONTINUES)
(HOUSE CREAKS QUIETLY)
(WHISTLING STOPS)
(KEY CLICKING)
- The key.
- (GASPING): What key?
- The damn hide-a-key.
- Hide-a-key?
What kind of white shit...?
(PANTING, WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTS)
Oh, shit.
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(GABE YELLS, FAMILY GASPING)
(GROANS)
- (FAMILY GASPING, WHIMPERING)
- (DOOR CREAKING)
(GABE GRUNTS, PANTS)
(GASPING)
(GABE GROANING)
(GLASS BREAKING,
FAMILY GASPING)
(GLASS CRUNCHING,
GABE GROANING)
- Mom?
- Just stay close.
- What's going on?
- (FOOTSTEPS SCURRYING)
(GASPING, WHIMPERING)
(GABE WHIMPERS, GROANS)
(WHIMPERING, SHUDDERING)
♪ ♪
(WHIMPERING)
(WINDOW SHATTERS,
FAMILY SCREAMS)
(GROWLING)
(CHOIR SINGING OMINOUS MUSIC
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(QUIET GROWLING)
(WHIMPERING, PANTING)
(QUIET GROWLING CONTINUES)
What?
It's us.
(QUIET GROWLING CONTINUES)
(ZORA WHIMPERING)
We don't have anything here.
This is our summer home.
- Gabe.
- We just got in today, so...
(RASPY): Once... (SWALLOWS)
upon...
...a t-ime...
...there was a girl.
And the girl had...
a sh-adow.
The two were connected,
tethered together.
When the girl ate,
her food was given to her
warm and tasty.
But when the shadow was hungry,
she had to eat rabbit,
raw and bloody.
On Christmas,
the girl received
wonderful toys,
soft and cushy.
But the shadow's toys
were so sharp and cold,
they'd slice
through her fingers
when she tried
to play with them.
The girl met a handsome prince
and fell in love,
but the shadow,
at that same time,
met Abraham.
It didn't matter
if she loved him or not.
He was tethered to
the girl's prince, after all.
Then the girl had
her first child,
a beautiful baby girl.
But the shadow,
she gave birth
to a little monster.
Umbrae was born laughing.
The girl had a second child,
a boy this time.
They had to cut her open
and take him from her belly.
The shadow had to do it all...
herself.
She named him Pluto.
- (GROWLING QUIETLY)
- He was born to love fire.
So, you see,
the shadow hated the girl
so much for so long,
until one day
the shadow realized
she was being tested by God.
(QUIETLY): Excuse me.
Excuse me.
What do you want?
You could have my wallet.
You-you could have the car.
Gabe.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY): Yeah.
You can have the boat,
for all I care.
(CRYING): Nobody wants the boat, Dad.
How about this?
You take me to the ATM...
(YELLS)
What are you people?
We're Americans.
(RED PANTS, PLUTO SNARLS)
Tether yourself to the table.
(PLUTO GROWLS)
Addy, don't do it.
Maybe I should cut...
something off of you.
- It's... it's okay.
- (ZORA WHIMPERS)
(PLUTO GROWLING)
Just...
Don't hurt my children.
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
Yo.
♪ ♪
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Get your hands off me.
- ADDY: No. Gabe, no.
- ZORA: No, wait, no. Dad!
- (GABE YELLS)
- Wait. Wait.
Get off me, man.
(SCREAMS)
- (SNARLING) - (GABE SCREAMING)
- ADDY: Look, Gabe...
ADDY: Wait. Gabe.
GABE: Oh, please,
please, please stop!
- Stop, please!
- Gabe.
(GABE SCREAMING)
Stop, stop. Wait. Wait.
- Wai... (SCREAMS) Please!
- (GLASS CRUNCHING)
(PANTING)
- Okay. Okay.
- (GABE SCREAMING, GROANING)
(GASPS)
(ZORA WHIMPERING)
- (GABE GROANING IN DISTANCE)
- (ZORA GASPING, WHIMPERING)
- Mom.
- Little girl.
Run!
- Go.
- (GASPING, WHIMPERING)
(MAKES CLICKING SOUND)
(GABE GROANS IN DISTANCE)
(PANTING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
♪ ♪
(GABE GROANS IN DISTANCE)
(JOINTS CRACKING)
(GROANING)
(GABE GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
You want me, right?
(GABE YELLING IN DISTANCE)
(RED PANTS, PLUTO GROWLS)
ADDY: No.
- He's not going.
- RED: Careful.
He has a t-emper.
(GROWLS)
(GABE GROANING IN DISTANCE)
(GROANS, COUGHS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GABE GROANS)
- (ABRAHAM GROANING)
- No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, not that shit.
No. No.
- (GABE YELLS IN DISTANCE)
- Okay.
- I'm scared.
- (WHISPERING): Look...
- (GABE YELLS IN DISTANCE)
- Look at me.
- You're gonna be okay.
- (WHIMPERS)
Show him one of your tricks.
Okay.
(GABE GROANS IN DISTANCE)
RED: Go play, boys.
(PLUTO GROWLING, JASON GASPS)
Don't burn our house down.
(GIGGLING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(CREAKING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(CRYING): Stop, man.
Please stop.
GABE: (IN DISTANCE) No, no, stop, stop, stop.
- (SNIFFLES)
- GABE (IN DISTANCE): Please.
Come on, man, stop.
Stop it.
(YELLS)
I got a family, man.
Please don't. No.
(ABRAHAM YELLS, GABE GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(GROWLING QUIETLY)
(PLUTO GROWLING)
(JASON GASPING RAPIDLY)
(GASPING)
(PANTING, WHIMPERING)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(SNIFFLES)
(PANTING)
♪ ♪
(SHUDDERS, WHIMPERS)
(CAR CREAKING SOFTLY)
(GASPS)
(ZORA GASPING)
MAN: What the fuck?
Get off my car!
Are you...?
Come here. Come...
Goddamn it,
get your ass over here.
I said, "Come here."
Kid, I'm talking to you.
(SCISSORS STAB, MAN SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
What do you want?
(GASPS, SHUDDERS)
What?
What do we want?
We want...
to take our t-ime.
We've been waiting for this day
for so long.
I call it...
- (GLASS CREAKING)
- "The Untethering."
(BOAT ENGINE BUZZING)
(ENGINE SPUTTERS, SHUTS OFF)
(GABE PANTING)
(BOAT CREAKING)
(BANGING)
(DISTANT SHRIEKING)
(ABRAHAM BELLOWS)
(ABRAHAM YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS, EXHALES)
(ABRAHAM GASPING)
(PANTING)
(JASON SHUDDERING)
♪ ♪
(WHIMPERING)
(JASON GASPING)
(PLUTO GROWLS)
(BANGING ON DOOR,
PLUTO SNARLING)
(PANTING)
(BANGING, PLUTO WAILING
IN DISTANCE)
That's yours.
(GLASS CREAKING, CRACKLING)
(RED GROWLS, ADDY GASPING)
(BANGING AND WAILING CONTINUE
IN DISTANCE)
♪ ♪
(PLUTO WAILING)
(PANTING, GROWLING QUIETLY)
(DOOR CREAKS)
- (GRUNTS, PANTS)
- (SHACKLES CLINKING)
(FIRE WHOOSHING SOFTLY)
♪ ♪
(PANTING)
(BOAT ENGINE BUZZING
IN DISTANCE)
It hangs to the left.
It hangs to the goddamn left.
♪ ♪
(PANTING, SHACKLES CLANK)
(WOOD CREAKING, ADDY GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(ENGINE SPUTTERS, SHUTS OFF)
(GRUNTING)
(ABRAHAM YELLS)
(GABE GROANS)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(ENGINE STARTS,
ABRAHAM GROANS)
(WATER GURGLING)
♪ ♪
(EXHALES)
(QUIETLY): Jason.
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
- Jason.
- (FOOTSTEPS SCURRYING)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
Baby.
Come on. Come on.
(PLUTO ROARS, ADDY GRUNTING)
Let's go.
(BOTH PANTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Keys.
(SNARLING)
- Mom! Mom!
- Zora!
(PLUTO SNARLING, BANGING)
- (HORN HONKING IN DISTANCE)
- This way. Come on!
Come on, come on!
Go, go, go!
Hey!
(HORN HONKING)
(SNARLING)
(GABE GRUNTS)
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
(GROWLS, SHRIEKS)
Oh. Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go!
(PANTING)
(CHOIR CHANTING OMINOUS MUSIC
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(JASON PANTING)
(PANTING)
(SNORING SOFTLY)
(ELECTRICAL HUMMING)
(GASPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(COUGHS)
- Josh? What was that?
- What?
I heard something outside.
Okay.
A rustling.
Walking, like a person.
There's a person walking around
outside our fucking house.
It's probably a squirrel.
I don't know.
Would you please get up
and look?
I'm busy.
I'm... I'm busy.
So...
Maybe it's a-a pizza guy.
Maybe the girls ordered pizza.
Get up and take a look.
I'm scared.
Oh, I don't want to.
I want to stay down here.
I want to just stay
in my cozy spot.
- Get up and look.
- Jesus Christ.
Hey, uh, Ophelia, lights up.
OPHELIA: (AUTOMATED VOICE) Turning lights up.
KITTY: I feel like I heard the
backup generator go on, too.
JOSH: What do you know
about the backup generator?
KITTY: Can you stop being
an asshole for two seconds?
- Just look.
- All right. I'm looking.
I'll get my binoculars.
I see nothing.
I see beautiful stars.
Are you really looking?
Yeah, I'm looking.
Oh, shit.
No, yeah, I...
- There's something out there.
- Don't fuck with me, Josh.
I'm not fucking with you.
I'm serious.
There's something out there.
Look.
Look behind the car.
- Where? I don't see it.
- It's by the car.
- Look.
- I can't...
- Oh, shit.
- What?
(GASPS)
Oh, my God, it's O.J.
It's O.J. Simpson.
(LAUGHING)
What is wrong with you?
Seriously.
(SNICKERS, SIGHS)
Ophelia,
give me some Beach Boys.
OPHELIA: Playing "Good Vibrations"
- by the Beach Boys.
- Really? - Why not?
- It's our last night here.
- ("GOOD VIBRATIONS" PLAYING)
- Let's have a little party.
- Ophelia, turn it down.
OPHELIA: Turning down "Good
Vibrations" by the Beach Boys.
Would you chill out, all right?
There's nobody out there.
Just go back upstairs.
I'll be up in a few minutes.
Everything's gonna be fine.
- LINDSEY: What's going on?
- (KITTY SCOFFS)
JOSH: Uh, nothing.
- Nothing, guys.
- KITTY: Jesus.
The backup generator went on.
We're just trying
to figure it out.
- Go back to sleep.
- Just because we're in our rooms
doesn't mean we're sleeping.
Fine. I don't know.
Go back to your rooms.
Guys, we have to be out of here
at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow,
sharp, so...
♪ I'm picking up
good vibrations... ♪
- JOSH: Hello?
- Oh, my God.
(LINDSEY SCREAMING)
- (JOSH SCREAMS)
- KITTY: Josh!
(ALL SCREAMING, GRUNTING)
♪ Good, good, good,
good vibrations ♪
♪ She's giving me excitations ♪
- ♪ Excitations ♪
- ♪ Good, good, good ♪
♪ Good vibrations ♪
♪ She's giving me excitations ♪
- ♪ Excitations ♪
- ♪ Close my eyes ♪
- (KITTY GASPING, GURGLING)
- ♪ She's somehow closer now ♪
♪ Softly smile,
I know she must be kind ♪
(KITTY CONTINUES GURGLING)
♪ When I look in her eyes ♪
♪ She goes with me
to a blossom world ♪
♪ I'm picking up
good vibrations ♪
♪ She's giving me excitations ♪
♪ I'm picking up
good vibrations ♪
♪ Good vibrations ♪
♪ She's giving me excitations ♪
- ♪ Excitations ♪
- ♪ Good, good, good ♪
♪ Good vibrations ♪
♪ She's giving me excitations ♪
- ♪ Excitations ♪
- ♪ Good, good, good ♪
♪ Good vibrations ♪
♪ She's giving me excitations ♪
♪ Excitations... ♪
- Please stop.
- (ELECTRONIC CHIMING)
OPHELIA: Stopping "Good
Vibrations" by the Beach Boys.
(GASPING)
- Ophelia...
- (BEEPING)
Ophelia, call the police.
- (ELECTRONIC CHIMING)
- OPHELIA: Sure.
Playing "Fuck tha Police"
by N.W.A.
♪ Fuck the police, coming
straight from the underground ♪
- (SLASHING)
- ♪ A young nigga got it bad 'cause I'm brown ♪
- ♪ And not the other color, so police think ♪
- (KNOCKING)
♪ They have the authority
to kill a minority ♪
♪ Fuck that shit,
'cause I ain't the one ♪
♪ For a punk motherfucker... ♪
- Josh, we need your help.
- ♪ And thrown in jail ♪
♪ We can go toe-to-toe
in the middle of a cell ♪
♪ Fuckin' with me
'cause I'm a teenager ♪
♪ With a little bit
of gold... ♪
- Addy!
- (ADDY GASPS)
♪ Thinkin' every nigga
is selling narcotics... ♪
- (SCREAMING)
- Addy!
ADDY: (SCREAMS) No!
(SOBBING): No! No! No! No!
(GRUNTS)
- Go, go, go, go, go, go. Run.
- (ZORA AND JASON WHIMPERING)
(RASPY GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Come here!
- Huh? Follow me!
- (SHRIEKING)
Yeah.
(SHRIEKING IN DISTANCE)
GABE: (IN DISTANCE) Let's go, Bad Josh!
- (SHRIEKING)
- Let's go!
(BOTH PANTING)
Hey!
♪ It's gonna be a bloodbath ♪
♪ Of cops dying in L.A. ♪
♪ Yo, Dre,
I got somethin' to say ♪
♪ Fuck the police ♪
♪ Fuck, fuck, fuck the police ♪
♪ Fuck, fuck,
fuck the police ♪
♪ Fuck, fuck, fuck the police ♪
♪ Example of scene one ♪
♪ Pull your goddamn ass over
right now ♪
♪ Aw, shit, now what the fuck
you pulling me over for? ♪
♪ 'Cause I feel like it ♪
♪ Just sit your ass on the curb
and shut the fuck up ♪
- ♪ Man, fuck this shit ♪
- ♪ A'ight, smart-ass ♪
♪ I'm taking your black ass
to jail ♪
♪ MC Ren, will you please give
your testimony to the jury ♪
♪ About this
fucked-up incident... ♪
- ADDY: (IN DISTANCE) No! No! No!
- (CLATTERING)
♪ Because the niggas
on the street is a majority ♪
♪ A gang is with
whoever I'm steppin' ♪
♪ And the motherfuckin' weapon
is kept in a stash spot ♪
♪ For the so-called law ♪
♪ Wishing Ren was a nigga
that they never saw ♪
♪ Lights start flashing
behind me ♪
♪ But they're scared
of a nigga ♪
♪ So they mace me to blind me ♪
♪ But that shit don't work,
I just laugh ♪
♪ Because it gives them a hint
not to step in my path ♪
♪ For police, I'm saying,
"Fuck you, punk" ♪
- (GRUNTS "I DON'T KNOW")
- ♪ Read my rights and shit ♪
♪ It's all junk ♪
♪ Pulling out a silly club,
so you stand ♪
♪ With a fake-ass badge
and a gun in your hand ♪
♪ But take off the gun
so you can see what's up ♪
♪ And we'll go at it, punk,
and I'm-a fuck you up ♪
♪ Make you think
I'm-a kick your ass ♪
♪ But drop your gat
and Ren's gonna blast ♪
♪ I'm sneaky as fuck
when it comes to crime ♪
♪ But I'm-a smoke them now
and not next time ♪
♪ Smoke any motherfucker
that sweats me ♪
♪ Or any asshole
that threatens me ♪
♪ I'm a sniper
with a hell of a scope ♪
- (ADDY GROANING)
- ♪ Taking out a cop or two ♪
♪ They can't cope with me ♪
♪ The motherfuckin' villain
that's mad ♪
♪ With potential
to get bad as fuck ♪
♪ So I'm-a turn it around,
put in my clip ♪
- ♪ Yo, and this is the sound ♪
- (GUNSHOT SOUND EFFECTS)
♪ Yeah, somethin' like that,
but it all depends... ♪
(SHRIEKS, GRUNTS)
(CRASHING, GLASS CLINKING)
♪ Fuck the police ♪
♪ Fuck, fuck, fuck the police ♪
♪ Fuck, fuck,
fuck the police ♪
♪ Fuck, fuck, fuck the police ♪
- (KNOCKING SOUND EFFECT)
- ♪ Yeah, man, what you need? ♪
- ♪ Police, open up ♪
- ♪ Aw, shit ♪
♪ We have a warrant
for Eazy-E's arrest ♪
♪ Get down and put your hands
where I can see 'em... ♪
(JASON GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SHRIEKING)
(CHOKING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (THUMPING, SPLATTERING)
(PAINED SHRIEKING)
(SHRIEKING STOPS)
(PANTING)
♪ ♪
(CLUNKING, SHACKLES CLINKING)
(BAD JOSH YELLING)
(GABE PANTING, GROANING)
Come on!
(GASPS)
Goddamn it.
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
♪ ♪
(HEAVY THUD, BOAT CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(SHRIEKS)
(HISSES)
(GABE PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(CLATTERING, GRUNTING)
(GABE AND BAD JOSH YELLING,
GRUNTING IN DISTANCE)
(PANTING QUIETLY)
♪ ♪
(LAUGHING)
ADDY: No, no, no, no. Please.
No, no. No.
No! No, no.
No, Zora. No!
- Please, please.
- (ZORA GASPING)
No! No!
No, please, no!
- (ZORA GASPING)
- No, no, no.
(HEAVY THUMP,
ADDY AND ZORA GASPING)
(PANTING)
("I GOT 5 ON IT" BY LUNIZ
PLAYING)
(GABE GROANING)
♪ Creep on it,
on it, on it, on it ♪
(KNOCK ON GLASS)
♪ Whoa, see,
I'm ridin' high, high ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Kinda broke this evening,
y'all... ♪
(SIGHS)
It was unlocked.
(GROANS)
Boats are done.
I am done with boats.
♪ Light another joint
like Cypress Hill ♪
♪ I steal doobies,
spit loogies ♪
♪ When I puff on it,
I got some bucks on it ♪
♪ But it ain't enough on it ♪
♪ Go get the S-the-T-I-D-E-S ♪
♪ Nevertheless,
I'm hella fresh... ♪
I can't believe they're dead.
(LINE RINGING)
JASON: Why are they doing this?
WOMAN: (OVER PHONE) I'm sorry,
but all of our operators
are busy at the moment.
Please hold, and the next
available operator will...
It's all just craziness.
(OVER PHONE): I'm sorry,
but all of our operators
are busy at the moment.
Please...
How does 911 keep you on hold
all night long?
I just don't get it.
It's too many twins, man.
♪ You hella dumb-da-dumb-dumb ♪
♪ I come to school
with the Taylor on my earlobe ♪
♪ Avoiding all the
thick teasers, skeezers... ♪
How many of everybody
is there gonna be?
♪ Where the bomb at?
Give me two bucks ♪
♪ You take a puff
and pass my bomb back ♪
♪ Suck up that dank
like a Slurpee ♪
♪ The serious bomb
will make a niggy ♪
♪ Go delirious
like Eddie Murphy ♪
♪ I got more growing pains
than Maggie... ♪
WOMAN: (ON TV) The boardwalk
was getting ready to close,
and a bunch of us
had just gotten out,
and we were going to our cars
when the attack happened.
- Oh, shit.
- People were shouting, and...
- JASON: Don't curse.
- ...I-I just thought it was
somebody acting out,
and then we just saw red.
- REPORTER: Uh, you saw red?
- Yes, they were wearing red.
They didn't look right.
They had scissors,
and they were just walking up
to people in the crowd
(CRYING): and stabbing them.
REPORTER: You said
they were stabbing people?
WOMAN: Yeah, it was chaos,
and then we-we just
started running.
REPORTER: Where-where did they come from?
WOMAN: What? I-I-I don't know.
Someone said that they were
coming from the sewers.
REPORTER: The sewers?
Okay, how many are...
WOMAN: (WHISPERING) I'm sorry.
I think they're coming.
REPORTER: Uh, uh, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Um, okay, uh, so we certainly
hope everything is okay there.
It's too early to say
what exactly is unfolding,
but it does appear
we are in the midst
of a brutal
and terrifying attack
by people who are being
described as wearing red,
carrying scissors or shears,
and doing
what can only be described
as wreaking havoc on folks
- just out for a Friday night.
- GABE: And they look like us.
They don't even know that yet.
ANCHOR: Okay, Chris,
I'm gonna cut you off.
- Okay.
- We have new images coming in here.
Here, we see a man
- wearing red who...
- (DISTANT SIREN WAILING ON TV)
Okay, this...
this seems to be
a group of individuals
engaged in some sort
of demonstration or protest.
It-it's not clear at this time
if or how
these people are connected
to the attacks.
- ZORA: What is that?
- They are forming what looks
- like a human chain.
- GABE: That's them.
What are they doing?
GABE: I don't know,
but that would take
a shitload of coordination.
ANCHOR: So, obviously,
if you have children present
watching us right now,
you should turn them away.
We aren't sure
what is about to happen.
(SLASHING, MAN SCREAMS)
- We have to go.
- What? You're joking, right?
ADDY: Zora, Jason, help your father.
GABE: Wait, she's trippin'.
Where would we go?
- The police, right?
- ADDY: No.
We need to move
and keep moving.
We take the coast.
- We go to Mexico.
- Mexico?
(CHUCKLES): Okay. Whoa.
Whoa. Whoa!
We got everything we need here.
Food, water, backup generator.
We're as safe here
as we're gonna be anywhere.
Tell that to Josh and Kitty.
They're right here.
- You're scaring the kids.
- ZORA and JASON: Too late.
They think like us.
They know where we are.
They won't stop until
they kill us or we kill them.
Then let's make
some traps or something.
Like, some Home Alone
type stuff.
That way, if she comes...
Tell me you did not
just reference Home Alone.
- You know what I'm talking about.
- Gabe.
They've been planning this.
They have the upper hand.
This is the time to run,
not to be sprinkling
Micro Machines on the floor.
What are Micro Machines?
What's Home Alone?
We're not going anywhere,
and that's final.
You don't get to make
the decisions anymore!
So...
does this mean
we get their car?
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
(SIGHS)
Who's got the keys?
♪ ♪
(PANTING)
(QUIET CREAK)
(BAD LINDSEY SHRIEKS,
ADDY GRUNTS)
(SHRIEKS, HISSES)
(SHRIEKING)
(SHRIEKING LAUGHTER)
(SHRIEKING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
(BAD LINDSEY SHRIEKING,
GASPING)
(SHRIEKING STOPS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUFF PANTING)
(LOCK BEEPS)
(PANTING): Come on.
- JASON: Let's go.
- Get in the car.
Get in the car.
(DOORS CLOSE)
- I'm driving. - No way.
- (LOCK BEEPS)
- I told her no.
- (LOCK CLICKS)
Dad's leg is messed up.
You're handcuffed.
It's not safe.
I'm driving.
- Zora, no.
- (LOCK BEEPING, CLICKING)
I have the highest kill count
in the family.
You don't have
the highest kill count.
I killed both twins.
Wrong.
I just killed the second one.
I killed Kitty.
So that's one, one,
one and two. I killed two.
- I killed myself and Josh, so...
- (LOCK BEEPS)
- (LOCK CLICKS)
- Zo... It doesn't matter.
- Zora, get in the back.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- JASON: Look! - No.
- Oh, shit, put the windows up.
Put the windows up.
(GASPS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PANTING)
GABE: (SIGHS) Okay.
You're gonna want to...
back up.
- Buckle up.
- Huh?
(ADDY GRUNTS)
- ADDY: Zora!
- Whoa...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- (THUMPING)
Where is she? Did I get her?
(PANTING)
(ZORA GASPING)
(UMBRAE SCREAMING,
FAMILY YELLING)
She's there, she's there!
Jesus!
(TIRES SCREECH)
(ADDY AND ZORA PANTING,
WHIMPERING)
GABE: Okay.
(ADDY AND ZORA PANTING)
(GABE SHUSHING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(ZORA GASPS)
- Zora.
- (GABE STAMMERING)
GABE: Be careful.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Okay, you're going too fast!
(TIRES SCREECH)
(ADDY GASPS)
(GABE GRUNTING)
ZORA: She's dead now, right?
(WINDSHIELD WIPERS STOP)
- What are you doing?
- Mom.
GABE: Where's she going?
Wait... And she left.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- Your mom left the car.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(OWL HOOTING)
(ADDY SCREAMS,
UMBRAE CHUCKLING)
(UMBRAE GASPING)
(UMBRAE GRUNTS, ADDY GASPS)
(CHUCKLING)
Shh, shh.
(UMBRAE GRUNTS, CHUCKLES)
(PANTING WEAKLY)
Shh.
(UMBRAE TAKING LABORED BREATHS)
(UMBRAE GROANING WEAKLY)
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
(BREATHING STOPS)
♪ ♪
GABE: Whoa.
ZORA: Is that our car?
It's the one
that looks like me.
(THUMPING)
Shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What, what?
(SNAPPING FINGERS)
Stay in the car.
Lock the doors.
(GULLS SCREECHING)
(PLUTO CONTINUES
SNAPPING FINGERS)
♪ ♪
(FIRE IRON CLANKS ON PAVEMENT)
GABE: What is she doing?
(PLUTO CONTINUES
SNAPPING FINGERS)
It's a trap.
Get out.
(SNAPPING ECHOES)
(CHOIR SINGING OMINOUS MUSIC
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Please.
No.
♪ ♪
GABE: Jason. Jason!
ADDY: Jason?
GABE: Jason!
ADDY: Jason!
No! No!
- GABE: Addy!
- ZORA: Mom!
(GULLS SCREECHING)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
(WAVES SLOSHING)
(GULLS SCREECHING)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(GASPS)
♪ ♪
(CHIRPING BIRD SOUND EFFECTS
PLAY OVER SPEAKERS)
(GASPS QUIETLY)
(OWL HOOTING, ADDY GRUNTS)
(DISTORTED HOOT,
MECHANICAL HISSING)
(CHIRPING BIRD SOUND EFFECTS
CONTINUE)
♪ ♪
(PANTING QUIETLY,
RAIN PATTERING)
(WOOD CREAKING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(GASPS QUIETLY)
(STEAM HISSING)
♪ ♪
(METALLIC CLANKING)
(PANTING QUIETLY)
(GASPS)
(WHIRRING IN DISTANCE)
♪ ♪
(GASPS)
(MECHANICAL WHIRRING
AND CLANKING)
♪ ♪
(PANTING)
(EERIE HIGH-PITCHED VOICES
VOCALIZING AND ECHOING)
♪ ♪
GABE: Here.
- We can hide here.
- Okay.
- They probably got bandages and stuff.
(GABE PANTING)
Mom knows what to do.
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
Look.
It's the line.
Looks like some kind
of fucked-up performance art.
(SCISSORS CUTTING NEARBY)
♪ ♪
(SCISSORS CUTTING)
Where is he?
(SCISSORS CONTINUE CUTTING)
RED: How it must have been
to grow up with the sky.
To feel the sun,
the wind, the trees.
But your people
took it for granted.
- We're human, too, you know.
- (SCISSORS CONTINUE CUTTING)
Eyes, teeth,
hands, blood.
Exactly like you.
(SCISSORS CONTINUE CUTTING)
And yet... (CHUCKLES)
it was humans
that built this place.
I believe they figured out
how to make a copy of the body
but not the soul.
The soul remains one,
shared by two.
They created the T-ethered
so they could use them
to control the ones above.
Like puppets.
But they failed, and they
ab-andoned the Tethered.
For generations, the Tethered
continued without direction.
(SCISSORS CONTINUE CUTTING)
They all went mad down here.
And then... there was us.
(RUSSEL GRUNTS,
BOTTLES CLATTERING)
Put some heat on that one.
RUSSEL: Yeah, I guess
I missed my chance to go pro.
RED: You remember?
We were born special.
- I want number 11.
- Yeah?
♪ ♪
(CHUCKLES)
(DISTANT, PLAYFUL SCREAMING)
(RIDERS SCREAMING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHATTERING, SCREAMING)
(RIDERS SCREAMING)
(BELL RINGING)
Addy, you want to try it?
(CHUCKLES)
(OTHERS SHRIEKING, CHATTERING)
(LIQUID POURING)
(CAN CLANKING)
(SHRIEKING)
(SHRIEKING CONTINUES)
(BELL DINGING)
God brought us tog-ether
that night.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
♪ ♪
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
I never st-op thinking
about you.
How things could have been.
How you could have
taken me with you.
(CHUCKLES)
(SCISSORS CUTTING)
Years after we met...
(TCHAIKOVSKY'S "THE NUTCRACKER
SUITE: XI. PAS DE DEUX" PLAYS)
- (APPLAUSE)
- RED: ...the miracle happened.
That's when I saw God,
and he showed me my path.
You felt it, too.
♪ ♪
The end of our dance,
the Tethered saw
that I was different.
That I would deliver them
from this misery.
- I found my faith,
- (SCISSORS CONTINUE CUTTING)
and I began to prepare.
It took years to plan.
♪ ♪
Everything had to be perfect.
I didn't just need to kill you.
I needed to m-ake a statement
that the whole world would see.
(CUTTING STOPS)
It's our time now.
Our t-ime up there.
(SCISSORS CUTTING)
And to think,
if it weren't for you...
...I never would have
danced at all.
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING CLASSICAL
VERSION OF "I GOT 5 ON IT")
♪ ♪
(ADDY GASPING)
(YELLS IN PAIN)
(GRUNTS, SHUDDERS)
(WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
(ADDY GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(ADDY YELLS, GRUNTS)
(ADDY GRUNTS)
(ADDY GROANING)
♪ ♪
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS, PANTS)
♪ ♪
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS, YELLS IN PAIN)
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
♪ ♪
(FIRE IRON CLATTERS)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
♪ ♪
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(ADDY YELLS, SQUISHING THUD)
(SCISSORS CLATTER ON FLOOR,
ADDY PANTING)
(ADDY GRUNTING)
(RED GURGLES, CHOKES)
(ADDY PANTING)
(GURGLING, CHOKING)
(PANTING)
(WHISTLING WEAKLY)
(WHISTLING STOPS)
(RED CHOKING)
(NECK SNAPS, CHOKING STOPS)
(YELLS, SOBS)
(GASPING, TEETH CLICKING)
(GRUNTING, PANTING)
(CHUCKLING)
♪ ♪
(SHACKLES CLICKING)
(THUMP IN DISTANCE)
(WHIMPERS, GRUNTS)
(PANTING GRUFFLY)
(ADDY GASPS, JASON WHIMPERS)
My baby. My baby.
I found you.
Oh!
Look.
Look, look, look.
(CRYING SOFTLY)
(WHISPERS): They're all gone now.
Okay?
They can't hurt you.
You understand?
Uh-uh.
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(WHISPERS): No.
Everything's gonna be
like it was before.
(SHUDDERS): Yeah.
♪ ♪
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
RUSSEL: She wasn't in 'Nam.
Okay? She got lost.
For 15 minutes. That's...
DR. FOSTER: That can be very scary.
RAYNE: No, you don't know
what happened to her.
- Anything could've happened to her.
- RUSSEL: Okay, okay.
So how-how...
how do we get her to talk?
DR. FOSTER: Encourage her to draw,
to write, to dance.
Anything to help her
tell us her story.
(RUSSEL CHUCKLES)
(CRYING): I just want
my little girl back.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
(CHOIR SINGING OMINOUS MUSIC
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
♪ ♪
(SHUDDERING)
RUSSEL: Okay? She left.
- She...
- RAYNE: I told you to look after her.
- RUSSEL: Yeah. Yeah.
- RAYNE: Look at you.
- It's not my fault she left.
- Look at you.
RUSSEL: It's not my fault
she... Yeah, well, look at me.
Look at you. Look at you!
♪ ♪
("LES FLEURS"
BY MINNIE RIPERTON PLAYING)
♪ Will somebody wear me
to the fair? ♪
♪ To the morning
sings a lonely flower ♪
♪ Will a lady pin me
in her hair? ♪
♪ Mm-hmm, hmm ♪
♪ Will a child find me
by a stream? ♪
- ♪ Daylight will give a sunbeam shower ♪
- ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Kiss my petals ♪
♪ Weave me through a dream ♪
♪ For all of these
simple things and much more ♪
♪ A flower was born ♪
♪ It blooms to spread
love and joy, faith and hope ♪
♪ To people forlorn ♪
♪ Inside every man ♪
♪ Lives the seed of a flower ♪
♪ If he looks within ♪
♪ He finds beauty and power ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Ring all the bells, sing
and tell the people everywhere ♪
♪ That the flower has come ♪
♪ Light up the sky
with your prayers of gladness ♪
♪ And rejoice
for the darkness is gone ♪
♪ Throw off your fears,
let your heart beat freely ♪
♪ At the sign
that a new time is born ♪
♪ ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
(SINGING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
♪ Mm-hmm, hmm ♪
(SINGING CONTINUES
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
♪ Mm-hmm, hmm ♪
♪ For all of these
simple things and much more ♪
♪ A flower was born ♪
♪ It blooms to spread
love and joy, faith and hope ♪
♪ To people forlorn ♪
♪ Inside every man ♪
♪ Lives the seed of a flower ♪
♪ If he looks within ♪
♪ He finds beauty and power ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Ring all the bells, sing and
tell the people everywhere ♪
♪ That the flower has come ♪
♪ Light up the sky with
your prayers of gladness ♪
♪ And rejoice
for the darkness is gone ♪
♪ Throw off your fears,
let your heart beat freely ♪
♪ At the sign
that a new time is born. ♪
(SONG FADES)
♪ ♪
(MUSIC ENDS)
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44