Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
If this movie was aired in our universe,
it would make millions by now.
If it wasn’t for you, this movie wouldn’t have happened.
It’s life to meet and part.
I’m so proud to work with you guys.
What are you gonna do now?
I’m moving back home.
If I stop writing screenplays, I won’t be able to cover the rent.
Talay,
would you like to move in with me?
Your clothes are colorful.
They’re making my room a lot livelier.
Wait.
Not my room anymore.
Our room.
What are you saying?
I’m getting goosebumps.
You said you would watch a movie.
I am.
I prepared popped rice for you already.
Tun!
Why don’t you eat it normally?
I don’t want my hands messy.
Can I borrow yours?
My hands are clean.
I won’t be the only one with sticky hands.
What?
We should stop eating popped rice.
Better eat something else.
We should stop watching the movie.
Let’s get ready for bed.
Here.
Do you know who puts toothpaste on each other’s toothbrushes?
Who?
Come on. Think.
Anyone.
Who is the last person we see before bed
and the first person we see after waking up?
Can’t be anyone else.
Tun, what are you saying?
Just brush your teeth.
Tun!
Enough.
That latter part doesn’t sound right.
Do you want me to live with you or do you want something 18+?
Come on.
Anything can happen.
No.
Us living together will result in fighting all the time.
Tun.
About the rental,
I can help you pay.
No.
I’d feel bad if you just pay and don’t live there with me.
Besides,
the reason I want you to move in with me
is that I’m feeling a bit lost as I won’t get to spend time with you anymore.
Seeing you 24/7 is heartwarming.
You should spend time with someone else too.
You might find your portkey.
Don’t you want to go back?
I still can’t find my portkey.
Damn it! I just want to drink so bad.
There, there. Let me give you a warm hug.
Spend the night with me. I’ll give you free fried chicken.
That’s enough. Come here.
Do not take advantage of him.
Come here.
Here.
Why stopping me?
Sit tight.
I’m pretty lonely these days.
Tun has been gone. He doesn’t come at all.
Where is Tun, Talay?
No idea.
Since we disbanded, I haven’t seen him.
He doesn’t pick up my calls.
I haven’t seen him for a week.
My heart is shattered.
Too much. It’s just a week.
Not just a week.
It’s 168 hours or 10,080 minutes or…
Enough.
Do you miss him that much?
You don’t get it.
When we miss someone, a minute feels like a year.
Right, Talay?
- Me?
- Yes.
You two always stick together.
If one is missing, the other one can’t help but feel a bit empty.
Can you sing for me?
I want to hear music from our universe.
Sing it yourself.
I want to hear a song you sing.
I’m playing games.
Please, Talay.
It can be your favorite song.
The one by Paradox.
‘Love.’
No ‘Love’ now.
Let me play this game first.
You’re mean.
Yeah! The exams are all over.
Right.
Studying for the exams was exhausting.
My agony is finally over.
Are you sure?
You can’t graduate yet, Tess.
Why can’t I?
I have lots of accumulated scores.
I won’t get an F.
Not this term’s courses.
Did you forget you’re missing one more course?
Right.
You said you didn’t want to study too much.
So you didn’t enroll in the last English course.
You have to study alone now.
How lonely!
Right.
How lonely.
Why do people around me keep on missing?
So dramatic.
Let’s leave.
Let him play his music video.
Ahem.
Tun?
We see you’re lonely so we’re keeping you company.
We’ve got some beers.
Come one.
Let’s drink and watch a movie.
It’s a long night tonight.
Let’s watch the one you made.
It just hit the streaming app.
Sure.
I designed the ending scene already.
After the lead characters parted, they run into each other here one day.
It’s my first snow in life.
That means I’m the first one you see snow with.
If this movie was aired in our universe,
it would make millions by now.
If it wasn’t for you,
this movie wouldn’t have happened.
I’m going to bed.
Drowsy.
Tun.
I’m starving, Tess.
Let’s go eat.
Wake up.
He’s never been a morning person.
We must play hardball.
Ready?
1, 2, 3.
Tickle. Tickle.
Who are you here for?
Is Tun home?
He’s been like this since he got back.
Spending alone time in his room, not associating with anyone.
It’s good you’re here, Tess. Please deal with him.
Tun.
Talay.
What brought you here?
It hasn’t even been that long but you look a lot older.
Your ears are deaf.
And look.
Your mustache has turned white.
Yeah.
Now you’re as old as me.
What are you listening to?
Some music.
But I don’t know any of the songs in this universe.
♪ Oh dear love ♪
♪ Please look at me ♪
♪ Sometimes we meet on a heartbreaking day ♪
♪ You come in and embrace me softly ♪
♪ Oh dear love ♪
♪ Sweet love ♪
♪ You’re a beauty, my heart gets carried away ♪
♪ Look at you ♪
♪ Where are you? ♪
♪ Oh dear love, I want to meet you ♪
♪ You can do anything ♪
♪ Oh dear love, I love you ♪
The song you wanted to hear.
I played it.
I should leave now.
You came all the way here just to play me that song?
You’ve been gone for 9 days.
Do you have any idea how long 12,960 minutes I waited for you felt like?
Tun.
I…
I freaking missed you.
I know.
Because for me,
it was 777,600 seconds that I spent missing you like crazy too.
What about you?
What did you miss about me?
I miss…
your annoyance,
your care,
and lastly,
just you.
Hey!
I have a question.
Why did you disappear?
I don’t have much money left.
And I don’t want to bother Pakorn’s parents.
I tried to save money as much as I could.
I stayed in.
I didn’t contact anyone.
I didn’t go anywhere.
I only ate at home.
Is it that bad?
Then why didn’t you answer my calls?
Because if you said you wanted to see me
or if I heard your voice,
I couldn’t resist going to see you, Talay.
I tried to find a new job
but there was no job I wanted to do.
Why not?
Because you were not part of it.
A life of doing things alone was not fun at all.
I think we…
Tun, Tess,
I prepared you guys some snacks.
Come have some.
Yes, Mom.
Hello, Dad.
Hello.
Glad to finally meet you in person, Tess.
Ever since Tun got home, he hasn’t talked about anything.
He seems to forget everything.
He only talked about one thing.
You, Tess.
Really, Dad?
Did he gossip about me?
No.
He mainly said you’re great.
You’re so helpful. Like when he was put in jail…
Dad!
That’s enough.
Have you eaten anything yet, Tess?
Can I make you anything? You guys can eat together.
Thank you, Mom.
I’m just hungry.
Okay then. Just one second.
Honey, come help me.
Let the kids talk. Come here.
Of course.
Chop-chop.
Pakorn’s parents are lovely.
I guess this is such a warm family.
So lovely.
They always give Pakorn the things he likes.
Here.
Fill your stomach first.
Pakorn must like this very much.
I like it too.
I mean you.
What?
I like when you eat.
You make everything look so yummy.
Then I’ll eat them all by myself.
Who is it?
I’ll go get the door.
Don’t bother.
I just invited myself in.
I came very often.
How have you been?
I missed you guys.
I brought you guys northern Thai sausages.
Up!
What brings you here?
I missed your foul mouth so bad.
I know.
I’m so proud of it.
Now that we’re here, should we call Aou?
Do it.
Go ahead, Tess.
Hi, Aou.
(Hello. Hello.)
(What did you say?)
(I have no reception.)
(Hello. Hello.)
He’s probably doing some fishing.
He said he had no reception.
Uh…okay.
I just got my reception.
It’s nice and clear now.
Aou!
You. You. You.
Like that?
Hold on. I’m lost.
Is this destiny?
There’s no such a thing.
I destined this.
After you came, I called them here too.
Luckily, they are in Bangkok.
I freaking missed you guys.
Guys.
Friend Credits!
I missed this so bad. Haven't done it in a long time.
But first,
I need something to eat.
Stop.
You can’t eat these.
They’ve been reserved.
He said he would eat them all by himself.
No way.
Stop!
Nobody can have it.
Fine.
Friend Credits!
What?
It sparkled for a few seconds.
The sparkler?
You want more?
I meant us.
We shone for a short moment.
But I think…
we can go further.
That was just one failure.
Should we make more movies?
Make more failures.
No.
How sad.
Because it won’t be a failure this time.
Yes!
What about you, Tess?
Would you like to work with us one more time?
Let’s do it.
Go as far as we can.
I’ll talk to my dad.
To our brighter day.
Cheers.
Cheers!
You know, I missed you guys so bad.
I missed everything about you.
Every personality you guys have.
Like what?
You, for example, Up.
I missed your friendliness so much.
You make people smile while they don’t even have to ask for it.
And I missed your annoying aggressiveness and inappropriate behaviors.
You’re picking on me, clearly.
Hey, but I truly missed you all.
What about you?
What did you miss about me?
That’s tough.
Can’t think of one.
Nothing at all?
I missed…
your annoyance,
your shyness,
your nice singing voice,
your care,
and lastly,
just you.
Hey!
You’re not sleeping?
I was.
But then I heard your whispering sound.
It woke me up.
Were you talking behind my back?
No.
Nothing.
Just sleep.
I can’t anymore.
Take responsibility.
Make me drowsy.
How about counting sheep?
I don’t have any other ideas.
I read this from a book.
It says if we hear the sound of nature before going to bed,
we will fall asleep easier.
The sound of nature?
What is it?
Talay. (The sea)
I like the sound of the sea.
Whisper in my ear now.
What the heck are you doing?
Making the wave sound.
My ears are all wet.
Should we try patting your back and your butt?
I did it when I nannied my nephew.
I was about to say that.
How old are you?
I think you should just stop talking and you’ll be drowsy soon.
That’s a big yawn.
And now you’re the one drowsy.
Hey.
There’s one last method.
Ear massage.
I’ll do it for you.
Um.
Good night,
Talay.
Signs you’re falling in love.
There!
I saw that.
Who are you falling in love with?
Speak.
You’re wrong.
I’m just doing some research for my romantic movie.
Is that so?
Let me know if you need a protagonist.
I’m always up for it.
Now that we talk about it.
I want to know how we can tell if we like that person already.
You’ve dated so many people.
Why being so naive now?
I just feel like I don’t know love at all.
Sounds like a super dreamy dialogue from a movie.
To me, to want that person in life is considered liking.
That’s it?
Heck yeah.
Don’t overthink it.
Don’t complicate things.
So…
Who are you feeling it with?
I told you, no one.
You think I don’t know.
- You…
- Shut it.
Stop talking.
What are you afraid of, Tess?
You don’t need to be afraid of failing in the end.
What you should be afraid of
is letting that person slip through your fingers.
Whose RV is that?
It belonged to a friend of my dad.
How about we renovate it into a studio?
It’s an RV.
I’ve always wanted to have an RV.
Just like in this photo.
But I think it is missing something.
What?
Someone who’s willing to travel with you for the rest of your life.
What you should be afraid of
is letting that person slip through your fingers.
What the hell are you playing, Tun?
Are you playing a sad guy in a music video?
No.
I’m just thinking
about our next movie project.
What are you doing here?
I was helping my dad water the plants.
Then I saw you making an awkward face.
So I decided to watch you instead.
Pleasing to the eye.
Get lost.
I said go.
Tun.
Hm?
Whose RV is that?
That one?
It belonged to a friend of my dad.
My dad told me his friend needed money.
He sold it to my dad for a good price.
Your dad bought it and left it like this?
He doesn’t know how to make use of it.
It goes at the speed of a turtle.
Friend Credits doesn’t have an office.
How about we renovate it into a studio?
What?
It’s an RV.
We discuss work inside.
When ideas run out, we drive out there for more inspiration.
How do we start?
Go up there.
Remove these vines.
Me again?
Just help.
We’ll keep the passenger seat next to the driver.
And get rid of the rest.
We’ll build a table and chairs right here.
Then on the opposite,
there’s a shelf for books and movie DVDs.
Hey.
Ouch. It hurts.
Wait.
You’re drawing like you already have an image in your head.
Of course, I do.
I’ve always wanted to have an RV.
I used to think that when I’m old, I’ll drive my RV to places,
just like in this photo.
But I think it is missing something.
What?
Someone who’s willing to travel with you for the rest of your life.
The fridge is huge!
Hey, I love it.
So you guys disappeared because you did it?
The fridge is mine.
It’s for my luxurious drinks.
And I got the seat in the back.
Freaking comfy.
Since we’re all here,
I have a gift for our new studio.
What?
What is it?
Wait here.
What do you think it is?
Something expensive.
I can’t wait.
In a note from the tree planting class I took,
a tree with a very nice meaning was mentioned. So I bought it.
A Pink Trumpet tree.
Hold on, Tun.
How big is a Pink Trumpet tree when it’s fully grown?
Around 8-25 meters.
Wait.
Are you planting a 25-meter-tall tree in an RV?
Are you kidding?
Well, trim it.
Besides, won’t you be happy to wake up and see a pretty pink tree?
No.
I don’t think pink.
But its meaning is very nice.
It represents love and good wishes.
It fits romantic film screenwriters like us.
That’s true.
Aou.
What?
Let’s make room for our amulet.
Where should we place it?
Will it be good if we write about our life story in the screenplay?
I guess not.
Why not? It should be fun.
A man who travels to an unfamiliar world.
He is lost and lonely, and he needs to find someone to help him.
At last, he finds the one.
Then what’s next?
In the end, they…
Guys,
let’s capture you all on camera.
Come.
Just move a little left.
Snap me, Dad.
Be careful, guys.
Time for a photo.
You two switch places.
Better colors this way. Trust me.
I bought this so long ago that I forgot.
Glad I got to use it today.
Get closer.
Tess, closer. You don’t want to be out of the frame.
Sure.
In the end, they fall in love with each other.
What?
Will you spend tonight with me?
There are many things I want to do before I die.
But now
there’s one thing I want to do the most.
Yes, Dol?
What?
A guide video for new universal travelers?
Yes.
Do you see there’re lots of new travelers here?
It’s overwhelming for Joobjang and me to explain over and over.
You graduated Film and Tun was an actor.
Help me.
Please.
It doesn’t look nice here.
Should be from this angle.
See?
I checked every angle.
This is the best one.
The video is too flat.
Should be here.
Why so stubborn?
Don’t argue.
I’ve had so much experience.
Trust me.
You can’t.
I had work experience.
When they fight, they’re like boyfriends. Right?
Yeah.
No way.
Boyfriends don’t hit each other like this.
True.
Boyfriends don’t strangle each other like this.
That’s right.
Boyfriends don’t step on each other’s feet.
So that’s what universal travelers call ‘ship.’
You go away.
Trust me.
Let me go.
Back to work!
Okay.
The information part is done.
Now I want to interview universal travelers.
May I interview you two?
Is that a good idea?
Of course.
Help us. I’ll pay you with fried chicken.
My name is Talay.
In the other universe, I’m a colorist.
My name is Tun.
I’m an actor.
How do you feel being a universal traveler?
At first, I was shocked.
But I’m glad sometimes because I don’t have to work so hard anymore.
For me, I was so stressed out.
I just got the job I’d always wanted to do.
But then I traveled to the universe where I knew no one.
Lucky me,
I met Tun.
It was a funny story.
I just traveled here.
I was still lost.
Luckily, I met Talay.
He’s the light that saved me.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Tun and Talay.
I’ll send fried chicken right to your house.
I’ll prepare my stomach for that.
You do that.
Okay.
Bye now.
Bye.
I’ll see you tomorrow.
See you.
Come on.
Joobjang is so nice.
Right. I feel like I have another mom taking care of me here.
Hey.
Talay.
(Thank you.)
(I wish you get to go home before me.)
Okay.
Let’s cut to the last part.
Joob, you talk and end the video.
Okay.
To all universal travelers,
I do believe universal traveling happens for a reason.
What are you thinking?
What do you think we traveled between universes to learn?
No idea.
Perhaps if we stay a little longer, we’ll find out.
Maybe…
Maybe?
I traveled between universes just to meet you.
What?
Think about it.
If we didn’t travel here, we wouldn’t be eating fried chicken together now.
Duh!
Fried chicken is what I eat in whichever universe.
Here.
Take a photo and send it to Joobjang to say thanks.
Come on.
Look at your face.
Smile.
A happy smile.
Like this?
That smile doesn't say you enjoy the food.
It says you’re cute.
What should I do then?
Tell me.
Here. Let me help.
Hold the chicken.
Smile widely.
Smiley eyes.
Yes. Chicken closer.
Okay.
I know it.
Smile.
Smile widely.
1, 2, 3.
That’s the happy face.
Your eyes dazzle.
Don’t know if it’s because of the chicken or me.
Wow.
You don’t wait for me.
You keep talking and talking.
I’m hungry.
Here.
Hold it.
Yes, Dol?
What?
Joob suddenly had a heart attack and passed.
She had no history of heart disease.
How did it happen then?
This symptom has been proved.
It should be that the person in her body in the other universe died.
So Joob died too.
It’s normal for universal travelers.
No matter how many of us have passed,
I never get used to it.
I get you.
Joob always said nothing in life was certain.
Whatever I want to do, do it now.
But I never succeeded in doing it.
What do you want to do?
Tell Joob I love her.
I was too afraid to say it.
I thought I had all the time I needed.
She didn’t know I liked her.
She had no idea how much I wanted her to be my portkey.
Okay. Let’s cut to the last part.
Joob, you talk and end the video.
Okay.
To all universal travelers.
It is going to be tough at the beginning.
Don’t get discouraged yet.
Because you’re not alone.
I do believe universal traveling happens for a reason.
Maybe it’s a lesson for us to learn something we're missing.
I stand with every one of you.
Tun.
Hm?
Will you spend tonight with me?
Are you sleeping?
No.
Aren’t you going to ask why I asked you to stay over?
Because you’re sad about Joob.
Partly, yes.
I’m starting to be scared of death.
Life is so damn uncertain.
I’m afraid that one day I’d wake up
and people around me disappear on me.
You’re overthinking it.
What I fear the most is that it happens to someone I care about.
Especially, you.
I promise I won’t go anywhere.
Nothing will happen to me.
Someone like me doesn’t die so easily.
Thank you so much.
There are many things I want to do before I die.
But now
there’s one thing I want to do the most.
What?
Can I hug you to sleep all night tonight?
Good night.
Directed by Nuttapong Mongkolsawas
What are you doing?
You look like you’re going on a date.
I love it when you sing.
Hey.
That’s my t-shirt.
Well, it smells good.
I won’t let you go back alone.
Because I’ll find my portkey too.
Hasn’t it ever occurred to you that I’m your portkey?
This time,
I can kiss you, can’t I?