Knight!
This time I have to punish you.
I have to fire you.
Huh?
What?
You can't do that, boss.
He's the only one and the
best marketing that we have.
And he's never done anything wrong.
You can't do that.
Why do people always want to find the bad guy
instead of finding a solution to fix the problem?
I think we should buy a file restoration program
and try to restore the files, do you all agree?
We can't download it. This company blocks the
access to download any program by ourselves.
Auntie, when are you going
to stop doing things like that?
So...
What are we going to do with this now?
The IT staff is taking a day off today.
Fries.
You call Guy.
Huh? Guy?
Does it work?
Chill out!
I think...
Can you tell them to step away?
I can't breathe!
Drink it.
My family own a coffee shop.
Drink it, so you won't be stressed.
Thee.
Don't you think it's a bit odd?
How can the files just vanish?
Yes.
I think it's impossible if
you someone didn't delete it.
The files are very important too.
We would be in trouble if someone had it.
We should have used the Cloud
Storage that I suggested before.
The files won't be vanished?
It will.
What?
You're getting on my nerve.
But at least we will know
what IP user delete it.
Moreover, our work will be much eaiser.
And if we buy it with warranty,
and there's some problem,
we won't be responsible for it.
No risks.
And...
Is it going to be slow when we download
it? It takes so long. It's boring to wait.
For you, it might be difficult.
The internet connection
has to be very good.
Needs a good internet connection?
My home internet is so good.
I mean my imaginary internet. Amazing.
It works?
Yes. It's done.
You're amazing!
You've got it?
Yes.
We should tell boss.
Boss!
What's wrong with her?
She wants to take credit.
Why am I so unlucky?
Come on baby. It's ok. I
know you will get through it.
Boss!
We've got the files back. Yes! Yes!
Really?
Yes.
But no matter what, I have to fire Knight.
Boss, we can get the files back already.
It's a different thing. The
bad guy should be punished.
This time is a big deal.
Are you sure?
Chulee, tell Knight to come see me.
Ok.
Babe.
I don't want to do this.
I feel bad for him.
You're firing me?
Do you really think that I did it?
The evidence is showing that way.
But, does it show that I deleted it?
I did the photoshoot for you
even though I did want to do it.
So, why should I delete it?
Because you didn't want to do it.
How could you think that way?
You're...
not the same one I've known.
I'm the same me. What's
different is I have to go by rules.
What rules?
I'm not doing anything
and I'm not quitting.
But you have to quit.
Hold on!
There's only one truth.
The bad guy is in the office.
Dee.
What's wrong with you?
I've just borrowed your glasses.
Hold on. Don't fire Knight.
Why?
Because he didn't do it.
I've just check the CCTV.
I saw that the mouse and the chair moving.
That means something happened after that.
Boss, I also think
that Knight didn't do it.
And also we get the files back.
You both, please leave now.
You too, Chulee!
You said both, how would I know which one?
You think I don't exist. You said both
Babe, what about Sir?
I think you should call
Madam and ask her to help.
I have to bother her again?
Do you have a better idea?
Fine.
Hello, Madam. Did you know about Dee?
I have a favor to ask from you.
As I explained to you. If I fire him
now, there will be no one to train Dee.
And Knight is very good at
what he does. So, please help me.
Thank you.
All done.
Is everything ok?
Ok.
Darling. About that guy,
don't make a big deal about it.
He didn't do anything wrong.
If you fire him,
then who's going to train our grandson.
You always spoil him.
There are so many
people that can train him.
If he wants, I can train him.
But he doesn't let me.
And one more thing,
if he is...
You'll be the one who regrets.
And also, tell you beloved brother
don't let this happen again.
Thank you so much for helping me today.
So...
How have you been?
Well...
I'm the same old me.
I'm still waiting.
Waiting for what?
I heard that..
You broke up with Ohm?
Yes.
Well...
a while go.
So...
Are you seeing anyone?
No, I'm not.
But who knows.
Do you believe in...
Parallel Universe?
Maybe...
in another universe,
you and I...
probably...
are more than friends.
Today you get the credit,
but someday
I hope that...
I will get your heart.
What are you talking about? Go home.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
So now...
do you accept me to work with you?
What are you doing there?
Come with me.
Will you teach me everything?
Where should I start?
Why is it so hot today?
Baby Heya. I'm so hot. It feels
very uncomfortable in here.
I want to take everything off. It's
so hot. You see I'm all sweating?
If you're hot, why don't
you live in a fridge?
Your AC at home is broken?
Why do you have to
sleep in tent at the office?
Because I'm bored.
I can't take a vacation leave.
You know? That old
auntie has a good memory.
She knows everything, when it's my day off,
what I will do, when I will take a leave.
I'm so annoyed. I don't know what she eats
to help her remember everything very well.
Why are you crying?
Do you know...
remember things very well..
Is better than remember nothing.
I want my mom to be able to remember me.
Forever.
So...
what's wrong with your mom?
My mom's had Alzheimer for 2-3 years now.
But this morning...
she seemed not to remember me.
Not remember you?
It's ok.
I'm scared.
What am I supposed to do?
Don't be scared.
You don't have to be scared.
I have friends who are good doctors.
I will help you.
Thank you so much.
It's ok.
Too many documents.
How is it going?
You really get to do a
real internship today.
You're happy now?
You told me that you
would teach me some work.
Why am I here to put these documents away?
Song Thee said the other day that these
information can be saved in Cloud, didn't he?
We don't have to waste
papers and make it complicated.
What?
Just an easy job like this...
you complain already?
What about the other job...
would you be able to do it?
There are so many jobs for you today.
Really?
What are they?
Will you teach me everything?
Besides the marketing work...
will you teach me...
other things...
like you did in the car?
What car?
You got the wrong person.
Stop lying.
I can...
remember your eyes.
Oh!
What are you two doing here?
I'm organizing the documents.
That's good. I have to
find a contract with a client.
I want Heya to help me but I don't
know where she is. Can you help me?
You will find it.
Because today...
he has to organize all of
the documents in this room.
And also...
if you find it...
let Thee know. I'm gonna go now.
Thee.
It's a perfect time.
I've been wanting to talk to you.
What's the matter with Knight?
He's been kind of shocked
since the first time he saw my face.
But he seemed ok when
he talked to me in a car.
Wait. You've met him before?
Yes. When I called...
Don't tell anyone.
That time I had a fight with
my grandfather at the company,
so I called a ride to
take me out from there.
Knight was dropping a
passenger around there,
so he accepted my ride request
and we got to talk a bit in the car.
Because of his words,
he made me brave to come
out and find my own happiness.
But...
when I took of a mask,
he was shocked.
And when he helped me from Ohm,
he saw my face and he was shocked again.
I'm not even talking about when...
he saw me in boss' office.
I'm really not sure.
But from my point of view,
he has a persona of wolves,
he likes to be alone. He
doesn't like social interaction.
He just sits at his desk
alone all day, works quietly,
puts headphones on and not talk to
anyone. You can say that he's anti-social.
So, I think there's something that
Knight is afraid or doesn't like about you.
You've said a very long
speech. I only catch the last one.
Like I said.
But if you want me to
analyze it again, I think...
That's enough.
No need to analyze anything anymore.
By the way,
what does he like?
What he likes? You mean what is his type?
No. I mean...
what he likes to eat, what he likes to do.
Why did you ask? You
want to flirt with him?
Are you crazy?
I just...
want to find something to flatter him.
So, maybe it will make him not hate me.
But you seem care so much about
him, since that day the files were gone.
Normally, you don't do things like that.
Thee. I have to help him,
otherwise who's gonna train me.
By the way,
What about you?
You've had a crush on Veve since college.
Now you get to work together.
- Is there any progress?
- Be quiet.
People here have a
very good listening skill.
SEspecially, Auntie Chulee. So, be quiet.
Is someone talking about me?
So, how is it?
I don't feel that way now.
When we were working
on Miss Suzy's project,
I heard that you gave your all.
I had to do it for our company.
I can tell. Just confess now.
Yes. I like her but sometimes...
I don't know how to say it.
You haven't changed.
But as I said, how can you
get her as your girlfriend?
You take too long to get to
what you really want to say.
When it comes to feelings, no
need to take a long time, just say it.
Love is evaluated by
heart, brain comes after.
But it's ok, your chance is here.
What chance?
The chance that I will help you.
How?
Leave it to me.
Stop babbling. If you find
the contract, give it to me.
Why are Chao Sua's bags here?
Clean it up, please.
I'll get back to work now.
Ok.
Hey!
Screaming like that, how are
you gonna help him, Mr. Planner?
When did you come here?
At first I wanted to come in here and
Chao Sua's Mini Crispy Rice Cracker.
It's a small bite but very delicious.
I ate until I fell asleep.
But this flavor is very
good. You have to try it.
Actually I woke up already but I don't
know what Song Thee was talking about.
It was very long, so I
decided to get more sleep.
So, how are you gonna help him?
When it comes to feelings, no
need to think too much, just say it.
Gypsy cards reading?
Veve.
Hey.
Today we're having a
religious ceremony at our office?
Why is the holy thread very long?
Don't drop it.
Otherwise it won't be holy.
No, it's not like that.
Let's do this,
you...
hold...
this rope.
Hold this rope?
Yes.
And close your eyes.
What are you playing?
Then stand up slowly.
And follow this rope.
Ok.
I'm a bit scared.
Enough?
Keep going.
Ok.
Open you eyes, honey.
Open this paper and read it.
I have a crush on you
but I'm scared to tell you.
Hey!
Where did they go?
I have a crush on you
but I'm scared to tell you.
Or...
maybe Song Thee has a crush on me?
He's crazy.
Why didn't he tell me?
This bill is from Thep.
What kind coffee did you buy for
the client? It's 150 baht per cup.
Stop. The point is you bought 2 cups of coffee. 1 cup was
for yourself, why are you withdrawing the money for that?
Hey Auntie. I'm the one who does the work. I
went there for work. What's wrong with that?
Everything is wrong. And
there's a food bill from you too.
When are you going to stop
taking clients outside for meetings?
We have a meeting room in our place.
Did you really go outside to meet clients
or did you go out for a date with some girl?
Why are you playing
with the truth like that?
You're making it worse.
Auntie, do you want to quit being HR?
You want to quit being an accountant?
And start working for FBI or CIA.
It's only a coffee. It's not going
to make the company go broke.
I did it for our company.
When I want to get the money back, it's so hard. But
when you want me to pay in advance, it's so easy.
Yes.
I'm working in Office of Forensic Science.
And about you using the same supplier
for every work. You should stop it.
If I know there's something
behind it, I will kick everyone out.
Go for it. Kick me out.
Now I work only 40%, you're lucky enough.
I go ask other people to work with
us, they really don't want to do it.
Kick me out. I'm happy with that, so
I don't have to beg anyone for help.
You act like...
Moo Yong. Here.
Yes?
This is for you.
For me?
Why?
So you can use for your work.
I know you're very creative.
You will have something
to support your work.
And the most important thing
is the files won't be vanished.
Otherwise, we have to
restore again. It's so annoying.
You're such a payer.
You're very kind.
It's normal.
You bought an iPad for Moo Yong?
Where's the reciept?
Did you use the company's money?
What's the matter with you?
Why do you nitpick everyone?
Can't you think?
Today is his special
day, it's his birthday.
I just bought him a gift.
You're unbelievable.
We know very well that he won't buy something
like this for himself. He's very stingy.
How can he buy it? You know? When his salary
comes out, he has to send money to his family
So he's like this.
Happy birthday Moo Yong.
Thank you so much. But you give
me this without any works, right?
Open it. I already put a note for you.
It's your birthday?
Yes.
I have nothing for you
but I will sing for you.
I give you until lunch time. Give me all the
bills, otherwise you won't get the money.
She's unbelievable. Just sing happy
birthday, we still get a bill from her.
A person like her won't die beautifully.
Veve.
Is it a good idea?
That is Song Thee.
Don't worry!
He won't know. Trust me.
If you want to know, why
don't you just ask him?
Are you crazy? If this was a
trick, I would be so embarrassed.
Then, why don't you ask the
interns that like to pick on you?
I've been looking for them
everywhere. I don't know where they are.
Why do you want to know so much?
That you asked me to help you with this.
Hey.
Or...
you like him too?
That's why you want to know how he feels.
That's crazy. I don't like him.
I just want to know.
And a fortune teller told me
that I would meet my soulmate.
If he's the one, then it
will be good for me, right?
So I will have a boyfriend.
But if he's not, so we can clear the air.
Or...
it's better that I don't know?
Stop babbling.
He's coming.
You called me here, is there
anything you want to talk to me?
You've helped me a lot of times.
And...
This is Note. My boyfriend.
He wants to thank you
for helping me.
Boyfriend?
Yes.
If you want to order anything, go for it.
Don't feel bad.
You're so cute baby.
If I'm cute then...
you should give me a reward.
Huh?
You're crazy.
I don't want to kiss you here.
Are you crazy?
I'm shy. A lot of people here.
Song Thee is sitting here too.
It's inappropriate.
Right?
There's no one here.
Don't mind me. Go for it.
If you want to kiss each other, you can.
Hold on.
I will take a picture for you.
So you can keep it as a good memory.
You're so generous.
Darling.
Babe.
I'll be back.
Don't be too long.
Are you tired of the same trick?
What trick?
Well...
You have your friend
pretending to be your boyfriend.
For what?
Well...
I want to know.
About what?
I want to know
if you feels anything for me.
Yes.
What do you think?
Well...
If you want to know, come with me tonight.
Where are we going? And what will we do?
Come with me to find out.
Just tell me now.
So demanding.
Shit! Is this your plan?
Amazing!
No!
It wasn't me.
Veve is busted herself.
But that's ok. I'll say it's a success.
What about you?
I heard you in that room,
that you talked to Song Thee about Knight.
What did you hear?
Dude, I've been friends with
you since we were so little.
How could I not see it?
But...
What could you see?
You seem to care so much about Knight.
You do it just because you don't want
him to hate you, is that the real reason?
Huh?
So?
What are you saying?
You know it's impossible.
But I think it's possible. I've noticed
how he looks at you when you're unaware.
You're very observant lately.
Since you started
working with Auntie Chulee.
You're not going home yet?
No. I still have lots of work to do.
Is there anything I can help you with?
I've finished all the works
that you assigned me.
It's ok.
You should go home. It's getting late now.
Let me help you.
I know you can't do it all by yourself.
I'm a fast learner.
You want to help?
Yes.
And...
Your family is ok if you get home late?
They're ok,
I guess?
Ok.
Then...
You know what you have to do?
I don't know but I will.
Can I ask you something?
Why do you have to...
work very hard
when you already have everything?
Well...
long time ago
there was a driver once told me
to go out and live my own life.
I didn't say that.
You fell for my trick.
I know that you remember me.
Stop pretending.
I remember that you said
"Do you dare to go out
and love your own life?"
"Even it's a failure or success, are you
gonna be happy with what you choose?"
Because of my words?
Yes.
The life turning point of many people
can happen because of a few words.
And you?
Are you happy with what you've chosen?
Yes, I am.
Because my happiness...
is right in front of me.
These paper works in front of me here
make me happy and I can improve myself.
That's good that you're determined.
Of course I am because I want
to prove myself to my loved one,
the one who's right beside me.
My grandparents, I want prove and
show them how much I love them.
Ok.
Of course it's ok because...
That's enough.
Do your work now.
Then we won't get to do...
If we don't work, then what will we do?
Choose the right one. Radio Media.
Meet the target customers' needs that are ready to buy the
products and can get to more than 50 million customers per month.
Contact DV8 Limited
Company. Call 092-4923377
Oh. There's DIFA too.
Put a weapon to your brand with DIFA. The
better agency and gives you more than anything.
What now?
Why is it always me in this situation?
Get to work. Go!
Quickly.
Why are you so into this?
I'm peacefully and beautifully dead today.
What happened? Tell us.
It's about our oppa and Dee.
Your imagination again.
Knight and Dee like each other?
Spit it out.
It's nothing. She just
made it up in her head.
No, I didn't. It's true.
What are you doing here?
You believe in this kind of stuff?
Yes.
What did you pray and ask for?
To tell you how I feel.
Are you crazy? No one
does something like that.
I'm just scared to say it.
And how are you gonna redeem your vows?
A Thai dance.
A Thai dance?
I don't know. The other day I heard you and Moo
Yong talked about it, so I wanted to try it.
I didn't think it would work.
So...
how...
did you know that Note and I are friends?
Since you guys were in college,
you guys were bestfriends back then.
Wait!
How did you know we've
been friends since college?
I studied in the same college as you.
You saw me there.
Why didn't I know about this?
I don't remember you.
I was out of your
sight. It's just like that.
So, when I'm in your sight
now, I have to play in a character.
Although we are best friends,
doesn't mean we can't be more than that.
That's true.
But Note's girlfriend is my friend.
What a small world.
And...
How did you like me? And
when did you start to like me?
You ask so many questions.
It's a past, just leave it there.
Why?
Now I still like you.
I like you so much.
Go for it.
The stage is yours.
Since we're here...
I will capture this moment.
Keep dancing.
Am I doing it ok?
Yes.
Come dance with me.
Nope.
Just a little.
Come here. I'll tech you.
Teach me what? You
can't even do it yourself.
Come dance together.
One hand like this,
the other hand like this.
Like this?
Yes.
Go with the rhythm.
Really?
Yes. You're doing good.
Yes. That's right.
Like this?
Yes.
But I'm doing off the beat.
It's ok, right?
Yes. It's ok.
Ok.
If I want you to say you love me...
do I have to pray for it again?
And now, you're not scared to say it.
Today I'm introducing you
a new Marketing Consultant.
Hello everyone.
Did Dee do anything
to give you bad feelings?
No, he didn't.
Give me your hand.
Many people here.
I'm delighted.
So, you two are working
together all the time,
don't you have any feelings for each other?
Get up on it and put your hands here.
Ok.