[Pong] My dad told me Rajabodin School
is the most prestigious
boarding school in the province.
This school is different in that
it emphasizes extracurricular activities.
The founder believed that
activities allowed students
to gain experience.
YEAR 1947
FOUNDER OF SCIENCE CLUB
We get to see what we like or excel at.
YEAR 1946
FOUNDER OF SOCCER CLUB
YEAR 1995
FOUNDER OF COVER DANCE CLUB
STUDENT CLUBS
[girl] Photo club is here.
It's photo club.
Hey, you.
[cheering]
[Pong] Soccer club is the most famous.
It's held the championship title
for ten years in a row.
Why is it so crowded?
[Pong] But the newest and most popular
would be this cupcake club.
The hottest imaginary couple in school
is the president of both clubs.
[all screaming]
Book is the soccer club's captain
that everybody loves.
My cupcake
is pretty, delicious, and perfect.
I'm giving it to you, Book.
[Pong] As for Eve, everybody respects her.
Everybody knows that Book belongs to Eve
because a prince belongs to a princess.
Isn't that right?
[Eve] Hello, everyone.
Today, Book and I,
in the name of the club presidents,
came here to welcome you guys.
[Pik] Book!
Book!
Book, here.
Hi, everyone.
I'd like you all
to explore and get to know each club
since you have to stay in it
for at least a semester.
[Eve] And I'd like to recommend my club,
the cupcake club.
[students applauding]
My club focuses on neatness,
delicacy, beauty,
carefulness,
and good manners.
Huh!
I'd like all of you to participate in
every club's activities.
And I hope
I could be of some help.
If anyone has a problem,
we are both glad to help you.
[whistle blows]
Whose ball is this? Hey, whose ball?
Whose ball?
Whose ball? Admit it! Is it yours?
Yours?
Don't know?
Shh!
180, Montri. 189, Somjit.
Come on.
Ready?
[whistle blows]
Hey, hey, hey! No! Shit.
[scoffs]
You're gonna hit on
that pink ball's owner, right?
Not a chance.
How come?
Because of this.
You surely can't handle her.
She isn't a tomboy,
but a school mean girl.
Hey! Why did you do that?
Hit her classmates.
Kicked a ball into a parent's face.
Finally, she kicked a ball into her coach
and got expelled.
So she came here
because of her mom's connections.
Don't pay attention.
How could I not?
She's all over Facebook.
Here.
She's quite cute.
But you should leave her alone
because of her character.
[Pik] What character?
Hey, nice shoes!
We do have many things in common, huh?
[whispering] He's doomed.
[Pik] Whoo!
Today, we've tried out for new members.
The first one is 190, Baworn.
-Give him a big hand.
-[all applauding]
Next, 198, Dome.
Yes!
Very good, Dome.
Okay, okay.
Next, 199, Pok Pong.
-Great.
-[Coach Ble] You made it.
Give them a round of applause.
Three people passed this round.
You three go meet at the club room.
Dismissed.
Wait, Coach.
Did I not make it?
[blows whistle]
-Okay, everyone, dismissed!
-Hey! How come he made it?
-It's not fair!
-Pik.
Come on. I'll take you to another club.
Pik.
Hey!
[Pik] Let me go.
I won't be in her crazy club!
I hate her.
And I don't want to make cupcakes.
Pik.
This club is not easy to get into.
I begged Eve so you could get in.
She wasn't even resentful
for this morning.
Hey.
Are you on her side?
Pik.
This school emphasizes
extracurricular activities.
And you got into a fight.
You could get expelled.
How about this?
You join it for this semester.
Okay?
Hey, you hear me?
[Pik] Yeah.
KEEP OUT
UNDER MAINTENANCE
Hi, Dad.
[Piya Pong on phone] Hey, how are you
doing, kiddo? How was the tryout?
-I made it on the team.
-So why didn't you call me?
How are your new friends?
They're good.
Great.
[Piya Pong] Glad to hear that.
Hey, call me often, okay?
Okay.
You came here to practice?
Me, too.
Care to join?
No. I just want to work out.
Practicing alone
is no fun.
I can train you.
No, thank you.
What's the matter with you?
I see.
You're upset about the rumor in the club.
You're so sensitive.
Why do you care about them?
Sucker!
But if you're good
and don't care about anybody,
nobody likes you, either.
GRADE 7 ROOM 1
[bell ringing]
Did you see the tryouts yesterday?
The player sucked!
The coach...
He must have bribed the coach.
Terrible passing and play. I knew it.
[chattering]
We should respect Coach Ble's decision.
But, sir,
school rules do not prohibit women
to be in the soccer club.
But they also say
we should respect the decisions
made by the club counselor.
Don't you think it's discrimination?
So you decided to kick the ball
into the coach
the same way you did
at the previous school, right?
-Well--
-That school
asked you to quit, so it wouldn't be
on your record.
But it's a cyber world these days,
there are no secrets.
[girl] Hey.
Duck!
All right, this group.
We're gonna practice the penalty kick.
A good penalty kick is not just about
speed and intensity.
You need to read the goalkeeper's mind
for which direction he's going.
Today, I'm gonna teach you
how to make a cupcake.
Let's do it together.
[all] Five, four, three, two.
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Five, six, seven, eight ♪
[all exclaiming]
[Eve] Pik.
Could you get me vanilla extract
from that cabinet, please?
Hey!
Oh!
[boy] Hey, Beckham. Go ahead.
Shit.
[Book] Mr. Protégé.
Are you gonna kick it? Come on.
Wow.
Nice shot.
Must have gone to Pluto. Go get the ball!
Vanilla extract.
You know it?
[girls laughing]
If not,
just bring me sprinkles.
Let me see the new member's work.
Well, I think this one should have
a little more glitter.
This color is very sweet.
Looks delicious. I like it.
Everyone,
take this as an example.
We don't want something like this.
It looks terrible.
[all laughing]
-[Eve] Mrs. Bright.
-Hmm?
Pik is not good at using her hands.
Pik, you need to try
and learn from Eve. Okay?
Eve, could you train her?
-I'll step outside a bit. I'll be back.
-Okay.
[Mrs. Bright] You guys stay here with Eve.
Good job, everyone.
Pik, when you make a cupcake,
think of it as a treat
for the person you love.
So you'll make it with care.
If you even have such a person.
[all laughing]
[all screaming]
[screaming]
[Pik] Mrs. Bright!
[girls screaming]
Hey. That's Piya Pong's son, isn't it?
I thought he'd be good like him.
-Just wait and see.
-Is that Pik?
Care to join?
Okay.
[Pik] Since today,
Evil Eve got get punished,
we're gonna play "Kick the ball into Eve."
This is very relaxing.
Hey! Where did you kick it to?
Let me show you.
Here, see? Your eyes look that way.
Kick it to Evil Eve.
Shit.
-Whoa!
-How about that?
Hey!
You got it! It hit!
[exclaiming]
Having fun?
-Yeah.
-If so,
let's play together again.
Maybe tomorrow?
You'll get better if you practice more.
Come practice with me.
Okay?
Promise.
Great.
You're so lucky
to be accepted into the soccer club.
I really wanted to get in.
But in the end, I couldn't.
You got into this school
because you want to play soccer?
Actually, I...
want to play soccer with Book.
But since he got into this school,
we've hardly played together.
You're tight friends with him, huh?
Yeah.
Our houses are next to each other.
He taught me how to play soccer
when we were little.
How about you?
You came to this school because
you wanted to play ball?
Yeah.
You really like soccer?
My dad was a soccer player here,
and he wanted me to be one.
What if you can't?
I don't know.
Just keep practicing, maybe.
You? If you can't stand
the cupcake club, what will you do?
I'll quit the school.
[chuckles]
Hungry?
I've got something good.
Here.
I made this.
Is it edible?
Want to eat it?
Cheers.
In one gulp, okay?
[groans]
What's happening?
What?
[both screaming]
Stop!
Are you touching me?
[Pong] Woohoo! Yes!
Hey,
well,
it came out of the underwear.
-How do I put it back?
-Shit. Wait, no.
I'll do it.
We need to fix this right now.
All right, that's everything.
So do it. What are you waiting for?
Well, I don't remember
how to make it at all.
Shit.
All right then. We'll try it all.
Serious?
Yuck! Bitter.
Want an egg?
Be a little serious.
I can't do it anymore.
I think it's gotta mix as a cupcake
to work.
I think I'd better call my dad.
No! Are you crazy?
Your dad wouldn't believe us.
Anyway,
may I use your body to play soccer
for a day?
What?
What about me?
Please, please, please.
Promise me first that we're gonna find
a way to switch back.
I promise.
Hey, Pong. Where have you been?
Hey, Mr. Protégé,
did you forget to masturbate this morning?
Hmm.
Bonita!
This is what a Rajabodin lady looks like.
You may go now.
Five, four, three, two.
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Five, six, seven, eight ♪
♪ Five, six, seven, eight♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
[door slams]
Pik. Come here.
[chuckles nervously]
We're all friends here.
Pik, you can go to that table.
All of you at that table just move
to the other tables.
-[girl 1] Okay.
-[girl 2] Good.
[Mrs. Bright] Let's go. Come on.
From today on,
I'll have Eve be by your side
until you know how to make a cupcake.
Mrs. Bright, are you sure it's a good idea
to have Eve...
[Mrs. Bright] I'm sure that Eve
can catch you up with everyone.
Eve, are you also willing
to train her overtime?
For our cupcake club,
I'd be happy to.
Very good.
Go there now, then.
Go. Come on.
Chop-chop.
Today, we're gonna learn
how to crack eggs.
Good.
I think it's good.
Keep the enemy close,
so she won't be near Book.
[Mrs. Bright] Grab an egg, everyone.
[Eve] Grab an egg.
Wider side is down.
Narrower side is up.
Then crack it.
Useless.
Couldn't even crack an egg.
You just ruined it.
Look. Crack it just once.
Then open it.
And normally, a beautiful,
well-mannered girl
would keep the egg shell like this.
Today,
we're gonna play as a team.
The non-freshmen in one team.
The freshmen in another.
To test your skills and potential.
To see who are superior.
Ready? Get in position.
[blows whistle]
Go, go.
Take it. Good.
Good.
Book, I scored a goal!
Hey.
I'm sure it's the sprinkles.
Evil Eve asked me to get it
from the cupboard the other day.
And...
But I randomly picked it.
So I don't know which one.
As you have seen,
there are 38 bottles of them.
But don't be hopeless just yet.
Let's try until we find it.
Let's do this.
While we're looking the switching formula,
I'll train you in soccer,
since we have to try making cupcakes
together anyway.
It's a way to say thank you.
Once we switch back, you'll be ready
and as good as me.
If so, we have to practice every day.
Sure.
And you have to promise me
that you will make the lineup.
I promise.
So let's start from this one.
You send your dad
the clip of me playing this afternoon.
Come on.
Your dad would be proud.
Here.
Send it.
Now, we're gonna switch some positions.
Pong and Dome,
go to the non-freshmen team.
Gug and Tony,
go to the freshmen team.
[whistle blows]
Pong, pass it to me.
Hey!
[boy] Book, shoot it!
Yes!
Book!
That was great.
I'll get to see Pik's cupcake
today, right?
Of course, Mrs. Bright.
Looking good.
Eve, you trained her so well.
Keep trying, okay?
Two.
Three.
Four.
Anyway,
we are
in sync on the field.
Speaking of which, I think
you play like a girl I know.
Well,
I'd like to be your bro.
Get back to counting.
Where was I?
-Seven, maybe?
-Seven.
Seven.
Hold it like this. Okay. Begin.
Push it. Slowly.
Slowly.
Till the end. Push it.
Then pull it up.
Pik, you're just frosting a cake.
Why are you so excited?
This is not it.
Here. Your cupcake looks
and tastes better.
Eve taught me.
I'm full now.
[sighs]
By the way,
I might get to play in the Jaturamitr Cup
this Saturday.
Wow, are you joking?
I'm serious.
Coach let me play
as a midfielder recently.
[cheering]
[Satit] Welcome to the Jaturamitr Cup
Championship Game,
which consists of the top four
schools in Thailand
competing with each other.
For today,
We're "Ja" Satit Krikul
and "Borboo" Bouranij Rattanavichien.
We're the announcers.
Yes. Today is a match
between the Blue Whales
of Rajabodin School,
the defending champions.
They will play against the Golden Bus
of Ponsririn School.
This "Golden Bus" nickname says something
about how they play
and their style, obviously.
[Satit] The game between Rajabodin
and Ponsririn is about to start.
I noticed earlier that
Coach Jay, Ponsririn's coach, walked over,
but Coach Ble wouldn't shake his hand.
So I think the fun
won't just be on the field.
There's something going on outside, too.
Rajabodin's coach would not have a truce.
The game between Rajabodin
and Ponsririn is starting now.
Ponsririn gets to kick off.
[Bouranij] They are in yellow shirts.
Polsirrin meet
the defending champion, Rajabodin,
who are superior in terms of play style
and dignity. But at this moment,
Ponsririn get the ball
through to the right,
reaching the back line.
Send it across to the center.
Too slow. Shoot and a miss.
[cheerleaders chanting]
Now, Rajabodin get a chance to attack
for the first time.
There's someone on the right,
someone on the left. He's going alone.
[boy] Tum, pass it back here.
Pass it here!
So far, the game is tight.
But as you can see, Rajabodin's number 16,
Chatchawan Tamsri, can barely walk
and is limping.
He's about to be substituted.
And number 15 coming in
is Pok Pong.
Wait a minute. His last name
sounds familiar.
It is the same last name as
a former forward legend
of the national Thai soccer team.
[Satit] Long-time soccer fans
must know this name,
-"Tuk" Piya Pong Pue-on.
-[Bouranij] Let's see in his play
if he's related to Piya Pong or just
has the same name.
[players shouting]
[whistle blows]
[all cheering]
[Eve] You were awesome, Book!
Tired?
I've played as I promised.
Was it a fluke?
No way! This was all me.
I look so cool right now.
You are very good.
When did those two become so close?
[Pong] Come on. Let's take a selfie.
Thank you so much, Pong.
Hey,
do you want me to tell your dad
that, after the game, you don't want
to be in soccer club anymore.
No, no.
Don't say anything.
Okay. It's up to you.
Be good.
Hi, Dad.
Hello.
How did you get here?
I asked the coach for permission.
Dad, this is Pik.
Here is the clip of the game
that I was in.
Look. See? I came around with the ball,
passing the first person, the second,
then the third. Was I cool, Dad?
What a bragger you are!
Hmm?
You appear so introverted,
but you brought a girl here, too.
It's not like that. We're just friends.
Hey!
Don't be shy, Pik.
Dad, these days,
girls like guys with cute little faces.
And guys like strong girls.
Normally, he's not lazy like this.
He must be really tired today.
Let me help you.
Dad, you...
-I mean, you bake?
-Sure!
What you just ate,
I made that myself.
Since Pong is in boarding school,
I have some free time.
While I was free,
I just cleaned up the house.
And I found this.
His mom's baking set.
So I tried it out.
I can bake, too.
I'm in the cupcake club at school.
Really? I thought you were
in the same club.
Pong can do well when he's doing it
with the one he loves.
When he was younger,
he liked to bake with his mom.
As for soccer,
he started to play after his mom died,
and I quit the national soccer club
so I could take care of him full-time.
I thought
you wanted him to be a soccer player.
It's probably because when he was little
I liked to tell him about soccer.
So he probably assumed
that I wanted him to be a soccer player.
But, actually,
being a soccer player has a plus side.
So...
if he quits soccer
and doesn't know yet what he wants,
will you be mad?
Mad about what?
He's my son no matter what.
You're so sensitive, huh?
[Pik] You told your dad
about quitting soccer?
[Pong] Yeah.
With your body, I have the courage.
Thank you, Pik.
Your chest is really flat.
Not very comfortable.
[chuckles]
Oh, shit.
You'll be trapped by Pik.
[all exclaiming]
[Dew] You're quite popular now.
Don't you have to bring
the cupcake to Pong?
Later.
Why did you come by here?
About the trip this weekend,
what would you say?
Wait. I told you that I have to go home,
didn't I?
Well...
if you could go,
where would you like to go?
Hmm. Maybe go see a movie,
go shopping in a mall, have lunch,
something like that.
Pik.
You don't want to hang out with me, right?
You ask because you want
to ask Pong out, right?
No, no.
Listen.
You have stayed at his place.
It's too late to chicken out.
If I were you, I would walk
straight up to him
and ask him if he wants to go on a date
and where. That's it.
-Really?
-Yes.
Let's go. Right now.
-Right now?
-Yeah.
Pong is very popular now.
Better hurry before someone snatches him.
He's popular?
-Book.
-Yeah.
In this coming match with Nonthavit,
I'll pass you the ball to shoot.
I don't believe it.
-You can shoot it yourself.
-Yeah.
If I make the lineup and we win,
let's go celebrate.
Get back there.
Come on.
[Dome] Hey, Pik.
What a surprise! You came just in time.
Who do you come here to see?
Hey, Pik.
Good to see you. I need to talk to you.
But I have to talk to you first.
Come.
Wait.
She just wants to ask Pong
to go on a date this Sunday.
[Dome whispering] Wow. Date on Sunday.
This is your surprise?
Where are we going?
-Where do you want to go?
-Pik.
Your mom called me and asked you
to come home this weekend.
But I already have a date with Pong.
If she wanted to talk to me,
why wouldn't she call me directly?
Let's do this. This weekend,
we'll stay overnight at your house.
We'll hang out in your neighborhood.
Many places around there.
Okay?
But I think we should do this.
Her house is next to mine.
Let's hang out and stay at my house.
[Dome] You three spend the night together?
You, Pong, and Pik.
Great. What a scandal.
Are you sure about this?
Well, then I'll invite everyone
in the club.
-Let's go together. Good?
-What?
Tony hired some guys to join.
If his team wins, he'll buy them a treat.
Be careful.
Let's get them all at once.
I've got something good.
[boy] Fuck!
[in English] You're dead!
[in English] You're dead. Hmm.
[crashing and screaming on TV]
-Hey.
-Yeah?
I'm sorry
that I encouraged you to make
the first move on Pong.
Your date has become a group date.
It's all right, Dew.
Pik, let's go outside and talk.
-Tony, I'll be right back.
-Yeah.
Hey, come here. Sit closer.
Pik.
What's the matter with you these days?
Something bothering you?
No, nothing.
If that's all, I'll go back inside.
Wait. Let's chat.
Don't feel annoyed about
coming here in a group
because, today,
I wanted to tell you
that you did a good job.
You care more about teamwork.
I really mean it.
Was I really terrible?
That was before.
You used to be self-centered.
You didn't care much about others.
I can understand, though.
You were an only child, growing up.
But today, you did a very good job.
I can see that you have grown up a lot.
Now you have lots of friends,
like Dew and Pong.
Very Good.
Can you also see
that Pong has changed?
Yeah.
He seems to be more confident
in what he says and does.
Book, I really want to know,
between me and Pong,
who do you like to play soccer with?
Actually, both of you
have the same playing style
and similar characters.
I like to play soccer with both.
You seem to prefer him.
You seem to be more comfortable with him.
It's maybe because
I'm a guy, and he's a guy.
So we seem to work well together.
But you seem
to be closer to him anyway.
You practice with him
and talk to him,
but never play with me.
If I need to answer that right now,
I think I like him a lot.
But I'm not sure if I should tell him.
If he doesn't feel the same,
it could spoil all of the good things
we have right now.
Why are you sleeping here?
Dew is snoring.
Hmm.
[yawns]
Pik.
Did Book say anything to you
before going to bed?
And what did he say to you?
We just talked about...
if we want to tell the truth,
but someone can't take it
or might resent it,
should we say it?
Hmm.
Book taught me to be considerate
when saying anything.
You're in between me and Book.
You gotta be a pillow for me, too.
[Pong] No cupcake to taste today?
-[Pik] I forgot it in my room.
-What?
Well, then today I teach you
how to get the ball around.
When you get the ball around the opponent,
you have to be focused.
Watch and learn.
You haven't found the switching formula?
How long will it be?
Why? You don't like the body you're in?
It's not that. I just want
to be with Book in my body.
Why are the girls so crazy about him?
Because he's cool,
especially when he's playing soccer.
I ATE ONE. WAS STARVING.
VERY DELICIOUS -DEW
Can I run with you?
Your face is so red.
Are you sick?
Well,
I'm a little sick. I'll be okay.
It's the last ten minutes.
Rajabodin, the superior team,
still couldn't score.
It could be that Triston Do is the coach
for Nonthavit this year.
Their play style has improved
a lot out of nowhere.
[Satit] That makes a rising star
like Pok Pong Pue-on
unsure how to handle it.
[Bouranij] Speaking of him,
in the first match,
he did very well.
But in this match, he's a little odd.
Doesn't want to pass the ball
to teammates who are free.
Can't maintain how he performed
in the first match.
Pok Pong is playing so differently.
[Satit] Rajabodin has lost the ball
to Nonthavit again.
The game is dragging a bit.
[Bouranij] We haven't seen
any improvement.
Look, everything they do is a mistake.
[Satit] The ref just blew the whistle
to end the game. It's a tie, 0-0.
Rajabodin fans are so disappointed.
[Bouranij] Looks like Rajabodin
lost a great chance.
If we lost today, it's because of you.
[boy] Hey, that's enough.
[Coach Ble] Hey, stop!
Fighting like dogs!
How are you doing?
Fucking Tony started it.
-Let's talk about that later.
-Coach also benched me.
And in the end, we tied.
If I had been in the game,
we would have won.
But I think, today, you played like you
didn't care about your teammates.
You passed the ball to Book only.
You can play soccer now?
Okay. You're good at this.
How dare you criticize me?
You couldn't even tell your dad
that you're not good enough
to be in the team.
Pik, what's wrong?
Just mind your own business.
Pong.
What did you do to her?
Why was she so upset?
We just had a little fight.
Don't be angry.
I am.
Because I like you.
Book.
Fuck, Book.
Pong!
What?
I'm sorry.
I need your help.
I don't want to be like this anymore.
Book said he likes me.
I want to be with him as a girl.
Believe me.
Even if we can switch back,
he doesn't like you.
You're saying this
because you found the formula?
You found it, right?
Why didn't you tell me?
Being like this is not my preference.
But I can see you're enjoying it.
I don't want to be like this anymore.
Let's go. Make a cupcake right now.
You...
are worried about your dad?
No.
Your dad is okay with it.
You're doing this
because you don't want me to be with Book?
Why, Pong?
Pong.
Pong!
Coach Ble decided to punish
you and Pok Pong
by suspending you from practice.
You're the captain of the soccer team.
You shouldn't have let such a scandal
leak onto social media.
May I say something, sir?
First, I would like to say sorry
for everything.
I know that I have tarnished the long-time
image of the school and soccer club.
But may I ask one thing from you?
Please punish me only.
Pong had nothing to do with it.
At the time,
what I did was purely from my feelings.
I'm not even sure
how I really feel about it.
I only know that
I like Pong a lot.
Such a gentleman.
You're a Rajabodin gentleman.
Ladies.
Why don't you come in
and take his picture?
Cheese!
So cute.
Pik, how come your cupcake is ugly again?
Because when we make a cupcake,
we think of the one we love.
Pong.
What do you think of the rumor?
What about you?
I don't know.
I only know...
that I'm very happy right now.
Let's take a selfie.
Okay.
Let's be together.
Bye.
Oh!
Here.
[squeals]
[man on TV] How could you do this to me?
[woman on TV] You did it to yourself.
You can't blame me.
[man] What happened? I don't
understand why you've changed.
[woman] I told you from
the beginning that I like someone else.
You can't say that I have changed.
[Eve] Let's eat a cupcake.
Delicious food can make us feel better.
Here.
Eat it.
Don't let those scumbags
ruin our perfect cupcakes.
Not all men are like that, Eve.
Your dad called and said that,
this coming match,
he'll bring a coach
from the national team.
That's all I came to tell you.
Pik.
Believe me.
Book likes you not only because
you two get along...
but because you're a guy.
Stay out of this.
From now on,
I'm okay with being in your body.
I get to play soccer,
be with Book openly.
I can take it.
[boy] They're girly desserts.
Are you really gonna eat it?
Really?
[Book] Pik.
[Coach Ble] What is she doing here?
[all exclaiming]
[Eve] Pik.
Book.
What's up with you?
Care to join?
[cheering]
May I use your body to play soccer
for a day?
[Pik] Promise me first that we're
gonna find a way to switch back.
I promise.
[Pong] You're doing this
because you don't want me to be with Book?
Why, Pong?
Why are you doing this?
Because I love you.
Huh?
These are examples. From one to three.
Let's review the answers,
how we came to these mathematically.
We have come to the solutions
of questions one to three.
Does anyone still not understand?
Anyone?
Those who understand it all,
raise your hand.
Okay, not everyone.
[Pong] I haven't seen Pik since.
She stayed in her room.
I saw only Book.
Pong.
Book.
Let me say this.
Whatever you think of us,
how good you think it was,
I'm not the same Pong you knew.
I'm so sorry.
[crowd cheering]
[announcers chattering]
[Satit] The defending champions,
Rajabodin, are playing against Taweewat.
They are ten-time champions.
Let's see if they can defend
their championship again this year.
[announcers chattering]
[Pong] I got to play
in the championship match.
Neither Book nor I could play well.
I played really terribly.
And Book seemed disheartened.
Everybody thought that
we couldn't play well
because we had broken up.
[crowd exclaiming]
Except my dad.
Dew and Dome said,
when Pik learned that Book and I
stopped talking,
she got even worse
than when she had a fight with me.
Damn it!
[Pong] Pik came out
and went to cupcake club.
Grabbed every kind of sprinkles
to eat back in her room.
But she didn't know that I had got rid
of the switching ones.
Fern. Linchee.
[Pong] Eve didn't get why Pik changed.
But she accepted it.
[Dew] Pong!
Pik has just left the room
carrying a ball.
[Pong] I tried to see her,
but she didn't let me.
The only person she talked to
was Book.
As soon as he knew that
she got angry easily again,
he got worried about her.
He is there for her as always.
I don't know what he talked to her about.
Hey, Pong. Pong.
Have you heard?
Pik is really fearless.
She quit school without telling anybody.
I saw her mom picking her up last night.
Yeah. You go ahead.
I'll meet my dad over there.
Okay. See you at practice
-next week.
-See you.
[Pik] You were right, Pong.
Book didn't like me.
Thank you for being me
and letting me be you.
Let's play soccer again this summer.
[chuckles]
We're "Ja" Satit Krikul
and "Borboo" Bouranij Rattanavichien.
We're the announcers.
-I scored a goal!
-Hey.
Losing a boyfriend to a guy
is not easy to accept.
Bonita!